Watch this, it's really cool.
Call Leonard Hoffstadder.
Did you say:
"Call Hellen Boxlightner?
Call Leonard Hoffstadder.
Did you say:
"Call Temple Badsaidor?"
Let me try!
Call...
Calling "Rajesh Koothrappali."
That's very impressive.
And a little racist.
If we're all through playing
"mock the flawed technology,"
can we get on with Halo night?
We were supposed to start at
8:00. It is now 8:06.
So we'll start now.
First we have to decide
if those lost six minutes will be coming
out of game time, bathroom time
or the pizza break.
We could split it
two, two and two.
If we're having anchovies on the pizza,
we can't take it out of bathroom time.
Oh, what fresh hell is this?
- Hey, Penny. Come on in.
- Hey, guys.
See a Penny, pick her up,
and all the day
you'll have good luck.
No, you won't.
Can I hide out here for a while?
Sure. What's going on?
There's this girl I know
from back in Nebraska, Christy.
She called me up,
and she's like, "Hey, how's California?"
And I'm like, "Awesome,"
'cause, you know, it's not Nebraska.
And the next thing I know
she's invited herself
out here to stay with me.
8:08.
Anyway, she got here today
and she's just been in my apartment
yakity yakking about every guy
she slept with in Omaha,
which is basically
every guy in Omaha,
and washing the sluttiest
collection of underwear
you have ever seen in my bathroom sink.
Is she doing it one thong at a time,
or does she throw it all in...
...like some sort
of erotic bouillabaisse?
- He really needs to dial it down.
- I know.
So if you don't like this Christy,
why are you letting her stay?
She was engaged to my cousin
while she was sleeping with my brother,
so she's kind of family.
I apologize for my
earlier outburst.
Who needs Halo,
when we can be regaled
with the delightfully folksy
tale of the Whore of Omaha?
I don't think she's a whore.
No, yeah, she's definitely a whore.
I mean, she has
absolutely no standards.
This one time she was at...
Where's Howard?
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
I understand you're new in town.
Oh, good grief.
Season 1 Episode 7:
The Dumpling Paradox
I cannot believe Christy
let Howard into my apartment.
And I cannot believe people
pay for horoscopes,
but on a more serious note,
it's 8:13 and we're
still not playing Halo.
Fine. We'll just play one-on-one
until he gets back.
One-on-one? We don't play one-on-one.
We play teams, not one-on-one.
One-on-one.
The only way we can play teams
at this point is if we cut Raj in half.
Sure, cut the foreigner in half.
There's a billion more
where he came from.
If you guys need a fourth, I'll play.
- Great idea.
- No.
The wheel was a great idea,
relativity was a great idea.
This is a notion,
and a rather sucky one at that.
Why?
Oh, Penny, Penny, Penny.
What, what, what?
This is a complex battle simulation
with a steep learning curve.
There are myriad weapons,
vehicles and strategies
to master, not to mention
an extremely intricate backstory.
Oh cool.
Whose head did I just blow off?
Mine.
Okay, I got this.
Lock and load, boys.
It's the only way we can play teams.
Yes, but whoever's her
partner will be hamstrung
by her lack of experience,
and not to mention the fact...
There goes your head again.
It's not good sportsmanship
to shoot somebody who's just re-spawned.
You need to to give them a chance to...
Now, come on!
Raj, Raj!
She's got me cornered. Cover me!
Cover this, suckers!
- Penny, you are on fire!
- Yes, and so is Sheldon.
Okay, that's it.
I don't know how, but she is cheating.
No one can be that attractive
and this skilled at a video game.
Wait, Sheldon, come back.
You forgot something.
What?
This plasma grenade.
Look, it's raining you.
You laugh now-- you just wait
until you need tech support.
Gosh, he's kind of
a sore loser, isn't he?
To be fair, he's also
a rather unpleasant winner.
Well, it's been fun.
We make such a good team.
Maybe we could enter a couple
of Halo tournaments sometime.
Or we could just have a life.
I guess for you that's an option.
- Good night.
As usual, nice talking to you, Raj.
What do you suppose
she meant by that?
She's an enigma, Raj.
And another thing-- there's
a certain ethic to the game, Penny,
- a well- established...
- She's gone.
She could have said good-bye.
Okay, I have a problem.
It's called carpal tunnel syndrome,
and quite frankly you deserve it.
What's wrong?
Howard and Christy are...
kind of hooking up
in my bedroom.
Are you sure?
I grew up on a farm, okay?
From what I heard,
they're either having sex
or Howard's caught
in a milking machine.
Do you mind if I stay here tonight?
No, take the couch, or my bed.
I just got new pillows.
Hypo-allergenic.
The couch is good.
Hold that thought.
Leonard, a moment.
Let me guess.
You have a problem with this.
- Where do I begin?
- It's up to you. Crazy person's choice.
First, we don't have houseguests.
Frankly, if I could afford
the rent, I'd ask you to leave.
Your friendship means
a lot to me as well. What else?
Well...
our earthquake supplies.
We have a two-man, two-day kit.
So?
So if there's an earthquake
and the three of us are trapped here,
we could be out of food
by tomorrow afternoon.
I'm sorry, are you suggesting
that if we let Penny stay
we might succumb to cannibalism?
No one ever thinks it'll
happen until it does.
If you promise not to
chew the flesh off our bones
while we sleep, you can stay.
- What?
- He's engaging in reductio ad absurdum.
It's the logical fallacy
of extending someone's argument
to ridiculous proportions
and then criticizing the result.
And I do not appreciate it.
I'll get you a blanket and a pillow.
Okay, since I'm obviously
being ignored here,
let's go over the morning schedule.
I use the bathroom
from 7:00 to 7:20.
Plan your ablutions and bodily
functions accordingly.
How am I supposed to plan
my bodily functions?
I suggest no liquids after 11:00 p.m.
- Here you go.
- Thanks, Leonard.
Wrong.
I'm listening.
Your head goes on the other end.
- Why?
- It's culturally universal. A bed,
even a temporary bed,
is always oriented with the headboard
away from the door.
It serves the ancient imperative
of protecting oneself against marauders.
I'll risk it.
Anything else should I know?
Yes, if you use my toothbrush,
I'll jump out that window.
Please don't come to my funeral.
Have a good night.
Sorry about that.
- That's okay.
- FYI--
his toothbrush is the red one in
the Plexiglas case under the UV light.
Got it.
- Sleep tight.
- Thanks
Funny expression,
"sleep tight."
It refers to the early
construction of beds
which featured a mattress
suspended on interlocking ropes,
which would occasionally...
Sleep tight.
What are you doing?
Every Saturday
since we've lived in this apartment
I have awakened at 6:15,
poured myself a bowl of cereal,
added a quarter cup
of two percent milk,
sat on this end of this couch,
turned on BBC America,
and watched Doctor Who.
Penny's still sleeping.
Every Saturday
since we've lived in this apartment
I have awakened at 6:15,
poured myself a bowl
I know.
You have a TV in your room.
Why don't you just have
breakfast in bed?
Because I am neither an invalid,
nor a woman celebrating Mother's Day.
What time is it?
Almost 6:30.
I slept all day?
No, it's 6:30 in the morning.
What the hell is your problem?
Okay, this cereal has lost
all its molecular integrity.
I now have a bowl
of shredded wheat paste.
Hola, nerd-migos.
Why do you people hate sleep?
Are you wearing my robe?
Yeah.
Sorry, I'll have it cleaned.
That's okay, keep it.
- Where's Christy?
- In the shower.
By the way, where did you
get that loofah mitt?
Yours reaches places
that mine just won't.
You used my loofah?
More precisely,
weused your loofah.
I exfoliated her brains out.
You can keep that, too.
Then we'll probably need to talk
about your stuffed bear collection.
In here, milady!
Here's my little engine that could.
There's one beloved
children's book I'll never read again.
Hi. Christy.
- I'm Sheldon.
- Right.
You're Howard's entourage.
So, Christy, what are your plans?
Howard said he'd take
me shopping in Beverly Hills.
Yeah, no, I meant plans to find
someplace to live.
Other than with me.
Not that I don't love having you,
but it's...
It's a little crowded.
Penny, you're always
welcome to stay with us.
Oh, terrific.
Now we're running a cute little B & B.
Let me offer a little
outside-the-box thinking here.
Why doesn't Christy stay with me?
- You live with your mother.
- I do not.
My mother lives with me.
Then it's all settled.
Christy will stay with Howard,
Penny can go back to her apartment,
and I'll watch the last 24 minutes
of Doctor Who.
Although at this point,
it's more like Doctor Why Bother?
- Sheldon, you just can't dictate...
- No more talking! Everybody go!
So what do you say?
Want to repair to Casa Wolowitz?
What is that, like a Mexican deli?
I'm sorry,
I should have mentioned this earlier.
My last name is Wolowitz.
That's so cool.
My first Jew.
I imagine there aren't very many
Kosher Cornhuskers.
But you're still taking me shopping?
Anything you want.
Okay, I'll go pack my stuff.
When they perfect human cloning,
I'm going to order 12 of those.
Can't you see she's using you?
Who cares? Last night,
she pulled off her blouse and I wept.
I know her. Okay?
She'll have sex with anyone,
as long as
they keep buying her things.
- Really?
- Yeah.
If you'll excuse me,
I have some Bar Mitzvah bonds to cash.
I'm sorry, we cannot do this
without Wolowitz.
We can't order Chinese
food without Wolowitz?
Let me walk you through it.
Our standard order is:
the steamed dumpling appetizer,
General Tso's chicken,
beef with broccoli,
shrimp with lobster sauce
and vegetable lo mein.
Do you see the problem?
I see a problem.
Our entire order is predicated
on four dumplings and four entrees
divided amongst
four people.
- So, we'll just order three entrees.
- Fine.
What do you want to eliminate?
And who gets the extra dumpling?
We could cut it into thirds.
Then it's no longer a dumpling.
Once you cut it open it is,
at best, a very small open-faced
sandwich.
Hi, fellas.
Where's your annoying little friend
who thinks he speaks Mandarin?
He's putting his needs ahead of
the collective good.
Where he comes from,
that's punishable by death.
I come from Sacramento.
Can we get an order of dumplings
but with three instead of four?
No substitutions.
This isn't a substitution.
It's a reduction.
Okay.
No reductions.
Fine. Bring us three orders
of dumplings.
- That's 12. We'll each have four.
- That works.
If we fill up on dumplings,
we need to eliminate another entree.
No eliminations.
If we have extra,
we'll just take the leftovers home.
And divide it how? I'm telling you,
we cannot do this without Wolowitz.
Wolowitz is with his new girlfriend.
If you had let me invite Penny,
then you would have had your fourth.
Have you seen Penny
eat Chinese food?
She uses a fork and she
double-dips her egg rolls.
- We don't order egg rolls.
- Exactly,
but we'd have to if she was here!
Can we please
make a decision?
Not only are there children
starving in India,
there's an Indian starving right here.
There's an idea. Why don't we
just go out for Indian food?
You're nice boys.
Tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to bring you
the four dumplings.
When I'm walking over to the
table, maybe I get bumped,
one of the dumplings fall to the floor.
No one has to know.
I'll know.
- How about soup?
- Yeah, we can always divide soup.
What about the wontons?
Hey, guys, what's up?
It's Halo night.
So?
With Wolowitz spending all of his time
with your friend Christy...
She's not my friend. Friends do not get
their friends' Care Bears all sweaty.
Right. Anyway, uh, with Wolowitz
occupied elsewhere,
we had something
we wanted to ask you.
Yes.
We would very much appreciate it
if you would be the fourth
member of our Halo team.
I don't think I need to tell
you what an honor this is.
That's so sweet, but I'm going out
dancing with a girlfriend.
You can't go out;
it's Halo night.
- Well, for Penny, it's dancing night.
- You go dancing every Wednesday?
- No.
- Then that's not "dancing night."
Why don't I play
with you guys tomorrow?
Tonight is Halo night.
It's like talking to a wall.
All right, now, Sheldon,
you and I are about to have a problem.
Sheldon, remember,
we role-played this.
Yes, but you didn't portray her
as completely irrational.
All right, fellas,
I gotta go.
But good luck.
Maybe we should've asked if we could go
dancing with her and her girlfriend.
Assuming we could dance--
which we can't--
there are three of us
and two of them.
So?
It's the Chinese restaurant
all over again.
I assure you that
cutting a dumpling in thirds
is child's play compared with three men
each attempting to dance
with 67% of a woman.
For God's sakes, Sheldon,
you're driving me crazy!
Your anger is not with me, sir,
but with basic mathematics.
I'm pretty sure my anger is with you.
What's happening to us?
We're falling apart.
- Who are you calling?
- The only man who can restore
any semblance of
balance to our universe.
Hi, this is Howard Wolowitz.
And this is Christy Vanderbelt.
We can't get to the phone
right now because we're having sex!
You're not going to put that
on your message, are you?
Nah, I'm just kidding.
I'll re-record it.
Sheldon, think this through.
You're going to ask Howard to choose
between sex and Halo.
No, I'm going to ask him to choose
between sex and Halo Three.
As far as I know, sex
has not been upgraded
to include Hi-Def graphics
and enhanced weapon systems.
You're right, all sex has is nudity,
orgasms and human contact.
My point.
You can take the damn plastic
off the couch once in a while!
Why, so you and Howard
can hump on it?!
Ladies, ladies,
I'm sure there's a middle ground.
Shut up, Howard!
You guys talk. I'm gonna take
my scooter out for a little spin.
You happy? You drove
your own son out of the house.
Why don't you stop...
What are you doing here?
It's Halo night.
He's not a man, he's a putz!
And don't you take that tone with me,
you gold digger!
- What'd you call me?
- You heard me!
And I'll tell you something else,
you're barking up the wrong tree.
'Cause as long as you're around,
Howard is out of the will!
You know what?
I got better offers. I'm outta here.
That's right.
Go back to Babylon, you whore!
So, Halo night, huh?
I thought she was the whore of Omaha.
Sheldon, you got him in your sights!
Fire! He's charging his plasma rifle!
I can't shoot now. I'm cloaking!
- Raj! Kill Sheldon!
- I can't see him!
That's why they call it
cloaking, dead man!
- Start throwing grenades!
- I'm all out!
Hey, guys.
My friends and I got tired of dancing,
so we came over to
have sex with you.
Raj, hop in the tank!
- We said no tanks!
- There are no rules in hell!
Son of a bitch. Med pack!
I need a med pack!
Told ya.
There's a sniper.
Use your rocket launcher!
All I've got is a Needler
and I'm all out of ammo!
And now you're out of life.
Why'd you hit pause?
I thought I heard... something.
What?
No, never mind.
Sorry. Go.
www.tvsubtitles.net