- Is Nyborg the right PM?
- You need a media adviser now.
Hanne Holm is with the Express.
Are you going to resign?
- We haven't even started yet.
It's total chaos.
We're still us, aren't we?
I sent you a message.
An homage to babies.
I just had an abortion.
- How come we're never in sync?
Kasper?
You're good.
- Thanks.
"If you hush up a ghost, it grows
bigger. " - Greenlandic proverb
See you.
- TV1 News. Simon Bech.
It's for you.
I'm afraid she just left.
He insists on speaking to you.
Says it's top priority.
Katrine Fønsmark.
I have some information
you'll appreciate.
Who is this?
- Meet me in the parking lot.
Leave it at reception.
- I want to hand it over.
Come out here alone.
It's a matter of national security.
I'm leaving in five minutes.
It's up to you.
Have you got two minutes?
- Sure.
Katrine.
Hello.
See anything?
- Just a silver Renault.
Shit.
- Was that all?
Yeah, I think so.
Thanks, anyway.
Stop. Don't turn around.
Stay put.
Step back toward the car.
Why didn't you come alone?
What did you expect?
- Look inside.
Who are you?
It's a scoop you can't refuse.
- I need to know who you are.
You can topple the government with
this. Just look inside the envelope.
What is this?
American CIA detainees?
These photos could be doctored.
- Well, check them.
They're all on this USB stick
in a higher resolution.
Look at the sign on the hangar.
- Thule Air Base.
CIA detainees on Danish territory.
There's your evidence.
Who are you?
- I contacted you.
Why me?
- Because you tend to be disobedient.
GOVERNMENT
Episode 4- 100 Days
A WEEK LATER
My source contacts me
and not vice versa.
He demands anonymity, but he works
for the Defence Intelligence Service.
Are you 100 percent sure?
- I saw his ID card.
Can we mention his name?
- No.
We'll call him a source
close to the military.
What's his motive?
- He says he loves Denmark.
Don't we all?
- There's more to it than that.
Our photo guys have okayed
the photos.
Semi-professional equipment.
High resolution. No Photoshop signs.
When are we going to run it?
Do you trust your source?
- Completely.
We're all on the line here.
- Do you realize the potential of this?
Didn't you get the Cavling Prize once?
I have other responsibilities now.
- You know we're good to go.
Calm down. We're going to run it.
What the hell did you expect?
Go ahead, Katrine.
The US is using Thule Air Base
as a transit base for CIA detainees.
Welcome to the TV1 News.
Where did TV1 get those pictures?
- They won't reveal their source.
The military must have some idea.
- They're looking into it.
Let's talk about your first 100 days.
You've had 100 days in office.
Good morning.
- The press loves that kind of stuff.
We need a positive
to heighten your profile as the PM.
Sure, but I want it to be
a concrete political result.
Just you wait.
- Sanne, clear my morning schedule.
You're going to the hairdresser's.
- No, clear my morning schedule.
Thank you.
I'll get rid of her,
but the union will put up a fight.
The Security Council
is waiting -
with the Ministers for Justice and
Defence and their department heads.
Who do they think the leak is?
- They don't know.
The Greenland Premier is on
his way down to get a statement.
We owe him an apology.
We're historically disinclined
to offer Greenland apologies.
It implies responsibility
and entails unforeseen expenses.
Have a plan of action ready by noon.
I'm not taking the fall just because
Hesselboe was Bush's little lapdog.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Don't get up.
Are we allowing the Americans
to land CIA detainees in Greenland?
Look, don't you play
cloaks and daggers with me.
Do these flights take place?
- We don't know for sure.
Our agreement with the US forbids us
to check their planes at the base.
Isn't that agreement from the
Bush era? It can't still be in effect.
CIA is a state in the state.
It's hard to disempower them.
What has Washington got to say?
- The Ambassador is coming in later.
Good. Make it clear to him that their
long-time ally expects an explanation.
I see no reason to jeopardize our
otherwise good relations to the US.
What about our otherwise
good relations to Greenland?
Greenland is not our primary
concern right now.
I am the minister responsible
to Greenland, and I am concerned -
about the way the press uses this
to expose our policies as a sham.
We give them home rule,
yet we still rule supreme.
Who is going to buy us time
with the press, until we know more?
Keep me out of it.
I say the Minister for Defence.
The leak did come from his ministry.
Thule Air Base employs a lot
of people. Who says it's one of ours?
The military doesn't fear the press,
Troels.
I never said so, Troels.
- Hans Christian, go on TV tonight.
We doubt the authenticity
of the pictures and will bide our time.
No, we're checking their authenticity
and take the matter very seriously.
Okay.
- Good.
The News calls the detainees illegal.
But no one's been able to document
that the detainees are in fact illegal.
Maybe you can use that.
Yes, Mom.
Minister for Defence, good evening.
How could these renditions take place
on Danish territory?
Denmark and the US have enjoyed
close relations for many years.
Why on earth should the US wish
to violate Danish territorial laws?
Give him hell, Ulrik!
The orange suits invariably make you
think of the Guantánamo detainees.
Guantánamo is being closed.
I see men in orange jumpsuits.
The same jumpsuits are worn
by thousands of American criminals.
What makes these detainees illegal?
Answer me that.
You're not going to pursue the matter?
We're looking into it
and take the matter very seriously.
But that's all I can say for now.
You're not letting him off the hook!
- Next, the declining real estate...
Why didn't you pressure him?
- What is Katrine doing in my ear?
You could've asked him what
the detainees are doing in Greenland.
When a minister cuts you off
all shifty-eyed, he's lying!
Could this wait till after the show?
Ulrik, that was a lousy interview.
And you're on, Ulrik.
Congratulations. Thorsen managed
to put a lid on the issue on the News.
It's not over yet. The Foreign Policy
Committee wants an explanation.
You want me to go?
- It won't be hard.
Doubts have been raised as
to whether the detainees are illegal.
And you just spoke to the Americans.
What explanation did they offer?
- The Ambassador didn't say much.
A simple yes or no will do. Does the
CIA carry out renditions in Greenland?
"It's on a need-to-know basis.
And you don't need to know. "
You let him put you off with that?
- They guard their foreign policy well.
But as the Minister for Foreign Affairs
you represent the wronged party.
What about the Committee?
- I'll handle it myself.
You came home to comfort
the lonely housewife?
I've been around wimps all day.
Thank God I'm not married to one.
Pantyhose is impossible.
Why is the door locked?
- We're rearranging the furniture.
Can I have some chips then?
- Sure.
You're a gorgeous man.
Drop dead gorgeous.
We haven't had sex in three weeks
because I've been beat.
How about if we have regular days
just to make sure we get it done?
Why not have sex when we want to?
Sure, but we could have regular days,
too. Tuesdays and Saturdays?
Tuesdays, I'm done with the minister
meeting, and Saturday is my day off.
This conversation is far out.
Scheduled sex with the PM.
You didn't exactly pound
on the Minister for Defence today.
It was a crappy interview.
You can topple the government.
- It happened under Hesselboe.
The civil servants
have known all along.
You can't get civil servants to talk.
I'm talking.
- No, you're whispering.
You're an anonymous source.
I need more.
I've got something for you.
Come on.
Transcripts from the tower at Thule.
Landings and takeoffs.
The highlighted one
is the plane on the pictures.
It took place.
And here... Two missing men,
issued by the Human Rights Watch.
Afghan peasants
abducted by the Americans.
The guy in the red hat
is on the picture from Thule.
That proves they're illegal detainees.
Why are you doing this, Carsten?
- Honor.
Elaborate on that.
I've been with the military
for 25 years.
When I see the flag, I see something
I'm willing to die for.
As a young man
I served on the Sirius Patrol.
I've traveled 9,000 miles
on dog sled in Greenland -
through a darkness
you wouldn't believe.
That sort of thing makes an impact.
These past ten years we've lost
every degree of sovereignty -
in relation to the US. We've turned
into their eager little brother.
We take part in their wars without
demanding a legitimate reason.
We help them detain
innocent people.
We let them use our territory
as they please.
How long has this been going on?
- A long time. Since 9/11.
Before that, they brought
nuclear weapons up there.
When one of their planes crashed,
spilling nuclear weapons on the ice -
we helped them clean up their mess.
There's still a bomb lying up there.
At some point it's got to stop.
It's been going on far too long.
I'm prepared
to go all the way with this.
I know the risk you're taking.
I'll get your story out.
Can I have your number?
- No way.
I need to be able to contact you,
or else I won't get any further.
Use a word you don't usually end
your newscast with. Snow.
Hello.
- Yes!
Good morning.
Katrine Fønsmark?
Police.
How did you get in contact with
the man who gave you the pictures?
Did you contact him?
- I'm not naming my source.
You'd better.
- Can I get your names? Some ID?
Two police officers are trying
to force me to name my source.
What are your names?
Let me see some ID!
Let me talk to Pia.
So, are we agreed on Greenland?
The Premier is waiting.
He's here?
He's waiting outside?
He's used to it. They're finding it
hard to administrate their home rule.
They need us. We just gave them
the right to their own underground.
What if they find oil?
They cannot have it both ways.
I'd give him 15 minutes, max.
- I'll give him a cup of coffee.
No money, no apology, but we regret
the incident at Thule Air Base.
Though we don't know what happened
exactly. If anything at all.
Niels Erik, you've been
Permanent Secretary for eight years.
You're on the Security Council.
Tell me about these flights.
I don't recall having been present at
meetings where they were mentioned.
Please.
- Birgitte Nyborg.
Jens Enok.
- Welcome to Denmark.
The old place hasn't changed...
...apart from the artwork.
A change of system entails new art.
- Hopefully more than that. Sit down.
Thank you for coming down.
We don't quite know what
has been going on at Thule Air Base -
but we're working on...
It's okay.
You don't need to explain yourself.
We've done our duty by meeting.
You can't apologize.
You didn't violate
Greenland's territory.
We're locked in our old positions.
Greenland is no match for Denmark -
just as Denmark is no match
for the US.
Kalaallit Nunaat.
That's Greenland in Greenlandic.
It means
'the land of the Greenlanders'.
But that's wishful thinking
more than reality.
I regret that.
How about that coffee then?
- Sure.
Torben, you'll call them back.
Tell them you'll call them back.
I'll call you back.
Intelligence almost broke in earlier,
demanding to know my source.
Sure they were intelligence officers?
- The police didn't send anyone.
This shows we're on to something.
- It's the Director General's call now.
I need to make sure
it'll stand up in court.
Look at this.
I met my source last night.
The flights are real, and the detainees
are illegal. There's the proof.
My air force expert okays
the landing transcripts.
I want to interview Hanne Holm
tonight. She's an expert on Thule.
She says this is a clear continuation
of our patronizing foreign policy.
Torben, are you bailing on me?
My source is putting his life
on the line for us.
This is a matter
of national importance.
Isn't this why we became reporters?
- Shut the fuck up.
It's fucking good. We'll break it on
the radio and go all out on TV tonight.
Got a light?
- Sorry.
Kasper Juul.
- Is the PM available tonight?
I'm available for anything tonight.
We want Nyborg to comment
on the case on the 8:30 news.
The Foreign Policy Committee meeting
didn't add anything to the case.
Listen to the Radio News
in two minutes.
- Can we have the PM first?
- Have we got a date?
I'm not naming my source.
- Would I ask you to?
Okay, then. Deal.
- Deal. Bye.
Svend Åge.
Got a light?
I hear the PM's having coffee
with miffed Eskimos.
I think they prefer
to be called Inuits.
I know the wee Mrs. Nyborg
loves indigenous people -
but just how indigenous
can you be, I ask you?
What do you mean?
- They can't govern themselves.
Their young are uneducated.
Their corporate sector is based
on a mix of corruption and Stalinism.
They drink like crazy
and abuse their children sexually.
How's that related to CIA's flights?
- Your cabinet needs Solidarity.
Don't let the Foreign Policy
Committee's left-wing members -
bully you into giving Greenland
concessions.
The Freedom Party will support you.
- Can I tell that to the PM?
Sure. The Reds are eager to give the
Eskimos all the home rule in the world.
If you want home rule,
you must be able to rule yourself.
An intelligence source reveals
to TV1-
- that the CIA detainees on the
flights to Thule were indeed illegal.
Several detainees are allegedly
innocent Afghans -
- who went missing a long time ago.
The Foreign Policy Committee
convenes in an hour and a half.
They'll want to know
where the press gets their info.
The leak must be an officer.
The military is like a sieve.
Cut it out.
- It was the US ambassador.
They're afraid
we may feel pressured -
into giving Greenland a say
in future military agreements up there.
The Social Solidarity Party's
barking up that tree, too.
The Freedom Party promises us
their support -
if we refrain from giving
Greenland any concessions.
What if the source keeps leaking?
Where will it end?
It ends here. The police are
on their way out to charge TV1.
They're guilty
of receiving confidential information -
because it was stolen from
the military and distributed by TV1.
But you can't.
- It's the law.
But arresting reporters is lousy PR!
- Worried about your little girlfriend?
Cut it out!
What are we doing?
Collaborating with the Freedom Party
to oppress the Greenlanders?
Arresting reporters?
Just 100 days in, and we sound
like the previous cabinet.
That's realpolitik for you.
- Not this cabinet's realpolitik.
We get the PM,
if she makes a statement.
For our backdrop I want a close-up
of the detainees at the base.
And I want you to hold
the actual landing transcripts.
Everyone can relate to them.
Good evening. Police.
TV1 is under suspicion for
distributing stolen information -
and those responsible will be
charged according to section 152D.
Torben Friis, Pia Munk,
Ulrik Mørch and Katrine Fønsmark.
This prohibits any further publication
of said information.
The Director General
has been informed.
Fucking hell.
What a joke!
This is a historic moment.
- Excuse me.
Can I talk to you?
- The PM's got the committee in 15.
Exactly, and I just talked
to the Ministry for Defence.
There's something you should
know about the flight to Thule.
SL means Security Landing. That is,
they landed for security reasons.
A forced landing?
- Exactly.
A technical problem forced
the plane to land at Thule.
That changes everything.
Let's ask her how she feels
about freedom of speech.
How can they even begin to think
this will stop us?
We need to talk strategy.
- I just spoke to the Director General.
While we're being investigated,
we're not publishing the transcripts.
What?
- That means they'll win.
Nor can we show the pictures.
- Katrine can refer to them.
I can't interview Hanne Holm
about a picture I can't show.
And that's why
she's not coming tonight.
You're putting a lid on it.
- No. The PM is still coming.
She'll get a chance to defend herself.
Ulrik, for fuck's sake.
- I guess Torben's right.
I can't work this way.
- You're a pro.
The only one, it seems!
- This is an order.
End of story!
Crap!
I'm sorry we called you in.
Torben won't let you go on.
I can't use the transcripts,
nor the pictures from Thule.
He's putting a lid on it?
- By order from above.
Katrine, can I talk to you?
Gee, Friis. I didn't know
your model came without balls.
Yesterday, TV1 brought pictures
of illegal detainees landing at Thule.
We have reason to believe they're
genuine. How do you feel about this?
The flight did take place.
- You confirm this?
Yes.
We've looked into the matter -
and it turns out
it was a forced landing.
When a plane is in distress,
you don't ask what it's carrying.
This is evident
from the landing transcripts.
We're under police orders
not to use those transcripts.
I can't comment on that -
but this cabinet is not out
to curtail freedom of speech.
The plane made a forced landing?
Have there been other flights?
Not to my knowledge.
- Time's up, Katrine.
To my knowledge
there haven't been any more.
But you can't guarantee...
- Cut, Katrine!
I'm afraid our time's up.
Thank you for coming.
Perhaps it was naive of me to think I
wouldn't lie during my first 100 days.
You didn't lie. To your knowledge
there haven't been any more flights.
The States have considered Greenland
their little playground since WW2.
You shut the case down and offered
the press a fine explanation.
You ought to be happy.
- I just hope I can sleep at night.
Why don't I go to Greenland
and offer them an explanation?
A gesture. We need a positive
after 100 days. You said so.
I had hoped for something
a little sexier than Greenland.
Just make the arrangements.
Call that an interview?
Why didn't you use my material?
My boss put a lid on it.
I've put my life on the line.
You promised to go all the way.
We're up against the police.
And my wimp of a boss won't let me
use the material you gave me.
Why didn't you tell me
it was a forced landing?
It's just one of several landings.
- So the PM lied on TV?
Whenever the Americans land there
with captives, it's a 'forced landing'.
Do you realize who we're up against?
I never should have come to you.
I'll get back to you. Bye.
We'd better not.
- What's up?
I can't tell you.
Who was that on the phone?
- I can't tell you.
See what I mean?
- Let's just keep it personal then.
Maybe you need to talk
about the child you just lost.
Are you mad?
- Every woman's favorite question!
You lost the first round, okay?
- We lost? How about democracy?
Calm down.
Ask me a question,
and I'll give you an honest answer.
Did you know
I was going to be charged?
Did you?
Yes, maybe.
- This isn't working.
Why didn't you warn me?
Your minister got me charged.
- Höxenhaven isn't my minister.
Did you tell me about the transcripts,
or did I hear about them on the news?
And what if I had called?
- Then you'd have been loyal to me.
Strange.
Someone's been here.
Someone's been here, for fuck's sake!
He got away.
- They hacked into my computer.
A reporter's computer!
He was right.
Was that why you wanted to meet me
at the café? Are you in on this?
Do you know
what you're accusing me of?
Just a moment.
Who is it?
- The boozer you got fired.
I think Intelligence
broke in yesterday.
Sounds plausible considering
the game you're playing at.
I called in my friends.
If the police persist, they have
to charge 40 to 50 reporters.
In other words,
they'll have to drop the case.
FREEDOM OF SPEECH
UNDER PRESSURE
I don't know what to say.
- A 'thank you' would be nice.
Now your wimp of a boss can't
prevent you from covering the case.
So get to work.
- I need to find a new angle.
Put your source on TV. Live.
- No. He still works for the Service.
Not for long. They'll find him.
Tell him that unless he comes forward,
all this has been in vain.
Do you know why he's doing it?
- He wants us to stand up to the US.
He's willing to die for the flag.
- God, men are primitive.
Just get him to make a statement first.
Have you any way of contacting him?
Maybe.
That's all for now. I'm glad we got
through it all before the snow came.
"Before the snow came. "
Is that our new exit line?
I was lost for words.
- Will someone please get this glass?
Did you see all the headlines?
Nice with all this collegial support.
And what a triumph for democracy.
- I thought you put a lid on the case.
When you learn to shut up, you'll have
a glorious future ahead of you.
Is that our main story today?
- We can't squeeze more out of it.
It's still a great story.
- It's already been told, okay?
Anything else?
- The PM is going to Greenland.
Great. Let's get some pictures
of the plane taking off.
I bet it's all spin and no bark.
- The cabinet feels guilty, obviously.
Or maybe Nyborg stands
for a new kind of leadership.
Our only piece of evidence
is that one forced landing.
Did your source give you any more?
Did he?
No.
- So much for Deep Throat.
Let's not forget the story
about the charges brought against us.
And let's try and get
that eloquent Eskimo -
to say a few words
about the menu Nyborg is in for.
Just pile it on thick.
Torben?
- Yes.
There's someone I want you to meet.
Carsten Ockels.
Defence Intelligence Service.
That forced landing wasn't
the only CIA flight to Greenland.
I'm prepared to come forward
and tell the whole story.
Have a nice flight, ma'am.
- Thank you, Simon.
Some Greenland statistics.
The most recent financial scandals.
The suicide rate is on the rise.
Alcoholism and all that.
- For my information.
They say it's so beautiful up there
you tend to lose your bearings.
Intelligence is on to the
whistleblower, so he's out of our hair.
What's that supposed to mean?
- Have a nice trip to Greenland.
You called, babe?
- Are you staying the night there?
I don't know. Why?
Well, it's Tuesday,
and I get to ball the PM on Tuesdays.
Have a nice trip, baby.
Kasper will be here in two minutes.
It's going to be a hectic trip.
You have an hour and a half
with the Premier.
Then an hour with Parliament,
a brief press conference -
and finally the official handshake.
Do we have to stay the night?
- No, we're flying back tonight.
Greenland is behind us...
regarding time, I mean.
Sorry I'm late.
- Let's go.
About the official photo.
A medium anorak and size 7 kamiks?
I always forget my kamik size.
Get my coat, will you?
- Sure.
Why is Sanne coming?
- She won the draw.
A clerical employee
always gets to go.
The Ministry for Foreign Affairs got
this from the American ambassador.
The American President is gracing us
with a brief visit this summer.
Great, huh?
- In return for the Thule cover-up?
Spare me the self-righteous act.
Greenland gets a visit from the PM.
Great for them.
We put in a token appearance.
And then it's time to plan
the American visit.
After your 100 days, the leader
of the free world comes knocking.
The PM has arrived in Nuuk where
she's meeting with the Premier -
- to discuss the matter
of the controversial Thule pictures.
Your official kamiks are a size 8.
You're due at their Parliament at 2.
Welcome.
- Thanks.
I'm very glad to be here, and I hope
we can end this matter now.
What?
This 'matter' started 300 years ago
when Hans Egede colonized us.
And you expect to end it in an hour?
I was referring to the matter
of the American CIA plane at Thule.
Oh, that.
That only began 60 years ago -
when Denmark had an entire town
displaced in order to build the base.
I can put on a happy face
when I visit you.
But I tell it like it is
when you visit me.
What about your own responsibility?
- Did we ask to be colonized?
No, but it's hard for us
to give you increased home rule -
when nepotism, trade blunders
and corruption abound here.
Over 40% don't finish high school -
because your schools are too poor.
And we don't run your schools.
We're trying to fix that.
- Are you?
One could think you're just waiting
for the ice to melt and reveal the oil.
What if there isn't any oil?
Who do you think you are?
If you'd given me 24 hours, I could've
showed you what this is all about.
Show me what?
- You could meet the Greenlanders.
But you're not interested.
Kasper and Sanne,
come here, will you?
Re-schedule the press conference.
We're staying till tomorrow afternoon.
Thank you.
Carsten Ockels isn't here,
so we can't run the interview.
No, damn it.
- Yes, damn it.
Did you deliver? No.
That story is closed.
Run the early retirement story instead.
We can still say they always call
these flights forced landings.
Look, your source isn't here.
- I'll get him to come in tomorrow.
Katrine speaking.
Carsten, I thought we had a deal!
The Service is going to nail me
for breach of confidentiality.
You were aware of the risk.
- There's some stuff in my past.
I was heartbroken
after my wife's death.
I took a lot of pills.
I neglected my duties.
People will understand.
While I was with the Sirius Patrol,
I was charged with rape.
The charges were dropped, but...
- You were guilty?
Today I received an envelope
with everything.
Copies of prescriptions -
old psychologist's statements,
reports on a DUl charge, the rape.
They're going to depict me
as a sick, untrustwon'thy person.
They left me a message. They know
my daughter's got a new teaching job.
No school wants to hire
a rapist's daughter.
Those were their very words!
- They want to scare you off.
I'm coming over.
- They're going to dishonor me.
We can still do it.
Let me interview you tomorrow...
You're losing a story.
That's all.
Carsten, the girl that was raped -
was she a Greenlander?
Did Ockels call?
He hung up on me last night.
Sit down.
I need to talk to you.
Look...
I just got a call from an old friend
in the police.
Carsten Ockels was found dead
this morning.
Probably pills, but the official
cause of death is a heart attack.
Intelligence has put a lid on it.
They killed him, the bastards.
Well, we can't say that on TV.
But it's still a good story.
And it's yours.
Tell that story if you want to.
About your meeting,
and what he told you.
I'm behind you all the way.
Intelligence is still going
to defame him.
And that's going to hurt his family.
Dead or alive,
they're still going to...
...dishonor him.
The choice is yours.
He only lived to be 19.
Our biggest problem is that
we're going to die out as a people.
The birth rate is dropping.
Our young people leave Greenland.
But the worst thing is
the skyrocketing suicide rate.
All the young men
are killing themselves.
Like him.
What have you done about it?
- We've tried almost everything.
Suicide hotlines,
psychologists, anti-depressants.
But it's just getting worse.
20% of Greenlandic youths
have tried to commit suicide.
It's a tragic world record.
Why is this, do you think?
Suicide has always been
part of our culture.
People threw themselves
off a mountain -
which was called
'the place where you fall down'.
But they were old people who had
become a burden to their families.
Back then suicide was an act of pride.
Maybe our young commit suicide
because they take pride in nothing.
Why do Greenlanders drink?
Why are our children abused?
People have forgotten who they are.
I have a plan for my country.
If I'm to succeed -
we must give our people back
their self-respect.
I want the suicide rate to drop.
- But how?
Let Greenlanders have a say
in the major issues.
Political security matters
and foreign affairs?
But that you can't give us, can you?
Kasper,
we have to talk to the Americans.
Things have got to change.
- Don't rock the boat.
The President's visit is
in all the papers.
Set up a meeting with the Ministers
for Foreign Affairs and Defence.
Damn, I forgot presents for the kids.
I bought some stuff for them.
Why ruin a good thing?
You sell our policies.
I make them. Get it?
Hi.
Are they asleep?
- Yes.
Mom!
- Hi, sweetie.
What a welcome.
- Did you get us anything?
Indeed I did.
A genuine polar bear tooth.
Huge, huh?
A Tupilak! I'm bringing it
to school tomorrow.
It hope it contains a soul.
- I'm sure it does.
Off to bed.
- Good night.
Sleep tight, kids.
See you tomorrow.
What's that?
- My little black book.
I'm keeping score.
Saturday you were beat.
Tuesday you were in Greenland.
That makes two.
So we have to borrow.
It all adds up to: You have to spend
the next 14 days on your back.
Call it a work injury.
How was Greenland?
It was magnificent.
It was depressing.
Ugly.
I think it's the most beautiful place
I've ever seen.
All rolled into one.
I'm not sure we did Greenland
a favor by discovering it.
Oh, it's pretty.
It's baby seal.
You couldn't find something
a little less PC?
Sure. There are a pair
of musk thongs, too.
"Major Ockels was
a treasured employee -
and the Minister for Defence
appreciates his loyal service. "
Was it right of me to shut the case?
You spared him the humiliation
of being smeared by the press.
So yes, you did.
- But he died in vain.
His information didn't lead
to anything.
I think it did.
Negotiations over the expansion
of the US radar at Thule have begun.
For the first time, they take place
in Greenland led by the Premier.
The negotiations are expected
to end in two weeks -
- but may protract, now that
the Greenlanders have a say, too.
The American President
has cancelled the state visit -
- allegedly due to
a busy schedule in Washington.
TV1 News, Katrine Fønsmark.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst