Let's go through the press release.
- It's 10:30 p. m. Get a life.
I come to apologize,
and you treat me like a stalker.
If you're going to work,
you'll have to go next door.
Good night.
Benjamin is my spinning instructor.
- Spin off and let the grown-ups talk.
Don't talk to people like that.
- Are you seeing him?
"Politics is war without bloodshed. "
"War is politics with bloodshed. "
- Mao Tse-Tung.
Good morning.
Tomorrow, 10.30 a. m.,
you receive Grozin.
Then he has tea with the Queen.
7:30 p. m.,
gala evening at the Royal Theatre.
Gala at night,
pinstripes during the day.
The dissident
Vladimir Bayanov arrived yesterday.
- He and Grozin are mortal enemies.
- How do we deal with it?
We praise our Danish democracy -
- for accommodating two opponents.
We stress our belief
in freedom of speech and press.
See you in an hour.
You father says you arranged
for him to sleep over tonight.
I forgot to tell you. Sorry.
Hi, Dad.
We can't wait to see you.
But we're really busy,
so do you mind taking a cab?
Or the metro. Sure.
Maybe you can even borrow a scooter.
See you.
So, your Dad's paying us a visit?
- He's coming to hear this guy.
Vladimir Bayanov is giving
a poetry reading in Copenhagen.
So what's the plan?
Hello! What's the plan?
- We'll just pamper him a little.
I'll pamper him, you mean.
This is my first state visit.
Give me just two days.
Great planning to have your dad
come at the same time.
I'd appreciate it,
if you looked after him a bit.
He's a little lonely back home.
I thought he got his second wind
after the divorce.
Just one night. Two, max.
He always patronizes me.
- The man is a teacher.
He sees me as the evil capitalist.
- I don't want to discuss my dad.
Will you help me out? Thanks.
- You don't want to discuss it?
Not now.
- Okay.
When is the PM planning
on coming home today, then?
GOVERNMENT
Episode 6- State Visit
President Grozin will be sitting here
across from you.
Will there be press photos
prior to the meeting?
What do you think?
- As little press as possible.
Grozin has a reputation
for being a brutal leader.
And that's why I'm passing on the
chairmanship of the OSDD to him.
What about the gala evening?
- The Queen is running that show.
We're just guests,
so sit back and enjoy it.
The Minister for Energy and Climate
has good news.
Show him in.
We closed the deal.
President Grozin is going to buy
for one billion euros wind turbines.
They confirmed it?
- The Turgisian embassy faxed me.
Both North Wind and the Ministry
for Foreign Affairs confirm it, too.
Grozin is signing the deal
after the press conference.
So your scene
at the climate summit paid off.
Denmark will be Europe's largest
export nation of green energy.
The Russians might very well
be next in line to buy.
Great story! The cabinet creates
more jobs, a greener environment -
and embarks on an exports
adventure in the former Eastern Bloc.
It may make the industry like us.
- Does this change our press strategy?
Yes, give them the full package.
All smiles, Birgitte.
Oh well, convictions
aren't carved in stone.
"It's an honor to pass on the torch
of democracy to the Turgisian nation -
as a token of my admiration
and respect... "
We don't need to admire him,
just because he buys wind turbines.
Have you got two minutes? I've been
asking for a meeting for 14 days.
Sure.
Reports from Amnesty International
and Human Rights Watch -
describe injustices committed
by Grozin's Turgisian security service.
Amnesty says minorities are
persecuted in Turgisia.
I know of his reputation. Many praise
his democratic results too, though.
They can't even hold
democratic elections.
To let Grozin chair
the Organisation for Security -
Democracy and Development
is an outrage.
I didn't make the decision.
I'm just passing on
the chairmanship.
You're receiving him officially.
You would have joined in my protest
before you turned pragmatic.
You don't have to be pragmatic -
because you lead a party
that's hovering 1% above the hurdle.
I'm PM. Also for those who didn't
vote for me. Remember that.
Thank you.
Turgisia has a population of 21 mio.,
it lies near the Black Sea -
and is bordered by the Ukraine
and Russia.
The country seceded from the USSR
and became a republic in 1991.
Grozin was elected president in 1996.
In the mountain lives
the Sarkesian minority -
who led by Vladimir Bayanov
are fighting to gain independence.
Our correspondent in Russia
has sent us this report.
You have a minute and a half.
- Grozin, Turgisians and Sarkesians.
A bit of a tongue twister, isn't it?
Thank you.
Well, what do you think?
You should never wear anything else.
Is it for the Royal Theater?
I won the draw.
- Again?
Impressive. You must be cheating.
Do you address the Queen
"ma'am" or "Your Majesty"?
Is this a hypothetical question?
You're right. I bet
it's going to be a boring ball.
Is my speech ready?
- Yes.
TV1 requests a comment on Bayanov's
visit and resistance to Grozin.
I have to pick up the kids.
- They smell blood.
Amnesty is holding a protest
at the same time as the gala evening.
Just tone it down a little.
- I can't ask Phillip to pick them up.
Let me pick them up.
- That's nice of you, Sanne.
That's really nice of you.
I look forward to welcoming Grozin -
and discussing how to strengthen
democracy in the OSDD countries.
Mom?
I'm not going to meet Bayanov, but
I don't mind him voicing his opinion.
Mom?
I'm glad he uses the opportunity
to speak freely in this country.
Will you be quiet?
- Magnus wet his pants.
I have to go now. Kasper Juul will
answer any further questions.
Why didn't you say you had to go?
Hi.
Hi. Why did you take a bath?
He wet himself.
- Okay.
It's the third time this month.
- You didn't tell me.
I did.
- Do you think anything's wrong?
When was the last time you watched
an afternoon movie with him?
I think he misses you.
He wins more time with you
by wetting himself.
Sure, blame it on me.
- I didn't say that.
After this visit I'll get more time.
- Yeah right.
I need to talk to you about something.
Have you got North Wind shares?
Yes.
I have to ask you to sell them.
Why?
Grozin is going to place a one billion
euro order with North Wind.
That share hasn't been
worth much for years.
We cannot make a profit
off my cabinet's policy.
We've had those shares for years.
It's just a coincidence.
You have to sell them.
As soon as possible.
Look... Are you serious?
I'd like to talk to you
about my shares with North Wind.
Granddad!
- Guess who!
Welcome to Copenhagen.
- Good to see you.
Hiya, champ.
- Hi, granddad.
Do your thugs check everyone?
- Only you.
My bodyguards
are just doing their job.
What's eating you?
I just sold some shares
at a considerable loss.
I thought you were good at that stuff.
Oh well, money's just paper.
How was your trip?
Who are you interviewing?
- Vladimir Bayanov.
A Turgisian poet and dissident.
Katrine, let's go over the script.
We open with Bayanov.
He's on his way over.
Let's go over the script
after you've changed.
Hi. Is this a bad time?
- I'm a little busy.
Let's meet later.
- I'll call you when I get off.
Okay. Bye.
Somebody got themselves
a young boyfriend.
He's not my boyfriend.
- What is he then?
I don't know.
- Are you seeing anyone else?
He's not my boyfriend.
Are we done here?
Thanks.
Are you alright?
- Oh, sorry. Yes, I'm fine.
Vladimir Bayanov. I believe
I'm being interrogated by you?
Yes.
Would you like us to go over some
of my topics before we start?
Why?
- Well, just...
No. I have nothing to hide.
You can ask me anything.
I'm not President Grozin.
- Of course not. Welcome.
"In a single word,
my life will start anew. "
"I was born to know you,
to call you by your name: Freedom. "
Man, that's good. Mind if I cram
some culture into your kids?
No, I only have commerce
and football to offer them.
Are we out of wine?
Bayanov is fantastic.
The house was packed.
I felt like a kindred spirit.
There's an old rebel in me, too.
Hi, Bjørn.
- The Turgisian embassy faxed us.
They want us to arrest Bayanov
and extradite him.
Arrest him for what?
- Terror and high treason.
Various crimes against Turgisia.
The list is long.
- Any evidence?
- Just a long list of accusations.
Write it off as a routine enquiry.
- Are you sure?
According to your ministry -
Bayanov has been living
in exile for 10 years.
Grozin has tried to have him
extradited numerous times.
And now he's trying again.
We won't comply.
Who's going to be arrested?
- You weren't supposed to hear.
Bayanov?
- I can't tell you.
What does democracy mean to you?
- It's like asking what love means.
- Please elaborate.
Well, it's so difficult to explain,
but yet so easy to understand.
We would not die without democracy -
but democracy develops
the human race.
It forces us to embrace and understand
those who think differently.
You are one of the most prominent
members of the Sarkesian minority -
who is fighting for an independent
state, often with violent methods.
Do you find that violence
is sometimes necessary?
Yes, violence is necessary because
Grozin is trying to destroy my people.
Should we not defend ourselves?
But sometimes the Sarkesians
do more than that.
There have been bombs killing
civilians and other acts of terrorism.
Do you sympathize with that?
- Politics is war without bloodshed.
But war is politics with bloodshed.
- That doesn't answer my question.
Before Chairman Mao became
the leader of a great nation -
he was called a terrorist.
Before Yitzhak Shamir became PM,
he too was called a terrorist.
If you win your war, you're
remembered as a great politican.
If you lose, you're remembered
for being a terrorist.
Mr. Bayanov,
are you a terrorist?
Is Grozin?
Thank you very much
for coming in today.
Hi, beautiful.
Anything wrong earlier?
- What?
Would you rather I didn't stop by?
No.
Maybe.
I mean, it's my job.
I don't want to get things mixed up.
We're not getting married tomorrow.
- No. It's okay.
Katrine.
- Call that an interview?
What's your problem?
- Are you alone?
Look, my boss evaluates me.
You don't always have to call.
I hope they gave you hell
for flirting with your interviewee.
I'm not listening to this. Bye.
Ready? Here we go. Voilà.
Good morning.
Pancakes and coffee in two minutes.
I borrowed your bathrobe. Okay?
- Sure.
Good morning. What's this?
- My tux.
But it's tails.
- Oh, I thought...
I'll call my secretary.
- No, I'll handle it.
Where are you going?
- The Royal Theatre.
Go get dressed
before you eat pancakes.
Get well soon.
Trine is sick and can't come tonight.
- You're kidding.
What's up?
- The sitter just cancelled.
I'd better stay another night then.
Do you mean that, Dad?
- Sure. Anything to help.
Great.
Turgisian President Grozin is here
to take over the chairmanship -
of OSDD.
Grozin has just arrived
at Parliament -
where Birgitte Nyborg will receive
him and introduce him to her cabinet.
Welcome to Denmark.
Has Turgesia placed an order with
North Wind worth one billion euros?
Turgesia, too, has a responsibility
to reduce its CO2 emissions.
We believe that our future
lies in wind energy.
But can you confirm
that you have placed the order?
We'll take questions later.
Mr. Grozin, please come this way.
I understand that Vladimir Bayanov
has not been arrested.
Correct. We received a request for
the arrest of Mr. Bayanov yesterday.
And?
- It was simply a list of accusations.
As you're probably aware,
we can't act without evidence.
Bayanov is a well-known terrorist.
There's no international arrest order
on him. I mean no disrespect.
It's impossible for me to arrest
a man who's legally in the country.
Legally? Bayanov?
- He's here to talk about his poetry.
Let me tell you
about Mr. Bayanov's real poetry.
Bayanov was the brain behind the
bombing of our police headquarters -
last month.
The Chief of Police and
five other men on duty were killed.
And almost 20 other people
were badly wounded.
There is your evidence,
Mrs. Prime Minister.
Have the Ministry for Justice
assess this rightaway.
We will be looking into this.
What's up?
- What have you done with Bayanov?
I did a fine interview.
- Yes, very fine.
It was fucking good.
All the international networks
want to use the interview.
Congrats. Now, do you mind...
Let's get Grozin to comment on it.
Meet Bayanov somewhere in town.
I want you to follow up
on Bayanov and Grozin.
Get cracking.
What do we know about the bombing?
Is she available?
- Better try later.
He'll be here shortly.
Close the door.
Well, find out and get back to me.
Are you going to arrest Bayanov?
- Not if I can avoid it.
I know it's bad press.
- It may be worse not to.
The international media know
we have both Grozin -
and the "terrorist" out to overthrow
him. The BBC asks for a comment.
Not now.
The Minister for Justice.
- Hi, Troels.
What do you think of the evidence?
- We can't say if Bayanov's innocent.
My legal people don't consider
the evidence conclusive.
Bayanov may have been connected
to some bomb people at one time.
Can I say the case doesn't hold up?
- No.
We can arrest him
under the new terror laws -
that give the police wide powers.
Exactly why my party voted
against the terror package.
I can hardly use it
to arrest an innocent man.
It's a serious matter not to act.
- Let's say we're looking into it.
How long is Bayanov staying?
- We need to make him leave.
That would solve our problem.
- But how?
We'll leak Grozin's request
for his arrest and hope he skips town.
What if he doesn't?
- He will. The guy's not an idiot.
You're due at the theatre
in an hour and 20 minutes.
Okay, so the plan is to get Bayanov
to leave, if possible.
Thanks.
You called?
Has anyone seen the jewelry
I had in a little black box?
On the desk.
- Fancy, huh? Cuff links and earrings.
They're beautiful!
The PM's Office borrowed them.
What about the Grand Cross?
- My party doesn't accept orders, you.
When will you be back?
- After you go to bed.
We'll have fun. Have you ever
tried my cardamom waffles?
This is ridiculous.
- No, it's my job.
It's your job to accompany me.
- Three steps behind her.
Thank you. What time is it?
You look amazing.
- At last you look like newlyweds.
I need to go.
- Quick!
We'll shake the water off the lily.
Get going.
Pretend you're married.
- They are.
Aren't you?
- See you.
Tonight we're transmitting live -
- from the gala performance
of "Swan Lake" by Tchaikovsky.
Keep an eye out for Grozin.
Birgitte Nyborg
accompanied by her husband.
Your mom is the most beautiful woman
in the goddamn world.
The spitting image of your grandma.
Bayanov just spoke
at the Amnesty protest.
He's going to go on TV1 and leak
the news about the arrest order.
Dammit! Tell Höx to get Intelligence
to lean on Bayanov.
Honey, you have guests.
Mr. Grozin. Lovely to see you again.
- The pleasure's all mine.
My wife Irina.
- Enchanted. Nice to meet you.
This is my husband Phillip.
Did you tell Bayanov about the arrest?
I'll tell him.
All hell is breaking loose. BBC just
ran breaking news on Bayanov.
Turgesian authorities link him to
the bombing of police headquarters.
Shit.
I'll ask him for a comment on that.
If he's behind a terror attack
in his own country...
I can't put him on the air.
The Director General is concerned.
We don't know if he's guilty.
- But if he is...
In your interview he almost
condoned terror, live on the air.
This could be huge.
We can't back out now.
I have to clear it
with the Director General.
Do you want me to go?
Yes, dammit. But if he turns out
to be a terrorist, we won't run it.
Understood?
- Yes.
Keep your cell switched on.
The Russian Minister for Foreign
Affairs wants us to arrest Bayanov.
He criticizes us for not acting.
We have to do something.
We're warning him as we speak.
Hopefully he's leaving the country
right now.
- We've reached the interim.
- Let's hear about the menu.
The Queen is hosting
a standing souper.
The menu offers lumpsucker canapé,
salmon and shrimp -
- and croustade with game.
Bayanov isn't leaving. TV1 just
announced an interview with him.
Mr. Grozin, I understand...
I understand that Bayanov is still
a free man giving interviews on TV.
And the BBC knew
that we wanted him arrested -
and warned him one hour ago.
How did they get story?
I've no idea. You're not implying...
Why has the Danish PM chosen -
to stand by a terrorist instead
of the next chairman of the OSDD?
Here we see Birgitte Nyborg
entertaining President Grozin.
He has still not been arrested.
Do the lives of eight Turgisian
policemen mean nothing to you?
Of course they do, but I cannot
pre-empt a police investigation.
The Prime Minister can order
Bayanov detained -
until the police investigate
the matter.
A lack of goodwill on your part
must force me -
to reconsider my investment
in Danish wind energy.
Why should I place a billion euros -
in a country that does not care
for my people's security?
I strongly recommend immediate
action and the arrest of Bayanov.
Now the German Chancellor
is backing the arrest.
Russia wants him arrested. The world
press is whipping up the story.
You have to consider arresting him.
We can always release him again.
Arrest him, but discreetly.
Have you got a warrant?
Is this legal?
Why are you arresting him?
We have free press in Denmark.
Viggo, over here.
Poet and dissident Vladimir Bayanov
has just been arrested.
In the last 3 years, 71 political
activists have disappeared in Turgisia.
Will Bayanov be number 72?
PM Birgitte Nyborg finally gave in
to international pressure.
You arrested Bayanov?
- Dad...
Do you know what goes on
in Grozin's socalled democracy?
You don't know what's going on.
- You arrested him without evidence.
Or is that a lie?
Mommy sure is
wearing the breeches, huh?
Stop it.
What a fabulous evening.
Can I take this dress to bed?
- You had your share of champagne.
We didn't get to dance. Come on.
Yes, let's dance.
You treat women like shit,
don't you, Kasper?
Vicious rumors.
I need these documents copied for
a Security Council meeting tomorrow.
Don't shit where you eat.
Good little proverb, don't you think?
Did you see Katrine Fønsmark's
report on Bayanov's arrest?
No? Well, maybe you should.
Why are you arresting him?
Why is he being arrested?
Have you got a warrant?
Poet and dissident Vladimir Bayanov
has just been arrested.
In the last 3 years,
71 political activists...
Gunning for the Cavling Price,
are you?
- I don't have time for this now.
- I don't care.
I'm not alone.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Who's there with you?
- Does it matter?
Your littlejock?
- Yes.
Katrine, I just want to...
Katrine?
Come here.
We can't keep at it, Benjamin.
- Hey, speak for yourself.
Yes.
What do you want?
I give you a scoop,
and this is how you thank me?
You hung up on me.
- You were dissing me.
Anyway, I told you I had company.
That's why you came.
I just want to...
- Hi.
Hi, Benjamin.
Are you dating?
- Stop it. You're drunk and stupid.
I just said hi.
- Hi. Bye.
But are you dating?
Benjamin, you scored way out
of your league. I think he's ugly.
Go home!
- Want me to get rid of him?
Go inside and wait.
- She told you to go inside.
She told you to get lost!
Calm down, for fuck's sake!
- Let him go, Benjamin.
Fucking idiot!
Let's go outside and talk.
I'll be right back.
Kasper, go home
and let's try to forget this.
A spinning instructor!
What the hell were you thinking?
He's studying at the university.
- Let's all play Trivial Pursuit, then.
What the hell is your problem?
- He's not...
He's not good enough for you.
What the hell are you doing?
We can't see each other
in private anymore.
It just won't work.
Now go on home.
Go home.
You couldn't sleep either?
You get that from me, I think.
Thanks for the great genes.
I'm sorry I flew into a rage earlier.
It was unfair of me.
- It's okay.
A nightcap?
- Maybe we shouldn't, Dad.
Right.
It's just that
you reminded me of your mother.
She was hard
just before the divorce.
I'm PM. I don't know
if you can imagine...
I don't necessarily love
all the decisions I have to make.
You're okay,
Phillip and you and the kids?
Sure.
- So were we the first couple of years.
But suddenly we stopped talking.
I've always told you
how happy I was with the divorce -
and how much better
my life has been ever since.
It's not true.
I miss your mother every day.
That divorce is the worst thing
that ever happened to me.
That's why I have the odd drink
now and then.
I know, Dad.
Birgitte, promise me one thing.
Promise me that you and Phillip
will always stay together.
I promise, Dad.
Good morning.
You're up early.
When is your dad leaving?
- Today. Why?
Talk to him.
- I have a Security Council meeting.
Maybe you could talk to him.
- No. He's your dad.
I'm too tired to talk about this now.
I'll talk to him.
But as he's leaving today,
I don't really see the point.
I'll wake the kids.
Good morning.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
- Please.
Got any milk?
- Sure.
Yes... Yes, of course.
Grozin wants Bayanov extradited.
- That's out of the question.
What's the procedure?
- His request isn't unreasonable.
OSDD is all about the membership
countries helping each other.
The only OSDD country
opposed to it is France.
How long can we detain him?
- We need to get him out ASAP.
A terror suspect in a Danish prison
could cause security problems galore.
Nothing under Danish law
prevents the extradition.
He'll be executed
within 24 hours, but hey...
Turgisia abolished capital punishment
six years ago.
Still, 71 of Grozin's political
opponents disappeared last year.
Or so Amnesty International claims.
We can't hand him over.
- You want to sell your wind turbines?
Don't you?
- Not if we have to commit a crime.
The Greens can't hand over
a dissident to an uncertain fate -
just to sell our wind turbines.
How much is a human life worth?
- This is a ridiculous discussion.
One billion is a lot of money. Maybe
the Russians will buy wind turbines.
If we corner that market...
Are we debating if Bayanov's head
is worth one billion in exports?
We're just about to pass on the
chairmanship of the OSDD to Grozin.
You must have faith in him
as a democrat.
Faith in an man guilty
of human rights violations?
Neither you nor your party
need to back this.
Denmark is extraditing a terror suspect
according to the law.
The law is not up for discussion.
- We need to make a decision.
Soon you'll be next door
for your photo shoot with Grozin.
We don't have to make a decision.
I have to.
Let's sign the extradition agreement
after the ceremony.
And now I want to be alone.
Good morning, Mr. President.
- Good morning, Prime Minister.
Mr. President, are you ready
for the press conference?
Excuse me. Could I have a moment
alone with the President, please?
Of course.
You too.
Would you care to sit down?
- Thank you.
What will happen to Bayanov
if we hand him over?
Let's not discuss that
on a day of celebration like this.
I can't hand him over,
if you won't tell me.
That is for the Turgesian people and
the Turgesian legal system to decide.
I mean no offence, but I really need
to know more than that.
Let me ask you a question.
Why do you consider yourself -
a better and more democratic
leader than I?
Why would you ask me that?
- Oh, I think you know.
How old is the Danish democracy?
160 years? Ours is 20 years old.
It takes time, Mrs. Prime Minister.
It takes time.
The Turgisian people are not used
to being asked, but to being told.
It is in the... DNA of my people
to obey the leader.
So if I understand you correctly -
it is you who will decide
what will happen to Bayanov?
Are we playing games?
- I hope not. A man's life is at stake.
When our democracy is 160 years old,
we can talk.
Until then I will not take any more
arrogant lessons from you.
Hand over Bayanov before
I sign any contract with North Wind.
By the way, I understand
it is your custom -
to pick the journalists yourself
at the press conference.
Well, I have a favor to ask of you.
Here is a list of journalists that
I do not wish to take questions from.
Please respect that.
"My nation believes
in the principle of free press -
and will uphold and defend this
in our constitution. " Recognize it?
It's part of the OSDD treaty you're
signing today as the new chairman.
There is a time and place for
free press. Today is not one of them.
No more games,
Mrs. Prime Minister.
Make sure Grozin gets this question.
We need your help.
- I don't want to talk to you.
Ask Grozin about this.
- Are you dictating my questions?
You have to.
- We have free press in this country.
You get the final question.
Believe me,
it's a question you want to ask.
Ladies and gentlemen of the press,
please take your seats.
Yes?
- Lindsay McGuilder, Guardian.
Is President Grozin satisfied
with the arrest of Vladimir Bayanov?
Yes, I'm very happy with the help we
have received from our Danish friends.
TV1.
How strong is the evidence
against Bayanov?
That is a question for the Danish
police. I cannot comment on that.
Was that the last question?
Before we end this press conference,
I'd like to say that...
The President and I have noticed the
criticism in the international media -
that Turgisia is taking
over the chairmanship for the OSDD.
But I'd like to quote President Grozin
from his inaugeration speech in 1996.
"Democracy is not a principle
you can bend. "
"It's either or, it's yes or no -
and today my nation, Turgisia,
has chosen to say yes to democracy. "
I think we have the time forjust
one last question. Katrine Fønsmark?
Yes. This is for President Grozin.
Does your investment in Danish
wind technology depend -
on the arrest and handing over
of Vladimir Bayanov?
I have great faith
in the Danish legal system -
and I can assure you
that I do not link -
the wind energy deal
with the case against Bayanov.
And thank you.
I think that was the last question.
I really appreciate your answer
to the last question -
because I'm not
going to hand him over.
And thank you very much.
- Thank you.
What's going on?
- Your dad's staying the weekend.
I just can't stand it,
even if he is a sweet old hippie.
I'm going to stay at a hotel.
- Wait. Give me two minutes.
Hi, Dad.
I've decided to stay the weekend,
so we can get some time together.
We haven't seen much of each other.
- No.
Dad, you can't.
I need some time alone with Phillip.
And Phillip needs his bathrobe,
his coffee and his red wine.
I need to keep the promise
I gave you last night.
Yes. I understand.
I'll pack my things.
Bayanov, who has been detained
in Denmark the last couple of days -
left the country tonight.
He was satisfied with the outcome
and flew on to Paris -
to talk
at a human rights conference.
President Grozin finished
his state visit today.
After having taken over
the chairmanship of the OSDD -
- he signed a deal with Danish
wind turbine company North Wind.
Turgisia has questioned
a number of the terms in the deal -
- so the deal isn't closed yet.
The kids are asleep.
- Okay.
Were they sorry to see him leave?
- A bit.
But you're happy, I hope.
Well, let's tidy up.
- No, I'll do that.
But first I want you to stay put
while I get...
...the best Turgisian wine there is.
One of the perks of the state visit.
I can't pronounce it, but it means
"the blood of the martyr".
Yup.
Well?
You do know
that your wife loves you?
I love her, too.
But I don't know about the PM.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst