Everyone knows I had an affair
with Yvonne a while back. It's over.
You can't just take off for days.
I got scared and thought
you were with another woman.
I was.
Yesterday, a press release stated -
that your husband is resigning.
My husband cannot benefit
financially from my policies -
- as long as he's married to me.
Clear your desk!
Take some time to consider,
if you want to be part of this team!
Why won't you talk to me?
- Because we don't talk, Birgitte.
We used to, but not anymore.
"A prince never lacks legitimate
reason to break his promise. "
The PM is under a lot of pressure
when she opens parliament.
The Moderates stand
to lose five seats.
The Greens stand to lose two,
but Labour stands to gain five.
The cabinet would lose its majority,
if we had an election today.
My guest today is editor-in-chief
of the Express, Michael Laugesen.
In today's editorial you advise
Birgitte Nyborg to resign.
Yes. Nyborg has lost her bearings
because the problems are piling up.
- A fatal mistake for a PM.
- You've graded her ministers.
You only give Minister for Finance
Bent Sejrø three out of ten.
Nyborg only just makes a five.
Aren't you being a harsh examiner?
I'm sure the public agrees with me.
What is her plan for Denmark?
I'd really like to know.
I don't think she's got a clue.
Birgitte, you can't live on coffee and
newspapers. My wife baked rolls.
Great.
Because these fridges are empty.
How are you?
- Apart from the polls?
Cabinet seats cost.
You know who's benefitting by it.
Labour.
- Exactly.
They're going
to put the squeeze on you.
What should I do?
- Give them a bit of what they want.
But not everything.
How are things at home?
- I don't know.
It's a mess.
We're avoiding each other.
We take turns in being with the kids -
and tell them the other one's
at work. And then we smile.
And where's Phillip?
- I think he's seeing someone.
It doesn't matter.
Believe me.
It hurts right now,
but it doesn't have to mean it's over.
My husband is having an affair.
I don't know any happy marriages
at Parliament.
We're great at compromising at work,
but lousy at it at home.
We don't even talk.
- So go home and talk to him.
You can't focus on work. Arrange
yourselves around where you stand.
You can't be happy all the time,
but you can arrange yourselves.
And eat your roll.
GOVERNMENT
Ep. 10- The First Tuesday in October
...every generation.
The energy, the faith, the devotion,
which we bring to this endeavor -
- will light our country
and all who serve it.
And the glow from that fire
can truly light the world.
And so, my fellow Americans:
Ask not what your country
can do for you.
Ask what you can do
for your country.
Let us make individual freedom
a common cause -
so we are free to...
...free enough to dare fight
for our common cause.
Let us create a Denmark where
everyone is free to try his fortune -
but bound by a common cause.
What do you want?
Have you been here long?
No.
I just came to catch up on work.
Sundays tend to be quiet.
What do you think?
- About?
The speech.
You were eavesdropping.
That's none of my business.
- Come on, Sanne. What do you think?
Well, I think you might like
to use another word than "bound".
It's as if it's something
we don't like.
"Bound by a common cause" sounds
like we don't like the common cause.
No, it encourages participation.
- It's not really my field...
I shouldn't have asked you.
Shut the door behind you, okay?
Ask not
what America will do for you -
- but what together we can do
for the freedom of man.
Looking desperate, Juul. That
opening speech giving you trouble?
Or have you joined the ranks of us
workaholics who work Sundays, too?
By the way. Obese little Leif Vinther
from "Stars and Royals" -
has been staking out Marienborg -
and says the PM has been sleeping
alone these past weeks. Is that true?
Being PM must put a strain
on one's private life.
Particularly, when you have to remove
your husband from a top job.
That's a hoax.
- It is?
You owe me one, Kasper.
Dogs!
Fine, Bjørn. Hi.
- Hi.
We need to stress our collaboration
with Labour in the speech a bit.
Was that Marrot?
Are the recent polls
swelling their heads?
Birgitte...
Rumor has it you're sleeping alone
at Marienborg.
Do we need to talk about that?
- No.
We just don't need negative stories
about your personal life.
Don't you need a bath?
Have a nice Sunday.
- You too.
I didn't know you were home.
- Well, I wasn't.
We need to talk.
- Yes.
We need to find a more valid solution
for our family life.
I didn't know you were here.
I really need a shower.
Sure.
We can talk afterwards.
- Okay.
Where have you been?
Okay...
Who is she?
- Birgitte, don't.
Who is your girlfriend?
- She's not my damned girlfriend.
Her name is Sasha. She works
for the agency who got me the job.
So she's your headhunter?
- Yes.
After you resigned, you...
- You resigned for me.
And then you slept with her.
You came straight from her now?
Yes, dammit.
- So you're having like an affair?
Sorry. I just can't talk to you
like this.
You reek of her! Come home
smelling of another woman.
Birgitte...
Hello?
Where the hell have you been?
- Rhodes.
With the pensioner's club?
- Open it.
How come you didn't get a tan?
- I hate lying on the beach.
I stayed in my room watching
the news. Simon is their new anchor.
How come?
- Well, I got fired.
After that interview with the PM.
Technically, I'm on holiday,
but I doubt he wants me back.
Jesus Christ.
Maybe it's for the best.
We didn't see eye to eye. He sucks up
to the brass and chases the ratings.
I want to dig deeper.
Just turned 30-
and you want to decide the line
of the country's largest network.
If now isn't the time to be
an idealist, when is?
I don't expect you to understand.
What's that supposed to mean?
- You never were an idealist.
You've always said
you can sell any message.
People change, you know?
I'll drink to that.
- Welcome home.
Good morning.
Did you read the speech?
- Yes. It needs a little work.
I agree. It does seem to echo
the words of someone else...
We need to discuss another issue.
Sit down.
Ever since I had to ask Phillip to
resign, we've been having problems.
I've spent a lot of my time
at Marienborg.
Okay.
- Yes.
I don't know where we're headed,
but I want it kept under wraps.
Of course.
Still, we have to brace ourselves
for the rumors you mentioned.
TV1 keeps asking for an interview,
both professional and personal...
No way, Kasper.
- I think you should reconsider.
If you and Phillip were
to act the happy couple -
we'd be able to refute the rumors.
You want us to act?
It would work,
if people were to see you together.
Of course, we need a skilled reporter
to interview you.
Who did you have in mind?
- Katrine Fønsmark.
She doesn't stick to the deals...
- That's the way we like them.
Sure, when I as Minister for the Press
honor investigative journalists...
She can create the private space
that becomes you so well.
This is our chance to control
whatever gets out of here.
It could help the lousy polls.
Torben. Kasper Juul speaking.
I've got a gift for you.
That portrait of the PM...
Are you in love with her?
No, of course not.
I miss you.
But I can't find you.
And when I do find you,
I don't always recognize you.
I know you pay a large price.
I just don't know
how I can change anything right now.
I can't invent more time.
It's not that you're away a lot.
It's that you're not here when you are.
That's how you see it.
The fact is we both make sacrifices.
Yes.
I don't want to lose you.
I have a proposition.
We stick together
and weather the storm.
I move back home.
You're my husband in everyday life
and in public.
And I'll just have to accept
that you sometimes seek...
...intimacy elsewhere.
I'm about to open Parliament
and fight for a budget bill -
with a cabinet
on the brink of collapse.
Birgitte, are you serious?
- Yes.
Promise me two things.
I want you to be discreet
about your extramarital affairs.
And I need you to participate
in a TV1 interview -
in which we end the speculations
about our personal lives.
Laura, let's go.
Magnus.
I don't want to go.
We don't have time for this.
- I don't want to!
I'll take him.
- Sure?
See you. Have a great day.
Get your bag.
- I don't want to go to school.
But you have to.
- I don't want to!
But, sweetie...
Good morning.
- Good morning, Magnus.
Magnus has come to work with me.
- What about the camera crew and...?
Magnus, great to see you.
I could do with a hand.
I bet you're good at clipping stuff.
I apologize for not getting you
a better secretary sooner.
There's no rush.
I like her interpersonal skills.
Sure, but those aren't the skills
we need here.
Is it opportune to have them film you
when you bring your son to work?
But they won't.
- Good.
Everything ready for the 8:30 news?
- Yes.
Excellent.
Hi, Katrine. There's no need
to lurk in the shadows.
Hi.
- Well...
Miss Fønsmark and I've had a deep
and personal talk about journalism -
and the chain of command here,
and we agreed to have another dance.
Great.
- Yeah, great.
Katrine just got
a very specific assignment.
The portrait of the PM
we've worked so hard to get -
has finally come through.
The PM's Office said yes?
- Yes.
Both at home and at the Office?
- Yes, beginning today.
I've decided to give Katrine
the assignment.
Congratulations, Katrine.
- Hang on.
I've been up for that portrait
from the very start.
Later, Ulrik.
- No, now.
I contacted the PM's Office
a week after Nyborg came to power -
and now Katrine gets it?
The Director General and I agree
that Katrine should do the interview.
She has a knack for creating
an intimate space for a conversation.
An intimate space?
- Yes.
You should discuss this in private.
- No need to.
Is Katrine anchoring again?
- Yes. I never promised you anything.
Has this got anything to do with
her ex being the PM's media adviser?
End of discussion.
- Torben...
This isn't over.
I wish I were dating
the PM's media adviser.
The Princess is back.
- Welcome back.
Thanks, Pia.
Okay, fine. Talk to you later.
Kasper, this TV1 interview...
I can't do it.
They'll be here in four hours.
- I know. My family's coming apart.
Laura doesn't talk. Magnus cries
and doesn't want to go to school.
Okay.
What if we get to see their material?
Edit it?
Edit material for the news?
That's a first.
We can't afford to put you
through the tabloid wringer.
Particularly not now.
See what you can do.
It's your idea. You've got four hours.
Jesus, Torben...
I'm afraid we're going to have
to cancel the interview.
Funny!
You are shitting me, right?
Sorry.
You can't. I have two teams standing
by day and night the next week.
I rehired a pain-in-the-ass reporter
because you requested her.
I'm sorry,
but you were outbid.
By whom?
- 2 are giving us editing rights.
What?
I don't fucking believe it.
I have to ask them what's going on.
- Be my guest.
But I doubt they'll own up to it.
It's unheard of.
- Yes.
In violation of every code.
- Torben, I thoroughly agree.
But it's practical for us,
as you very well know.
I knew you'd never agree to it.
- Damn straight!
And I accept that. Even if it only
goes for the personal part.
At her home. Out of consideration
for her children and her husband.
Birgitte is a considerate woman.
That's what makes her interesting.
- I know.
I understand your point of view,
and that's why 2 gets the story.
I'm sorry we wasted your time.
Hey, hey... Kasper.
Come back.
Shut the door.
If you get what you want,
I get a free hand at the PM's Office.
No monkeying around on your part.
- I want it in writing.
Fine. You'll get it in writing.
Thanks for the coffee.
The opening speech you just read
is just the first draft.
It's weak on environment.
- I disagree, Amir.
We still aim to increase the CO2 tax
and the level of green energy.
Sure, it's a compromise in relation
to the Greens' proposal -
but those are the terms
in a cabinet such as ours.
Any questions?
Yes.
- I want to discuss the polls.
They're not on the agenda, Pernille.
We can discuss them later.
- Sure.
Yes.
Please stick to our agreement,
when the camera crew is present.
Bjørn tried to talk to you yesterday
about the polls. In vain.
I had other things on my mind.
- Labour is the largest party now.
We want the minister seats
to reflect that.
What do you want, Bjørn?
- We feel it only fair...
The Ministry for Finance.
- That's Bent Sejrø's.
After the news about his affair
with Yvonne Kjær we can't trust him.
You can't be serious.
That's an old smear story.
Did the affair help the budget bill?
- That was my craftmanship.
Bent ranks lowest
on the popularity lists.
He holds the purse strings. Name me
one popular Minister for Finance.
The Minister for Finance is here.
- Ask him to wait, please.
Bent is getting on, too.
You have both the PM's Office
and the Ministry for Finance.
They ought to be divided among
the two largest cabinet parties.
This is not an ultimatum. We expect
you to make the necessary decision.
Thank you for our little chat.
- Thank you.
Great. I'll see to it.
I will. Okay. Bye.
Let's see, if it was just
a lucky punch last time -
or if you really do
have a knack for speeches.
Later.
Magnus and I are really busy.
I can't both look after Magnus,
do my work and now yours, too.
How about if we meet tonight
and go through the speech?
I'll buy sushi.
- Tonight?
Deal.
- Okay.
Hi. We're finished...
The PM brought her son to work?
Is that a regular thing?
- Bye for now.
Let me talk to him.
- No.
No, I'm not curtailing the free press.
Just be glad you got the interview.
Word is you got me the assignment.
You'd never do that, would you?
Nope...
- Thanks.
See you.
Kennedy's speech writer was
of Danish heritage. Damn straight!
Theodore Sorensen.
His parents emigrated to America -
giving their son the chance to write
speeches that changed the world.
The greatest thing about
Kennedy's inaugeration speech is -
that it's got pathos -
and it creates a feeling
of solidarity with the President.
Well, get cracking then.
Ask not what Nyborg can do for you...
...'cause she's not going to listen
anyway. So do your own stuff.
Sanne, I can't just copy it.
Maybe I can copy the build-up.
It's a three stage rocket.
- How do you mean?
Kennedy begins a sentence
with "ask not" three times.
That creates rhythm. The rhythm
takes us down into our body.
A politician should never speak
to the head alone, but to the gut, too.
And to the heart.
That's where the words settle.
I didn't think there'd still be anyone
here. Lights are out in the hall.
Yeah, but Birgitte needs
her speech tomorrow, so...
I've been giving him a hand,
but I was about to leave.
Thanks.
- Well, drive safely.
I hope you clean up your mess.
I don't want secretaries bawling
their eyes out in the PM's Office.
Of course.
- Good.
I look forward to hearing your speech.
Can the PM still find time
to bake and mow the lawn?
No, I don't bake.
Phillip runs the show at home.
My work is at the Office.
And my baking's terrible.
Being the PM
requires a lot of one's family.
Thank God,
we're all set on making it work.
Was that task division prepared
when the election results came in?
No, we weren't prepared
for anything like that.
I think the most important thing
is having the right husband.
And I have.
Otherwise itjust wouldn't work out.
That makes heavy calls on the right
man. Where do you find the energy?
Well...
Finding the energy
for the people you love -
comes quite naturally, really.
Are you going skating tomorrow?
- Yes, I'm going with Mathilde.
I can drive you.
- You don't have to.
Can I leave the table?
I'm finished.
It was great.
- Thank you.
Great food.
I've got that meeting.
- Yes.
Thanks for your help.
I think the interview went really well.
Will you be back
before the kids wake up?
Of course.
Bye.
Hi, Kasper.
- Sorry to disturb.
I've arranged
with the head of news -
to go through the interview
tomorrow. Katrine won't be told.
If we make any changes,
he'll say it was his call.
I don't like it.
It's below our standards.
It was your idea.
I'd never have agreed to it otherwise.
Dig out your inner cynic
or regard it an order -
- if that makes it easier.
Okay? Bye.
Laura?
Where did Dad go?
- He had a meeting.
What kind of meeting?
- I don't know. Just a meeting.
What are they meeting about?
- It's just a meeting.
What kind of meeting?
- Just a meeting, Laura!
I'm sorry. Sorry.
I guess I'm a bit tired.
What's going on with you and Dad?
- I don't know.
We're going through a difficult time.
We make each other very unhappy.
But we're fighting.
We'll work it out.
That makes heavy calls on the right
man. Where do you find the energy?
Finding the energy
for the people you love...
- It comes quite naturally, really.
- And cut.
How about the clip where Phillip
talks about Birgitte's devotion?
Which one?
- There was this one clip.
Go on... That one.
What word sums up Birgitte?
Devoted.
I've never met anyone
as devoted as Birgitte in my life.
Shejust can't help fighting
for the things she believes in.
You wanted that out before.
Edit in a clip of Birgitte and the kids
between those two statements.
We have the two clips of her
helping the kids with their homework.
Ulrik, didn't you see
the 'Do not disturb' sign?
Have we got a new editor?
Where's Katrine?
Ulrik, we're working.
Do you mind?
Katrine, I just saw something
that might interest you.
Watch this then.
- Devoted.
I've never met anyone
as devoted as Birgitte in my life.
Shejust can't help fighting
for the things she believes in.
Sanne, I don't want to be disturbed.
Birgitte?
Hi.
I didn't stay at Sasha's last night.
- You don't have to tell me.
I haven't slept at all.
I've been sitting in the car all night
thinking about yesterday.
Remember when we saw
Lars Hesselboe and his wife on TV -
just after the election?
We didn't want to end like them.
That was one year ago, Birgitte.
- We need to give it time.
No. Please listen
to what I have to say.
The best thing
that's ever happened to me...
...is what you and I had.
You and me.
But... in that interview yesterday -
we turned all that into a travesty.
And we aced it.
I mean, we...
We sat there betraying it
with big smiles on our faces.
But I won't, Birgitte.
And I can't.
What do you want?
I want a divorce
as soon as possible.
I don't want this to be
what we remember.
Excuse me.
Christ!
- Birgitte.
Kasper. We have a problem.
I'm getting a divorce.
Are you absolutely sure?
- Yes.
About the portrait...
- I'll handle it.
Thanks.
Devoted. I've never met anyone
as devoted as Birgitte...
I'm afraid we have to call it off.
- What do you mean?
We can't show it.
- But we've edited it.
Things have changed.
I want you to delete all footage
from the PM's home.
No way! We've been working
around the clock. You can't ask us to.
Torben Friis has given us full veto
over the program.
How's it going?
I presume you cleared all this
with your people?
What's the problem?
- Have you got a minute?
We have to find a compromise.
- We have an agreement.
Yes.
I presume Katrine doesn't need
to know anything about this.
I'll make it look
as if it came from upstairs.
The Express keeps writing
about my affair with Yvonne.
It's pure spin.
Someone is out to discredit me.
Who?
- It could be anyone.
Hesselboe... to get Yvonne
back in the fold.
These rumors are bound
to make her keep her distance.
Or Labour.
- Why?
You said yourself their polls are
making their heads swell.
No! Oh, to hell with it.
I'm not going
to let that crap get to me.
How is your wife taking it?
- She...
We've arranged ourselves.
What about you?
It was too late.
I'm getting a divorce.
Oh dear.
Is there anything I can do?
We need to talk.
"The prize is awarded for the series
on the legal system's pitfalls -
told with deep respect for that
most sacred virtue of journalism. "
"Political independence
and impartiality. "
That was the Cavling Committee's
motivation for awarding you the prize.
How the hell could you do it?
- 2 was going to get the portrait.
You let the PM's media adviser
edit a news story!
As the largest network in the country
we have many agendas.
Appropriations, the new media bill,
thousands of things.
No, there's only one thing!
You betrayed your responsibility.
Abroad, reporters risk their lives to
defend the free press. You piss on it!
You let them shut you up,
and I want no part of it.
I'll e-mail my resignation.
I'm sorry about you and Phillip.
Tell me, if there's anything I can do.
Thanks.
Let's keep it under wraps for now.
We won't tell the kids until Tuesday
after the opening of Parliament.
And when we do go public,
keep it short and usentimental.
The more we tone it down,
the less sympathy you'll get.
You can't have it all.
That reminds me of the speech.
Great work, but I want
the speech to be more ambitious.
Fine. What do you want?
Why should I vote for you?
Have you got any agenda
apart from clinging to power?
We've made a hell of a lot of changes
this past year.
What do you want?
I want to tell the Danes
they're better than they think.
They've forgotten that -
in their quest for a new car
and a cool kitchen -
a great family,
a mistress and a yacht.
We've been busy
pursuing our own happiness.
And we feel unfairly treated,
if we don't get it.
But we can't have it all.
Don't make it a slap on the wrist.
We want people to come together.
Danes are all for solidarity. They're
always ready to make sacrifices.
But we lost sight of it. Now we just
sing about it at funerals.
"Fight and live for all you love. "
That could work.
I've got it,
and you're going to love it.
I'm going to write it in the Hall
of Mirrors. Say I'm in a meeting, okay?
Kasper, about last night...
Sure.
Listen, I...
I loved going over the speech
with you.
And I loved...
I loved...
Under normal circumstances
I'd ask you out now -
hoping to pick up where we left...
But you can't have everything.
- No.
Birgitte.
The press won't let up on Sejrø.
- In whose interest, I wonder?
When a personal matter weakens
the cabinet, it interests the public.
We're talking about an old affair, not
high treason. I refuse to discuss it.
I hope you won't refuse to talk about
a more fair division of ministries.
Our Party is very insistent,
and the Greens back us up.
Have you held talks
behind my back?
Amir sympathizes with our stand.
I need to open Parliament on Tuesday
with my cabinet behind me.
I find your timing odd.
- Our timing is perfect.
We'll start off the year with a small
cabinet rotation to trim the team.
You want to stay in power.
We stand stronger with the public
than you do. That's the simple truth.
Well, thank you for our little chat.
Please sign these before you go.
Could I talk to you later?
- Sure.
I just had a little chat with Labour.
Inform the Queen
we're appointing a new minister.
I'll inform the Lord Chamberlain.
I want to meet with the Minister
for Finance before he leaves.
Set up a meeting with him.
- Very well.
Thanks.
Labour is putting the squeeze on me.
They say your affair has caused a lack
of faith between the cabinet parties.
Bullshit.
- Amir is backing them up.
Do they want me to make
a public apology?
"Sorry I had sex with that woman. "
- It's got nothing to do with that.
They're using the affair
to a different end.
Bent, they want
the Ministry for Finance.
Hell, Birgitte,
you don't have to comply.
I'm not finished yet.
Sure, I'm getting on -
but I'm experienced,
and I know the game.
Politics has always been my life.
- Yes, and this is politics.
I need you to resign.
Okay... I guess I'll have more time
for my hydrangeas.
It's the first Tuesday in October,
and focus is on the speech -
- with which Birgitte Nyborg
is going to open Parliament.
The PM's cabinet rotation
is the talk of the town.
Bent Sejrø has resigned
as Minister for Finance -
and Nyborg strengthened
the ties to Labour -
by making Pernille Madsen
his successor.
Commentators call this rotation -
a strong display of power
from a resolute and realistic PM.
The Prime Minister has the floor.
What ties a nation together?
As a young student, I was there on
the Town Square on June 26, 1992.
Denmark had just won
the European Football Championship.
That night I knew
we were one people.
One people who almost knew
the national anthem by heart.
We were amazed.
The past 140 years had taught us
we were a nation -
of kind-hearted losers who were
almost always beaten by the Germans.
Suddenly we had beaten them.
We've gotten used to the fact
that we can have it all.
Now that we aren't as rich anymore,
we feel lost -
and we worry about things that
would never have mattered before.
Look what I can do.
Each of us in Parliament
represents 30,000 Danes.
They've invested all their hopes
of a better future in us.
We need to act responsibly
way beyond party differences -
short-sighted bloc politics
and smear campaigns.
I believe we need each other.
I believe we belong together
as a nation.
I believe we're united by more
than separates us.
I believe deep down
we're the same people -
- who all rejoiced that night in June
on the Town Square.
For those of you who have forgotten
the lyrics, the anthem ends:
"Our ancient Denmark shall abide. "
Let's see to that...
...together.
Thank you.
Fantastic speech.
- You never were better.
Magnificent.
Lars Hesselboe, what was it like
to see someone else give the speech?
It was the usual empty rhetoric.
May I, off the record, commend you
on an exceptionally fine speech?
Thank you, Svend Åge.
I did what was necessary.
- That's what a PM does.
Kasper, great speech.
- Thank you.
Katrine, what's up?
Great speech. Probably
the best opening speech ever.
You don't sound very sincere.
- Oh, I'm sincere.
You're good at keeping things apart.
You can write heartfelt speeches
and still act the cynic.
I quit my job. I got wind
of your little deal with Torben Friis.
Let me explain.
- Forget it.
You've got your secrets,
and I'm naive. We never change.
Sure we do.
- No.
But keep dreaming.
So you quit. Then what?
There she is.
- Hi, Mom.
Great speech.
Congratulations.
We'll head on home.
When are you coming home?
- Late, I'm afraid.
Come along, kids.
Bye.
See you.
- Yes. See you.
Can I say something?
That was one of the best opening
speeches I've heard in my time here.
I didn't think
you'd last a year -
but if you keep this up,
we can keep up the good work.
I finally found due cause
to get rid of Sanne.
Staff issues, don't worry about it.
Your new secretary starts tomorrow.
Top-notch.
- Thanks.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst