Jay, I'm home.
Did Manny call?
No, because he's fine.
It was a slumber party,
not a gang fight.
I just want him
to fit in.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Do you care to join me?
You know, honey, there's a gun
in the footlocker in the garage.
If I ever say no to that question,
I want you to use it on me.
[Laughing]
[Haley Chanting]
Miss Mary Mack, Mack, Mack.
All dressed in black,
black, black.
Shh, shh.
[Whispers] What's wrong?
With silver buttons,
buttons, buttons.
All down her back,
back, back.
Why aren't they trying
to hurt each other?
I don't know,
but I'm afraid to move.
[Laughing]
You're really good at this.
Thanks.
What is happening,
Claire?
[Cameron] Mmm!
[Mitchell]
What do you think?
Now, that is a scone.
No butter. Nonfat.
Shut up.
[Doorbell Rings]
I'm gonna
go check on Lily.
Surprise!
Mom!
[Thud, Wings Fluttering]
What's that?
Sounds like a bird
hit the window.
Oh, God.
That's a bad sign.
Ow! That hurt, jerk!
[Growls]
Ow! I'm gonna kill you,
stupid!
Ow!
What happened?
Now I'm sad.
Hi, honey. Mmm!
Hi. I, uh-
I- I didn't know
you were in town.
You didn't call.
Well, I couldn't wait
to see your new baby.
Where is she?
Mitchell, who was that?
It's my mom.
Oh, yeah, right, 'cause
the last time she was here,
the refrigerator magnets
rearranged themselves...
into a penta- Grandma!
[Man]
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey
Hey, hey ♪
Hey ♪♪
Oh.
[Lily Cooing]
Mom. Mom, what are you
doing to her legs?
Tai chi. I did it
every day in Sedona.
Cameron, you should try it.
[Chuckles]
Mitchell's mother
has a problem... with me.
Last Christmas, for example,
she gave me a piece
of exercise equipment
and a lettuce dryer.
So, to recap,
I gave her a gorgeous pair
of diamond earrings,
and she gave me a hint.
And living in Sedona
has been transformational.
I get up every morning,
and I go to a Vortex
meditation site...
and work with a shaman
to finally understand how
to live my spirituality.
Yikes.
And I've learned that
the only way I can move...
to the next level
of my awakening...
is if we all can somehow...
get past... the incident.
Oh, no.
- The incident.
- Oh, boy.
I would like to congratulate
Jay and the lovely Gloria.
I'm very happy for them.
I wanted a big, beautiful
wedding with Jay...
because my ex-husband and I
got married...
in a tiny little office
of a judge in Colombia.
My mother wanted to go
to the wedding to show everyone
how okay she was with all of it,
so I convinced Dad and Gloria
to invite her.
Who warned you that that
was the worst idea ever?
Anyone? Anyone?
Oh.
[Chuckles]
Of course,
I've-I've moved on.
[Chuckling]
I was supposed to
come with a date,
but he just hurt his back,
which is very ironic
because he's young
and-and healthy.
My mom started drinking...
these cocktails called
"Horny Colombians"...
with some
of Gloria's uncles,
whom apparently the drink
was named after.
[Phil]
Oh, come on. They were funny.
They kept patting
my butt.
Somebody's full of herself.
It's a- It's a Colombian wedding
tradition, they said.
[Glass Clinking]
I would like
to make a toast.
Yeah.
Nana got totally wasted.
Uh, it was really funny.
Then it was gross.
To the bride
and the groom- my ex.
Thirty-five years
we were together,
and he couldn't wait 10 minutes
to run off with Charo.
- [Guests Groaning]
- That's a joke. That's a joke.
- [Rim Shot]
- Seriously, I knew they were
perfect for each other...
when I saw his wallet
and her boobs.
[Groaning Continues]
Take your hands off me!
- Mom. Mom.
- Oh, relax, Mitchell.
What, did you take
your Claire pill?
Let's just go get
a little fresh air, okay?
No, no.
And then it got weird.
[Mock Accent]
I'm Gloria! I'm Gloria!
I got her.
Kiss me!
Oh, hey, kiss me!
[Grunting]
No!
Oh, geez.
Nana is really strong.
[Guests Gasping]
Ayayayayay!
Ooh! Ayayayayay!
[Shouts]
[Guests Gasping]
During my vows to my first
husband, drug dealers burst in
and assassinated the judge.
This was way worse.
What can I say?
I drive women crazy.
[Laughing]
It's too soon, I guess.
- Everybody is going
to be there, Mom!
- I don't care.
Your father and I are not about
to let you drive two hours
to go to a concert...
and then spend the night
with a bunch of boys,
especially that 17-year-old
hormone you're dating.
- It's totally supervised.
- Oh, really? By whom?
- By Spencer Patine's uncle.
- Who's Spencer Patine?
You know Spencer-
the guy with the arm.
Wait. What kind of arm?
What does that even mean?
His uncle is Uncle Toby.
Oh, Uncle Toby.
I'll be sure to include that
in my Amber Alert.
Oh, my God!
Okay. Can I step in here?
I think I can help.
Haley, what your mom
is worried about...
is you getting your heart broken
when Dylan goes off
to college next year.
He's not going to college.
That's not what I'm-
He's not going to college?
He's in a band, okay?
They're going on tour.
Oh, this just gets
better and better.
Why are you always on me
about everything?
Because you need
to understand-
Okay. Everybody, calm down!
Let's start from the beginning.
What's wrong
with Spencer's arm?
[Grunts]
Mom, I'm home!
Ay, baby! Did you have fun
at the slumber party?
You must be exhausted.
No, I'm not tired at all.
I was the first one
to fall asleep.
What's on your face?
A smile from having such
a good time with my friends.
No. Come here.
Look.
Oh.
That's why they were laughing.
I thought it was my funny take
on current events.
Why would they do
something like that?
Don't worry about it.
Guys pull pranks like that all the time.
You just gotta prank 'em back.
You just gotta show 'em
you're willing to give
as good as you get.
What do you think?
Hmm.
Revenge.
I like it.
Well, Mom, instead of dredging up
the whole incident,
maybe we should just try and repress it,
like a- like a normal family.
I can't.
I need closure.
I'm about to embark
on a new journey.
- I met a man.
- Really?
His name is Chas, and he's
asked me to come live with him
in his foreign land.
- Wow. Where?
- Canada.
- You're moving to-to Canada?
- French Canada.
Oh.
Oh. Oh.
That's wonderful.
It is wonderful.
It's just that when I think
of all the awful things...
that I said to Gloria
and Jay and you and Claire,
I feel such guilt.
Give it time,
and see Banff.
Cam, please.
I just can't give myself
to him sexually.
Okay. Mom.
Did not see that coming.
Oh, oh. Don't get me wrong.
We satisfy each other
down there-
Oh!
Can't-
Don't wanna-
That's why I need
everyone's forgiveness.
I need your help, Mitchell.
Did you hear that, Mitchell?
Your mom needs your help to
make love to her new man, Chas.
That's not weird at all.
Mom, I- [Chuckles]
I'm just not really sure what
you're asking me to do, Mom.
Well, everyone's mad at me.
Oh-
Maybe you could pave the way
so that I can apologize.
Well, um, you know,
we are actually
all supposed to have
Sunday dinner tonight,
so maybe I could go around
and ask everyone if it's okay
for you to join us.
Oh! I knew
I could count on you.
Oh, my beautiful boy.
Mmm.
I love you so much.
There's a fish in nature that
swims around with its babies
in its mouth.
That fish would look
at Mitchell's relationship
with his mother...
and say, "That's messed up."
Hey.
Boy-
[Clears Throat]
Things with your mom
got pretty intense
down there, huh?
All like
East Coast-West Coast.
You feelin' me?
Act like a parent,
talk like a peer.
I call it "peerenting."
I learned it from my own dad,
who used to walk into my room...
and say,
"What's up, Sweathog?"
Honey, I would love to
let you go to the concert.
Are you kidding me?
I think concerts are rad.
- Hello? I was a Hall-Raiser.
- A what?
I followed Hall & Oates
around the country one summer.
"Rich Girl"
just spoke to me.
I was dating this girl.
Not- Not dating.
I guess I was
following her too, kind of-
Okay, Mom just doesn't trust me,
and it's not fair.
She trusts you.
It's just that weird stuff
happens at concerts.
- Boys get urges.
- Ew.
Dad, is there
something you want?
Yes, there is- to connect
with this girl right here.
Now, come on.
Pretend I'm not your dad.
We're just a couple
of friends kickin' it
in a juice bar.
- What's a juice bar?
- Okay, a malt shop. Whatever.
Dad, I don't-
No. Who's Dad?
Who's Dad?
I'm- I'm Marcus from Biology.
Hey, Haley. How's it going
with you and Dylan?
Has he tried anything
inappropriate with you? Girl.
[Ringing]
Hey.
[Girl]
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Just talking to some dork
I met in a malt shop.
[Doorbell Rings]
Hey, Mitchell. What's up?
Hey! Just in the hood.
Do you- Do you remember
how Mom gave up a career
to raise us?
Promising career.
Oh, God.
Claire?
Mom.
Why so long?
I know, I know.
It's weird when we haven't
talked for a while.
I mean your hair.
Mmm. Mmm.
Well, if I can't
tell you, who will?
[Mouthing Words]
So, Mom wants you to know
that she's very sorry
about the incident,
and-and she wants us
to forgive her.
How very nice of her
to say that through you.
Do you see?
The sarcasm is so hurtful,
like a whip.
You know how growing up,
we all have that voice
inside our head...
that tells us
we're not good enough?
Well, mine was outside my head,
driving me to school.
Uh, so- so anyway, Mom really
wants to smooth everything over
with Dad and Gloria.
So I was thinking, uh, would it
be okay if she maybe joined us
for dinner tonight?
Because it may be
the last time
you ever see me.
Well-
Okay. Wait, Mom.
What are you talking about?
Well, I'm- I'm moving...
to a far
and dangerous place.
Canada. But, uh, she met
a man named Chas.
Yeah.
He's a logger.
Uh, like a lumberjack?
No, he logs blood samples
into a cholesterol study.
Anyway, until I'm past
this whole wedding debacle,
I can't be intimate with him.
Oh.
We do things
to each other.
We use our hands.
Oh, my Lord.
Hey, Nana.
Oh, my little comet!
Hi.
Oh, look at you.
You're all grown up.
Hmm. Tell Mom that.
She won't even let me
go to a concert.
Overnight,
with her boyfriend.
[Laughing]
What are you
laughing at?
Oh, karma's
a funny thing, that's all.
- Remember Ricky?
- Oh, God.
Ooh. Who's Ricky?
[Claire]
No one.
Ricky was your mother's
boyfriend,
and he looked
like Charles Manson.
And one night,
she didn't come home
until 4:00 in the morning.
4:00. Wow. Wow.
Mom, what were you
and Ricky doing?
Nothing. We were doing nothing,
and he was a very sweet boy,
which you might have known
if you bothered
to get to know him.
- Dylan's a sweet boy.
- [Scoffs]
Dylan. Dylan isn't Ricky.
Ricky- Ricky was a poet.
Dylan writes songs.
Awesome songs.
And maybe you would know that
"if you bothered to get to know him."
Ha!
[Laughing]
Okay, you know?
First of all,
I am not my mother.
I don't judge people before
I get a chance to know them.
So you invite Dylan over
to dinner tonight,
and if he's as sweet
and as kind as you say he is,
then I have no problem
considering letting you
go to the concert,
after I do
a background check
on Uncle Toby.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, Mom.
I'm gonna go call him!
That's very revealing.
That's my parenting style.
- No, I meant your blouse.
- Mom!
Claire, wait. Come-
Not making this easy.
Claire, come on.
Stop, stop, stop.
Just let her come to dinner,
apologize to Dad and Gloria,
and she and Chas can live
happily ever after.
In Canada.
Wait. Why don't you make her
fix this, instead of you
doing it as usual?
Whoa. What's that
supposed to mean?
Mom makes a mess,
and there's Mitchell
to clean it up.
That is so not true.
If anything, you're
the one with the screwed-up
relationship with Mommy-
With Mom.
Wow. "Mommy"!
No, I didn't say it-
Damn it.
Ooh. Fine. Fine.
She can come, but she's
gotta clear it with Daddy.
"Daddy"?
I did not say "Daddy."
You said "Daddy."
Hey, Dad.
Mitchell, what are you
doing here?
Uh, I'm sorry to bother you.
Can I talk to you and Gloria
for a second?
She's out dealing
with a Manny situation.
- He set a kid's bike on fire.
- Why?
Oh, I might have told him
to get even with some kids,
and he went all Rambo with it.
[Shouts]
Not my best parenting moment.
[Chuckling]
Not your worst.
What's up?
Uh, well, you know,
uh, Mom's in town.
Your mom?
No, your mom.
She's back from the grave.
Yes. Yes, my mom, Dad.
My mom would be less scary.
Listen, she's a wreck about
what happened at the wedding,
and she wants
to come to dinner tonight
to apologize to everyone.
Still her little errand boy,
I see.
No- Why does everybody
keep saying- No.
I- I'm just trying
to piece this family
back together.
So, you'll talk to Gloria
about Mom coming to dinner?
Oh, Gloria
would never go for that
in a million years.
She's still furious with
your mother, which is why
I'm not talking to you.
What did I do?
This conversation
never took place.
That's not very nice.
I drove all the way here.
You were never here.
- You never even called.
- I would've called, but I
thought it would be better-
What's happening here?
Listen, I would love to
get this thing behind us,
but Gloria would never
forgive me if I pulled
a fast one on her.
That's why you're going to
pull a fast one on her,
and I'm not going to
like it one bit.
Okay, that's just great.
No, that's great.
So, it's all up to me.
I can't hear you
because you're back home,
and I'm taking a nap.
[Sighs]
[Doorbell Rings]
D-Money! There he is.
Hey.
Come on in.
Hi.
How you doing?
Good. Um-
Uh, hey, everybody.
This is Dylan.
Hey.
Hi, Dylan.
He has
a very gentle soul.
You got that from "Hey"?
So, Dylan, see you
brought the ax.
Yeah, yeah.
I just came from practice.
Sweet.
- Miss those days.
- Oh, you were in a band?
Could have been,
but in high school I was really
all about my magic, so-
Oh, my God. Over.
[Doorbell Ringing]
- Oh, that's gonna
be Dad and Gloria.
- Oh, Mitchell.
I know it's silly,
but I'm a little nervous.
Oh. That's not silly.
You should be.
[Door Opens]
Hola.
Hola. How are you?
Manny?
Phil.
Nice mustache.
Thank you.
Don't make fun.
He may burn your house down.
- Oh, boy.
- Dede.
- Hi, Jay, Gloria.
- What is she doing here?
What does she mean,
"What is she doing here?"
- Mitchell told you I'd be here.
- Lies!
I couldn't tell her,
because she wouldn't come.
Gloria, uh, my mom wants
to apologize for everything.
So you just spring it
on Gloria like this? Mitchell,
what the hell is wrong with you?
- I don't want her apologies.
- Who could blame you, honey?
Which is why this is
a terrible idea by you!
Jay. Manny. Let's go.
Oh, wait, wait, Gloria.
I- I just want to
tell you how sorry I am
for ruining your wedding.
I was struggling
with being alone.
Meanwhile,
Jay moves on so easily,
and-and not with just anyone-
with a... young...
and smart
and beautiful woman.
I don't expect you
to forgive me.
If I were you, I'd want to
punch me right in the mouth.
[Sighs]
I think we've had enough revenge
in this family for one day.
Ah. Okay. Y- You see?
Yeah, we're all
gonna move past this,
and because of me,
who's not a mama's boy,
but is a caring person with
wisdom and emotional insight.
So make a note, bitches.
It's not a good color on you.
I forgive you.
Oh, wow.
I am not prepared
for this.
I just-
I- I wanna rip
your head off!
What?
¡Una loca peligrosa!
[Phil]
What are you doing?
You ruined my wedding!
Oh, no!
Oh!
I got Gloria!
- I got Gloria!
- Mom, come on.
- [Gloria] ¡No! ¿Qué pasa?
- Unbend your legs.
I got Gloria.
Stand up like a big girl.
Come on.
All right. Stop it. Stop it.
Stop it, the two of you.
I am so sorry about this.
No, it's cool. It's cool.
This is ridiculous.
Gloria didn't steal me, Dede,
and you know it.
We grew apart for years,
and you left to find yourself,
remember?
I thought I could
handle this.
- I'm so sorry.
- You don't say sorry anymore!
That word means nothing
in your mouth!
I got Gloria.
I don't know
what just happened.
[Dylan]
I do.
I mean, it seems
pretty simple to me.
You're reaching out,
trying to hold on
to something awesome.
Um, maybe-
maybe you shouldn't-
Look, look, look.
I'm not used to this-
the whole big family thing.
In my house, we don't
even talk to each other.
You know, it's funny-
the first time I saw Haley,
I knew I liked her.
I mean,
she's beautiful and everything,
but it's-it's not just that.
It's that she's got
this killer confidence-
you know, the kind of confidence
that you get from having
a family like this...
that's passionate...
and accepting
of hot foreigners...
and gay dudes
and nutty people.
You know,
a family that actually
loves each other.
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this, but maybe
we should let her go with him.
He's perfect.
Everybody, Haley says
that Dylan is a musician,
and he writes
some great songs.
Yeah.
Play something, bro.
Well, I guess so,
if you want me to.
We could all use
a nice tune right now.
This is, uh, actually
a song I wrote for Haley.
It's called
"In the Moonlight."
Lovely title, Dylan.
Thanks.
♪ The stars are falling
from the sky ♪
♪ And you're the reason why ♪
♪ The moon is shining
on your face ♪
♪ 'Cause it finally feels ♪
♪ It's found its place ♪
♪ 'Cause baby, baby ♪
♪ I just wanna do you
do you ♪
♪ Do you wanna do me, do me ♪
♪ Underneath the moonlight
the moonlight ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ Maybe I will steal you
Uh, steal you ♪
♪ Just so I can feel you
feel you ♪
♪ Maybe that would heal you
heal you ♪
♪ On the inside ♪
She's so not going.
Not a chance in hell.
♪♪ [Ends]
[Mitchell]
♪ They don't seem to mind ♪
♪ The moon is shining
on your fa-a-ace ♪
♪ And it finally feels it's ♪
♪ Found its place 'cause ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ I just wanna do you, do you ♪
♪ Baby, you can do me, do me ♪
♪ And I will do you, do you ♪
[Together]
♪ Maybe it would heal you
heal you ♪
♪ From the inside ♪
♪ Inside ♪♪
Never good
at harmonizing.
That was good.
ENGLISH - US - PSDH
www.tvsubtitles.net