Hmm, let's see.
Global warming.
And getting a "b."
The phone ringing in the
middle of the night.
That I'm too much
of a perfectionist.
Honey, this isn't a job interview.
Oh, man.
Job interviews.
Nothing.
Yeah, right.
What about the pigeons?
Oh, I don't like them.
They're shifty.
Losing mitchell.
Oh!
Hotel bedspreads.
Never getting my driver's license.
Or getting one and
the picture sucks.
Dying alone.
Oh, haley, sweetie,
did you find your shoes?
Mom, please, not today.
I just wanted to know
if you found your shoes.
Why are you hounding me?
I'm freaking out right now!
You need to relax.
It's just a driver's test.
It's my third driver's test,
and if I fail again,
I have to wait six
months to retake it.
That's six more months of
you driving me everywhere.
And then I'm like,
"there's no way I'm wearing that."
And she was like, "well, if you don't
wear it, then you can't play." "like."
And then I was like, "well, you know what?
That's fine by me." honey, "like."
And she was like, "well, if you don't play,
then --" "like." "like."
Mom! Mom! Stop! Stop
saying "like" all the time!
You're embarrassing me! Stop it!! Like,
like, like, like, like! Aah!
Mm.
Haley, found your jacket.
Why is everyone on me?!
God!
Ignore her.
She can't focus on
two things at once.
Always a good quality in a driver.
Sweetie, we need to get you some
shoes for the dance tonight.
No, we don't. I'm not going.
What are you talking about?
Why would you not be
going to the dance?
Because school dances are lame.
A bunch of immature boys
Trying to impress you
with how cool they are
When they're really
just a bunch of dorks.
ready to go down under, mate? Yes.
What are you doing?
Treasure hunting. Treasure hunting.
Wow.
a few days ago, the cable
guy was under the house.
When he was leaving,
he said to haley,
"wow, that's quite a collection
you've got down there."
Here's the thing -- we have no
idea what he's talking about.
All week, luke and I have been
getting more and more excited
About what it could be.
I bet it's really
cool old magazines.
Yeah.
Or a bunch of necklaces
made out of animal teeth.
Or bugs frozen in amber.
What if it's really
expensive bottles of wine?
Or a suit of armor.
What if there's ancient
indian arrowheads under there?
What if it's gold bars?
Oh, you think?
For god's sakes, why don't you
go under the house and look?
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, cam. Cam, where did
we get this dolly from?
Oh, from janice and olivia.
They brought it over yesterday.
Lily loves it.
It seems a little frilly,
you know, coming from them.
What, because they're lesbians?
That's sort of an offensive
stereotype, don't you think?
Yeah, I suppose. I'm sorry.
Oh, hey, did they bring
back our coffee maker?
Nwe got off to an awkward start
they werewith our pediatrician,
A very nice asian
lady - irrelevant.
...Named dr. Miura,
So I took the bold step of
inviting her over for brunch.
I'm sorry, uh, "bold"?
She said no patient had
ever done it before.
Yeah, subtext -- "this is weird."
I didn't hear any subtext.
Do you hear any now?
I don't even know why
we're doing this.
Because what if lily gets sick
and there's a tamiflu shortage?
Who do you think's gonna
get that medicine?
The patients she likes, that's who.
Well, maybe if you bake her a cake,
She'll give us free x-rays.
It's all about making connections.
Why do you think the dentist
gives me all that free stuff?
Um, because he's a huge queen
and he has a big crush on you.
Really? Do you think so?
Mom? Gloria: Hmm?
I have a fever.
Ay, mi amor, come here,
and I feel you.
Oh, I don't want you to get you sick.
It could be fatal.
Then by all means,
stand next to me.
Let me feel you.
Ay, papi, but you're not warm.
Uh, probably because
you were cooking
And your hands are warm.
I'd better skip the party
tomorrow just to be safe.
Oh, yeah, the party.
What?
The party.
I understand about 20% of
what goes on around here.
The party is at an amusement park,
And manny is afraid
of roller coasters.
Poor kid.
I don't know where he
gets his fear from,
Because his father's not
afraid of anything --
No bulls, no heights,
no helicopters, no fast cars.
But go to dinner with him and
wait for the check to come.
Then you'll see fear in his eyes --
Like the waiter's a ghost.
Excited?
Yeah.
We're like ponce de
leun and his son.
Little ponce.
Who's that?
Famous treasure hunters.
His name was ponce?
He'd get made fun of at my school.
They'd probably call him "pants."
"pants."
Or maybe, um, "fancy ponce."
that's a good one.
All right.
Let's do this.
Animal chittering ] oh, hey, wow.
You okay, dad? Yeah.
Yeah, I am. Yep.
Gonna take a little more
than getting trapped
In a small, dark space
with a wild animal
To rattle your old man. All right.
You never want your
kids to see you scared.
You want to be that rock
That they can grab ahold
of in a stormy sea.
Actually, a rock would sink,
so a floating rock.
Let's start over.
It's windy, and you've
got a lot of papers.
Okay. Let's do this, buddy.
okay, good recon.
Got the lay of the land, so...
Aren't we going in? Yep.
We are, but won't it be fun
If we did it with ski
goggles and barbecue tools?
I guess. Yeah.
Yeah, let's do that.
All right.
Can I just say,
that is a lovely outfit?
Oh, thank you.
Well, it's just nice to see
you out of your lab coat.
You actually have
quite a nice figure.
Take it down a notch.
We're just trying to make a friend,
Not initiate a three-way.
Oh.
Lily looks great.
Do you think so?
Shouldn't she have more teeth?
I see these kids running
around at the park,
And they look like sharks.
Don't worry. She's perfect.
Aren't you, lily?
Oh, look how calm she is with you.
She's usually very fidgety
around new people.
Well, I just think she senses
You're gonna be a
good friend for her
During in good times
and - and flu season.
Mommy!
Did shjust -- did she just say...
Oh.
Well
Her first word was every gay
father's worst nightmare.
mommy. Oh.
But I know that manny's sad
because he's missing the party.
Why don't we take him somewhere
to take his mind off it, hmm?
I could have guessed he'd have
trouble with roller coasters.
That kid gets woozy at barbershops
When they spin his chair
towards the mirror.
How about we take him to the
pier and go fishing, huh?
Manny!
He likes to fish? Yeah.
He comes from a long line
of fishermen and smugglers.
But I encourage the fishing.
Manny, you like to fish?
Fishing? Yeah.
You want to go to the pietoday?
Is this a trick to see
if I'm really sick?
No, maybe the fresh air
will make you feel better.
Well, then, yeah,
'cause there's no place where
I'm more at one with --
Just get your coat.
Are you nervous? Shut up, alex.
I was just asking.
I'd be nervous if I were you.
Alex, leave your sister alone.
She's gonna be fine.
As long as I don't
get the same guy.
He's so mean! You probably will.
You won't. He hates me.
He doesn't hate you.
He yelled at me.
You drove into the bushes.
Oh, no, it's him.
Please don't be for me.
Hi.
Oh, thank god.
Well, come on.
I don't have all day.
I'm gonna throw up.
Okay, no. This is
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna get in that car,
put on your seat belt,
And take three deep
breaths and relax.
This guy sees hundreds
of kids every day.
He probably doesn't even
remember you, all right?
Okay. Okay.
Yo! Let'move it, two strikes.
That's more than
three breaths, honey.
See how much better this is?
The truck goes in, it gets video,
And then we get a preview
of whatever's in there.
How ingenious is that, huh
Are you too scared to go in?
Why would you say that?
Well, when you stuck your head in,
you screamed a little.
I told you, that was
the house settling.
Besides, this is so much cooler.
This is how nasa does it.
Now, hand me the
itty bitty booklight.
Yeah.
Final piece of the puzzle.
Blast off!
Hey, dad?
Yeah?
How are you supposed to steer
If you don't know
where you're going?
Stay in the present, buddy.
Got to do it by feel.
You got to get all jedi on it.
Uh-oh.
Did you just lose my truck? No.
You just lost my truck! No,
I didn't!
That w my truck!
Grandpa just gave it to me!
I told you to stay in the present!
Stop yelling!
Truce?
Yeah, sorry.
This is delicis. Oh, thank you.
The recipe's from the now-defunct
gourmet magazine.
Why do all the things
I love go away?
Look, I don't even think
she said the "m" word.
No, we heard it.
It was clear as day.
I-I just don't know
what we've done wrong.
I quit my job so I could
stay at home with her,
But maybe it's not enough.
maybe we're not providing her
With the feminine
energy that she needs.
Yeah, I wouldn't be too
concerned about that.
You -- you know it's because you're asian,
right? Mitchell: Cam!
No, I'm sorry.
What, am I just supposed to ignore
The giant panda in the room?
Pandas are from china.
I -- well, it doesn't matter.
Okay, okay, um,
I think what my hysterical
partner is just trying to say --
And if I may --
That for the first six
months of her life,
Lily was raised by
very loving asian women
In an orphanage, with whom
she clearly bonded, you know.
And then suddenly you come
in with all of your...
Asian-ness and -- and - and
breasts and womb, lady bits,
And it -- it all just comes
rushing back to -- to her,
And...
You guys are overreacting.
I'm sure lily just strung
A couple of random syllables togeer
And they happened to sound
something like that word,
But that's all.
Do -- do you really think that?
Of course! Yeah,
she -- she's right.
She's right.
We're being ridiculous.
Your daddies are being ridiculous.
Mommy!
Okay.
Mr. Tucker?
No, no, she's -
she's - she's made her choice.
She's made her choice.
Uh, left turn.
Here?
At the intersection, yeah.
Okay.
Left.
What?
I said, "left." you're going right.
Wait! No, wait! I'm trying, okay?!
Pull over.
No, I can do this!
Pull over now!
Why are you crying?
why do you hate me?
Oh, hell.
Haley, I don't hate you.
You seem like a nice girl.
You remind me of my daughter,
Which is why I want you to
live a long and happy life
And be safe.
And not hurt my daughter.
I really want my license.
I've been practicing a lot,
I swear.
You gonna drink and drive? No, sir.
You gonna text and drive? No, sir.
All right.
Let's start this
from the beginning.
Could you smile first?
I'll be less nervous if you smile.
Okay, that didn't help.
Just go.
Today feels like a
good day for halibut.
Hey, jay, did I ever tell you
About the time I used peanut
butter and jelly for bait
And I caught a thresher shark?
You tell me a lot of funny things.
Why are we going this way?
It's just another way to .
Uh-oh. Something's going on.
What are you talking about?
Wake up, old man.
She's trying to get me
on that roller coaster.
No, she's not.
Yes, I am. What?
Told y.
Manny, you have to face your fears.
That's why we're here?
But y didn't you let me
in on your little plan?
Because you're the worst liar.
He would have seen
right through you.
I don't want to go on
the roller coaster.
Manny, you were afraid
to light the barbecue,
But now your eyebrows
have grown back
And your salmon is legendary.
What if fall out?
I will catch you.
That's not possible.
He would crush you.
W-what if I throw up?
I will clean it up.
It wouldn't be the first time.
Ah, geez, these are new shoes.
You're not gonna let up, are you?
Baby, I think you know the answer.
fine, let's get it over with.
that's my boy!
Vamos, jay.
No, I'm not going on that.
That's bad for my back.
Your back is fine.
Yeah, I got an inner-ear thing.
Oh, please. Don't tell
me you're scared, too.
Scared? What - what
is this scared stuff?
What -- what am I,
a child? I'm not scared.
You see? You're the worst liar.
Well, if he's not going,
I'm not going.
Oh, for god's sake, fine.
I'll go alone.
Here, take my girly purse.
And you, my floppy hat.
And if you need it,
there's the ladies' room.
I'm not man enough to fight this.
Here, hold my purse.
Oh, hell!
You know, honey, I think I know
Why you don't want to go tonight.
Because school dances are lame?
No, 'cause you don't
know how to dance.
That's not it.
I can help you with that.
Come on. Oh, god. No!
Come on. No! Mom!
Oh, yeah, back in the day,
I was quite the dancer.
Oh, my god, you and dad together
suddenly makes so much sense.
Mom! Mom, stop! Stop!
Please, stop. I know how to dance.
I just don't want to be
part of that freak show.
Sweetheart, you're a beautiful gir
Someone ll ask you to dance.
I know that. It's just stupid.
Somebody will ask you.
Why do you keep saying that?
But what if they don't?
Honey, if they don't,
Then you do the exact same
thing I told your sister, okay?
Take three deep breaths and relax.
Even the advice I get
is a hand-me-down.
Mom, I did it!
I passed!
Aah! Oh, my god!
I got my license!
I got my license! I got my license!
Haley, car's not in park. Oh, oops.
You better run to that counter. Go.
Run! Run! Right now!
I still can't believe
you lost my truck.
It's gone, buddy. Let it go.
You know, maybe it's better
We don't solve this little mystery.
Sometimes treasure's more
sparkly in your imagination,
Where it could be
gold or baseball cards
Or pirate maps.
Do you really think there could
be pirate maps under there?
I'm 100% sure it's possible.
All right. I'm going in.
What?
Really? Buddy?
Whoa!
What do you see?
Nothing. It's really dark in here.
Wait a minute.
I think I see my truck.
It's right over there
by the -- uh-oh.
What?
I-I think I'm stuck.
How are you stuck?
My belt loop got caught
on a pipe, and it's hot!
Have you tried wiggling?
Dad! It's hot! Hurry!
I'm coming, buddy!
And hurry! There are
spiders in here!
Oh!
Coming!
And I'm sorry if we got
all weird in there.
Oh, it was fine.
Well, we'd like to say it's
different than how it usually is,
But you've seen us enough to
know that that's not true.
Guys, listen.
I had a very complicated
relationship with my mother.
She was born in japan
crazy-traditional.
She didn't want me
to become a doctor.
She wanted me to get
married and have kids.
But my father -- we would talk,
And he would actually
listen to what I wanted.
Anyway, what I'm trying to say is,
Having a mother isn't always
what it's cracked up to be.
And if you ask me,
Having two fathers who
care as much as you do
Makes lily the luckiest
little girl in the world.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you for that.
That's very sweet.
Thanks. Thank you.
And how are things with
you and your mom now?
ugh.
The only way she'll be happy is
if I'm some asian stereotype,
But that just isn't me.
I didn't see those!
I'm coming, buddy!
Over here.
That's a spider web. Oh, god.
My boy was in trouble,
So I put my fears aside,
and I came to his rescue.
Now, does that make me a hero?
Yes, it does.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Hey, everything's gonna be okay.
there!
Thanks, dad.
Hey, just what dads do.
Let's get out of here.
I want my truck.
Really?
It was a christmas gift!
Could you go get it?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Scoot. Scoot through.
There it is.
Got it.
You okay?
Yeah. Are you okay?
You know what? I am okay.
Hey! Hey.
we did it! Whoo-hoo!
We're under the house! yeah!
What the heck?
We're down here.
Why don't we see what we got,
huh? Yeah.
Two intrepid explorers...
Make their way on a journey --
Dead bodies!!
We called the police and got
a bunch of detectives over.
Turns out it was the last
owner's Halloween decorations,
Which is pretty funny.
At least, I thought it was.
Everybody's afraid
of something, right?
Heights, clowns, tight spaces.
You like it, jay?!
I did it! Whoo!
Those are things you get over,
But then there's our children.
Will they fit in?
Will they be safe?
Those are fears you never get past.
So, sometimes, all you can
do is take a deep breath,
Pull them close,
and hope for the best.
Bye! Eyes on the road!
Love you!E!
Whoo-hoo! Oh, god!
I mean, things don't
always work out.
Oh, cam, I think she wants her doll
I don't know where it is.
Mommy.
When you squeeze the doll,
it says, "mommy."
Did -- did you know that - no clue.
the doll says, "mommy."
The doll says, "mommy.
" the doll says, "mommy!"
But you got to love
it when they do.
Mom says there's an old
trunk in the attic.
Oh, yeah, my grandpa's
old steamer trunk.
In this movie I saw,
there was this old trunk,
And there was a secret compartment,
And when you opened it,
There was a whole
bunch of paintings
By the world's greatest painters
Hidden in the war.
My grandpa was in the war.
Should we go up there?
Totally. It could also be diamonds.
Or a samurai sword.
Or the declaration of independence.
You know, it almost doesn't
even matter what's up there.
What matters is what you do
With the money from
what's up there.
We could get a motorboat.
Or a robotic gutter cleaner.
Or an indoor pool.
Or a two-man submarine.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net