"that's too much cologne."
"that's how girls end up dead."
"don't talk black to me."
"it's inappropriate because
she's your teacher."
How do you even talk black?
Like, end words with "izzle"?
Alex: It's talk back, you idiot.
Oh.
"act more like an adult."
What does "act more like
an adult" even mean?
[ laughing ] look at you. You're soaked.
That is so lame!
You're the one who wanted to do it!
What are you two doing?
I picked up one of those water weasels.
You hook it on the end of the hose
And it flies around in the air.
Just...Like a weasel.
[ laughing ] yeah,
look at how awesome. He's so wet.
I put the weasel in my pants.
[ laughing ] he totally did!
Dork. Is there a reason
why my window is wet?
Hmm, very difficult to say.
Um, I don't know.
Up fi-- ow. Ow!
What's wrong?
Sweetie, are you okay? A little -
a little twinge.
Yeah.
I'll call 911.
Maybe the firemen will come.
No, no! No. No. No! Give me it!
The firemen in our town have
a reputation for being...Hot.
Do I resent that?
Of course not. These guys are my friends.
I play basketball with them.
I bake for them.
My question is -- what's hot?
Jay: Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
We're coming.
Manny, it's inappropriate
because she's your teacher.
What's the big deal, anyway?
It's a surprise, you'll see.
Oh, my god!
Gloria: Jay, you didn't!
Yes, I did. I got us into that new benihana.
Huh?
They got a chef there
That can flip a shrimp into his own hat.
What the hell?
Dad! There's my boy!
[ laughs ]
What the hell is he doing here? Jay.
No, he was supposed to
pick up manny yesterday
And disappointed him again, as usual.
Now he just sails in here out of the blue?
I don't like the guy.
Do I have reasons? Yeah.
Good reasons? Yeah.
How many reasons do I need? None.
I don't like the guy.
-- Sync by honeybunny --
www.addic7ed.com
So, I would have called,
But while I was buying
this boat for a friend,
I got chased out to sea by another boat.
Were they pirates?
I didn't stop to ask.
It's not hard to tell.
Did they have curvy swords
And sing songs about how
fun it is to be a pirate?
[ laughs ]
Wo jay, such a beautiful house, huh?
So, we were just headed out to dinner.
What, you think I show up empty-handed?
I brought dinner -- lobsters!
Did you catch them with your bare hands?
No, but I bought them
with my bare hands.
Wow!
And I have some nice wine,
a good cuban cigar for jay.
Hey, why don't you take a picture
of him with your new camera phone?
I don't have a camera phone.
Yodo now.
Awesome!
All this excitement, my heart is just going.
Now, listen to me, you bring that with you
When you come to visit me this summer.
We'll go in a racecar with my friend,
And after that, maybe a bullfight.
I know all these guys, the matadors --
They are like artists.
You're quite the bullfight artist yourself.
Uh...Manny,
Why don't you sh your father to the kitchen?
Por favor, dios mío.
Someone put onome music. Tonight, we dance.
Oh, we're gonna dance.
Oye, mi amor, ¿está bien que
me quedo aquí esta noche?
Ay, javier, yo no sé. Espérate
para ver qué puedo hacer.
What did he say?
Does he need money for the lobsters?
Jay, be nice. "be nice"?
I could be sitting grill-side
Watching a guy build an onion volcano.
Instead, I got rico suave in my kitchen,
And I got a stolen boat in my driveway.
If it was for me, he'll be out of my life.
But it's good for manny
to be with his father.
I just can't believe you
ever fell for that act.
Colombians can be veryersuasive.
They can make you agree to
things before you even know it.
You must have been pretty naive.
Yeah, but now I'm with the right man, okay?
Right.
Javier is only going to stay one night.
Good.
Wait. What?
[ television plays ]
[ lily hiccuping ]
Don't be mad. I just got up to change her.
Well, mitchell really wanted
to ferberize the baby.
Ferberize -- it is a method
Of getting the baby to
sleep through the night
By, yes, basically letting
her cry herself to sleep.
Torture.
It's not torture, cam.
It's just hard if you happen to be a person
Who hates to hear another person suffer.
[ crying ] [ lily crying ]
Or two people suffer.
[ sobbing ]
No, no, you got up to comfort her,
Which only teaches her
that every time she cries,
Her daddy will come in and cuddle
her and put on her favorite --
What are we watching?
Brian de palma's controversial
masterpiece "scarface."
For the baby?
She happens to like it.
I don't know if it's the
colors or the -- the sounds.
Oh, here comes the nightclub massacre.
She loves it. Watch her little eyelids.
It's so cute. They get so heavy.
Phil: Oh! That's bad!
Oh, honey.
I'm fine. No, I'm fine.
I'm just -- okay, that's cancer!
Maybe it's just a kidney stone.
"just," claire?
What's going on, guys?
It's nothing. Go back to bed.
No, but, dad -- don't touch me.
I bet it's just a kidney stone.
"just" again.
Someone get yo mom a glass of water
And a piece of gravel from the driveway
And she how she likes it.
Why is everybody yelling?
Something's wrong with dad.
Don't frighten him. Come here.
Oh! That's got to be death!
Death is coming!
Okay, you need to go to
the hospital, dad. Yeah.
No, no, no. I just need a pill.
Get me the biggest one you can find.
Honey, breathe. Just -- just breathe.
That's what I told you
when you were in labor
And you threw my smoothie at me.
Pill!
Okay, I'm calling.
No, no! It's fine.
It's actually -- it's fine. It's passing.
It's passing. I'm sorry to alarm everyone.
I think I was probably just overreacting
Because there's an alien inside of me!
Oh, close it down.
Oh, I'm definitely gonna call.
All systems down. All systems down.
Son of a bitch.
What's the matter?
He's playing on my pool table, that's what.
Probably got himself a nice drink, too.
Where are you going, jay?
Just to check things out, okay?
Come on. You hear that?
Now he's messing around
with my remote control.
You can't hear that from here.
Hey, there.
Hey, jay, listen, I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
No, no. I'm a light sleeper.
That's what happens when you get older.
, you're not old.
I didn't say I was old.
I never sleep much, anyway.
Life is just more
interesting after 2:00 a.M.
You know, the liquor tastes better,
The, uh -- the women are more beautiful.
What is it they say?
That the night belongs to
the poets and the madmen.
[ both chuckle ]
Which are you?
Perhaps both.
But I think maybe you, too, huh?
I see a picture over here
of you on a motorcycle.
You ride?
I used to.
"used to"?
"used to"?!
Jay, the saddest words in
any language, my friend.
Yeah.
Hey, help me out here.
Everybody sees you as this great guy.
You know, you live this life of adventure.
How come I don't buy a word of it?
All I see is a dad who doesn't show up.
Hey, manny knows me. I live in the now.
Well, I was living in the yesterday
When manny was crying outside that door
'cause you didn't show
up for the tenth time.
And when I don't come,
You think, what, I'm just off
chasing a good time, hmm?
You ever think it might be
hard for me, coming here?
Why? Because of gloria?
Because of you.
[ billiard balls clacking ]
[ lily crying ]
Mitchell: Cam.
[ crying intensifies ]
Okay, they're on their way.
Okay. Kids, gather around
Like you're hugging me,
but don't touch me, okay?
Now, look, I'm gonna be fine.
We know, dad. We don't know that.
It's a miracle I'm standing up.
But, look, in case
[straining] anything happens
[ exhales sharply ]
I want you to know that
if I'd have had time,
I would have fixed that step.
Thanks, dad. I love you.
[ sniffling ]
Don't cry, luke. I'm okay.
I broke the coffee table.
That's okay. What?
I broke the glass coffee table.
The one you swore you didn't break
And then we blamed esperanza and fired her
And she stole a turkey at
thanksgiving for her family
And got deported?
Yeah. Damn it!
I'm sorry! [ straining ] you will be sorry.
[ doorbell rings ] okay!
They're here. Really?
Okay.
[ exhales deeply ]
Did you hear that?
Hmm? Luke broke the --
Hey, you changed your clothes.
Well, I-I had to get dressed.
Into that sexy, clingy --
Oh, my god. It's the firemen.
No, sweetie. And lipstick!
I'm out here convulsing in agony
And you're looking for cute tops to wear?
I just threw on the first
thing I could find.
Well, we got a minute,
If you want to try on
[straining] some tighter jeans.
Oh, phil, sweetie. [ grunts ]
No, by all means, claire,
we want you looking your sexiest
When the hunky gay firemen get here!
How we doing?
We're great.
He meant me!
Oh, right. Ow!
[ crying ]
Mitchell: Cameron.
[ crying intensifies ]
Oh, listen, jay, you're a
tough guy to compete with.
I mean, look at all you have.
So manny has to suffer?
No, you're right.
Look, I'm going to try harder.
But, you know, maybe it's a good thing
That he has the two of us.
From you, he learns stability.
From me, he learns how to be spontaneous --
Grab life by the throat.
Well, we do a little throa
t-grabbing ourselves around here, you know?
We were on our way to
benihana when you showed up.
Hey, as long as my boy follows his passion.
The worst career decision I
ever made was playing baseball,
But I loved every minute of it.
You played baseball? [ scoffs ]
I lived baseball.
I only made it to triple-a,
But I played with all those guys --
Sosa, mcgwire.
You look like played some.
Well, I played in high school.
I was all right.
Never hit a curveball.
So that's a dream of yours, to hit a curve?
Used to be. "used to be."
Ugh, por favor.
I said that again, right? Please, come on.
You're right. I shouldn't say that.
[ laughs ] what are you guys doing?
Manny, did we wake you up? I'm sorry.
No, I was doing my science extra credit.
Of course you were.
So, can I play?
That's up to your dad.
Actually, I think we're done
with pool for right now.
I have a better idea for the three of us.
Vamos.
So, how do you know this guy?
He owes me a little favor.
This is the coolest night ever!
Now, let's see about that curveball.
[ whimpering ]
Out!
I thought you were -
those were pillows.
Come on.
Cameron, do you realize
how infuriating this is?
The whole point of ferberizing
Is to teach her to put herself to sleep
And you keep ruining it.
I can't help it. I'm like a mother bear.
When I hear my cub crying,
I have to run to her.
Except you're not a bear.
Get in our room.
Get. Cam, get in there.
Get in there. Cut it out.
All the way. Our room.
Get. Get in there.
Come on. Come on. Get in there. Get!
[ siren wails ]
That's so unfair. Why not?
Because that's how girls end up dead.
Hey, honey.
Hey, guys. We just wanted
to see how you were doing.
Is this a bad time?
No, we're just giving him something
to relax before the procedure.
Which is gonna go just fine.
Oh, we know. We don't know.
In case it doesn't,
Promise me you'll be nice
to your new fireman daddy.
Unbelievable.
My wife got dressed up for
the firemen last night.
I didn't get dressed up for the firemen.
Those heels were really high.
You put on heels?
Let's drop it.
What are they doing to you, dad?
I have a little, scratchy rock inside of me,
And they're sliding in a
tube and sucking it out.
You're not scared, are you?
When was the last time you
saw your old man scared?
When you walked through the spider web.
When we were playing with the ouija board
And the wind blew the door shut.
There was no wind, buddy.
Werought something forth.
This stuff's really hitting me.
My insides feel like velvet.
Why don't you guys wait
out in the hallway, okay?
Feel better, dad. I will.
Love you, dad.
Love you. Love you.
Luke, buddy, hold back a sec.
It's not gonna happen, okay,
But there is a scenario where you
could be the man of the house
And you need to know all the
pin numbers and passwords.
741 --
I don't want to be the man of the house.
Now, don't talk black to me.
Honey, your dad's gonna be fine.
Why don't you wait out in the hall?
I'll be right out, okay?
Honey, I'm just gonna run them to school.
I'll be back right after. Okay.
Claire? Yeah?
You did get dressed up, didn't you?
I pulled on the first thing I saw.
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
I'll drop it.
'cause this stuff is
making me fall asleep...
Mm-hmm....And if I never wake up,
I'd hate for the last
thing you ever said to me
To be a lie.
[ exhales slowly ]
I might have gotten dressed
up just a tiny bit.
[ exhales slowly ]
I knew it.
Oh, damn it.
Why are you so tired today?
Any reason I can't take him?
I'm surprised you're up.
I know what time you went back to bed.
Oh, it was nothing.
We just went out, we hit a few balls,
And you'll never guess where --
I guess javier knew a guy -
and you know what?
Now that he knows you,
the next time he needs something,
You are the guy.
Iay! Idios mío! Did you take him with
you?
You couldn't wait to get
to school to do that?
Manny, vámonos para el colegio. Let's
go.
We're gonna be so late. Ivámonos!
Vamos a llegar tardísimo, manny.
¿qué te pasa? Get in the car.
I thought you said you wanted
me to bond with javier.
I said be nice, jay.
I didn't say take manny out
all night and play games.
Then we got hogs.
Go to sleep!
If I wanted to be married to a wild man,
I would have stayed with javier.
[ horn honking ]
Javier: Aha! ¿qué pasa?
Dad! Por dios, no.
Jay: What the hell?
[ laughs ]
Hey, hey, hey. Wait a minute.
You're not leaving, are you?
I've got school.
What? School. Yes, school.
That's where people go to learn things,
Like not to keep children up all night!
He told her?
He's weak.
Well, listen, you said you used to
like riding motorcycles, right?
So I brought you one.
I know, but I kind of got work.
[ scoffs ] work. Go, jay.
Yeah, go, jay. Gloria: Yes, go, jay,
And take manny with you, too!
Okay.
No, manuel alberto, in the car,
Or I put you in the trunk!
Jay, I'm not gonna argue anymore.
I'm not gonna say anything else.
Do whatever you want.
But I don't want to hear you any more
Saying that colombians are crazy,
Because you're the one that is acting crazy,
Even though he's the one
that is making you act crazy,
So I don't know what the
hell I'm talking about!
Manny!
[ lily crying ]
You didn't need to come home during naptime.
Mm, I think we proved last night that I did.
Well, she's back there now,
So why don't you go so
you don't get in trouble?
That's okay.
I told everyone that I
have an unreliable partner
And they understood.
Okay, you know what?
I don't need to sit here
and be condescended to.
I'm gonna make myself an ice tea.
I will bring you down.
You can't bring me down.
I'll sweep your legs.
[ crying continues ]
There's something wrong with
you that the sound of our child
In such distress doesn't bother you more.
She is not in distress,
And thisust proves that you
need this more than she does.
I'm ferberizing two babies.
Raccoons slipped into the lawsons' home
And stole a loaf of bread.
Your point?
That we left lily's window open a crack
And those raccoons need something
to put between that bread...
[ crying intensifies ]...And that is lily's
"help me" cry.
I'm coming for you, lily.
You will not. You're not com-- cameron.
Let me go. Hey, stop!
Let -- let --
Let go! Get off me!
What are you doing? Stop it! Slow down!
I will not slow down. Ow!
Stop being such a baby!
I'm coming for you! Ow!
Ow, ow.
What?
Oh, my ankle.
Oh, what? My ankle.
[ crying ]
[ door opens ]
Oh, I guess you didn't
Kill yourself in the motorcycle today.
Well, I figured you were
looking forward to killing me,
So I'm not gonna take that away from you.
Hey, did javier call you?
No, why?
He's dragging me to this bar
With some of his old baseball pals.
He was supposed to be here at 5:00.
Ah, he's dragging you, huh?
Yeah, I figured it would be okay.
I mean, I've seen half these guys play,
And javier says it's cool.
What? What's the joke?
Nothing.
It's just funny to me
that you make fun of me
Beuse I was seduced by him,
and here you are --
No one is getting seduced.
I'm doing this for manny.
Oh, yeah, it's very important for manny
That you two go and have a
nice picnic in the mountains.
First of all, it wasn't a picnic.
We stopped for coffee.
They just happened to be selling crepes.
Just let me know when he calls, all right?
Geez, it's almost 6:00.
[ muffled laugh ]
Claire: The kids are so
excited for you to come home.
Oh, me too.
Yeah, luke made you a sign.
Oh, he's a sweetie.
Yeah.
You seem great.
I am great.
Good.
Except for that firemen thing.
You remember it. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay. Look, I am sorry.
I'm so sorry. Ah, no.
Sorry. There's no excuse for it.
I-I think I just spend so much
time in dowdy mom clothes,
And I'm covered in paste and peanut butter,
And I just --
I wanted to feel attractive
for a second, you know?
I'm sorry. I really --
Honey, I just
-- just need a little bit of time.
Gonna be fine.
Okay. Yeah.
Okay.
I was already fine with it.
Here's the deal -- claire messed up.
She owed me. This never happens.
Old phil has a golden ticket.
Now, I could have cashed that in
right away for something small --
Get out of cleaning the garage,
a week at circus camp.
Oh, still fresh. Yeah.
But the longer you hold onto it,
The more the guilt builds, the more you get.
Five years -- trip to paris with my buddies.
10 years -- sweet, little convertible.
20 years --
Hello, fully articulating,
five-function robot
That can read my mind
And has feelings.
Phil, you're not leaving
Without saying goodbye, are you?
Hey, elaine.
Is this your husband? Uh-huh.
Goodbye, paris.
I'm visiting my sister,
And he was entertaining us all
afternoon with his card tricks.
Oh.
Is that phil? Hey.
[ laughs nervously ]
Hey, mom, phil's leaving.
Without a hug?
Wow.
Goodbye, fully articulating,
five-function robot
With the ability to -- goodbye.
Brittany, hurry, honey. Phil's leaving.
Ow.
You're fine.
How's your ankle?
It's cold.
I'm sorry I hurt you.
No, no, don't be.
I'm --
I could have just as easily hurt you.
Well, it's cute that you think that.
Listen, cam, I-I can't
always be the bad cop here.
I know it's my issue,
But she can't grow up with one huggy,
happy, cuddly dad
And one frowny, lesson-teachy dad.
Because guess which one
She's gonna ask to walk her down the aisle.
[ sighs ]
O-- y--
Okay, you know what?
I can be the bad cop sometimes.
I'll always make her eat her vegetables.
Okay. Dentist.
Deal. Good.
As long as you make her practice her violin.
Oh, yeah, the violin. I like that.
And we're both walking her down the aisle.
[ winces ]
Assuming you can walk by then.
Ow! Do you need to go to
the hospital for that?
No, god, no. No, it's not that bad.
You meant call 911, didn't you?
Firemen.
Yeah, you call and I'm
gonna go change my shirt.
So, if I'm supposed to act like an adult,
Is that act like adults
I see in the world...
Water weasel!
...Or the adults in my family?
'cause if it's the ones in my family...
Come on. Let's go.
All right.
Then...
How hard could that be?
Aah!
Really got me fired up about my magic again.
[ blows ]
Is...This your card?
Yes. Oh, my gosh!
It's -- it's not, is it?
No, uh -- no, it's -- 's not.
The hardest part is when
people forget their card
Because then I look like the idiot.
All right, let's do it again.
We really have to go. You think I like this?
I'm sorry. Here. I'm gonna
teach you one, okay? Oh, my --
On the count of three, just grab this.
You ready? Put your hand out. Okay.
1, 2, 3.
There it is.
No. What was that? Wow.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net