Y up from cocoa beach.
Hey, son.
Working hard?
He's gonna say, "hardly working."
I meant to tell you
he was driving out.
Did he say it?
Oh, yeah!
good kid!
He wasn't supposed to show up
for a few more days.
Well, guess what he brought us.
A dog...To keep.
Yes!
Yes.
Yes, I should have told Claire
about the dog.
And I was going to.
But I-I was just waiting for her
to be in the right mood.
Actually, I did get one "right
mood" a couple nights ago,
But...I cashed that in
for something else.
Am I in trouble?
Oh, really, really big.
Okay, I'm a little scared.
How bad is this?
Oh, well...
We have a new rule --
No sleeping in the bedroom.
Mr. Pritchett?
Ben.
Ben Dugan.
I went to High School
with Mitch.
We were in the drama club
together.
That's right.
Yeah.
Geez, I didn't recognize you
without that old-guy makeup on.
You know, you and Mitch knocked "the
sunshine boys" out of the park.
Mitch was really great in that.
I always thought
he should be an actor.
Eh, he's got a real job now.
He's a lawyer.
Ah.
How about you?
Still acting.
Fantastic.
Actually, it's exciting.
I'm in a new movie --
"maple drive" -- just came out.
You're kidding me.
Look at me --
I know somebody famous.
Uh, anyway, I got to go.
Great to see you.
Good to see you, too.
Yeah.
Kid's a movie star.
Hey, how'd it go in there?
No cavities,
and I got a free toothbrush.
Hey,
you want to go to the movies?
I just heard about a good one.
But I'm supposed to be
in school.
You're supposed to floss, too,
But you got away with that one.
Come on. Let's go.
One of the greatest days
of my life
Was when my old man
sprung me from school
And took me to the track.
I wanted to do the same
type of thing for Manny.
Plus, I figured when Gloria
heard about it,
Maybe it pays off
in the bedroom.
I wonder if that's why
my old man did it.
Oh, crap.
Your mother-in-law
just had to have the dog.
Turns out she's allergic.
And the pet store
didn't have a grace period
Or a return policy or anything?
I got him from the pound.
Was there a twister in Kansas?
'cause there's a house
in my driveway.
welcome home, Mr. Dunphy.
always a pleasure, Mr. Dunphy.
Indeed it is,
Mr. Dunphy.
Place it there.
Ah, I shall, I shall.
I miss this.
Get in here!
my dad is awesome.
He's awesome.
He's always up.
He's always happy.
I mean, he and I are best buds.
We're like two peas in a pod
Or Siamese twins
or a snake with two heads.
They've actually been all those
things for Halloween.
Yeah.
Hey, this must be scout, huh?
I should warn you --
he sheds.
I made the mistake of letting
him sleep with me on the road.
Now my sheets look like
two bigfoots did it.
pardon the language.
How's mom?
Speaking of big feet, eh?
She is on a cruise
with her girlfriends,
Some of which
are not totally unattractive.
Mm. Uh, that reminds me -- she
sent some gifts for the kids.
Um, I will be right back.
You three get better acquainted.
Will do.
Fun.
I cannot believe you got a dog
without consulting me.
This was
a major family decision.
It was wrong.
Yeah.
And I'm sorry.
Mm.
But we have talked about
getting a dog for years,
And you're the only one
who wasn't into it.
Because I knew that I would be
the one taking care of it.
That's not true.
Oh.
No, we will all help.
Mm-hmm.
This is a great chance to teach
the kids responsibility.
That is exactly what you said
about Luke's paper route.
Sync by kuniva for addic7ed.com
Hello?
Is anyone in there?
Red's a good color on you.
Aah!
It's just a movie.
Oh, he's so cute!
Look at his little face.
I always wanted a dog.
Thanks, grandpa.
Okay, but remember, having a dog
is a major responsibility.
Everyone in the family
has to pitch in.
Can do, Mrs. D.
Not you, Dylan.
Oh, phew. 'cause I got
a lot on my plate right now.
Hey, look who's here.
Uncle Cam.
Hey, we heard about
the new addition,
And we had to come right over!
Cameron,
so good to see you again.
Now, that is a shirt.
Oh, well, thank you, Frank.
I get them online.
I'll send you a link.
Oh, well, at home,
I smoke sausages.
I'll send you a link.
classic.
And this must be Lily.
Oh, yes. She just couldn't wait
to meet the new doggy.
I think she's good right here.
Let me get in there
and get some of that dogginess.
Oh, there it is.
Haley, I got to go.
What's wrong?
That was Brian.
He just quit the band.
What? Why?
He's moving to Portland.
His parents got back together.
Oh, that sucks.
I know.
Now we're gonna have to cancel
the gig tomorrow.
Maybe you can find
another drummer.
No, I think it's too late
for that now.
I play drums.
Huh?
Well, I mean,
I haven't played in a while
Since Lily's come along,
But if you're in a jam...
I can jam.
Well, you know,
I totally would,
But I'm not sure we like the
same sorts of music, you know?
Oh, what, because I'm gay I'm just
gonna want to play show tunes?
, because you're old.
Wow, that hurt more, Dylan.
Give him a chance.
It's better than canceling.
You're right.
Don't want to lose
the deposit on that fog machine.
Okay, let's do it.
I used to be a music teacher,
But I gave that up
as soon as Lily came along.
Yes, well, we just felt
that it was really important
That one of us stayed home
to raise her, so...
Yeah, and that's not a judgment
on other people's choices.
It's just that we happen to be
a very traditional family.
Yes, that's what
the disabled lesbian shaman
Who blessed Lily's room
said, too.
How you doing, buddy?
All right, relax.
Oh, geez.
That is impossible.
My dad is the happiest guy
on earth.
It probably just sounded like
he was crying.
Have you heard the noises he makes
when he gets out of a chair?
No, I know what I heard.
I think this has something
to do with your mom. What?
Yeah, he came here alone.
Think about it.
She's on a cruise.
Yeah, and they never take
separate vacations, so...
No.
No, if something was wrong,
My dad would tell me about it.
No, Phil, he wouldn't,
Because you guys never actually
talk about anything.
We talk all the time.
He crank-calls me at work
like three times a week.
Crank calls don't count.
It counts for fun.
No, honestly, I think
that you should find out
What's going on with your dad.
It's going to be nothing.
My dad isn't like your dad.
There's nothing deep and dark
inside.
His hard candy Shell
is just...Hiding more candy.
I think he wants to go out.
Go boy.
Smart dog.
I hate to break it to you, but
I think all dogs can do that.
I'm gonna play outside.
Ow!
What happened?
Okay, should I just play
a little something?
Yeah, but, you know,
if it doesn't work out,
Don't feel bad.
Well,
hopefully this is --
This is like riding a bicycle
And will all come back to me.
that's the loud one.
So...Here we go.
Hm
Oh, silly me.
I had the sticks
in the wrong hands.
Wow.
Dude, you should label
those sticks.
Is that the alarm?
Has our perimeter
been breached?
It's not the alarm.
The doorbell won't stop ringing.
Maybe a demon is ringing it.
Not a demon.
Ay!
Who keeps ringing the doorbell?
We're pretty sure it's a demon.
Oh, yeah?
there.
If it were a demon,
it would keep on ringing.
Not if he's already inside.
I'm getting a weapon.
What were you thinking?
Who takes a little boy
to a horror movie?
That's loco, Jay.
Th is no big deal.
You want scary?
When I was his age,
I lived through
the Cuban missile crisis.
I slept th a butter knife
under my pillow
In case I had to fight
some soviet colonel.
Why would they send a soviet
colonel to get a little boy?
Because I could identify
every commie plane.
What are we talking about?
Look, all I'm saying, being
scared is part of growing up.
Manny will get over this.
It builds character.
I'll take the first watch.
You two might as well
get some rest.
It's gonna be a long night.
Character.
Dad?
Come on in.
It's open.
Hey.
Don't tell me --
you need a cup of sugar.
nah, just, uh...
I was just wondering,
I don't know, uh...
Anything on the old noodle?
Other than a bad toupee?
I'm kidding, of course.
This is my real hair.
Well, okay.
Wait a mute.
I want task you something.
Am I'm putting you
in a bad position
With this whole dog thing?
Claire seemed
a little...Put out.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Claire didn't like me at first,
either.
I can't blame her.
Dismissed.
Oh, dad, um, you know what?
I, uh...
Claire saw something,
And she'd kill me if I --
if I didn't ask.
What is it?
Would you wear pants to
breakfast, for crying out loud?
You got me again.
Right in the funny bone.
All right.
Come on, scout.
Let go of it.
No, no, no!
Ugh!
Dog.
Look at this!
How did he get ahold
of your bra?
Well,
uh, we were out on a date,
And he has
a really nice car, so --
How do you think?
He got it
out of the laundry basket.
I can't take my eyes
off that dog for a second.
Why don't you just keep him
in the crate?
I tried that.
He figured out how to get out.
I thought you were dealing
with your dad.
Oh, yeah. I did.
He's fine, so...
Whoa, you got that from
a two-minute conversation?
I asked him point-blank
if he was okay.
He said he was,
so I just --
Just swapped some jokes
and moved on.
Phil, the man needs
more of a push than that.
Look, if he wants to talk to me
about it, he will.
Geez, someone's panties
are in a bunch.
I thought I was showing
concern and --
No, right there.
Oh, my God.
That damn dog.
Guys, a little help.
I have to go to the bathroom,
And I'm not gonna do it
in here.
Hey, I got Chinese.
Sweet.
I'm starving.
Oh, we have guests.
Yeah, hey. We were just having
a little jam session.
You know Dylan.
This is Craig. This is Neal.
I'll always remember him
as the stranger holding my baby.
Can I talk to you
in the kitchen for a second?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, hey, guys,
let's -- let's just take five.
What's up
with "21 jump street"?
Oh. Oh, well,
their drummer quit,
And I'm gonna fill in for
him tomorrow night. No, no.
We have pepper's après-ski fondue
party tomorrow night, Cam.
Oh, no.
So you'll just have to
tell your band
That they're gonna have to find
someone else.
You know what? No, I'm not gonna
let these fellas down.
I made a commitment.
You made two commitments, okay?
And you know how pepper is.
Everything has to be perfect.
He gets mad if you don't wear
a big sweater.
Yeah, I remember. I got so hot last year,
I almost went facedown in the Gruyère.
So I'm going by myself.
Is that what you're saying?
I just feel like
I kind of need this.
To round out
your college applications?
It's just that because
I'm always home with Lily,
I just feel like I'm going
a little bit stir crazy.
Look at the den.
Every time I finish painting it,
I start all over again.
It's like
the Golden Gate Bridge.
I'm gonna go back to jamming.
Aah!
Yeah, we got to fix this.
Hey, what's with the big sweater
at a concert?
Is that a gay thing?
No, dad, it's for my friend
pepper's après-ski fondue --
Yeah, yeah, it's a gay thing.
I hope they start soon.
I don't think scout
likes to be left alone.
You love the dog.
No, I don't love the dog.
I love my couch,
And the dog was looking at it
like it was a giant sausage.
Good news, you two. You're
getting your driveway back.
I'm hitting the open road
in the morning.
Oh, already?
Yeah.
Anxious to get home and see mom,
huh?
No, I'm just gonna drive
wherever the wind blows me,
Which is usually
into the next lane.
Can we get some sodas, grandpa?
Okay, but just one.
I'm driving.
Come on.
He's not going home?
He's never been away
from my mom
For longer
than a doctor's appointment.
Honey, I know.
I told you.
I always felt bad
For people with
emotionally distant fathers.
It turns out I'm one of them.
It's a miracle
I didn't end up a stripper.
Hey, thanks, everybody,
for coming out.
These are some songs we wrote.
1, 2!
1, 2, 3!
♪ baby, don't leave me ♪
♪ I just, I want you to know ♪
♪ I want you to know ♪
♪ there's something inside me
that I cannot control ♪
♪ I cannot control ♪
Our boyfriends totally rock!
I know, right?!
Well, the plan was to watch him
for 10 minutes
And then run out
to pepper's party.
♪ ...My veins ♪
♪ my blood runs... ♪
But he was so great up there,
how -- how could I leave?
♪ but don't be afraid ♪
♪ I'll be your vampire ♪
It was his moment.
Come on!
Wow!
I know!
And his moment went on
for a really...
Really long time.
Turns out, I could have
run to the party
And made it back for the end...
Of his moment.
Manny, go brush your teeth
and get ready for bed, okay?
Your bed.
Can I watch TV?
Only 10 minutes.
Okay.
Hey, Jay, it's Ben Dugan.
I got your message.
Uh, yes, I'm happy to help out.
I'll swing by tonight.
What's that?
That's Ben.
That's the guy
who was in the movie.
I figured when Manny sees him,
sees how nice he is,
He'll realize it's all pretend.
You think that will work?
That guy's a sweetheart.
Manny's gonna spend
two minutes with him.
He'll explain
how the movie's made.
He's even bringing
his fake machete.
Thing's made of rubber.
Hey, are you Manny?
I'm here for you!
Look what I got.
Aah!
Mom, he's here!
Que pasó?! Que pasó?!
Que pasó?!
Ay!
We're gonna need a bigger bed.
Oh, geez.
Oh, my God.
I think that's him.
hey!
You stayed.
Yeah. Well, you know,
I'm -- I'm with the band.
I thought the gig
was a little sloppy in spots,
But I think once I learn
all the songs...
I thought -- I thought this
was a one-time thing.
Are you kidding?
We destroyed in there.
Did you hear that one lady
screaming my name?
That was Phil.
He had a red bull.
Hey, guys, good gig, huh?
Yeah, totally awesome.
Heck of a gig.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
I thought you were in Portland.
No,
my parents broke up again.
I'm not moving.
I can stay in the band.
Well, this --
this is awkward.
Uh...
Cam.
Oh, a-awkward for me.
Good luck following that,
Ringo.
I believe this belongs to you.
I don't want to drag the house
along with me.
Come here, you little monkeys.
Bye, grandpa, we'll miss you.
I wish I could take you
with me.
Yeah, drive safe, grandpa.
I'll try.
You sure you don't want to stay
for breakfast?
No, I ought to be
hitting the road.
Whelp...Adiós.
Dad, hold on.
Hmm?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Guys.
I don't think
you're being honest with me.
I-I know something
is going on with you.
What's up?
Something up?
Well, my boxers are, uh,
riding a little high.
I'm not in the mood for jokes
right now,
Although you nailed that.
Thanks. Thanks.
Great stuff.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
Oh, it's nothing?
Nothing to do with mom?
No!
Well...Yeah.
I've fallen in love.
Oh, my God!
Who is she?
He.
What?
It's that little guy
right over there.
Come on over here.
Come on.
There you go.
Oh, look at him.
Driving across country,
This little bastard nuzzled
his way right into my heart.
Didn't you?
So, this is just about you
not wanting to leave the dog?
Well, you should tell mom.
Those three days
on the road with him
Were the happiest of my life.
You should leave that part out.
I don't want to keep scout
if it makes grandpa sad.
Yeah, I know, sweetie,
but grandma has allergies,
So scout has to stay with us.
Well, she could always just get
some allergy shots.
Honey, you don't want
to put her through that.
Well, hell, back in the day,
I got a vasectomy for her.
Dad, dad, please.
Scout's --
scout's your dog.
He should go with you.
Okay, you twisted my arm.
Thanks, son.
Thanks for poking through
the armor.
You're poking through the armor
down there.
What?
Made you look.
You are a treasure.
Come on, scout.
Let's mosey.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait.
He loves that.
Oh, I bet he does.
No, scout.
This time, I drive.
You still got it!
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
But I think
I might have actually
Gotten even closer with my dad.
I can't believe he took my dog.
Bye, pop! Bye, grandpa!
Love you!
Bye, dad.
Bye, grandpa! I love you!
Luke, stay!
Come back soon!
I'll see you later!
Luke, stay!
Luke!
Stay!
Sync by kuniva for addic7ed.com
Frank.
Hey, Jay!
Good to see you.
Great to see you.
Didn't expect to find you here.
Well, listen, when my
granddaughter's boyfriend's band
Plays an under-21 club
With my daughter-in-law's
brother's gay partner,
I show up.
That's just how I was raised.
I don't think you met my wife,
Gloria.
Hola.
Well, it's a pleasure.
You are a lovely woman.
You must be Frank.
Okay, then.
You are hotter than a Las Vegas
sidewalk on the 4th of July.
did I go too far?
Not you, Frank.
No.
www.tvsubtitles.net