Bravo!
Bravo, manny,
bravo!
Well, when I heard
manny wanted to fence,
I was like, "sure.
"uncoordinated kid,
lethal weapon --
How can this go wrong?"
[ whistle blows, buzzer ]
[ laughs ]
Yeah!
Gloria: And what
do you think now?
I'm proud
of our little zorro.
I mean,
I worked with him a little,
But the kid's got skills.
It's in his blood.
His father
was a master swordsman.
He was an artist
with his sword.
I mean, the way
he throws the sword --
I mean,
he was legendary.
You know, this nice moment
I'm having with your son --
You're...
Kind of wrecking it.
Sorry.
[ buzzer ]
Did you know that fencing
goes back to the 12th century?
You know what's even nerdier
than fencing?
Knowing when it began.
I don't think
you're a nerd, alex.
Shut up, dork.
All right!
That's my boy!
Whoo!
Would this be easier if
we suspended you from a crane?
Cameron: Any monkey
can shoot a home movie.
I pride myself
on shooting home films.
Yeah, but, cameron,
you always just take
things a little too far.
No, I don't.
Okay, your nephew's
first birthday.
That's not fair.
You brought
a wind machine.
To be fair,
my vision was --
cameron,
you brought a wind machine.
Who puts wheels
on cribs?
[ buzzer ]
Mi tigre!
Yes!
Ay, sorry. Sorry.
[ laughs ]
That's okay.
No! No, no, no, no, no!
Phone died!
No biggie.
Your battery probably
just statically defracticated.
What?
It means you can recharge it
with static electricity.
Just rub it
on your hair.
Jay: Yes!
You know, I used to go
to the houses of my friends,
And it used to bug me,
their kids'you know?,
[ chuckles uncomfortably ]
Because there was never
a trophy in my house.
Not until this one.
[ laughs ]
[ chuckles
uncomfortably ]
Can we
switch seats?
Cam,
people are staring.
I know you're not
supposed to care,
But it's kind of cool
to have a kid in your house
Who's the best at something,
you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah,
our kids are great.
They're the greatest.
Gosh, we're blessed.
We are.
But, um...
Are they the best
at something?
I'd have to think
about that.
Well, alex is great
at every single thing she tries,
So, you know,
she'll find her specialty.
She will.
And --
and haley is...
Haley is so pretty.
Gorgeous.
Oh, gosh.
Gorgeous girl.
I mean...
So, she can meet someone
who's the best at something.
That's right.
And then,
I guess that leaves luke.
We dropped the ball
a little bit on that one.
Yeah, a little bit.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
[ metal clashing, buzzer ]
Bravo!
Yeah!
How about a nice round
of applause for our winner,
Manny delgado?
[ cheers and applause ]
bravo, bravo!
Manny now moves on
to thehampionship,
Where he'll be competing
against caroline markum.
[ applause ]
We'll see you all back here
at 4:30.
All right!
Bravo!
[ speaking
spanish rapidly ]
What she said.
[ laughs ]
Wow. This means more to dad
than it does to manny.
Yeah, it's his chance to be,
you know, father of a chamon.
Well, second chance.
But we all know
how the first time went.
Did I say
something wrong?
No. No.
I'm -- I'm very happy for manny,
that's all.
Everything's not always
about claire. Geez.
I want to thank you
guys for coming by
and supporting the kid.
You guys are the best.
[ laughs uncomfortably ]
Why, claire?!
Come on, sweetie.
Really?
Well,
that took a while.
Well, she's been asleep
for 20 minutes.
It just took me some time to
sneak out without waking her up.
Kind of like the first time
you slept over here.
I had a meeting.
All right, let's talk
about why you got your
panties in a bunch.
What's up
with you and your sister?
Nothing is up.
Mm-hmm.
Or could this have
something to do with...
Ice skating?
Cameron: When mitchell
and claire were kids...
This is interesting
to no one.
Excuse -- please let me finish.
Thank you.
When mitchell was 10...
11.
...And claire was 13, they were
competitive ice dancers.
Figure skaters.
Oh, for god's sakes,
I'll tell the story.
Yes, my sister and I
were actually a very good team.
We were called
"fire and nice."
I was "fire,"
'cause of the red hair.
And claire was "nice,"
Because it was ironic
and she wasn't.
And mitchell
is still upset
Because claire quit the team
right before some meet.
"some meet"?
The 13-and-under
regional championships.
Just the emerald city at
the end of my yellow brick road.
Wow. You did it.
What?
You made figure skating
sound even gayer.
So, seeing your dad
so proud of manny
Didn't stir up
any resentment?
Mnh-mnh.
Okay.
Okay, fine,
you always do this.
Instead of letting your feelings
out, you bury them,
And then they bubble up later
in hurtful ways.
Okay, you know what,
you -- [ sighs ]
Yes, all right.
Listen, I might still be holding
a little resentment,
But that's...
Embarrassing and petty,
And it's not a good color
on me.
It's kind of like
you and yellow.
You love me
in my yellow shirt.
It makes you
look like the sun.
Okay. Bubbling.
Hurtful bubbling.
Now you know why
I left early that morning.
Ha! I knew you didn't
have a meeting, cam!
I knew it!
There must be something wrong
with this phone.
I've rubbed it on my head
for, like, an hour.
What?
Alex.
[ chuckles ]
Oh,
you're such a geek!
At least I didn't
give myself a bald spot.
Oh, my god! Mom!
Alex, don't be mean.
Haley, stop making yourself
such an easy target.
This feels right, buddy.
I'm telling you,
this feels right.
What are you guys doing?
Pursuing excellence.
We made a list of areas
the baseball. Excel at, and...
Love it.
Yeah.
I read it only takes 10,000
hours to achieve excellence.
You've already got, like, what,
how many hours playing ball?
Well, I played,
like, one season.
So, like,
6,000 hours?
Yeah, I can see
why you ruled out math.
Claire: Yeah, of course
I want luke to be successful.
But I don't think that a parent
can just force that.
I think you just
have to have faith
That the kid's
gonna find his own way.
[ sighs ]
Besides, luke already is
the best at something --
Being my son.
[ chuckles ]
It sounded a lot less lame
in my head.
I have got a good feeling
about this.
This is gonna be
your sport.
Last year, you said
basketball was my sport.
Look, I've said a lot of things
I wish I could take back,
But I can't.
What I can do is be
the dad you need me to be
To help you
become masterful.
You want
to be masterful?
I guess.
There's my killer!
Okay.
Our journey
of 10,000 hours
Begins
with a single pitch.
I believe in my boy!
I ain't
gonna quit you.
Let's burn one in here.
That's good.
That's a good start.
Okay, you...
Rest that cannon
while I run this down, okay?
Okay.
Let's keep all the batters
right here.
Oh! Should have --
should have worn my cup.
Should have
wo my cup.
Home run!
This one's
really in here, buddy.
[ breathing heavily ]
Okay.
Very, very, very, very good
first hour.
Toss me your glove.
I'll put some oil...On it.
[ breathing heavily ]
Yeah.
[ speaking spanish rapidly
and forcefully ]
Everything okay?
Yes, I was telling
my grandmother
How great was manny
today.
So, that wasn't
angry talk?
No, silly,
that was happy talk.
Ah, I'm beginning
to understand
Why there's so much conflict
on your continent.
Here, check this out.
Aw, jay.
[ chuckles ]
Jay loves to make t-shirts
for special occasions.
Come on, baby,
show them.
A few years back,
my granddaughter haley ran a 5k,
So I had a few of these
made up.
It's just fun.
[ laughs ]
I love it when
you're so proud of manny.
You know,
I'm not gonna lie.
Seeing him out there
slicing those kids to pieces,
You know,
it -- it gets to you.
Oye, gracias, mi amor.
Manny:
I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's okay, papi.
Hey, champ. I got
a little something for you.
And I have something
for you.
Here.
I will not be needing it
anymore.
But the finals.
I am retired.
Jay:
You can't retire.
It's just not fun
anymore.
Well, it's probably
just butterflies.
Come on,
you're gonna be fine.
Look, if he doesn't want to,
it's his decision.
Oh, the hell it is.
He shouldn't be doing anything
that makes him nervous.
Papi, I support you.
I'm not nervous.
I just don't want
to fight a girl.
What?
Defeating a woman
would be a mark on my honor.
Why? Because men are always
so superior to a woman?
Uh...
Uh, uh!
So superior that you cannot
even finish your sentence?
Dude.
Manny, you always call yourself
the lover of women.
But if you don't compete
with this girl,
You're showing me
and all the women
That you don't
respect us.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
So take back your sword and go
fight this girl like a bull!
Okay.
Can't hear you!
Okay!
I can't hear you!
That's really
as loud as I can go.
Phil: What does it take
to make a great salesman?
It's no big secret.
You just follow the abc's
of salesmanship --
Always be closing.
Don't ever forget
Great home ideas
just keep lurking mostly nearby.
Often, people question
realtors' sincerity.
Take umbrage.
Violators will...
Oh, shoot, "x," "x," "x"...
And this is
the great room,
Although "great" hardly
seems to do a room
like this justice.
Weird squiggly painting
not included.
I actually love it.
I do, too.
It's really beautiful.
Um, all --
all custom built-ins.
And you'll notice just --
just tons of natural light,
So that's great.
Did I need the sale?
Yes.
Was I worried?
No.
Why? Because.
Because why?
Because I won't sell anything
I don't believe in.
And when I believe, you believe.
I can sell a fur coat
to an eskimo.
Yeah, phil, I'm sorry.
It's a beautiful house.
But I'm just not sure
how kid-friendly it is,
And we have
two small children.
I mean,
these stairs alone --
Dad, this place
is awesome.
Not now, luke.
Did you see
the backyard?
It's got room for,
like, 10 tree houses.
And the bedroom's got a window
on the ceiling.
I wish
we could live here.
I wish you'd go back out
to the patio, where --
Do you really?
Oh, yeah.
Our house sucks
compared to this one.
Hmm.
It really does.
[ chuckles, snorts ]
There you are.
I'm gonna get changed,
and then we're off to
manny's match, okay?
Dad doesn't
want me to go.
What? Why?
Remember when you were all
worried that our son's a dud?
Okay, that's not exactly
the way I remember it.
Turns out
he's a natural.
At what?
At selling.
Hey, titans of
residential real estate.
That's right, I'm talking
to you, sandy brewster,
Skip woosnum,
j.J. Mccubbin.
Hear those footsteps?
That's luke dunphy,
And he's gonna drink
your milkshake.
That's amazing.
Right?!
Incredible.
So, the owner's coming back
in an hour with her husband,
And I need him.
I am telling you,
that kid is a genius.
There's the rainmaker!
Why is your ipod
in your mouth?
I'm charging it.
Alex.
Alex!
Cameron:
So, there's no part of you
That wants to clear the air
with your sister?
Nope.
Okay, fine. That's your family's
way. I'll respect that.
But you should know it's hard
on the people who love you.
Cam, stop being
so dramatic.
We feel the tension.
We hear the words
that cut like knives.
Hey, guys!
I brought orange slices.
Okay, you know what?
I can't bear this.
Claire,
mitchell still resents you
For quitting the figure-skating
team when you were kids.
Ladies, come inside
with me, please.
Work it out.
Come on.
Thanks, cam.
Is he serious?
Is that what your little jab
was about this morning?
Okay, no --
yes. Okay, yes.
Yes, I'm -- I guess
I'm still a little angry.
But, you know,
you stole my moment, claire.
Yeah,
21 years ago.
Okay, no,
but it doesn't matter to you
Because you had
your own moments.
You had cheerleading
and high-school plays
And, uh, making out
with the quarterback and --
Oh, come on.
You made out with him, too.
Yeah, but we had to
keep it a secret.
You shouldn't have quit.
It was selfish.
You want to know
why I quit?
I quit to protect you.
From what?
Glory? Fame?
No, come on.
Press conferences?
I was bigger
than you.
than you,
And I was afraid
you wouldn't be able to lift me.
You were -- you were dropping me
in practice,
And I didn't want you
to humiliate yourself...
I dropped you twice.
In front
of all of those people.
Three times.
You dropped me
all the time.
[ sighs ]
Come on.
Can't you just forgive me
and move on?
[ breathes deeply ]
Of cour-- yes, yes.
Yes, of cour--
I'm sorry.
Ugh.
God, this must seem
so petty to you, huh?
Well,
it's a little silly,
But we all have our thing,
don't we?
I'm just glad
you're getting it...
Out of you.
Are you trying
to lift me?!
Let me.
You are!
You're trying to lift me!
Stay focused, stay loose,
and stay angry.
Who's the toughest?
I am!
Who's the bravest?!
I am.
Who's the baddest?
Can you guys
ask all the questions now
So I don't have to
keep lifting this?
Go.
Go get 'em!
Are you all set?
Yeah.
Okay, go get 'em!
Good luck!
[ chuckles ]
Excuse me --
is this seat taken?
No, sit.
Oh, thank you.
Oh,
is manny yours?
Yes.
Oh, he's quite good.
I saw him earlier.
Ay, thank you.
Yeah.
Is she
your little girl?
Oh, caroline?
No. No.
Sadly,
her parents passed away.
I'm her nurse down
at the children's hospital.
But all of my patients
are like family to me.
Oh.
[ sighs ]
Man: Well, our boys
are enjoying themselves.
Yeah.
I can talk about crown moldings
and recessed lighting
Till the cows
come home,
But nothing compares
with that sound right there.
[ sneakers squeak, thud ]
luke: Ow!
Oh.
Ow!
Hey, buddy.
Oh, he's fine.
My foot!
I think it's backwards!
[ chuckling ]
it's not backwards.
What happened?
It's the stupid floors.
They're too slippery.
Oak. Also known
as nature's pillow.
It's like ice.
Now, let's not start
blaming the floors.
You shouldn't
have been running.
I saw a ghost.
G-ghost? [ chuckles ]
Hey -- phil dunphy.
O-kay.
That's me.
That's acting like
a natural shoehorn. Okay.
Probably better
all take our shoes off
For this part
of the tour.
Follow me.
She's our
little miracle.
Oh.
I only wish
her father
Had made it back
from afghanistan to see this.
[ sighs ]
Oh! There's
our cheering section!
Over here, you guys!
[ chuckles ]
Oh, my god,
we have to stop him.
Maybe I can
pull the fire alarm.
Expect no mercy.
Bring it on, big boy.
[ whistle blows ]
I-I'm glad
dad's proud of manny. I am.
I just...
It would have been nice
to see him that proud of us.
And by "us,"
I mean "me."
[ scoffs ]
And you sincerely thought
that the path to dad's approval
Was going to be
through figure skating?
Mitchell, I am fairly confident
that dad's proudest moment
Was when you finally took off
the flame-red unitard.
I am not claiming
that any of this is rational.
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being
such a pill, okay?
I...
Actually always felt
very guilty for quitting.
Look, I know how much
you loved figure skating.
I...Never
really loved skating.
Uh, what?
[ chuckles ]
um, all right.
This is gonna sound
a little gay.
But, um, when --
when you and I skated together,
You know, you weren't
the mean older sister
And I wasn't the --
the clingy little brother.
We were --
we were a team.
And, well,
let's face it,
We've kind of grown apart
in the past few years,
And -- and with
mom and dad's divorce,
We were on opposing sides,
and I just...I...
I just -- I miss
being on your team.
That's...
...A little gay.
Okay, there we go.
Claire,
where are you going?
Claire?
No way!
Get up.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
[ breathes deeply ]
Don't drop me.
[ whistle blows ]
[ buzzer ]
[ metal clashing ]
Oh!
[ whistle blows ]
[ buzzer ]
Put it away
or lose it.
[ whistle blows ]
[ buzzer ]
Woman: That's awful.
Somebody's got to
put a stop to this.
That's it, mitchell.
[ whistle blows ]
[ buzzer ]
So, can we take you and caroline
out for ice cream?
We can't.
She's diabetic.
Of course she is.
Let's get
out of here.
Let's get this thing
in the trunk.
I can't decide if I'm feeling
more proud or mortified.
Gloria:
How about now?
Jay: We tell our kids it doesn't
matter if you win or lose,
But let's be honest.
Winning feels pretty great.
There's nothing like
that golden moment in the sun.
[ laughs ]
I think every parent probably
wants that for their child.
You know, maybe a little bit
for ourselves, too.
[ laughing ] buddy!
So, sometimes,
we push too hard.
And that leads to a lot
of resentment and guilt.
Yes!
So, how much is too much?
Here's where I come out.
Guilt fades.
Hardware is forever.
You're mad,
aren't you?
I'm not mad.
Yes, you are.
No, I am not.
You're
a little jealous.
I'm...Happy
for the two of you.
All right, come on.
We'll do one.
Stay there.
For real?
Yep.
Feel better?
Yeah.
Oh, do me now.
Come on.
What are you
talking about?
Are you serious?
Cam, no! Ow!
www.tvsubtitles.net