Hey, i though you were gonna take out the garbage.
I am.
Phil.
Yes, getting it.
I was --
I was gonna get it.
Dylan.
Hey, mrs. Dunphy.
Um, I'm just waiting for haley.
Did you ring the bell?
I texted. She said she'd
be down in just a minute.
Oh, great.
Tell her I said hi.
I will.
Dylan!
D-money!
Chillin'
with dylan the villain.
"d" to the "y" to the --
hey, mr. Dunphy.
Hey, come on in.
You're just in time
to catch the end of the game.
Oh, I'm not really
a baseball guy.
[ cellphone beeps ]
haley says hi.
I-I was just being facetious.
Come on.
I'll catch you up.
Sit it. Park it.
Come on, I don't bite.
[ growls ]
kidding.
[ chuckles ]
I'm kidding.
Okay, see that guy?
He's the tying run.
Interesting story
about him.
He's been stuck
on second base forever,
And I'm pretty sure
he's gonna try and steal third,
Which is just
a terrible, terrible idea.
How are you
and haley doing?
I wish I could stay home
with you and fly toy airplanes.
These aren't toy airplanes,
manny.
These are models,
and they're very complicated.
You want to fly
one of these,
You got to be familiar with
airfoil, drag, lift, and thrust,
And these are all principles
of aerodynamics.
The box says, "12 and up."
What?!
You can fly toy planes
with jay next time.
Today you have to spend time
with luke.
Why?
Because his mother
invited you, so you go.
Family needs to be close,
right, jay?
I'm pretty sure
this is a typo.
Men need their hobbies.
Manny's father
had many hobbies,
Like hiking in the desert,
That kind of skiing
that they drop you from the...
How do you say in english?
The [imitates helicopter]
Helicopter.
Yes.
Once, on a dare,
he even boxedd with an alligator.
Wrestle.
You wrestle --
you can't box with alligators.
Are you sure?
How would they get the gloves
on those lile claws?
Aren't they like tiny,
little hands?
No!
Okay, now I forgot
what we were talking about.
Anyways, hobbies are important
for the men,
Whether you're
risking your life
Or flying little planes
from a safe distance.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
what are you doing?
We're just gonna
buy some diapers.
It'll just take
a second.
This is costco.
Yeah, which is where
we buy diapers.
Since when?
Do you remember
when we adopted that baby
A few months back?
Since then.
Mitchell is a snob.
No, n-no,
I'm -- I'm discerning.
Official slogan for snobs.
When we first met,
he wouldn't even look at me
Because I was a hick
from the farm in missouri
And he's a big city mouse.
Who says "city mouse"?
Country mice.
[baseball game plays
on television ]
I think I'm gonna
go wait in the car.
Okay.
Hey, if you're on your way out,
can you grab the garbage?
I got it.
Okay, we got it.
He's a little jumpy.
Oh, go figure -- a teenage boy
doesn't want to hang out
With his girlfriend's dad.
I thought
we were past all that.
I'm all about...
I'm all about taking it
to the next level.
Really?
I thought you were all about
keeping it real.
Yes, but the whole point
of keeping it real
Is so you can take it
to the next level.
Did you really
not know that?
You haven't exactly taken it
to the next level with my dad.
What are you
talking about?
We've been married
for 16 years,
And you still walk on eggshells
around him.
What?!
Are you kidding?
Jay and I are total buds.
[ doorbell rings ]
You -- you want
to just hang out?
Brought six friends,
so that just...
[ chuckles ]
Let's...
-- Sync by honeybunny --
www.addic7ed.com
Manny brought his favorite game
to play with luke.
It's called "empire."
You use strategy
to expand territories
And take over the world.
Luke is gonna love that.
He's out back playing.
Do you need me
to get you something
While I'm out shopping?
That's such a nice offer,
but I think we're good. Thanks.
Okay, what about this?
You don't even say hello
to gloria and manny?
Hi, gloria and manny.
Okay, mom,
what about this?
No, you're wearing a dress.
[ sighs ]
mom, come on!
What?
It's gonna kill you to look
like a girl for one afternoon?
But it's a wedding
for some friend of yours
That I never even
heard of.
It's nonnegotiable.
You can borrow a dress
of haley's again.
No, that sends
an ugly message --
That I'm haley.
You know, instead of trying
to force me to wear a dress,
Why don't you worry about
getting luke to wear some pants?
What?
Why does he do this?
Luke!
Pants! Come on!
Phil: Jay and I are buds,
for sure,
But with kind of
an invisible asterisk.
Um, he's not, uh --
he's not a talker...
Or -- or a hugger.
Once, he ran over my foot
with his car.
To -- to be fair,
he had just given up smoking.
But, basically, we're buds.
Do you have to
just stand there?
You're making me
feel uneasy.
Oh.
[ clears throat ]
Oh, for god's sake,
sit here.
Here, hold this wing like this
while I adjust this.
Okay.
Come on. Here.
Not too hard.
Okay.
Alex, why don't you
come shopping with me?
Maybe I can help you find
something that you like.
That's a really nice offer,
but it's not really her thing.
Actually,
I'd love to go.
See, you don't know
what my thing is.
You have no idea
I know what your thing is.
Your thing is to provoke,
Just like
your sister's thing
Is to never
come out of her room,
And your brother's thing --
Oh, well,
there's your brother's thing.
Luke!
Put 'em on!
Mm-hmm.
Our relationship's
always been stuck
In that primal place
where it started.
You know,
he's the old silverback
Protecting his females.
Then along comes this younger,
stronger gorilla,
Swinging in, beating his chest,
you know.
Naturally,
the ape ladies come running,
Presenting
their nice scarlet behinds.
Papa ape wants to stop all that,
but he can't, you know.
That's -- that's life.
I'm not the enemy.
The enemy is poachers.
That'll do it.
Don't touch it.
[ sighing ]
all right.
You want to go fly it?
Sure.
Oh, hey.
I got the toothpaste
and the soap.
Good. Now we can open
that general store.
I thought we were just here
to get diapers.
We had a saying
on the farm --
As long as you're bringing
the mule to the market, you --
I feel you
rolling your eyes at me.
We met at one of pepper's
legendary game nights.
I remember mitchell
because he kept rolling his eyes
Every time I would get
a little boisterous.
I did not!
A little bit.
Yeah,
maybe a little bit.
We were --
we were playing charades,
And I-I had no idea
how to act out my clue,
And all I could think of
to do was...
And without missing a beat,
cam says --
"casablanca."
All I did was this...
Can we just please get
the diapers and get out of here?
Fine, but I want to stop by
the wine section first.
[ chuckling ] wait.
There's a wine section?
Yeah, a really good one --
just past the tires.
No way, they do not have --
oh, my god.
Oh, my -- cam. Cam.
The paper shredder
I wanted, huh?
Confetti and crosscut --
yep.
[ laughs ] ohh!
Oh, my god, amazing.
Yeah.
Cam...
What is this place?
[ timer dings ]
Those cookies smell like heaven.
Your own recipe?
No, I just throw them
in the en.
And added the secret ingredient
of caring?
Sure.
So, you and luke
having a good time?
I don't know.
He won't come out of his box.
Maybe I'll just stay here and
spend some time with my sister.
Oh, right, I guess, technically,
I would be your stepsister.
My mother says we are never
to use the word "step"
Because it means
"not real,"
And we are
a real family.
Mm.
So, what is the matter,
claire?
What?
You seem sad.
It's just stuff with alex --
you know, kid stuff.
Ugh, kids.
You don't have to tell me.
My school is full of them.
I was thinking, after lunch,
We can go and do
a little shopping.
I'm not getting a dress.
I don't care.
I'm not your mother.
I know.
You're my grandmother.
Step-grandmother.
Anyways, today,
think of me as a girlfriend --
Two girls out
for an afternoon of fun.
What do you usually do
with your girlfriends?
I don't know. We go out.
We talk, drink wine.
Can I drink wine?
No.
Some friend.
Well, you can still
talk to me about anything.
Yeah, adults always say that,
but they don't mean it.
When my mom says
I can ask her anything,
I really can't.
She just freaks out.
I won't freak out.
Shoot.
Okay.
How many men
have you slept with?
Eight. Next.
[ plane engine buzzing ]
Now can I try it?
No.
I should get one of those.
I've always loved planes.
You know, if things
had gone a little
differently in my life,
I think I would have
been a pilot.
Hey, what would happen
if you turned the remote off
And then back on
real fast?
Yeah, you would have been
a great pilot.
So, can you do a --
can you do a loop-de-loop?
If I wanted to.
No way!
Can I try it?
No.
Okay.
I can see why you like this.
It's so peaceful.
It's like the whole world
just...Disappears out here.
I remember
this one summer --
I'll tell you what.
Hmm?
There's another trick
called "threading the needle."
I used to do it with claire
and mitch when they were kids.
You want to try it?
How does it go?
You grab one of those hoops
over there
And go to the far, far, far end
of the field and stand there,
And I fly the plane
through it.
Um, that sounds awesome!
And then I get a chance
flying it?
No.
Okay.
How's this?
Not far enough.
Go on.
Okay, further down.
Está bien. Más lejos.
You can't go too far.
Right, okay. I get it.
I get it!
How's this?
Good! Now stand still!
Don't move!
Ay!
Let's do it!
Whoo!
I love it!
[ laughs ]
You drove the plane into my face.
You must have moved.
I told you to stay still.
I didn't move!
Try not to talk.
I want to make sure
nothing's broken.
[ groaning ]
Alex and I
can't just disagree.
I mean, she has to turn
everything into a fight.
Hmm, a strong,
independent woman.
Sounds like somebody else
I know.
I was never hostile,
thou.
This -- this whole thing
with the dress --
Never had this problem
with haley.
Maybe alex doesn't want
to compete with her big sister.
Maybe she's trying
to create her own identity.
Put her in a dress
and she disappears.
For one afternoon.
I wouldn't give up being myself
for even one second.
Wow.
Sometimes it's hard to remember
you're only 10 years old.
And three-quarters.
Yeah.
[ telephone rings ]
[ clears throat ]
hello?
Olives?
Yeah.
You got it.
[ beep ]
Mitchell,
I found the diapers.
They're over here.
Cameron,
guess what I found.
Coffins.
They sell baby formula,
and they sell coffins.
You can literally buy
everything you need
From birth to death.
Oh, my god,
look at these diapers.
[ gasps ]
look how cheap they are!
Oh, you know
what we should do?
We should get enough for like
the next year or two, right?
Where would we keep them?
They sell sheds.
Really?
You want to buy a diaper shed.
We're those guys now?
The guys with the diaper shed?
Just grab two more.
I'm not grabbing two more,
mitchell. It's time to go.
No, come on, come on.
We need a --
Excuse me. Where did you
get that flatbed thing?
Over there.
Go grab
one of those.
Really?
Yeah.
Get two.
I'm in the applesauce aisle!
So, anyways, after charades,
we went out for coffee,
And I learned
that he loves art,
He plays the piano,
he speaks french.
Un peu.
So, you know,
I-I misjudged him.
Yeah, I'm sort of
like costco.
I'm big, I'm not fancy,
and I dare you to not like me.
Yeah, and I'm kind of
more like that, um...
Oh.
What is the name of that little
shop we went to in paris?
You are such a snob.
"casablanca."
I have a small flower
on my ankle
And a tiny, little butterfly
on my...
Thigh.
How high up?
Very high.
Did you do it
to look sexy?
No, did you do it
for a guy?
Does grandpa like it?
No, no, and yes.
That's gross.
Mm.
Let's go back
to your piercings.
No, no, no.
I've answered enough
of your questions.
Now it's your turn
to answer one.
What is it?
Why you don't want
to wear a dress?
Because I don't want
to look like haley
And her stupid friends.
I wear dresses,
and I don't look like haley.
You are haley,
just...40 years older.
10.
20.
Deal.
Alex, why are you fighting me
on this?
It doesn't matter
if I dress up.
I'm not pretty
like haley and you.
That's ridiculous!
You're beautiful!
I'm not.
But that's okay.
I'm the smart one.
Hmm, the cute busboy doesn't
know that you're smart.
What?
He's been smiling at you every
time he comes to the table.
He does not!
Why do you think we are
the only people with bread?
Look, one day,
you are going to want
To date a cute guy
like that.
When that day comes, you're
gonna want to look beautiful,
And then
you'll wear a dress.
So, you ever kiss
another girl?
That's no way to talk
to your grandmother.
Was my mom hard on me
growing up?
Yeah, she was,
but you know what?
Back then, everything
was betty friedan
And gloria steinem.
They didn't understand --
Gloria:
Hola. We're back.
Alex: Hello.
Hey, how'd it go?
It was great.
Did you have fun with luke?
Well, not --
we had a great time.
Alex, I've been thinking,
and...
If you don't want to wear
a dress to the wedding,
It's not the end
of the world.
It's all right.
I bought one.
[ both laugh ]
Do you see how she has to
provoke me?
We'll talk about it
next week.
[ phil groaning,
pounding on door ]
Jay: Clear the way.
Coming through. Coming through.
Ow! Ow!
I need to rest my face.
You're fine.
You'll be all right.
Oh, my god! Dad!
Little accident.
Nothing big.
I was in a plane crash.
What happened?
We were threading the needle,
and somebody moved.
No, I didn't.
You did it on purpose.
That's the painkiller talking.
He's a little loopy.
How bad is it?
Well, the wing is cracked,
the propeller's bent,
But I can --
I mean phil.
I was in a plane crash.
Thanks, dad.
I didn't ask him to be there.
He insisted.
He took a chance.
This is what happened.
Kind of like the time
you ran over his foot?
You ran over
his foot?
That was an accident.
You know, dad,
you did it on purpose.
We all saw the tire marks
on the lawn.
I had just quit smoking.
[ phil groans ]
See, you're upsetting
your husband.
Water.
I'll get it.
[ sighs ]
You okay?
Gloria.
Thank god you're here.
Don't worry.
I'm here, too.
Who's this?
Jay:
Wasn't my fault.
Oh, I have seen you thread
the needle a million times.
You never miss.
Yeah, I must be getting old.
Why don't you just admit it?
You never liked phil.
And put that down.
You do not get a cookie.
Jay: I like phil.
It's just that sometimes
he tries too hard, you know?
And it's just kind of...
Irritating.
Okay, maybe he tries
too hard
Because you make zero effort
with him.
You know what?
In the 16 years
that we've been married,
Have you one time told him
that you liked him?
Not in those
exact words, no.
No, not in any words, dad.
How do you think
that makes me feel?
Water.
You've never told your son
that you love him?
Whoa, whoa,
when did we jump to "love"?
And he's technically
not my son.
Ah. So that means that you
don't love manny, either?
Well, sure I do.
I mean, believe me,
when I was in that park,
I really wished
manny was there.
For what --
So that you could fly
the plane into his head? Huh?
Dad, thanks so much
for bringing phil home.
I found one of your little flaps
in his hair, so...
Actually, this is called
an aileron. It controls the --
Yeah, 'cause that's what matters
right now.
Bye, dad.
Hey, phil.
Phil: Jay.
Ow!
What,
are you made of china?
[ groans ]
Phil, I just want you to know,
I'm sorry.
And whether I missed
or you moved --
I didn't.
Either way...
I just want to say
that I like you.
Really?
Yeah.
What do you like about me?
You're a nice guy.
You try real hard.
I do.
You're a good dad.
I am a good dad.
Come here.
Come here, you.
[ groans ]
This feels so right.
[ door opens ]
What's going on?
There was
a little accident,
But jay's telling phil
how much he loves him.
Oh, well,
that's nice for phil.
That's great, since he's never said
anything like that to my boyfriend.
Let it go.
No, it's not okay.
Mitch is right.
You go in there, too, cam.
Come on.
You're kidding.
Jay!
Come on in, cam.
A ttle hug?
Get in here.
[ all grunting ]
Say it, say it!
I like you, too, cam.
What do you like
about him?
Oh, geez.
Where did you get
that camera?
Only the greatest store
on earth.
Thanks, dad.
Manny, picture.
Get in there, too.
Phil:
Get in here, manny.
[ mitchell laughs ]
Say, "cheese!"
Don't push it.
Together: Cheese!
Picture!
Cheese!
Cheese! Queso!
[ laughter ]
Cameron: How beautiful!
Jay: Oh, boy!
Phil: Doesn't it feel like his
arms could go around the world?
I think I strained something.
I always wanted a daughter.
To dress her up
with pretty dresses,-
Do her hair, her nails,
her makeup.
[ chuckles ]
No one knows this, but for
the first year of his life,
I made up manny
like a girl
And told everybody
that he was my daughter.
[ laughs ]
But just for a few times.
I didn't want to mess
with his head.
When he found the pictures,
I told him
That it was his twin sister
who died, you know.
Transcript by addic7ed.com
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net