Ordinarily,
I'm a rule follower,
But when someone tells me
I can't bring my own snacks
into their stadium,
That's when I get a little nuts.
It's a free country, right?
Let's just say it ruffles me...
...When some goobers...
...Tell me I have to spend half my payday...
...On their hot dogs.
Please, just remember
the family portrait.
We only have the photographer
for an hour.
Okay.
Okay?
And, sweetie,
did you have a chance
To try on the white pants
I put in your closet?
Oh, what do they look like?
Is there really a more clear way
to describe white pants?
Sweetie, if they don't fit you,
You're gonna be the only one
not wearing white,
And then you're gonna stand out
like "where's Waldo?"
Actually, "where's Waldo?"
doesn't stand out.
He's super hard to find.
That's the challenge.
This portrait is incredibly important to me.
Also, his name is just Waldo. Sorry.
I spent weeks trying to find
a time that works for everybody
And finding
the right photographer.
So if you could just promise me
That you'll cooperate, okay?
I promise.
Okay.
This is amazing
that you're doing this.
Mm, thank you.
You're wonderful.
Thank you.
Get in here.
Okay.
Oh, no can do.
Oh. Oh.
I love you.
Bye.
Where's my good underwear?
The question is,
Why isn't all
your underwear good, Jay?
You make a nice living!
The new maid keeps mixing up
my underwear with Manny's.
Put on the first thing
I grabbed --
It was like
a crotch tourniquet.
You got to talk to her.
Why me?
Hola. You both speak
the same language.
She's Portuguese.
Do you know how offensive it is
That you put all of us in the same mixing pot?
I'm sorry.
Please apologize to her
When you tell her
not to put my underwear --
I can't talk to her!
Hey, guys.
Hey!
Where's Luke?
I'm going instead.
Luke suddenly remembered
a school project due tomorrow.
Oh, that's tough.
But it's a good lesson
for the kid.
You know, you ma a commitment,
you got to follow through.
Yeah.
What is the project?
Uh, he has to interview somebody
who lived through the 1960s.
Oh, no.
Hello.
Yeah, Luke.
Oh, sure,
I remember what I said.
Yeah, come on over.
All right.
Gloria, you're gonna have
to take Manny to the game.
Yay. Manny, vamos!
I'm still getting dressed!
Hey, mom!
I think my diet's working!
My underwear won't stay up!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, so delicious.
Yes.
Hey, you're okay with me not
going with you today, right?
I have been hired to sing
at a wedding this weekend.
I was plucked from obscurity
after a particularly stirring
karaoke performance.
So I guess you could say
I'm a professional singer now.
I don't know.
Well, they're paying you
in flowers, so...
Well, I would have blown
the money on flowers anyway.
They're saving me a step.
Plus, all the great divas
are rewarded in flowers.
They're also given paychecks.
It's just, I'm really bad
at small talk, so...
I get it.
It's not a problem.
Are you sure?
Because you've been quiet
all morning.
It's because I'm resting
my instrument.
Okay.
I feel tension.
Kobe!
Kobe Kobe!
Kobe! Kobe!
Hey, hat can I do for you?
Do you like being
a basketball...Player?
You serious?
I choked. I didn't think
you'd look up heret me.
Little preparation next time.
It's a mental game.
Dually noted.
All right.
What's wrong?
That broken step.
It's gonna ruin
our whole family portrait.
Okay, here's my idea.
I'm really excited about it.
The whole extended family,
all dressed in white,
In a single-file line
down the staircase.
Oh, like a line on the highway.
No.
Or a-a ski jump.
Why -- why would I want
a ski jump?
I don't know.
My idea was to have
the whole family on a giant bed
Like in "Willy wonka."
Yeah, but that's ridiculous.
Ridicu-licious.
I don't see anything.
So I'm crazy?
No! You're...Not.
Your father was supposed
to fix that step.
Mom, you're obsessing over
the tiniest little thing.
So you do see it.
Yeah.
What is the big deal
about this one picture?
Honey, you know what?
I don't expect you
to understand.
But all right.
When you're a mom,
everything goes by so quickly.
In a minute,
Luke's gonna be shaving,
And Alex is gonna be
off at college,
And --
and you're gonna be...
...You're gonna be doing
something great.
Just want to freeze
this moment as it is right now.
You know?
I do.
I know I don't show it,
But this family's still the most
important thing that I -- screw it.
I'm gonna fix the bastard.
I mean, seriously,
how hard can it be?
If your father can do it,
I can do it, right?
All right.
I just need to...
Like, lift...
Oh. Now I see it.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
These seats are amazing!
Why you have candy
coming out of your pants?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Huh?
I brought my own snacks.
Not because I'm cheap. It's.
Plus, I get a little rush
from the danger.
Be cool! Be cool!
Be cool!
Just look straight ahead.
I've never felt more alive.
Whoo!
Okay, I just made it worse.
I'm not freaking out, though.
I'm gonna call your dad,
And he's gonna tell me
how to fix this.
"Oh, my God, it's dad"
Where?
Right there, behind Kobe!
Oh!
Oh, how weird is this?
Quick. Quick. Tell me something
to say that'll freak him out.
Tell him I'm pregnant!
No, I'm not gonna say that.
Okay, here we go.
How funny is this?
He it's Phil.
You know what to do.
Well,
that was pretty funny.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Ohh. Ohh. Ohh.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sorry for that.
Hello?
There is a pigeon in our house!
What do I do?
Who is this?
Never funny.
Not funny now.
Calm down.
You know, I grew up
around many animals.
One time,
a rooster attacked me,
And my mom wrung its neck,
and we had it for dinner.
Great time for an anecdote.
Help me!
It's more afraid of you
than you are of it.
Pigeons aren't scared
of anything.
They stand on electrical wires.
You're gonna be fine, Mitchell.
You know what?
Just as long as you don't --
Oh, you know what?
They're starting. I got to go.
Okay. Bye.
As long as I don't what?!
Cam, as long as I don't --
Oh.
Ooh, the kiss Cam!
Wouldn't it be embarrassing
if the camera was on us
And then
the crowd started --
We're related.
Not by blood.
Touch me,
and there will be blood.
Not us.
What's wrong with you?
It's the kiss-cam --
When it lands on you,
you're supposed to kiss.
It's my wife's dad's
second wife,
So, legally okay,
but still weird.
That was awkward.
And...We're back.
Ay, come on.
It's not a big deal.
Thank God
for caller I.D.
So you don't have to talk
to your wife.
Oh, we're gonna talk,
mister.
We're gonna talk and talk...
Dad!
Mom saw you on TV!
You're dead.
Here's the thing.
The kiss-cam is only supposed
to be for the enjoyment
Of the people at the game!
They never show that on TV.
What people do in the privacy
of their own sports arena
Should be their own business.
So, in '66,
I worked at my grandfather's
office-supply business.
You know, your ink,
your staples, your legal pads.
Am I going too fast for you?
I feel asleep for second.
Did you do anything interesting
in the '60s?
Well, one summer, I swept up hair
At my other grandfather's
barber shop.
Ugh, you're killing me!
What do you want?
I don't know.
Brian Beckwith's grandfather
marched on Washington.
Artie Beckwith?
He couldn't walk two feet
without complaining.
He marched on Washington?
He told Brian he did.
With Martin Luther king Jr.
Martin Luther king?
Guess who cut his hair.
What?
Do you know who cut
Martin Luther king Jr.'s hair?
Neither does Luke's teacher.
So, the barber shop
was in Washington?
Okay.
Did you cut
any other famous hair?
Oh, yeah, the Kennedys,
Richard Nixon,
All the astronauts.
How do you think buzz Aldrin
got his nickname?
Awesome.
♪ we love to play
in Lily's room
♪ we don't need any milk ♪
Okay, you know what, Lily?
I am a man.
I am going into the kitchen
to get your milk.
Whaaaaaaaaa!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Ohh!
Come on.
♪ ave Maria ♪
♪ Gratia plena ♪
♪ Maria, Gratia plena ♪
♪ ave, ave Dominus ♪
♪ Dominus tecum ♪
♪ Benedicta tu in mulieribus ♪
♪ et benedictus
fructus ventris ♪
♪ ventris tui, Jesus ♪
♪ ave Maria ♪
Then one day,
wilt Chamberlain shows up.
He says, "can you take
a little off the top
For my friend here?"
And it's Elvis.
No way.
Greatest singer
that ever lived --
After Sinatra.
I'll fight any man
who says different.
My dad says the greatest singer
who ever lived
Is Peabo Bryson.
Then I guess
I got to fight your dad.
Yeah. I guess.
Luke says grandpa
wants to fight you.
Why does everything
have to suck?!
Let's just do the picture
another day.
I think I'm getting a pimple.
No!
Do you know how long it took me
to book this photographer?
Maybe by the fireplace.
Yeah.
That's a classic
old-person spot for a portrait.
Yeah, if I'd ever bothered
to paint that hideous WA
Claire is a perfectionist,
Which sometimes
is a good thing,
Like when it comes to
picking a husband.
Sometime it's a bad thing,
Like when, uh, everyone else
sees something beautiful,
And all she sees
is the teeny, tiny flaw.
No.
Hi.
My house is a disaster.
Can we do this picture at your place?
Yeah, yeah, that's --
that's not gonna work.
Maybe one more layer --
and tight, really tight.
Dad, can you call them again?
I just did.
They're on their way.
Game went into overtime.
I know,
but we're losing the light,
And the photographer
has got to get
To a bar mitzvah in 10 minutes.
Oh, red wine.
Really? Now?
You know, honey,
I think you're getting
A little too uptight
about this.
Mm-hmm.
It's hard to breathe.
Oh, you're fine.
What'd you do to him?
He's turning blue.
Yeah, but his clothes will stay white.
We're home!
Oh, thank God!
Hello!
Manny, let's go change.
Mwah!
Hey.
There's my beautiful wife.
I know you're mad at me,
And I know this foam finger
can't map for everything --
Honey, you just go change, and we'll
talk about what you did later.
Okay. Hey...
Thank you so much
for those tickets.
Gloria tells me
you had a real good time.
Not really.
No, I didn't.
God, I love your daughter.
Ohh! I should --
I should come by
and kiss that step --
Fix that step.
Ugh, you're acting like I wanted
to destroy the house.
No, I just think it's odd
That the majority of things
you destroyed
Were sent to us by my mom.
Oh, okay, okay, okay,
So while I'm fighting off
that filthy creature,
I actually stop and say,
"oh, you know what?
Here's the opportunity
I've always been looking for
"To destroy
our kitschiest objects."
"kitschiest"?
Oh, she's gonna love that.
You know, if you would have just
come with me to the wedding,
None of this
would have happened.
Okay, so you are angry.
Mitchell, I get it.
You're terrified
of small talk...And birds.
You're just lucky that pigeon
didn't want to chat you up
About the weather.
Hello, Jay.
Hello, guys.
Oh, God!
Oh, you look like the guy
from "dance fever"!
Thank you.
Deney Terrio.
Cleveland, Ohio.
Dad, really.
That is not a compliment.
That's why I wanted you
to try those on earlier.
Turn around.
The picture can't happen today.
My pimple's getting worse.
Oh, honey, I am so sorry.
Can you stand?
Yeah?
Well, then,
the picture's happening.
It's all anybody's gonna see!
I wouldn't be so sure
about that.
Did you get a look
at her dress?
What?!
Why would I look at her dress?
I love you!
Uh, Mrs. Dunphy.
The sun is setting.
Oh, okay, yeah,
this is happening.
Everybody, come on, let's go.
Hold it.
Be careful.
I stained some furniture
out there this afternoon.
Of course you did, dad.
Anything else
I need to know about?
Maybe the neighbors
on either side
Are having a paintball fight.
Now, watch this.
Dad, in his infinite wisdom,
stained furniture today.
Don't touch it.
It's wet.
Hurry, hurry!
Put that down, sweetheart.
Okay, okay, we got it.
Now we're gonna go out here. We're ready.
Oh, my God!
Are you kidding me?!
Ay.
All right, how do you --
How do you turn
the sprinklers off?
Ay, of course,
because I'm Latina,
I'm supposed to know everything
about gardening and sprinklers!
You were here
when they installed it!
Ay, yeah. Ay...
The box is across the yard.
You mean
the now-soaking-wet yard?
That's great.
We are screwed.
No, we're not.
We haven't unwrapped
our secret weapon yet.
Luke walks over there,
"hurt locker"-style,
Flips the switch,
and boom! --
Or, not boom --
water off.
Put the "he" in "hero," son.
Oh.
Ohh.
"hurt locker."
It's -- it's more like
"squirt locker."
Really?
That wasn't funny?
I actually pity you guys.
No! No time to celebrate!
Stop it!
We don't have a lot of time.
All right, everybody, if I can
have the little ones out front --
You know what, sir?
If you don't mind...
I've got this.
Come on, people.
Let's get out here.
Haley, Alex, I need you to
unwrap your brother, all right?
I need the Dunphys
over on this side.
Dad, you're in the middle.
Mitchell, Cam, Lily
on this end.
Okay.
Listen.
Uh-huh?
I know I screwed up,
But if ever
you're in my arms again...
Phil, not now.
Yes, now!
I don't want to look at this
picture when I'm 80 years old
And you're long dead and know
that you were angry at me
When we took it!
Phil, we'll talk
about what you did later.
Okay, everybody.
Eyes over here.
I didn't do anything.
She kissed me.
What?!
Who kissed you?
Gloria.
What?!
It was the kiss-cam.
Why did you kiss Cam?
No, I kissed Phil.
He told me I had to.
No. No. Okay.
Hang on a second.
Was this before or after
You ignored the phone call
from your wife?
You saw that, too?!
Mm.
Could we please just take
the damn picture?!
Okay, everybody, one more time.
Just so you know,
I am angry with you.
I knew it!
Oh, damn it!
It was a big day for me,
And he didn't to go because
he doesn't like small talk!
Would it be
terribly inconvenient
To just postpone this hissy fit
for a few minutes?
Okay, you know what?!
Maybe some of us don't want to
take a picture today! Thank you!
Yeah, and, please, Claire,
don't try to make Mitchell
Do something
he doesn't want to do.
Oh, shut up, Cam!
Okay, stop it!
Stop it!
Everyone!
Listen, this took me forever
to put together,
So I don't really care
who kissed who
And who's got a pimple
on her head,
And who is wearing an
outrageously inappropriate dress!
We are gonna get together
and act like a normal family
For 1/10 of a freaking second,
And we're gonna do it
right now.
Come on, let's go.
Get your hands off or me!
No. No, make me.
Make me. Make me.
Oh, this is ridiculous!
You're both uptight
about everything!
You didn't want to go
to a wedding with him
Because you didn't want
to make small talk?
That's how I met Gloria.
Do you remember the first thing
I said to you?
Yes.
"I like chocolate,
I like fruit,
But not together."
You couldn't come up with that,
Ivy league?
And you --
you would be a lot happier
If you weren't so obsessed
with everything being perfect.
Look at us here all in white.
What are we, a cricket team?
News flash --
life is not perfect, Claire.
Now, calm the hell down!
Okay, dad, that's great.
And that's really easy
for you to say,
But do you think
I like being like this?
No, I don't.
So if you have some
quick and easy fix,
Why don't you just
give it to me right now?
Ohh!
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Jay! Oh!
Oh, my God!
I-I got this, baby.
No! What are --
Why did you do that?
Two people are dirty!
Well, three.
Okay, you know what?
That's for "kitschy."
Mud fight!
No.
Oh! Oh!
Don't do that!
Stop!
Oh!
Haley, stop it!
No!
Excuse me!
Are we still doing this?
No.
No, we're not.
Now we are.
Ready!
Whoo-hoo!
Aah!
Say "cheese."
Say "cheese!"
Back in '68,
When I was sweeping up hair
in that barber shop,
I had this mental picture
of the family that,
If I was lucky enough,
one day I would end up with --
Perfect wife, perfect kids.
Guess what.
I didn't get any of that.
Wound up
with this sorry bunch.
And I'm thankful for that
every day.
Well, most days.
I think I'm just gonna go
with the Elvis stuff.
Yeah, I would.
To the right...To the right...
And a skosh to the left.
There we go.
Whatever.
I'm gonna have to take
the picture down
When I repaint the wall anyhow.
Kill me now.
What?
Don't know how...
I got so lucky.
Mm-hmm?
I love you.
I love that picture.
Yeah.
Is that a chip on the frame
right there? No. No.
I can see it.
Honey!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net