Milady.
Actually, claire and I
Were supposed to go to hawaii for
our honeymoon... Mm-hmm.
...But something els came up.
I got pregnant with haley.
My bad!
We didn't even have
a proper wedding.
We just went down to the
courthouse on a Tuesday.
The judge sentenced me to
life with no chance of parole.
You begged me to marry you.
It's true. I did.
Oh! Hold on, my bride.
Allow me. Oh!
Whoa. What are you doin'?
Being romantic.
God, you're solid.
Sweetie, put me down.
Oh. Go on. Okay.
Honey, come on.
Let's turn this vacation
into a honeymoon.
Sweet pea, I'm a mom
traveling with my kids.
For me, this is not a vacation.
It's a business trip.
Let's go.
Wow.    Wow. Wow. Wow.
This'll do. It's beautiful.
Aloha!
Welcome to the
four seasons maui.
What do you think, manny?
I'm home.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I can't believe we have
our own hotel room.
Score! There's an iron in here!
Don't you want to
keep our room neat?
You know, in case we entertain.
Who would we entertain?
I ticed some lovely tweens
down by the kids club.
Maybe we can find a nice
spot near them by the pool
And send over a couple
of virgin mai tais.
They may be interested in two
sophisticated men like us.
I am a bathroom martian.
Beep. Boop. Boop.
I'm from the nebula
of the great toilet.
Beep. Boop. Beep. Boop. Bop.
I want the biggest
cheeseburger you got.
Instead of salad, I want fries.
Instead of fruit,
I want chili fries.
Haley, sweetie,
put the phone down
And put on some sunscrn, please.
We have got to stay
on these kids all day,
Or else they're gonna burn.
Totally. Listen.
They put on the littlest bit
of sunscreen in the morning,
And they think it's got
them covered for the --
Are you watching
gloria in my sunglasses
Is she moving in slow motion,
or is my brain doing that?
Phil, this is important.
Go ahead. I'm glistening.
Hey, everybody!
We're on our way to see the
world's largest banyan tree.
Does anybody want to come?
Now, why the hell would
anyone want to leave paradise,
Take a hot bus
ride to see a tree?
The great thing about cameron
Is that he's adventurous,
like I am.
And we -- we both like
to immerse ourselves
In the culture and really
get to know the locals.
We've made friends
all over the world.
We're still in
touch with elunga,
A man we met on
safari in tanzania.
We actually send him
all of our old clothes.
He was a very nice
man when we met him,
But based on his recent letters,
I have a small fear
he's become a warlord.
Jay, I'm gonna go to the gym
to work out a little bit.
You want to come with me?
I just ordered an
extra-long straw
To avoid accidentally
doing a sit-up.
Mm.
Ah, look at this. My brother.
What's up, jackass?
Happy birthday,
you dumb son of a bitch.
Ha! Birthday's tomorrow, moron.
I never understood
this relationship.
So, 63, right?
Hey, you can count.
You know dad was 63
when he died.
Huh? Hello?
Thanks for reminding me.
Ah, don't worry.
He never took caref himself.
He ate like crap
and drank too much.
So, anyway, irene's begging me -
Hey, gloria, wait up.
I'm comin'.
Hey. Hi.
Hi.
So, I was thinking we
book a couple's massage.
Mm-hmm.
I accidentally looked in on one.
They seemed really relaxed
until they noticed me.
Haley, that's enough.
Get off the phone.
Luke! Pull up your trunks!
This bathing suit
looks great on you.
Thanks, sweetie.
Haley, come on. Off the phone.
No way! Kira got her
hair straightened?
Claire, consider this a
grand gesture of my love.
What are you -- oh,
my god! What did you do?!
Phil, what are you thinking?
That is an expensive cellphone.
It's just the beginning.
Buckle your seatbelt, lady.
You're being wooed.
In nature, fathers are
known to eat their young.
Is it because they're delicious?
No.
It's because they want
to give their female --
Bear, giraffe, what have you -
the honeymoon they never had.
Just to be clear, I'm not
condoning eating your kids,
But I sure as heck know
why giraffes do it.
What?
Come on, sleepy!
Ay, jay!
Come on, honey! Get out of bed!
I just booked us
on an outrigger.
But it's your birthday.
You don't want to sleep in?
Come on.
No, no. I just
came from the gym.
I don't know. 500 pounds.
500 pounds? What am I,
a forklift?
To tell you the truth,
The call from my brother
scared the hell out of me.
I decided to get in
better shape quick.
Didn't want to end
up like my old man.
Although he did die
doing what he loved --
Refusing service to hippies
who came into his store.
Manny's the worst roommate ever.
Everything he finds, he folds.
I know -- sweetie,
it's only for a few more days.
Last night we had a fire drill.
Not the hotel. Just us.
Hi, guys. Hey.
Hey.        Hey.
So, what's today's
big adventure?
I'll bet the kids
want to go with you.
Well, it is a big one
the lavender ranch,
Where they grow 45 different
varieties of lavender. 45.
You hear that,
kids? 45 different varieties.
Yeah, I can't sell that.
Go with god.
Oh, well, more lavender for us.
When mitchell and I first met,
I may have exaggerated my
interest in adventurous travel
By implying that I had any.
But it's one of the things
he loves most about me,
And I can't tell
him the truth now.
It would be like
lewis telling clark
That he didn't like to walk.
Side note --
We're very good nds with a couple
named lewis and clark.
Clark bought a big,
sparkly belt in new orleans
That he calls his "
louisiana purchase."
Mom, haley keeps
stealing my ipod.
All my music is on my phone.
What else am I supposed to do?
Manny watches the news.
You guys don't even
watch the news.
Aloha. Hi. Sorry, folks.
This pool is for adults only.
Aw.
Don't turn around.
What?
Trust me. Just keep walking.
Wait. Where are you guys going?
Guys?
What just happened?
Ooh, so, we can
drink lavender tea
While eating lavender scones.
Oh, neat.
So is this an
all-day thing, or...
Oh, no. I know what
you're thinking, cam.
Don't worry - we'll
still have time
For the whaling village.
Oh. Good. So...
Okay.
I can't.
What?
I-I don't want to go.
I know I said I'm not a
stay-by-the-pool type of guy,
But I really am, mitchell.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that I
like adventure,
But not every
minute of every day.
Can you just go by yourself?
But the lavender ranch --
It's -- it's something two men
are meant to do together.
On or off, folks?
Well, I'm on.
I'm off.
Think about what
youmissing, cam.
It's an entire ranch
full of lavender.
You're not making the compelng
case you think you are.
Hey, you little monkeys!
No standing around!
There you go!
Here goes another one!
Here! Here comes another one!
There you go!
I thought you were one of ours.
Hey, jay!
Be careful. You're gonna
hurt somebody...Liku.
Don't get too comfortable.
I reserved us a tennis court.
yay.
Thought that one
of the advantages
Of marrying an older guy
Was that I was going
to be able to relax.
But all the swimming and
running and rowing --
It's just like how some of my
relatives got into this country.
You know? Claire: Hmm?
You look prettier now than
the day we got married.
Oh, honey, and you are
even more handsome.
I did pushups in the bathroom.
you're funny.
You're nice.
I have always been nice.
I've always been funny.
Well.
Mom? Dad?
Ignore her.
That could be anyone.
Phil and claire dunphy?
Yes, haley? Honey, what is it?
I'm gonna go get some shaved
ice at the hotel next door
With some kids.
What kids?
Just some kids I
met at the pool.
Okay, I should go with her.
Claire, no. You have
to learn to let go.
Turning a family
vacation into a honeymoon
Takes commitment.
You can do it. Eye of the tiger.
Hello?
I should at least meet them.
No.
That is not eye of the tiger.
Okay. Okay.
All right, hey, honey.
Go and have fun.
And be back in time
For your grandfather's
birthday dinner, okay?
Thank you!
Okay! All right! Bye, honey.
Oh, god.
That feels weirand good
all at once.
I know. I was leaning up against
that nozzle a minute ago.
Hey.
Hey, you're back. How was it?
Oh, cameron, it was the
most incredible thing
I have ever seen in my
entire life. Really?
And you know who
else was there? Who?
Elton john. No.
Yes, and he was so blown
away by the beauty of it,
He sat down at their
lavender piano
And played "tiny dancer."
And we bonded, because he,
too, likes adventure.
Did that really happen?
No, that didn't really happen.
I'm just trying to get back
at you for bailing on me.
I'm sorry.
If it means anythi,
We've been relaxing here,
doing nothing.
Maybe you can join us tomorrow.
Oh, I-I can't.
I just don't -- I don't
find relaxing that relaxing.
I understand.
You are who you are.
Leilani. Yes.
You know what?
You know, I-I think it's
because of my parents.
It always is.
Kipu.
I mean, vacation with
my mom and my dad
Was them sitting
around like statues
When, you know, the only thing that me
and claire could do for excitement was
--
Oh -- was, you know, sit around
and listen to my skin sizzle.
You poor thing.
Sue.
So that's, like -- that's why,
when I'm on vacation,
I want to go out and
meet the locals.
I want to immerse
myself in the culture.
You know, I don't want to
sloth around all day --
Ah, sweet lady gaga,
that is good.
Oh!
Oh, thank you.
Mmm! What's this called?
Happiness.
Ohh.
I'm curious.
Is there any sand
left on the beach,
Or did you bring it all
up to our bathroom?
sorry, mom.
And now you're sitting
on my linen jacket.
I guess I can't
have nice things.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was there.
It's okay.
Oh! Luke!
Stop! I'm wearing that tonight.
I'm wrinkling your linen!
Ooh!
You know what?
! Out! I want you out!
This isn't working!
I don't care where you go,
as long as you don't stay here!
What are you saying?
What don't you
understand about "out"?
Fine. I'll just move
in with my sisters.
Ooh! Ooh!
Oh, no.
Who will pee all over
the bathroom floor?
I was brushing my teeth
at the same time.
You try and do that.
What did you do today?
I napped. You did?
I haven't napped in years.
Yeah, it feels good, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm. Good and weird.
Kind of like that one
nozzle in the infinity pool.
I wouldn't know.
Phil was hogging it.
Is it me, or is lily
more relaxed, too?
Oh, yes. She is.
I think it's because she's
ally picking up on our energy.
You know, it's like,
If we're tense,
she's gonna be tense.
And I think we need to
bring this new energy home.
It's gonna make
us better parents.
Lily! Oh! Oh! You let the --
What? What happened?
You didn't bring her out!
I thought you had her.
Come on. Let me paint you.
Oh, sweetie, that is so creepy.
Where is everyone?
Okay, let me just say
what everyone's thinking.
My jacket's a mess.
It wouldn't be,
But someone used the iron to
make grilled cheese.
I had bread, I had cheese,
and I had an iron.
What was I supposed to do?
Kids, kids... We don't care.
Hola. Hola. Hi.
Hey.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Where is jay?
He's not with you?
No, he came down
a long time ago.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll go have a look around.
Oh, he's probably in the ocean
Trying to pull a
tugboat with his teeth.
Well, look who
decided to join us.
And where is your sister?
She is in our
bathroom throwing up.
Well, what happened?
You're not going to like
this as much as I do, but...
She's drunk.
I knew I never should have
let her go. Gloria: Go, go!
That's awesome.
Guaranteed our bathroom
is still messier.
Where is the elevator?
Where?! I don't know!
I'm taking the stairs!
Lily, we're coming for you.
Hey, you. Where you headed?
Well, remember earlier,
in the pool,
When you convinced me to
let haley go next door
With complete strangers?
And you were totally
on board, yeah.
Mm-hmm, yeah, well,
she got drunk,
And now she's
upstairs throwing up.
But she's just a kid.
Who would serve her?
We did, honey - on
a silver platter.
Look, you convinced me
to relax and let go,
And now this happens.
I'm sorry, but we -
we shouldn't feel bad
About wanting a little
time for ourselves.
Sweetie, this isn't a honeymoon.
We have kids.
You have got to let this go.
From now on,
I am not losing sight
of them for two seconds.
Nothing gets past me.
Did you find jay?
I'm getting worried.
I'm sorry. I have
to deal with haley.
No. You know what,
sweetie? I will deal with haley.
You go see if you can find dad.
I'll look for him out there.
Lily, where are you going, huh?
Oh, my god.
I'm so sorry. Oh, my god.
Wow, what were you thinking?
One of the kids had an I.D.
, and she bought some drinks.
Mm-hmm.
I tried one and
then another one.
It was stupid.
Yes. Yes, it was stupid.
But you are really lucky
That this did not end as
badly as it could have.
This is why we
always say to you,
"when you drink,
you make bad decisions."
I know. I know. I just --
One minute, you're having
wine coolers at homecoming,
And the next...
The game of "truth or claire"
sweeps your high school.
Thanks for not yelling at me.
Oh, honey... That
would just be cruel.
I'll wait till you
feel better to yell.
I don't think I'll ever
feel better.
Does this happen
every time you drink?
Yes.
Yes, it does.
Jay?
Over here.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm stuck. I laid down.
My back went out.
Oh, well, don't you worry.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Grab on.
You know, phil,
this might not be the best --
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just gonna rock you.
Like a hurricane. I'm kidding.
You're too old to get that.
Here we go.
Wait, why don't you just
get someone who works here?
No, this is gonna work.
And...Oh! Ooh, wow!
It's spasming. Don't move. Don't move.
No. I don't want to get...
Um...
By the way, I just want to
thank you for this trip.
It's really been the
vacation of a lifetime.
Oh...
Nothing weird.
Aloha.
I keep my wallet in my
front pocket, so that's --
That's what that is.
Neck going --
I'm sorry.
Anyone! Anyone, help!
Security! Seal off the island!
This way. This way.
Lily!
you looking for someone?
Lily. We were so worried.
We just got distracted.
We're idiots.
Ay. Don't beat yourself up.
I used to lose
manny all the time.
Now I lost your father.
These things happen.
She's right, you know.
Did she say my father's missing?
Hmm?
We say we'll make time,
but life gets in the way.
I mean, I know we're parents,
But can't we be lovers, too?
This may be my worst
birthday ever.
There you are.
Oh, hi, honey. Hey.
He was stuck in a hammock.
It was actually really funny.
I was on top of him for like 20 minutes.
You need to go now.
Good night. Honey.
My back seized up.
Yeah, because you overdid it
After that phone call
about your father.
I can't believe I'm
as old as he was.
Let me sit down here.
You'd have liked
him - my old man.
I'm sure.
And he'd have loved you.
My god. That guy was a charmer.
Mm, I know the type.
Yeah, we had a lot of fun.
But I'll tell you something.
Our family vacations were
nothing like this here.
One week a year in a rented
cottage on lake erie,
Spiders this big.
I just wish he could have
seen how things turned out.
Well, if you keep
going like this,
Maybe you can tell him yourself.
Or I can tell him,
Because you're about
to kill me, jay.
My legs, my arms,
my back -- everything is sore.
So, I wore you out, huh?
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't get cocky, old man.
When I sit down,
I can still get up.
Hey.
Okay. Come on.
Mm.
Come here. Come here.
The rest of the
trip went better.
Haley's room stopped spinning.
And the monkey?
There she is!
Hey!    Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, honey. Do you want
some eggs benedict?
So creamy.
No. No? Mm.
Jay got back to the
vacation he always wanted.
And mitch and cam managed
to do some sightseeing
At a working banana
plantation...
Lily!
...Where they promptly
lost lily again.
Why did you dress
her in jungle print?
Because I thought
it would be cute!
She's gonna think
she's back in vietnam.
Lily! Lily, honey!
Me and claire?
We...
We had a great time.
But we never did
get that honeymoon.
I ink I just expected
a little too much
From this vacation.
You were so sweet to try.
It was dumb.
Like you said,
the thrill is gone.
I never said that.
No, it's over.
But wait.
Put a few seconds
back on the clock.
The kid still has a few moves.
Oh, my god.
I figured out why we
couldn't have a honeymoon.
Because we never had a wedding.
Oh, my god.
I still can't tell if you
think this is lame or cool.
I think it's incredibly cool.
Looks like I finally get
to walk you down the aisle.
Daddy!
Ow! You better walk me.
Okay. I'll try.
We're here today to celebrate
The renewing of
the marriage vows
Of phil and claire.
On this day,
They've chosen to reaffirm
their love for each other.
You may kiss your bride.
Oh!
I present to you,
still as husband and wife,
Mr. And mrs. Dunphy.
* it's the eye of the tiger *
* it's the thrill of the fight *
* rising up to the
challenge of our rivals *
* and the last-known survivor
stalks his prey in the night *
* and he's watching
us all in the eye *
* of the tiger *
Thank you for choosing welccontinental
airlines.Ight from maui to los
angeles.
Thank you.
You know, honey,
If anything were
ever to happen to me,
I would want you
to get remarried.
Okay. Mm.
That was a little fast.
Oh, no. I ju--
I just want to make you happy.
Okay.
Any idea of who you
would marry if --
Vicki conroy, probably.
She works in my office.
She's very organized.
The kids love her.
Are you guys talking
about vicki?
Yeah.
Mom, she's awesome.
Just so you know, if something
were to happen to me, I --
Oh, something's gonna happen to you,
all right.
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net