What are you doing with those?
Luke and I are doing a recycling drive.
If we collect enough bottles,
They build a school in africa.
Wouldn't that be so cool
To go to a school made out of bottles?
That would certainly
be a special school.
Did you hear what I said, parents --
"special school"?
Okay. Nobody make a big deal about it,
But I just broke up with dylan.
No!
Oh, my gosh. Are you okay, honey?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just -- I need to date
someone who has a clue,
Instead of an idiot who bangs his head
Every time he rides his
bike out of his garage.
Every time.
I'm sorry, honey.
I'm sorry for both of you.
I'll have to text him later.
Mm. I got to jump in the shower.
I'm gonna be late.
Where are you going?
I'm going to meet my friend valerie.
I haven't seen her in 15 years.
We used to work together.
You worked? Mm-hmm.
I can't imagine you working.
Luke, let me tell you something.
That is very offensive to women.
Your mom works very hard --
Just now, she works for us.
I will have you know
That I had quite the
little career going.
I was an account manager
at starcrest hotels.
I had a little cubicle,
And I -- and I wore my
tennis shoes to work
And changed into my work pumps.
It was very "working girl."
That's movie's so cl. Mm-hmm.
I don't mind saying,
I was making quite a splash.
Well, then, why'd you quit?
Well, haley, call me old-fashioned,
But I wanted to focus
on raising a family,
So...I married your dad.
And five months later, we...
Were...Four months away
From having this little bundle of joy.
Mm-hmm.
there's my lawyer!
Gloria got into a little car accident,
So my dad asked me to help her out.
And, uh, this is the first time
That my dad's asked me for legal advice,
And it's -- it's nice.
It's nice to know that
that he respects me in that way.
Well, mitchell is an amazing lawyer.
My dream for him is that one day
He'll be on the supreme court.
Why, cam?
So at parties, I can tell everyone
My partner is one of the supremes.
There he is!
The steely, grizzled veteran
Ready to do battle with
the plucky upstart.
Speed versus grace.
Brute force versus --
Let's just do this.
Jay and I are both gym rats.
I love the sauna
that's the dry heat --
And the steam -- wet.
And, of course, I am just
a kook for racquetball --
Club champ two years in a row,
Tonganoxie, missouri, rec center.
So, naturally, jay and I
have been trying for months
To get together to bang the
old hollow rubber ball around.
I have been avoiding
this day like the plague.
I mean, part of going to the gym
is the locker-room atmosphere.
And if I'm there with a gay guy,
It's just not gonna be the same.
I mean, for me, it's a locker room.
For him, it's a showroom.
She doesn't get it.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
* I'll let you see my scar *
What the hell?
Some people call me a salesman.
I call myself a "salesfriend."
So, obviously,
I need strangers to trust me.
I don't take kindly to it
When someone tom sellecks my bus bench.
Phil dunphy.
Phil, it's barbara.
The pattersons want
to back ouof the deal.
Why?! What happened?!
The wife's getting cold feet.
I told her to call you.
Okay. Fine. I'll handle it.
I'm not losing this sale!
By the way -- I've spent
way too much time on it.
Um, phil, do you take
elm when you come to --
I saw it, barbara.
It's a terrific gym, jay.
Very liberal with the towels.
I love that.
Showers are private,
in case you're wondering.
I wasn't, but thanks for the heads-up.
Now, that's a surprise -- boxers.
Is that necessary?
Well, I just always pictured
you as a tighty-whitey guy
Well, do me a favor
the next time you picture me,
Leave the underwear out of it.
Well, don't you worry.
The only thing I'm picturing
Is how clean the floor is gonna be
When I'm done mopping it with you.
Is that the best you can do?
'cause it's gonna take a little more
Than some lame trash talk
to get me out of my --
Gah! What the hell was that?!
Our butts pressed against each other.
They didn't press. It was glancing.
Stop talking about it!
Oh, come on. All the time
you've spent in the locker room,
This can't be your first moon landing.
You got a name for it? It's very common.
You got off easy. At least it
didn't happen after a shower.
Enough. We call that a splashdown.
That's it. I'm changing in the stall.
Excuse me!
You had your arm around her
with that humpy look you get!
No, that's not always how you look!
We're over!
So, I'd really like to talk to you,
mrs. Patterson,
And see if we can't
turn this thing around.
Uh, you've got my number. Thank you.
I said we are over.
Why don't you go out
for a nice bike ride?!
Dylan again, huh?
Some guys just do not know how to play
it.
Dad, what are you doing?
Oh, right.
Just, uh, tes
t-driving my new soup strainer.
I dug it out of the Halloween stuff
To see what people think.
Do people want their real-estate advice
From someone who leads or
from someone who follows?
I'm betting these babies are
coming back in a big way.
Buy low, sell high.
People are gonna see this and say,
"that guy's high."
Sorry to bother you, sir.
We're doing work next
door and nicked a main,
So we're gonna have to
shut down your water.
Oh, okay. No problem.
Yeah, it shouldn't be too long.
And if you happen to need it,
there's a port-a-potty out front.
Thanks. Yeah.
Hey. Nice mustache.
yeah, man.
You too, brother.
"you too, brother."
Haley -- she's the oldest, 15.
And then alex is 13.
And that's my baby, luke.
He's 11. Can you believe it?
Oh, my god. They're gorgeous. Yeah.
And things are still good
with "phil the thrill?"
Yes. Things are great -- great with him.
I'm so happy for you. Really.
I'm so -- I'm so happy
that you're happy.
thank you.
Well, and you, too.
I mean, your life is --
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's talk about you. Okay
Because, you know, you're --
You chose the...Mother.
You're the mommy, the yomm
y-mommy-mama person. Uh-huh.
Kind of squeezing the
ring right into my finger.
Was I? A little.
I'm so sorry.
And just then, it hit me.
She was jealous of me.
Yes, there had always been
A little bit of a
competition between us.
This was more serious.
She was looking at my life
As something that she'd always wanted...
But never had.
So, how's life in the trenches?
You know, you still got the
bastards on the 23rd floor
Making life miserable
For all the people
actually doing the work.
Same as ever, right?
One -- one difference. Mm-hmm.
I'm one of them bastards now.
Wait, you're on the 23rd floor?
Well, I'm on the 24th floor.
Wow, that's insane.
It's -- it's no big deal.
I mean, if you hadn't left,
It probably would have been you.
I was driving along this street.
The cars were parked just like this,
And -- boom! -- Out of nowhere,
he hits me.
Okay, so, he -- he cut you off.
Yes. Right.
A crazy driver.
You know, I used to be
a little bit like that.
I don't know,
maybe it's because of lily,
But I've definitely
become more considerate.
Like, I used to never let
people in, and now I do.
I'm just now getting that metaphor.
Okay.
So, what do you think?
Were there any witnesses? No,
just manny.
He was in the back seat.
It all happened so fast,
just like they say.
Yeah.
All right, well,
this is what we're gonna do.
I'll take a few pictures, and then
we'll sit down and write a statement.
Perfect.
I'll go and get us a table. All right.
Manny, come.
Uh, just a minute, mom.
I need to tie my shoe.
Okay.
Mitchell. Yeah?
Don't talk. Listen.
It was her fault.
I'm -- I'm sorry, what?
Don't look at me.
Do something. Take pictures.
Manny!
What kind of cupcake do you want?
Uh, that's okay! I'm not hungry!
That was a mistake.
Now she'll know something's up.
Are you okay?!
I'm fine!
She cut that guy off.
She's a terrible driver.
She's a danger to us all.
Okay. Wait. Now stop.
I-I thought she said he was parked
And then he cut her off.
Everybody looks parked
When you're going 100 miles an hr!
Manny, why didn't you speak up?
She can't take criticism
about her driving.
Once, an old lady yelled
at her at a crosswalk.
She honked so long the horn ran out.
Manny!
I've said too much already.
Are you hearing this?
Aah...
Point.
Hinder!
Aah! Boom!
Lucky shot!
That is game!
And, believe, match.
Yep. Fine. You won.
But, you know, what do you expect?
For the first half of the game,
I was distracted by what
happened in the locker room.
And you're sure it's not because
I'm a fabulous racquetball player?
You're average,
but I was a little thrown
By you touching me, which is unnatural.
Not to you, of course.
No, to you, it's like rocket fuel.
Oh, sure. When you're gay,
You just walk around giving
butt bumps to everybody.
It's like a high-five. It a low-two.
You know what?
I'm gonna prove that you won
Only because I was distracted.
We're gonna have a rematch
right here, right now.
Do you want to go up
against me again? Yes.
No! Damn it!
Hello! Hey, dad.
Uh, did you know that the
accident was gloria's fault? Yes.
I mean, I wasn't there,
But she's a horrible driver.
If she hit 10 cars,
I wouldn't be surprised.
If you knew that it was her fault,
Why did you get me involved?
Because someone has to tell her
She's in the wrong,
and better you than me.
That's great. I --
Here I am thinking that my dad
actually respects me as lawyer,
And, really, you're just
throwing me to the wolves.
Can't it be both?
Okay, dad, it doesn't
it doesn't bother you in the least
That your gay son's the
only one tough enough
To stand up to your wife?
Go get 'em, rocky. See you later.
Your father and I had a moon
landing in the locker room!
What's the matter with you?
What about you?
I mean, did you ever get
serious with anyone?
Thank you.
Oh, no. Not yet.
Ohh. Honey, you will.
Oh, no. I hope not. It's -- it's fun.
I'm sorry. I'm just
I'm waiting for some news.
What news?
I'm -- I'm up for the paris job.
The -- the head of the
international division?!
That's -- that's -- that's crazy.
Yeah, no, I mean, I'll never get it,
But it'd be great, 'cause --
Well, 'cause one of my
lovers lives in paris.
Oh.
I-I don't know what jumps
out of that sentence more,
You know, "lovers" or "one of."
Well, I'm single.
I mean, it's kind of what you do.
Uh-huh. I have one in paris.
Oh.
Um, I have paris, new york, miami...
I have a fourth one.
I'm forgetting my lover.
Last night, I vacuumed
the radiator thingy
Under the fridge, you know,
That collects the dust,
'cause you should,
And I don't, so...
oh, hey. Hold on.
Cross your fingers.
I'm not gonna lie.
The thought of valerie getting
the one job in the whole company
That everyone coveted -- well,
I wasn't a lover of that.
Okay. Okay, thank you.
Well?
Oh, they haven't made a decision.
They're -- they're
gonna tell me later on.
That's not what they said, is it?
Oh, yeah. It is. It is.
Oh, valerie, come on. It's me.
What are friends for
If not to be there for you
when you get bad news?
I got it! Oh, my god!
aah!
I'm the head of europe!
Well, you know, for the hotel,
Not the continent,
But...Yay!
Kind of, though. Kind of.
Why didn't you tell me when you
when you first heard?
Ohh...
'cause, you know.
And that's when it really hit me.
Valerie wasn't jealous of me.
She pitied me.
And part of me wanted to
take her back to the house
And show her everything she was missing
In her sad, childless, husbandless life.
But there's a little thing called "
taking the high road."
Why don't you come by
and meet everybody?
Oh, sure. Yeah, no, that'd be great.
Yeah, I mean, alex is just a genius,
And haley is turning into
this beautiful young woman.
And it makes me realize that motherhood
Is probably the most important
san francisco.
That was my fourth lover.
San francisco. "fourth lover."
It would have kept me up all night.
Yeah.
Dad, look.
Just a sec, buddy. I'm on my way
out to the bathroom. Check it out.
The aubreys had this
huge party last night,
And we got all these bottles to recycle.
Great!
What's jagermeister?
Um...
Well, you know how in a fairy tale
There's alwa a potion
That makes the princess fall asleep
And then the guys start kissing her?
Well, this is like that,
Except you don't wake up in a castle.
You wake up in a frat house
with a bad reputation.
Haley!
Luke, you're spilling it!
Aw, crud!
God!
Aah! Gross! A rat!
cool.
Hang on, I'm coming!
I believe you have something
that belongs to me --
My heart.
I thought I I.M.'d you to stay away.
Ow!
Haley!
Hello?
Dylan?
D-money?
Hey, buddy?
Hey, buddy?!
Hello, friendly neighbors!
Little help?
But I love you!
Well, you should have thought about that
Before you took that
skank sharon nicolini
To an anne hathaway movie!
I didn't take her. She was just there.
So you were just there by yourself
At ananne h!
I don't think so!
Yeah! Yeah. I like her movies.
She's everywoman!
Come on. Let's not fight.
Let's just discuss this like two u
n-immature adults.
Ugh!
oh. Oh.
Hello? Mrs. Patterson.
Hi. I've been waiting for your call.
Yeah.
Um, is there any chance
That maybe we could talk a little bit --
No, no. Now's perfect. That's fine.
I-I'm sorry. I couldn't hear you.
Let me just... Close my office door.
there we go. Much, much better.
Put the ducks on a row.
You're such a good lawyer.
Uh, yeah, I just want to make sure
We're 100% clear on
exactly what happened.
Oh, we're clear. I told you.
What? You don't believe me?
No! No! I just --
You know, sometimes.
Like, is it possible, maybe,
you were driving too fast?
Who said I was driving fast?
Yeah. Who?
I just -- I'm lookinat the street,
And I'm thinking if you
were driving a little fast,
It's possible that maybe
you didn't see the car --
You're like everyone else, huh?
You blame the latino driver.
Where I come from, they always
blame the latino driver.
Where you come from,
isn't everybody a latino driver?
Manny, tell him.
I can't 'cause I have
cupcake in my mouth.
Oh, come on! Don't blame your cupcake!
What? You think I'm guilty, too?
No. Fine.
I don't need you as a lawyer anymore.
And if you two think
I'm such a bad driver,
You're safer walking home!
Ciao!
Here it is.
It's really cute!
Yeah. We're pretty proud of it.
Here's your stupid cds!
And your clothes! And your poems!
Don't you do it!
Haley! I'm doing it!
Haley, stop it! What are you doing?!
Tearing out my heart!
Okay. Haley: Oh,
why don't you go get a hickey
From sharon nicolini?!
It's from my guitar strap, haley!
Oh, thanks for reminding me!
Um, my daughter haley and
her boyfriend, dylan, um...
This is a nice color.
Yeah. Um, listen.
This is not normal with all that, nor --
Where's that liquor smell?
Phil, honey?
Oh, my god. Luke? What is that?
Jagermeister.
Dad says it makes girls easier to kiss.
What happened to the rug?!
I had an accident.
Okay. Alex, what are you doing?
I'm trying to kill a rat.
Oh...
Sharon was helping me buy
you a birthday present!
Don't you get it?
! I love your ass!
I -- you know, I-I-I'm late.
And I should go. I know.
I know. Yeah.
And it seems like things
Have gotten a little wonky around here.
I don't know where phil is.
He's definitely --
Oh, my god!
Alex!
Where is your father?
He went outside to go to the bathroom.
Uh-huh. Oh!
it's not usually like this.
Oh, gross.
Let's just get married.
Okay.
You will not regret this decision,
mrs. Patterson.
And I'll tell you what --
We're gonna have you over to our
little house to celebrate, okay?
Okay. Buh-bye.
Sometime when you get a break,
maybe -- claire!
Claire! Phil.
Hey. Phil, what are you -- what are you
doing?
Just concluding a little business.
Very successfully, I might add.
Honey.
Hey. Hi.
Is that valerie? Yeah.
Whoa!
You look fantastic.
Thank you. Come here!
Oh... Get over here!
Okay. I'll...
How long's it been?
A long time. Oh, my goodness.
Oh, I can't touch you. Okay.
A little bit difficult.
The gulf divides us, eh?
So nice to see you.
Great to see you, though. Okay.
All right. Okay, then.
Thanks for coming by.
It's such a pleasure. Buh-bye.
Thanks for stopping by.
You have a beautiful family.
Yeah.
She looks great, doesn't she?
What is on your face?
One time!
Once!
One time I bring somebody
home who I want to impress,
And what do I find?!
A bunch of booze-drenched hill people!
You're sitting around in your underwear
And -- and chasing rats
And -- and fornicating in the stairwell?
Can I say something? No!
No, you can't, mario.
The is nothing left
to say but thank you.
Thank you all.
Ow!
I told you I'd win!
Not talking so much now,
are you, hotshot?
Hope you enjoy that nice hot shower.
But it's not gonna wash away the
shame of that 15-7 beatdown.
you should have seen
the look on your face
When that drop shot
just kissed the wall.
Ah. Okay.
Splashdown. Got me again. Yep.
Make the uptight straight
guy all embarrassed,
Except for one thing
doesn't even bother me anymore.
I could do this all day.
Here. Another one for you.
Maybe a couple of them.
Jay, I just noticed the sauna back here.
How big of a hurry are we in?
Biggest hurry of your life.
Scuse me. Scuse me.
Well, if you're going to be stranded,
Might as well be in a
place full of cupcakes.
I don't think you need any more.
Ay.
I'm sorry, guys.
It's true. I am a
defensive driver.
You mean you're defensive about --
I know what I am.
Let's go.
It's just that I don't like
When people just assume that I'm a bad
driver.
Maybe it was just like a little bit my
fault.
Well, you know, I'm glad
you can admit that, gloria.
Ay. But I'm still gonna need
you as my lawyer, mitch.
Why? Because this one --
It was not my fault.
I promise you.
That's what that sound was.
It was the big cupcake.
That was unreal. Mom was crazy.
I'm scared.
Look...
I know your mom pretty well. She's fine.
I'd be willing to bet she's
just composing herself,
Taking a nice, lg,
peaceful walk in the park.
Perfect.
At that moment, all I wanted
was to be with my family.
But of course, that meant
finding a way to apologize
To the people that I had
belittled and rejected.
Okay, you are so crazy.
That song totally rules.
Dad, you're crazy.
Crazy right.
Hey, honey. Hi.
Hey, mom.
No, seriously, dad. It's lame.
Seriously, luke. It's not.
Here, you got some mustard
or something on your face.
I think I know a little bit about music.
I was a deejay in college.
I had my own show in the
coveted time slot --
"daybreak with dunphy."
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not kidding you.
And I played rick astley.
Dad, that -- that's embarrassing.
* never gonna... *
Sing it, luke.
They could have been petty.
They really could have made me pay,
but they didn't.
And I've never loved them more.
Why the hell couldn't valerie have seen
them like that?
Hey, dylan.
Hey, mr. Dunphy.
What's happening?
Well, haley and i got
into another fight.
Oh. Yeah.
"say anything..."
Um, "good morning"?
No, "say anything..."
"newspaper."
No, dylan. "say anything...
" clutch movie.
"clutch movie."
She probably won't be up
for a couple hours still.
It's okay. It's not that heavy.
* do me *
* underneath the moonlight *
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net