Okay, your brother's lunch
is packed. You're buying
your own lunch.
Luke, Alex, come on.
Let's go.
There he is. Last chance
for the summer handshake.
[Imitates Explosion]
Dad.
Come on.
We're only halfway done.
I need help.
I was supposed to keep
a journal all summer.
It's due today.
Wow, first day of school
and you're already behind?
I'm dead.
All right. Tell me how far
you've gotten.
Okay.
- "June 21. Found a stick."
- Mmm.
"June 22."
That's it.
That's it?
It was
a really cool stick.
He's right.
It looked like a snake.
Getting everybody out of
the house in the morning
can be really tough,
especially
the first day of school.
From the minute we get up
at 7:00 till we drop 'em off
at school, it is go, go, go.
I get up at 6:00.
[Laughs]
I get up at 5:00.
Seriously.
I get up at 6:00.
That's you?
I thought we had a raccoon.
I can't believe my little boy
is going into the fifth grade.
He used to hold my finger with
his little hand and look at me
with those big eyes.
Mi niño pequeño, Jay.
Yup, they grow up.
Come on, Manny.
Let's get going.
How's my hair?
Hold on.
What are you wearing there?
That looks like
an old Christmas tree skirt.
It's a traditional
Colombian poncho.
I want my new classmates to know
I'm proud of my heritage.
I think you look very handsome.
Lindo.
Oh, really?
Am I driving him to school
or is he gonna ride his burro?
♪ You are a cutie pie
Yes, you are ♪
♪ You are a cutie pie ♪
Are you still
baby-proofing?
Everything we own is pointy.
Why is our daughter
dressed like Donna Summer?
She is not Donna Summer.
Clearly she's Diana Ross
from the R.C.A. Years.
How is Daddy
not seeing that?
- I really thought
you were done with this.
- I made no such promises.
I guess I'm somewhat
of a shutterbug.
Yes.
And my new favorite model,
of course, is Lily.
I just completed
a series of photographs of her
dressed as various pop icons.
Let's see. I've done
Olivia Newton-John.
I've done Madonna,
the early years,
Stevie Wonder-
Yeah, there are days when Lily
has more costume changes than Cher.
Cher!
How could I forget Cher?
That's embarrassing.
That's embarrassing?
[Man]
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ Hey, hey
Hey, hey ♪
Hey ♪♪
[Grunts]
Honey, you moving out?
Five more years.
A little help here?
This is why
we suggested the violin.
A cello is more in demand
in university orchestras.
You know what's not
in demand?
Oh, what?
Girls who play
in university orchestras.
Ha, ha, ha.
Here, I'll help you
carry it out to the curb.
Okay. Here.
Phil, put on some pants.
Come on!
This covers up more
than my bathing suit.
And don't remind me.
Haley, honey-
Don't forget, the driving instructor
is picking you up from school.
Can't he pick me up
someplace else?
I don't want kids at school
thinking I'm dating...
a 40-year-old driving instructor
who's not even cute.
Haley just got her
learner's permit.
We've been taking turns
driving with her.
One of the really standard
rules of the road...
is we want to keep
a safe distance between us
and the car in front.
And that is not safe
right there. Not safe.
Right.
Okay, merge.
I-
Merge. Merge!
[Horn Honking]
Merge! Merge! Merge!
Stop it!
You're freaking me out!
This navigation system
is all messed up.
It thinks we're in a park.
Oh, my God!
It is a park!
Away from the kids!
Aim for the lake!
Oh, my God!
Makes you realize
we're all just hanging
by a thread.
The last thing Manny needs
on his first day of school...
is you "undermelting"
his confidence.
- Undermining.
- Now you're doing it to me too.
I'm sorry, but there's
only two places anyone
should wear a poncho-
Niagara Falls
and log rides.
You think too much
about these things.
I wear all sort of daring
outfits all the time,
and people admire them because
I wear them with the confidence.
Yeah, I'm sure it's the confidence
they're admiring.
[Chuckling]
I just- I just think
it's a little over-the-top.
You know what?
You need to loosen up
and have fun.
I am loose. I'm fun.
Remember, uh, breakfast
for dinner last week?
My idea.
Ever since
we brought Lily home,
you've been tense.
All you do is
put child locks on things,
read parenting books.
Would you please stop and-
Here, just hold your daughter.
Hold her and relax.
All right, sweetheart,
come on.
Just relax.
Aw, sweetheart.
Ohh. Did you put
hair spray on this?
Just a little bit.
I'm gonna put some music on.
Cam, I have to go to work.
Dance with her.
Put a little boogie in it.
♪♪ [Disco]
Oh, come on.
Just dance.
You know you love this song.
This is actually
a really good song.
All right. Okay.
- Who's a dancing queen, huh?
- ♪♪ [Continues]
Put a little boogie in it.
See? Fun, right?
[Thud]
Oh, my-
Was that her head?
No, I think if it was
her head, she would be-
[Crying]
Yeah, it was her head.
Okay. Okay.
Yes. Yes, I know.
I got Boo-boo Bear
from the freezer.
Why do you have chocolate
on your face?
It was under a pie.
So you ate your way to it?
I made a judgment call.
You weren't there.
Do you think she's all right?
She didn't cry that much.
Maybe that's a bad sign.
You know, we should try
and make her laugh.
Why?
That's how we'll know
she's okay. Where's Doggy?
[Cameron]
Doggy. Doggy.
Here, Doggy.
There you go.
Moo!
- But it's a dog.
- I know. That's why it's funny.
Moo.
I don't think it's as funny
as you think it is.
Can we please
just call your sister?
No, no. Cam- Cam-
Why? So she can be all
judgmental and condescending,
like she's the expert
and I don't know how
to take care of a baby?
Mitchell, she is your family.
Of course she's gonna be
judgmental and condescending.
[Line Ringing]
[Phone Rings]
Hello?
Hey, hi, um-
Not a big deal.
Just wondering.
When your kids were small,
did you ever-
I don't know-
smack their heads into a wall?
Usually we just gave
time-outs.
No, no, accidentally.
Um, we just kind of
bonked Lily's head.
It wasn't very hard and she's
not acting any differently,
but I just worry-
Relax.
It happens.
Luke used to bang his head
all the time and he's fine.
Okay, all right, thank you.
Thanks. That helps.
Okay, okay.
[Whispering]
We gotta take her to the doctor.
Load up the car.
- Gloria?
- I'm here.
I, uh, just dropped Manny off
at school, and I realized...
I just dropped Manny off
at school.
Oh, boy.
And I was hoping we'd still
have a few more good years
before the mind started to go.
No, what I'm saying,
we have the day to ourselves,
the first time in months.
We should take advantage of it.
Go to the club, nice lunch,
some massages.
What about work?
I'm the boss.
Since I married you,
people are surprised
I come in at all.
[Chuckles]
Jay's very spontaneous.
He's always surprising me
with little presents,
fun getaways.
I wasn't the greatest husband
the first time around, but I'm
trying to do better this time.
And maybe
by my third marriage,
I'll have it down pat.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, that one's
gonna cost me.
What ya reading there?
A book?
Yeah. I've been meaning
to get to it for a while.
Ooh, it's got a map
at the beginning.
I like it when books do that.
Mm-hmm.
Don't you have an open house
this morning?
I rescheduled.
Thought you might
like some company.
[Grunts]
Well, the first day of school
can be tough for stay-at-home moms.
Now, you have to understand,
the kids are gone,
the nest is empty.
They are rudderless.
And a lot of guys
wouldn't even notice,
but I'm not a lot of guys.
I listen with my mind,
and if you pay attention,
women will tell you
what they want...
by telling you
the opposite of what they want.
The other day, Claire was, like,
"You have to move your car.
There's no space in the garage
for both of our cars."
And what she's really saying is
that, you know, I should
probably get a sports car.
I was sort of looking forward
to a quiet day.
Thought I'd just read,
maybe go for a run later,
that's it.
Great.
We'll run together.
You don't have to
do that.
I know.
Listening.
The thing is,
I like to run alone.
And I run kinda fast,
so-
So?
So I'm not sure you're gonna
be able to keep up with me.
[Laughing]
You're kid-
You're kidding, right?
No.
You really think
I can't keep up with you?
I'm not sure you can keep up
with this conversation.
I think you're forgetting that
I power-walk every morning...
and that I wear my special shoes
with the big soles,
which were designed
by a doctor.
Yes, I know.
But I run every day.
You really think
you can run as fast as me?
No, Phil, I think I can
run much, much faster...
than you.
Boom. Just like that,
the whole day changed.
It was game on.
She knew it. I knew it.
We both knew it.
[Sighs]
I just wanna read.
I think I'II order
what I had the last time.
What was that called?
You want me to say it because
you want me to roll my R's.
Come on!
Reuben.
[Giggles]
[Chuckling]
- Jay, what is this?
- Oh, looks like my old car cover.
Don't give me that.
This is Manny's poncho.
What is it doing here?
- Maybe he decided to take
it off on the way to school.
- What did you say to him?
Nothing.
I... told some jokes.
You say plenty with your jokes.
Jay, he looks up to you.
He respects your opinion.
We dodged a bullet on this.
Trust me. I've been
down this road before.
I remember one time
Mitchell decided to wear
a jaunty scarf to school.
I kept my mouth shut.
He got his jaunty butt kicked.
My dad has this perception that
I was very flamboyant as a kid,
which is just- it's nonsense,
because I kept
the whole gay thing
very under wraps.
You know,
I was just a guy's guy.
I was basically a jock.
You know?
So we should crush
Manny's spirit...
and destroy everything
that makes him who he is.
I'm just saying,
it's no fun to see your kid
get picked on every day,
getting tormented
just because he's different.
I'm telling you,
it rips your heart out.
Well, Batman
doesn't get picked on
and he wears a cape.
A poncho is just a cape
that goes all the way around.
Batman doesn't get picked on
because he's a muscular genius.
Manny can't make it
to the top bunk.
We're taking this poncho to
Manny at school. It's important
that he knows we support him.
And then we go
get those massages,
because that sounds good.
[Engine Starts]
[Footsteps Clomping]
I always take the stairs
two at a time. I don't even
think about it anymore.
The regular way
would seem weird.
Phil, let it go.
I'm faster than you.
If only there was some way
we could settle this
once and for all.
But how?
Huh.
You seriously
wanna race me?
I ran a half-marathon
last year.
Wow.
I'm half-scared.
Okay, we do
need to do this.
I'll go change.
Not now.
I got a conference call.
But how about after that?
- Great. This afternoon.
- Sweet.
Two at a time, two at a ti-
[Stumbles]
Son of a- Gotta fix that step!
Two at a time!
Already at the top, so-
Hi, I'm Dr. Miura.
I'm on call today.
Looks like we have
a little head bump.
Yeah, it happened
a couple hours ago
on a- on a doorjamb.
Uh, ouch.
We used to do
this thing in school...
where they would give you an egg
and you couldn't break it.
And it was supposed to
teach you how hard it was
to be a parent.
But the real thing,
i-it's so much harder.
You know?
We did that in my school too.
Didn't turn out so well.
I went through a dozen eggs.
Yeah, well,
he's a nervous eater.
No, I broke
a dozen eggs.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I just assumed that-
I know.
I know
what you assumed.
There doesn't seem
to be any mark.
Well, her head
was somewhat protected.
Protected?
- Was she wearing a hat?
- Yes, yes, like a hat.
It was a wig, actually.
Sort of a ghetto-fabulous
Afro thing.
I thought it might be
medically relevant.
Really?
You thought "ghetto-fabulous"
might be medically relevant?
Maybe I should just
finish with the exam.
Yes, thanks.
You'll be pleased to know
that Mitchell and I
intend on raising Lily...
with influences
from her Asian heritage.
That is fantastic.
Have you noticed any vomiting
since the head bump?
Uh, no.
No, no, no.
We've hung some art
in her room.
Some Asian art.
And then when she's
ready for solid food,
there's a fantastic
pho place...
right around the corner
from our house.
Am I pronouncing that right?
Is it pho? It's a soup.
I don't know.
I'm from Denver.
We don't have
a lot of pho there.
Uh, just to be sure,
could you show me
how hard Lily got hit?
And use your head.
Um, yeah. Really, it was-
it was just sorta,
like, uh-
You know?
Could I
see that again?
Um, it was just-
just a head bump,
you know.
How are you feeling?
Uh, fine.
So is Lily.
Babies are designed
to survive new parents,
so stop worrying.
You guys are doing great.
Thank you.
Denver.
[Bell Ringing]
I don't see any ponchos,
which means either the kids
don't wear them or the ones
who do wear them disappear.
We're doing
the right thing.
I support Manny
no matter what.
Children need to know
that you believe in them.
It's the most important thing.
If you tell them they have wings,
they will believe they can fly.
Oh, really?
I had a buddy,
went to Woodstock,
believed he could fly.
Didn't end great.
It's why hotel windows
don't open anymore.
Is something wrong?
Who's died?
No one, Manny.
Why would you
even think that?
In Colombia,
Manny went to Pablo Escobar
Elementary School.
If you were pulled out of class,
it was definitely to identify a body.
Well, we got
your poncho here.
I thought you said
it made me look like my neck
was wearing a dress.
That was a joke.
Oh, good!
It's still in the pocket!
What do you got there,
buddy?
My pan flute.
I'm going to play
some Colombian folk music
for my new classmates.
Huh. Great.
[Door Closes]
I have never been
more proud of you.
I'm sure your friends
are gonna love it.
Break the flute.
What?
The poncho by itself is fine.
The poncho, plus the flute,
plus the stupid dance-
my son will die a virgin.
That's right.
Hey, sport,
can I take a look
at that whistle?
Oh, geez.
Look at that.
And now
you stepped on it!
What?
Oh, darn!
[Crunch]
What's wrong with me?
Here, let me get it.
Thank you.
You know- Actually,
maybe you should do this.
Why?
I don't want to bump her head
against the door, you know,
pinch her with the seat belt.
Mitchell, how long are you
gonna beat yourself up
over one mistake?
Is this going to be
like the blond highlights
all over again?
I just- I think
I suck at being a father.
What are you talking about?
We're new at this.
Yeah, but you're such a natural.
I mean, look at you.
You walk into the room
and she lights up.
Y-You change her diaper
with one hand. I-
Nice.
I-I'm actually jealous of you.
There are so many things
that you do that I can't.
Y-You baby-proofed
the entire house.
You took care of all
the adoption paperwork.
Without you,
we wouldn't even have
a baby to injure.
Just a couple of forms.
Actually, that was
a lot of paperwork.
And you got her
on all those preschool
waiting lists.
Can't believe
you were gonna wait
until she was "old enough."
You see, that's what
makes us a great team.
We each have
our own strengths.
Now, who are
amazing parents?
We are.
I can't hear you.
We are!
Don't you forget it.
Okay.
Did we just lock our baby
in the car?
Did you put the keys in the bag?
I put the keys in the bag.
Oh, Mitchell, I told you not
to put the keys in the bag!
Come on!
Don't freak out!
Lily, it's okay!
♪ A-B-C-D-E-F- ♪
What, are you singing to her?
People get arrested for this.
♪ H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P ♪
Do all four doors lock?
Do you have a phone?
What?
♪♪ [Headset: Pop]
I didn't say anything.
Couldn't hear ya.
I'm cranking
one of my mash-ups.
Ah.
Hey, hey!
There they are.
How was the first day
back in prison?
Fine.
Yep.
What are you guys
doing?
Your mom and I
are racing to the mailbox
on Sequoia and back.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Oh, she knows.
[Chuckles]
Hey, buddy. Soon as I'm done...
kicking a little Mom butt here,
how about I school you
in some Mario Kart?
Can't.
Gotta work on my journal.
Lame!
Hey, uh, Alex. You?
Uh, I have a history paper.
Well, if you wanna see
a little history
being made right here-
[Alex]
Not really.
Okay.
[Door Closes]
Ready?
Are you?
I was born ready.
I came outta the womb wearing
tiny little golden wings-
Go!
[Shrieking]
I'm breaking the window!
[Woman]
Emergency assistance.
This is Trina.
Help! We I-
We locked our baby in the car
and people are judging us!
I swear to God,
I'm gonna break it!
Do not break the window!
You'll get glass on her!
Please tell your wife to relax.
Everything is going to be okay.
That's a man.
Really?
Don't worry, Lily!
Daddy's coming for you!
Sir, we just sent the signal.
The door should be unlocked now.
Check- Check the door.
Check the door.
It's not unlocked!
Oh. Oh.
Okay.
That is amazing.
How did they do that?
I don't know. It's just-
We got it. Thank you.
Did that come from space?
[Claire]
I run five miles a day. I have
a resting heart rate of 48.
There is no way I'm going
to lose a two-mile race
to Johnny Ski Pole.
[Gasping]
Saving my energy,
drafting off of you.
You feeling cocky?
Yeah, I am.
[Laughs]
Love it.
But after seeing that T-shirt,
I realized something.
The first day of school
is tough on all my kids,
especially
the one I married.
Boop-boop-boop!
Afterburners engaged!
Whoo!
Don't choke on my smoke!
And down the stretch
he goes.
I don't believe it!
Daddy wins!
Do you believe in miracles?
U.S.A., U.S. -
Oh, no!
[Haley]
Oh, Jesus!
[Gasps]
Oh, my- What was that?
Was that a person?
I'm good!
I'm good.
Dad?
Honey, are you okay?
I'm good.
Whoo!
You're getting better,
sweetheart.
Did I lose the race
to make him feel better?
Maybe.
But it just seemed like
he could use a win today.
We do strange things
for the people we love.
We lie to them,
we lie for them.
There may be some bumps
along the way, but we never
stop wanting the best for them.
That's what makes it
such a tough job.
Kind of the best job
in the world.
What are you doing?
Turn your eyes on the road!
Oh, my God!
[Siren Blaring]
Okay. Okay.
Uh-oh.
All right, sweetie,
this happens.
Remain calm.
That's the first thing.
Pull over right here.
I'll get out the registration.
Mom, I don't like cops.
Pull over right there.
I don't like cops.
I can't pull over.
You need to pull over!
No can do.
No can do!
Phil!
I got priors.
Parking ticket from the mall.
I never paid the parking ticket.
Keep moving, sweetheart.
Dad agrees with me.
I can speed up.
- This is not a movie!
Haley, pull over!
- [Siren Blaring]
ENGLISH - US - PSDH
www.tvsubtitles.net