It's just until grandma
can see them.
My neck hole
is too small.
Mine's itchy.
I'd rather be itchy
than choky.
Come on, phil.
Hurry up.
Okay, here we go.
Connecting.
[ muffled ]
come in, florida! Over!
Mom? Dad?
Hello, phillip.
[ chuckles ]
All:
Merry christmas eve!
A little --
little lower, dad.
[ deeper voice ]
merry christmas eve.
[ chuckles ]
Thank you --
thanks for the sweaters!
[ normal voice ]
oh, you're welcome.
You look beautiful in them.
Where's mom?
Mom is sinking fast.
Uh-oh.
She's in the bathtub.
[ laughter ]
They have that claw foot.
I know, yeah.
Hey, pops,
here's the tree.
And, uh, there --
there's the, uh --
There's the ornament
you sent us.
Right here.
There are the stockings,
Hung by the chimney
by claire.
Oh, still funny, son.
[ laughter ]
What the hell is that?
What is that? That looks like
a cigarette burn.
Was one of you smoking
a cigarette?
No.      No.
No.         No.
Which one of you
was smoking?
Not me.
I have a respiratory problem.
Obviously,
it wasn't you.
Now I've got a family of liars
and smokers.
Honey, come here.
You got to see this.
Did you shoplift
your christmas presents, too?
Haley,
keep that ugly sweater on.
Anyway...
Merry christmas!
-- Sync by honeybunny --
www.addic7ed.com
[ television plays ]
Are you crying?
What are you, a robot?
It's a deeply
emotional movie.
Manny, mi amor, I need you
to help me in the kitchen.
We got to finish this first,
gloria.
The kid's never seen
"miracle on 34th street."
That's because he always spends
christmas in colombia
With my family.
And all we see there is "salazar
and el oso save christmas."
Sounds like a classic.
It is.
Mom,
can we finish the movie?
Okay.
[ television plays ]
Aah!
What the hell is that?
[ laughs ]
inocente!
What the hell?
When you told me we were going
to watch this movie,
I got a joke copy
from the internet.
You are the inocente!
Well, maybe I'm
a little confused right now.
What is
this inocente stuff?
In colombia, practical jokes
are a christmas tradition.
The one that is fooled
is the inocente!
We tell practical jokes
on April fool's day.
Do not do that again.
[ laughs ]
Inocente.
Does it do it again?
Ah, it's ruined.
Are you kidding me
with this line?
I'm gonna ask santa for the last
45 minutes of my life back.
Oh, would you cheer up?
We're in santa's village
with our daughter.
Where were we
a year ago?
Uh, we were at the beginning
of this line.
Okay, you know what?
Somebody needs to get
in the holiday --
Son of a bitch.
[ carolers' song plays ]
Maybe it's not them.
Oh, it's them.
It's them.
Three years ago,
I formed a caroling group.
We were known as
"the greensleevers."
We would perform
at charity events, hospitals.
And they were very,
very popular.
Uh, last year...
One of my carolers --
andrew...
Staged a little coup...
And, he, um...
They kicked cameron
out of the group.
[ carolers' song plays ]
[ applause ]
thank you.
We're
the new greensleevers.
The new greensleevers.
Is there a slap mark
on my face?
I mean, why is edna
singing the low harmony?
It's like people
are applauding out of shock.
Let it go.
Okay, next.
Oh, finally.
Whoa.
Chuckles ]
Um, I'm sorry.
Can I -- could -- could you...
What happened
to the other santa?
Listen, we've been
waiting in this line
for a really long time,
And we just want a santa
that actually looks like santa.
Mitchell, it's okay.
No, no, no, cam.
It's not okay.
This is lily's
first christmas.
I want to make sure
everything is perfect.
And we're gonna wait
for the fat santa.
I knew this would happen.
I-I don't even know why
we hired this guy.
See?
Even his elves agree with me.
Thank you.
I didn't know christmas
made you so petty.
[ carolers' song plays ]
[ coughs ]
lackluster!
[ coughs ] I hate you!
This is unacceptable.
And I want to know
whdid this.
Hmm?
Nobody, huh?
I guess the couch did it
to itself.
I guess it came home after
a tough day, lit up a cigarette,
And then it burned itself.
Is that what happened?
Because that makes no sense.
If whoever is responsible
doesn't come forward,
Your father and I are just gonna
have to punish all three of you.
What?
Yeah.
That's not fair.
I can forgive the smoking,
But I can't forgive
the lie...
Phil.
Or the smoking.
No one wants to confess,
huh?
No?
That's fine.
'cause you know
what happens next?
We cancel christmas.
[ haley chuckles ]
Luke:
That's not fair.
Okay, dad, sure.
Phil has a habit of making
big pronouncements to the kids.
[ chuckles ]
One time I told luke
That if he didn't put his
dirty dishes in the dishwasher,
We would put them
in his bed.
Phil's problem
is follow-through.
We had no more dishes,
So we were eating cere
out of the goldfish bowl.
Okay,
guess where I'm headed.
To take down the tree.
That's right.
Come on, guys.
Whoever did is,
just take responsibility.
Don't put the rest of us
through this.
Luke? No?
This is really it,
okay?
Here we go.
3...2...1...
Okay.
Goodbye, dunphy christmas.
Haley, I guess
you're not getting that car.
I was getting a car?!
No, I was lying,
because that's what we do now.
Dunphys are liars.
I mean, what's with them
tossing out candy canes
after every carol?
It's pandering.
I think you made that clear
when you tossed them back.
Okay, how am I supposed to get
all this in the car?
Let me give you a hand
with that.
Uh, thanks.
Thanks -- thanks, santa.
Can't call me that anymore.
Just got canned.
Oh. Really?
Guess a couple of people
complained I wasn't fat enough.
Well, that's terrible.
That'shat I get for trying not
to have a second heart attack.
There you go.
Always a way to make room.
Take it from someone
who lives in his car.
Um...Oh, well,
thank you so much.
No problem.
Merry christmas.
Um, wait, wait.
Um, please, let me give you
a little something.
For -- for your troubles.
No, that's okay.
No, really, that's okay.
Do you really live
in your car?
Yeah, it's not so bad.
It's pretty roomy
since the wife moved out.
Well...
Why don't you come over
to our place for dinner tonight?
Seriously?
Yeah, it's christmas eve.
You -- you can't spend it
in your car.
Wow, that's really nice
of you guys.
Listen,
can I bring anything?
Ketchup,
soy sauce, straws?
We're good.
So, uh, why don't you follow us
to our house?
Okay.
In your house.
[ chuckles ]
All right.
Cameron.
What?
Okay, tonight 9:00 sharp,
we open one present each --
Pajamas,
which we sleep in.
Tomorrow morning, 7:00 a.M.,
Manny on the stairs
for the christmas picture.
Then we open presents.
In colombia,
they open presents at midnight
And stay up till morning.
I'm sure that they do,
But as you'll notice from the
absence of goats in the street,
We are not in colombia.
[ chuckling ]
come on, I'm kidding.
Why can't we mix a couple
of colombian traditions in?
Like what?
Like fireworks.
Come on, you don't have
fireworks in colombia.
You're trying to make me
the inocente again.
No, we do.
At night, the sky is beautiful,
very christmasy.
That doesn't make
any sense.
Look, every country
has their own traditions.
In our culture,
for example,
The baby jesus is the one
that brings the gifts,
Not the santa claus.
But that doesn't
make sense.
How could a newborn baby
carry all those prents?
They don't even know
where their hands are.
At least a baby
can fit through a chimney.
How would you sit
on the baby jesus' lap?
You'd squish it.
Manny, next year,
we'll talk about
Some of your little
colombian traditions, okay?
Maybe.
I know what "maybe" means.
It's like you're trying
to take away my whole christmas.
I can't believe
it's all gone.
Dad never follows through.
Are you sure one of your friends
didn't burn the couch?
Hey, don't look at me.
Only one of us was ever caught
playing with matches.
Luke.
That was a year ago.
Just admit you did it.
You admit you did it!
Okay.
Look, I have an idea.
Do you remember the movie
"spartacus"?
Here's what we do --
Luke, you tell mom and dad
it's your fault.
I didn't do it.
It doesn't matter,
because after you coess,
Haley and I will each confess
to the same thing.
How does that do anything?
They'll be so touched
that we're protecting each other
That they'll have
to bring back christmas.
That's awesome.
How does it work again?
We're gonna pass
into legend --
The parents
who canceled christmas.
I thought you'd be happy.
They'll write songs
about us,
Make one of those
christmaspecials
With those ugly little
clay people.
You're the one
who always says
I shouldn't be sa pushover
with the kids.
So this is where you decide
to make your stand?
Really, phil?
Okay, okay, look,
don't worry.
We're going
to have christmas.
We raised our kids right.
Whoever did it
will come forward...
Or the other two
will rat them out.
Mom? Dad?
Hey, luke.
What --
what can we do for you?
I did it.
I was playing with matches.
I'm sorry.
You, uh --
You did the right thing
by confessing,
But, um...
This is bad, buddy.
I mean, really bad, okay?
Claire,
you want to handle this?
Um, luke,
why didn't you say something?
Mm...I don't know.
Okay, well,
your father and I
Are extremely disappointed
in you.
So go up to your room.
Go on.
Alex!
We'll be up to talk to you
in a minute.
Haley!
What?
Say something!
About what?
I take it back!
What is going on?
These guys were gonna say
they did it, too,
And you were gonna
be proud of all of us.
Why would we do that?
I don't know what to believe
with this kid.
Liars!
I didn't do it!
Well, it wasn't me.
Don't look at me.
Seriously?
Wait.
Nobody did it again?
No, that's fine.
Guess what --
christmas is still canceled.
That's fine by me.
I'll start working on
next year.
Hey, and memo
to new year's eve and easter --
Watch your back!
So, after I left the marines, I
just kind of traveled the world.
Now I go from town to town
picking up odd jobs.
Oh,
kind of like the hulk.
[ chuckles ]
that's weird.
That was my -- that was
my nickname in the corps.
'cause of my bad temper.
Anyway,
thanks for having me over
And having me for dinner,
letting me do my laundry.
This has not been
a good day.
Um, scott, I-I have a confession
to make.
Yeah?
Um...
I didn't cl--
I didn't clean the lint tray,
So, um, your clothes might be
a little pilly.
Oh, no problem.
That's the least of my worries.
Thanks for everything.
You guys made my day.
It's the least
we could do.
What do you mean?
I don't know...
What I was saying.
[ chuckles ]
I-I just say
we never tell him.
Exactly. We give him some money,
a hot al, laundry.
I think we're square.
Agreed.
Okay,
how does this thing work?
Yeah, I think you just
press that button right
there in the middle.
Yeah.
Oh, my...
Okay, that -- well, that seems
a little high, doesn't it?
Yes.
I'm not putting lily in that.
It's like something astronauts
train in.
[ banging on door ]
y:
Ho, ho, ho! It's me!
Ho, ho, ho!
It's me!
It's your dad.
Yeah.
Hey, dad.
Hi.
Hey!
I brought your presents.
Aren't we seeing you
tomorrow, jay?
Well, these are
your christmas eve gifts.
You know the drill.
Oh, yeah.
You open those up
before bedtime.
They're pajamas.
Still keeping
traditions alive.
Well, someone has to.
I got two colombians at home
Trying to turn christmas
into cinco de mayo.
You know that's mexican,
right?
Ah, burrito, bur-right-o.
Christmas
should be christmas.
Picture on the stairs, hot
chocolate, opening the presents.
That was supposed to be
the good thing
About having a kid
in the house again.
I can have christmas
the way we used to.
I hear you, jay.
If I was home right now,
I'd be mixing up
a bathtub full of eggnog
And trying to squeeze
a greased hog into a santa hat.
You don't think
I miss that?
Do you?
The point is that those are
memories that I'll always have,
But now I have
the perfect opportunity
To create new memories
with my new family
That are gonna be
just as special someday.
Aww.
Cam's right.
We create new traditions
every year.
So...Who's ready
to try the swing?
'cause jay wants to eat
at 3:00.
Ay, manny.
Did you put this spider
in the fridge?
Oh, yeah.
Inocente.
Oh, papi, what's wrong?
I want to have christmas
like they do in colombia.
Jay is messing
everything up.
Manny,
try to understand.
Jay has great memories with
his kids when they were young.
And he just wants
to re-create them with you.
So, maybe the best gift
I could give jay
Would be christmas
like he used to have it?
You're such
a beautiful boy.
One day, you're gonna grow up
and I'm gonna miss
All the things that you used
to do as a little boy.
Okay, but if
this so-called santa claus
Doesn't bring me
a burgundy dinner jacket,
We're going to have
a big problem.
Honey?
Hmm?
Would it really be so bad
to back down?
And have the kids never
take any of our threats
seriously again?
Yeah.
Mm.
Or the kids could realize
That we're making
a supreme sacrifice
By giving up our power
to save their christmas.
Which would, in a way,
be the greatest gift
That we could ever
give them.
And which would paradoxically
make them respect us even more.
Mm...
Okay, forget that.
Go back one.
Hey, guys.
It was me.
What?
I found a cigarette
at school,
And when no one was home,
I...I tried it,
And...I-I guess I held it
too close to the couch.
I'm so sorry.
You can take
my christmas away,
But don't take it
from everyone else.
That is very noble of you
to care about the family,
But you still smoked
and lied.
That's really bad.
Now help me grab the tree.
Phil.
Claire: Phil.
Alex, come on back.
Starting December 26th,
You are grounded
for a full week,
And that includes
new year's eve.
But I was g--
no, nonnegotiable, so...
Phil: Mm.
Yeah.
Fine.
Everybody!
It's official!
Christmas is back on!
It is?
What happened?
Doesn't matter!
Stockings, lights,
ornaments, wreath!
Go, go, go!
Okay!
Um, that sounds like
a stressful job to me.
Mm, not as much
as you'd think.
They always made sure one of us
had a blank,
So nobody knew
who took the fatal shot.
This was mighty tasty.
Well, I don't want
to overstay my welcome
Or you won't have me back.
[ laughs ]
[ chuckles nervously ]
You guys enjoy
the rest of your night.
You're good people.
Scott, wait.
Wait.
Don't forget your laundry.
Oh, thanks. Thanks, thanks,
thanks. Merry christmas.
[ carolers' song plays ]
Scott, merry christmas to --
to you, too, and happy --
Son of a bitch!
What?
Oh,
it's the new greensleevers.
They're cameron's
old caroling group.
They kicked him out
this year.
I mean, it is one thing
to kick me out of the group,
But to -- to rub my nose
in it?
I'm turning on
the sprinklers.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
I know it feels good
to get even, belve me.
To see the fear
in a man's eyes is...
But there's something
that feels even better...
...Forgiveness.
Scott,
you don't understand.
This -- this group
was my "dreamgirls."
I was effie.
Do you know what the best thing
I did all day was?
Forgiving you
for getting me fir.
Um...
[ carolers' song plays ]
Andrew.
Ensemble.
I know it's no accident
That you're here
on my street tonight.
And I...
I just wanted to say to you all
that you sound great.
And...Merry christmas.
Wow.
Even your apology
is off-key.
Not cool, buddy.
Ooh! Ooh!
But -- but -- but what about --
what about forgiveness?
You were nice.
He was naughty.
Where were you
for so long?
Just a little
last-minute shopping.
What's this?
Buñuelos.
Who? What?
Cheese fritters.
It's a colombian traditional
christmas food.
Okay, new rule.
From now on, we do colombian
things when we're in colombia.
We do american things
when we're in america.
That means no more of your food,
no more of your music,
And especially no more
of your crazy holidays!
Inocente!
Jay!
What?
Did I say it wrong?
You two
are total inocentes.
You should see the look
on your faces.
And by the way, you know
how hard it is to get fireworks
On christmas eve?
[ laughs ] go, manny.
Thank you.
[ laughs ]
And here's another one for luke.
looks like a book.
I have a book already.
What is that?
Oh, my god.
The couch is smoking.
Whoa.
Whoa-ho-ho.
It's sunlight.
It's the ornament.
Luke: Cool.
It's like
a magnifying glass.
Hey, how weird is that?
It's burning a hole
in the exact same spot
That alex was smoking in.
Oh, haley.
Alex, why'd you take
the blame?
I didn't want
to lose christmas.
That is
so stinking beautul.
Get in here.
No.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Yes.In here.
Oh, yeah!
Bear hug!
[ laughter ]
You were going
to take christmas away
For something
that none of us did.
Well, um...
Christmas is about
moving forward.
I've never heard that.
Actually, honey, you did kind of
shoot your mouth off.
You called us
all liars.
Yeah, and then you took away
the biggest holiday...
Yeah, you did.
I don't know.
Let's -- let's not all get
worked up.
I made a mistake.
And people make mistakes.
And they make up
for those mistakes...
Mm-hmm.
...By taking their family
to Italy!
Haley: Oh, my god!
Yeah!
Aah!
Jay: We talk a lot about
tradition this time of year.
But as much as we love
our traditions,
Sometimes our best memories
Come from the times
that are the most untraditional.
We remember the year mom and dad
went crazy.
We remember the year santa
punched out the caroler.
But for me, this was the year
that the word "tradition"
Got a lot bigger.
[ "silent night" plays ]
Jay: There's cam.
Manny: [ laughs ]
Sync by honeybunny
www.addid7ed.com
Aah!
Oh, you did it again.
You got me again.
[ laughs ]
www.tvsubtitles.net