Can people change?
Well, that's a... tough one
that's a tough one
but i would say "yes",
people can change.
That's what I beliebe, anyway.
And I will
until the day I die.
You do realize you're proving
the exact opposite of your point?
See, she's changed. She used
to be very supportive about me.
Come on...
Phill!
Ow! Why is this
so loud?
Why is this
Make it stop.
I just installed a sweet
home theater system
at the family room.
The trouble is -
Claire struggles with technology.
Of any kind.
I mean, remotes,
cell phones, computers...
Haley, have you seen my blue...
- Hey, Mrs. Dunphy.
- Oh, hey, Dylan.
You know
I can see you, right?
***
Haley is just in the bathroom,
she'll be back in just a minute?
Thank you.
What are we poiting at?
At the TV.
Honey, no, I'm sorry.
It's a home theater.
What so I - I can't point
at the TV
when I wanna watch the TV?
- no.
You pointg at the reciever.
What's a reciever?
Imagine our home theater system
is a human body,
so, then, the reciever
is the brain.
The TV is the face.
- ***.
So, he says those lies,
and a lot many more.
His heart - Boom!
-Boom!
Quadruple bypass,
blow the valve.
He look who it is!
Hey, there he is.
What a coinkydink.
I was just getting some
flowers for gloria
for babysitting lily.
You want me to take them
to her?
I would,
But I have the most hilarious
card for her at home.
It's -- it's a hunky
antonio banderas type
In silk boxers,
and on the inside it says,
"thank you
for last noche...
But I can't find
my pantalones."
I'm not doing it justice,
really.
Hi, I'm cameron.
Oh, geez, I'm sorry.
Guys, this is cameron.
He's a, um...
A f-friend of my son's.
This is, uh, scotty, dale,
hugo, and shorty.
It's nice to meet
you guys.
You guys look like a scene
out of "jersey boys."
Ohh, so handsome!
Thank you.
Manny, are you wearing
aftershave?
Yes.
For my date.
This will be the first time
she will ever smell me.
Her name is whitney.
I met her
in an online book club.
We both like vampire fiction
and the romance of eternal life.
I think it's adorable
that manny has a date.
He even picked out
the lunch menu.
Grilled-cheese sandwich
and tomato soup.
Tomato soup because, you know,
That tomato soup
is like the blood
And the vampires
like to eat their blood.
And then he wants me
to take them out for ice cream,
Well, because
manny likes ice cream.
Oh, that must be her.
If this goes well,
you don't need to stick around.
Hi, I'm whitney.
I'm here for mny.
Sync by deGroote.
www.addic7ed.com
See how that works?
Sorry, sweetie.
Sorry, daddy.
Oh, it's all right.
We were just -- me and lily
were just using the time
To finally figure out
how to use the car's
voice-command thingy.
Oh.
Yeah, here,
check it out. Watch.
Cd player, next track.
Say a command.
Air conditioner on.
Damn it.
Wow, you're worse than your
sister with this kind of stuff.
It's a good thing lily
doesn't have an ejector seat.
Oh, guess what.
I ran into your dad
and some of his friends.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
And get this --
He, uh, he referred to me
as "a friend of my son."
Seriously?
Yeah.
Well,
I wasn't offended by it.
Well, I am.
I mean, w-would he refer
to phil as "a friend
of claire's?" no.
I've heard him call phil
a lot worse.
Just let it pass. I should
have never said anything.
No, I'not
letting it pass.
He needs to know that
that's not o
And if he doesn't like it,
he knows where he can go.
Enter a destination.
Hell!
Mexican food.
Shut up!
I came out of the closet
in my mid-20s.
I had to actually come out
to my dad three times
Before he
finally acknowledged it.
I'm not sure if maybe
he was hoping he heard it wrong.
Like I had said,
"dad, I'm gray."
And my parents,
they always just knew.
My mother says labor with me
took 36 hours
Because I came out of the womb
like this, "hello!"
Hey, dad.
Mitchell.
Hey, you guys know my son,
mitch.
Hey.
Hey, mitch. How's it
hanging there, buddy?
Hey, heyhey,
that's a great coat.
Where'd you get that?
Um, you know, I don't know.
It was a gift.
Really? What is it, suede?
Microsuede?
Some kind of lambskin?
It's very soft, you know?
Thank you.
Uh, can I talk to you
for a second?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Be right back.
Good seeing you.
What's the matter?
Um, "a friend
of my son"?
That's how
you introduce cam?
That's
why you came here?
Dad, it's -- it's just
more than a little insulting.
Cam and I have been together
for five years.
We -- we have a daughter.
It's --
Look at these guys.
They look like they came out
of the 1800s.
You see hugo over there?
After lunch, he ordered a sanka.
No, they're -- they're
not the ones that are
uncomfortable with this.
You are. You...
You've never been
completely accepting of me
And now that I have a family,
it's getting a little old.
These guys don't understand
the gay thing.
Why create an awkward situation?
That's all I'm saying.
That's weird, because
your friend shorty there --
Gay as they come.
You got to be kidding.
Mnh, no.
My gaydar is never wrong,
And it is pinging
like we're at a bathhouse.
What are you talking about, gay?
The guy used to be married.
Okay, well, that makes --
no, well, so did elton john,
Merv griffin,
cole porter --
Hey, you know what?
You know what? Listen to me.
You couldn't be more wrong
about this.
No, dad, u could not be more
wrong -- about a lot of things.
Good seeing you guys.
Yeah! See you!
That's a great coat!
Ping!
Phil dunphy.
Hey, it's me.
Hey!
Listen, I've got
a bunch of moms over here
Who want to watch
the talent-show dvd,
And I can't get
the sound to work.
Is there a picture?
Yes.
Be honest. Did you do that thing
where you get frustrated
And you start pressing
all the buttons?
No.
I have a theory
That phil installs overly
complicated things in the house
Just so he has an excuse
to talk to me like a child.
Last month,
it was the thermostat.
âª the snowflake button âª
âª makes it
cold, cold, cold âª
âª "set temperature"
makes it hold, hold, hold âª
âª the little flame
makes it... âª
Whitney:
This is so humiliating.
I am sorry.
It's okay.
He just seemed
so mature online.
How could I be
so stupid?
You're not stupid. Stupid
isot following your heart
And taking a chance
on love.
I mean, what kind of 11-year-old
talks like that?
Manny's an old soul.
Here,
use my handkerchief.
You see what I mean?
I'll just be alone for the rest
of my life, and that's okay.
No, don't say that.
In my country,
there is a saying that means,
"love is
just around the corner."
I come from a neighborhood
with a lot of prostitutes.
Maybe for you.
I mean, men must throw
themselves at you every day.
They'll do the same for you
if you just...
Just what?
Put out?
No, just --
like, the lipstick,
The hair, push-up bra,
you know.
What's it matter? I'm never
gonna be as pretty as you.
Believe me,
this takes a lot of work.
You just need to find
your inner beauty.
It's hiding beneath
a mask of insecurity.
Okay, he's starting
to freak me out.
Manny, go play.
Okay.
Mitchell, how do these
look to you?
Like they're dying.
I know, right?
I saidomething to the florist,
And he said,
"oh, don't worry about it.
They're gonna me back."
they're not coming back.
They've crossed
to the other side!
You are a funny man.
Why?
Well, because you're completely
bothered by the flowers,
But when my father introduces
you as "a friend of my son" --
Doesn't faze you
in the least.
Because the florist
played me for a fool.
Your dad didn't mean any harm.
He's just being who he is.
Uh, when I was back east
in law school,
My dad used to call me
every Saturday at 6:00 p.M.
Before people would go out,
Just, you know,
check in, catch up.
And then I think the christmas
of my second year,
I finally got up the courage
to tell him.
After that, I-I pretty much
just talked to my mom.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
I'm home!
We're here.
Jay, this is whitney.
We're giving her
a makeover.
Hi. You havesucy
And a really beautiful
house.
Thanks. Uh, you two
know each other how?
She's my date.
Of course she is.
I'll be in here.
I'll be right back.
I'm sorry this didn't turn out
like you wanted.
That's okay.
Probably didn't turn out
how you wanted it, either.
I'll tell you what.
If neither of us is
with anybody in 10 years,
How about you and me
give it a shot?
That's disturbing...
But maybe.
How was your lunch
with the boys?
Good.
Ran into mitchell and cam.
Ay, nice.
And you're
not gonna believe this.
Mitchell says shorty's gay.
Shorty?
Yeah, I believe it.
Oh, come on!
Well, he's a great dresser,
a great dancer.
That doesn't prove
anything.
And he's the only one of your
friends that never hits on me.
My friends hit on you?
Ah, yes, all the time.
But don't worry --
They're a bunch
of harmless old men.
They're my age.
I'm sure it's very hard
on shorty
To keep a secret
like that.
Jay, I think
you should talk to him.
What?
Yeah, you're the only one
with a gay son.
I'm sure he'll appreciate
opening up to you.
We're guys.
We don't "open up."
We talk about sports
and cars,
Getting up in the middle
of the night to pee.
But I'm sure you made it
very easy
For mitch
to come out of the closet.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna finish
my makeover...
'cause I care
about people...
Because I want to help them
change their lives.
Jay, I'm hinting that you
should call your friend, okay?
Yes, I'm getting that.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey.
Daddy in the hiz-ouse!
Phil:
Why would you do that
To a brand-new,
very expensive remote?
Because I lost my temper
and it didn't work.
Therefore, it's useless.
Well, honey, when it comes
to anything electronic,
You're not exactly
the best student.
I am very smart.
I had a 4.0 in college.
How about you?
I was almost that
Despite my substantial
time commitment to cheerleading.
I thought we agreed not
to bring up the cheerleading.
Cheerleading in my college
was cool.
The football players
were so jealous,
They wouldn't even let me and my
buddies trevor, scotty, and ling
Go to their parties.
Seriously, claire, you owe me
an apology for baking that.
Okay.
Phil, I apologize for breaking
the world's worst remote...
That you bought...
Stupidly.
Excuse me,
But the experts at cnet.Com
rated it the best remote.
They gave it
three-and-a-half mice.
Wow!
Well, I have an idea.
Let's invite
the gang from cnet over
And your old buddies
from cheerleading
And we can have
a nerd party.
Ling is not a nerd.
He built his own helicopter.
And if he was alive today --
Sweetie, let's not talk about
ling. It upsets you too much.
You know
what I'm gonna do?
Hmm?
I'm gonna buy a new remote --
the same remote.
And just to prove
how wrong you are,
I'm gonna teach our dumbest kid
how to use it
In 20 minutes or less.
Who's our dumbest kid?
Luke.
Luke?
No, luke understands
electronics.
Haley.
No.
Yeah. Haley.
Teach haley to use the remote,
and then I'll apologize.
Haley?
Mm-hmm.
Come on!
Jay: Hey, shorty.
It's me.
Uh, I was thinking of heading
over to the driving range
And hitting a few balls --
you want to join me?
I don't know.
Wear -- wear whatever you want.
Oh, my god.
Oh, god.
Mitchell: What?
The flowers --
they look so much better.
This is a disaster.
You do know what "disaster"
means, right?
You don't understand. I demanded
that they come exchange them.
I got all medieval
on the florist.
Cam, I heard you
on the phone.
You said
you were displeased,
But that's hardly
going medieval.
Excuse me.
I said "very displeased," and
I used my cowboy voice, so...
W-what are you doing?
I'm microwaving them
so they look bad again.
Well, that seems a little crazy,
doesn't it?
Oh, no.
That's the florist.
Look, relax.
Just take them out.
I'll get the door.
He'll never know the difference.
Hi.
Florist.
Hi. Yes,
uh, me on in.
He's -- he's over there
with the flowers.
Hello.
I don't know what happened.
They just, uh, somehow
lost their vigor.
They were like this
when we came home.
Cam. Cam...
Oh, my god!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, god!
God! God!
Look at that.
Two things flaming at once.
Damn it!
You know
what the problem is?
What?
You're not moving your hips.
They're frozen.
Hips?
Yeah, your hips.
They're frozen.
Here, let me show you.
No, it's --
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't fight me.
All right, shorty.
Just bring the club back.
Go ahead. All right?
Now turn those hips.
That's it.
Yojust got to relax.
You got to open up the stance
a little bit.
Spad 'em, spread 'em.
That's it. That'.
If you don't relax, you're
never gonna get that shaft
Where it belongs.
Hey, you know what?
How about a coffee?
Let's get a coffee.
Sure.
Phil: Now press the button
labeled "activities."
Where's that?
It's to the right.
To the right.
And then --
and now choose "watch dvd."
What?!
Honey, you got to focus.
We've only got 20 minutes.
Pretend --
pretend the mall's closing.
Dad, this is stupid.
I watch tv on my computer.
Why do I
have to learn this?
Because your mom
doesn't think you can.
Nobody can!
Haley, listen to me.
Listen to me.
I know this seems
impossible,
But this is
for all those times
That mom told you
she was right...
And you knew
she was wrong.
I'll do it.
That's my girl.
You know, that guy's
got a beautiful stroke.
Look at his pants. No pleats.
I like pants like that.
You think I can get away
with something like that?
Sure, why not?
Listen, shorty, uh...
We've known each other
a long time, right?
What, 30 years?
Yeah.
And, uh...
I sense
that you got a secret
That's maybe causing you
a lot of anguish.
You heard something,
right?
Well, I had the same situation
with my son, mitchell.
Really?
And I didn't handle it
too well, either.
And, uh...
I just want you to know
that you can open up to me,
That I'm gonna do all I can
to help you.
Well, I mean, I...
I never said this out loud
before to anyone,
But I guess if I did,
it would be you.
It's just that, jay,
you see, I'm, uh...
...I'm...
Go ahead.
Yeah, go ahead.
...I'm in debt.
Huh?
I owe a bookie 20 g's,
and he's a serious guy.
And you offering to give me
the dough -- this is beautiful!
Wait a minute.
You're not gay?
Gay?! What are you
talking about, gay?
I'm not gay!
Where'd you get gay?!
Come on, I mean, you're
blways talking about clothes
and everything, right?
My father was a tailor.
I like clothes. So what?
Are you calling
my father gay?
No!
My father landed on normandy
to save your ass.
You know, if you
weren't lending me 20 g's,
I'd knock you out
right now.
Take a check?
Cash would be better.
Haley, you ready?
Let's do this.
Turn on the tv.
Nice.
Mute it.
Un-mute it.
Put it on dvd.
Skip forward.
Wait. Um...
Okay. Back to tv.
Face!
Don't get all cocky,
phil.
Let's see what happens
to little haley when I do this.
Ho! Ooh!
Face.
Dad, w-what do I do?
Don't panic.
We went through this.
Just -- just think.
Give up?
Give up. Admit defeat.
Haley...
Okay, uh, let's see...
You put the remote
onto tv mode
And then pre input
till you get hdmi 1 and...
Whoo!
I did it!
She did it!
Fine, you proved
your point.
Everybody in this house
is smarter than me.
No, honey,
you're missing the point.
I taught haley how to use
the remote in 20 minutes,
So think how fast
you can learn it.
What's that
supposed to mean?
See what I'm saying?
Jay:
Mitchell, it's me!
Hey, dad.
Hi.
I'm here to let you know
your gaydar is broken.
Shorty is not gay.
No. I, um,
I knew that.
I just, uh -- I made
that up to mess with you
for dissing cam.
What? That cost me20,000 bucks.
What do you mean?
I reached out to him,
you know,
To let him know
it's okay to be gay.
You did?
Yeah...
Right after one of the stranger
golf lessons of my life.
Turns out what he is
is a lousy gambler,
D now I'm the one
on the hook for it.
Well, I'm so sorry.
Then why are you smiling?
I'm -- I'm proud of you, dad.
You're growing.
Just --
just stop it, please?
Don't you see how hard
this is for me?
See, I used to be
just like one of those guys.
Now look at me.
I got a house looks like
little colombia.
I got a gay son
and a chinese granddaughter.
Vietnamese.
Only you would know
the difference.
Okay, don't worry, dad.
You're not growing too much.
Whitney:
I'm a little nervous.
Don't be!
I'm sure
you look beautiful.
Whoa!
What do you think?
Look at you!
Really?
You gonna be fighting men off
with a stick!
I don't know about that.
Cameron!
Hi! Sorry
for the pop-over,
But I just wanted to
bring you these
To thank you for babysitting
lily again last night.
Oh...
Mwah!
Gracias.
You didn't need to do that.
You know I love lily.
I know.
Come in.
Say hello.
Hey, cam.
Cameron, this is
my new friend, whitney.
Whitney,
this is cameron.
Hello,
it's nice to meet you.
That...
Is a spectacular dress.
This old thing?
I don't know...
What about her hair?
Oh, my gosh.
It's like barbra streisand
in "the way we were."
One of my favorites.
Me too.
Okay, who is reading
"the forevers"?
I am.
[ gasps ]
I am so obsessed with this
whole vampire thing right now.
Me too!
I just met the sweetest guy
named cameron.
I think he might be the one.
Mitchell: Can people change?
I don't know.
People are who they are...
Give or take 15%.
That's how much people can
change if they really want to.
Well, I'll see you
when I see you.
Yeah,
thanks for com--
Okay.
Haley, sweetie,
wake u
What?
I need you to teach me
to use the tv.
Now?
Why can't dad teach you?
Because we're married.
Whether it's for themselves
or for the people they love.
That way.
Yeah. And then press --
Mnh.
I got it.
Yeah. Yeah, 15%.
But you know what?
Sometimes
that's just enough.
I did it!
All riall right.See you guys
next week, huh?
Jay, jay...
Listen, I want to thank yo
for, uh, you know,
Helping me out with that jam,
you know.
, it was nothing.
It was nothing.
No. No, no, no. And I got you
a little present.
Oh, come on.
You didn't have to do that.
No, I did.
Two tickets to see
the great michael bublè.
The guy sings
like an angel.
He's gonna be outside
at one of the amphitheaters.
Gloria's gonna love it.
No. I'm talking
about you and me.
Oh, you and me?
Yeah.
Oh, well,
that's a little, um...
Yeah, I thought
maybe we could have
A little picnic since
it's outside, you know?
I'll get some nice bottle
of wine, a little cheese,
Lay on a nice blanket,
all right?
Yeah, fine, yeah.
Yo, hey, I like your hair.
Who does your hair?
Huh? Yo, handsome,
who does your hair?
www.tvsubtitles.net