It's my stuff, okay?
Just keep your hands off
my stuff! Phil: Hey!
I didn't put my hands on your stuff!
Hey! Just a second, derek.
What is the problem?
Alex read my journal. I did not!
Why would I even want to read
your stupid journal?
Because it contains the details of a life,
And yo don't have one!
Ohh!
Alex, don't read haley's journal. Uhh!
Sorry. My daughters.
You got kids?
Oh. What grade are you in?
Phil! Oh, that's my wife, claire.
Luke was using my computer.
For this.
I'm gonna have to, uh, call you back.
He told me he needed it to do homework,
And then I find this --
A-a picture of a topless woman,
With the biggest boobs I
have ever seen,
Driving a tractor.
Okay, um, uh, first of all,
That's a combine, not a tractor. Phil!
Phil, it is smut, and our 1
0-year-old is looking at smut!
It's disgusting!
Completely unacceptable.
Here's the thing -- that was my picture.
Well, not really mine.
There's this guy at work
who sends out these links.
Does-- doesn't matter who. Gil thorpe.
He sent out another one
Of the same woman dressed as a battleship.
You know, the -- you get -- yeah.
And then one of the transformers.
And then it -- it...
Anyway, I had every
intention of telling claire.
I just wanted her to calm down first.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up
luke from his sleepover.
We need to talk to him about this now.
Claire, this isa very delicate .
If we don't handle it right,
Luke might end up having an
unhealthy attitude about sex.
Or agribusiness.
We'll talk about it when he gets home.
Okay. Fine.
But I am telling him that
every time he looks at porn,
God kills a puppy.
Maybe I should be the one to talk to him.
I am a very lucky woman.
I have a wonderful family, a beautiful home.
There's nothing that I would change.
I hate the dog butler.
I keep forgetting it's there,
And every time it happens,
it scares me all over again.
Sometimes, at night, I think ithe devil.
El diablo.
Barkley? He's hilarious.
I was in vegas last month,
and I was winning...
...And I thought, I could do the usual --
Be a chump, give the money
back to the casino --
Or I could do something smart
and buy something for myself
At the casino store.
He's already a family favorite.
Rub his chin a little under there.
He likes that.
There you go. Beautiful.
There you go.
He's a dog and a butler.
I mean, who couldn't love him?
stupid dog.
-- Captions by vitac --
Okay, ready to go.
Oh, make sure you pee first.
What am I, 7 years old?
No, you do not want to go during the show.
The marionettes stop what they're doing,
March to the edge of the stage,
and point at you.
Okay, that sounds terrifying.
It's really funny.
Oh, one of my favorite childhood memories
Was attending the moscow marionette theater.
I grew up one mile away from
missouri's largest water slide,
And third-largest in the country.
Oh, really? Cam,
you never mentioned that before.
You feel --
Feel like a torpedo.
Hey, cam, does the gardener
usually work on saturdays?
I don't know. He comes when we need him.
He's like batman, but straight.
Is he crying?
Oh, yeah.
We should probably...
Probably go out the back, huh?
He's clearly in pain.
How can you just turn your
back on a friend like that?
A friend? Really? Yeah. W-what's his name?
Cesar sal...Azar.
You made that up.
You were gonna say "caesar salad."
Was not.
Cam. Come on. Really?
ugh.
All right, don't worry, lily.
I'm sure we'll get to the show on time.
I'm sure dad is just gonna go out
And give an encouraging
word to the gardener,
Hopefully mention the snail problem,
And then we are gonna be --
No.
No, no. Cam, no.
Hello.
I don't think he speaks english.
Okay, this might be a good
time to mention to you
That the marionettes are
not kind to latecomers.
They bend over and show their bloomers.
Okay, I speak a little spanish.
¿señor, te gustaría hacer el agua
Y tenemos nuestra cama?
Gracias.
What was that?
I just asked him if he wanted
to have a glass of water
And sit down for a minute,
Like any kind person would.
I didn't find any more porn.
That was hardly porn.
It was a topless woman on a tractor.
You know what they call that in europe?
A cereal commercial.
I should go talk to him.
Honey, honey, honey, I got this!
I got this!
No, no, no, no, no. I-I got this.
I got this. I was his age once.
Breasts are like these scary,
mystical things
That he's drawn to, like frodo to mordor.
Okay, I'm definitely going to
talk to him. No, no, no, no!
Boys don't want their moms
talking to them about sex
Any more than girls want
their dads talking to them
About periods, bras,
and girdles and all that stuff.
You do know that women stopped wearing
girdles like 30 years ago, right?
Honey, I know. I know.
That -- that is --
That is exactly the kind
of sexual revolution
That our son is going through right now,
So...
Just -- let's just -- just trust it.
fix that step.
Just know I will handle this, okay?
Iel diablo!
Hey, gloria, do you have any idea
Why barkley was in the guest room?
I was just doing a little redecorating.
Sometimes it's good to move things around
Just to see how they look.
Yeah, but the guest room -- that's crazy.
He's not a guest. He works for us.
Hey, give me a hand here, will you?
I think his jacket shifted
while I was moving him.
We can't have you untucked,
our little butler.
That doesn't make any sense, does it, boy?
ay!
"ay"? What was that? Is he all right?
Ay, no. My bracelet got
caught a little bit here.
Well, don't panic. I'm not panicking.
All right, try to relax.
We can fix him. Let me take a better look.
Come here, boy.
Luke?
Hey, dad. Hey, buddy.
Um...Look,
You and I need to have a little talk.
About what?
Well, it's about computer stuff.
Um...
How do you make sure
you've deleted something
After you read it?
Sorry, jay. It was an accident.
You know, I'm beginning to think
You don't like barkley that much.
I mean, first you hide
him in the guest room,
And now this.
It's ridiculous! I didn't mean to hurt it!
First of all, let's cut the "its."
He is a he.
And you can pretend to
be innocent all you want,
But action speaks louder than words.
Yeah. They can be very revealing.
What are you trying to say?
Nothing, but you have to admit
That the dog butler is a little ridiculous.
You know what else I think is ridiculous?
That mountain of pillows
you have on our bed.
I feel like I'm working on a loading dock
Just trying to get under the covers.
They're pretty. They're a damn nuisance.
Okay, forgive me for trying
to make our home beautiful.
Well, you know, if I can put up with those,
You can put up with a piece of art.
This is not art.
It's an unholy mix between man and beast.
But fine.
If you love it so much,
put it wherever you want.
Thank you.
Where you going, to get some more pillows?
no, don't worry.
It'll be a long time
Before I bother you again with my pillows.
Why is dad in luke's room
with the door closed?
They are having a little talk.
Is luke being punished?
Is that your favorite thing,
When your brother or
sister gets into trouble?
My favorite is when they're both in
trouble.
So, what'd he do?
Did he cheat on a test? He's a cheater.
He did not cheat on a test.
Did he lie? Alex.
He lies all the time.
Alex. Sorry.
I'm -- I'm just worried about luke.
A lot of parents are hitting again.
I appreciate your concern,
But your father has it under control.
24.
25.
Flincher!
Free slap. Bring it up.
Ow! 29.
Cai be on the bottom now? Yeah.
Mm. How'd it go?
Well, he was really embarrassed,
But everything's -- everything's fine now.
What'd you say?
Well, you know, I kind of promised him
We'd keep everything between us.
Mm-hmm. Matter of fact,
He'd be mortified if you
brought it up with him...
Ever.
Oh, god. Really? Yeah.
That actually makes me feel kind of bad.
Well...
You're probably just feeling
a little tense from alis.
I know I am.
You know what might help the situation?
Really?
Right now?
I meant goint for a few pizzas.
Where's your mind?
I guess I live in a house
full of sex maniacs.
Amigo?
We can't help you if you won't come out.
Gracias por invitarme a su casa.
Me averguenzo de mis lágrimas.
What'd he say? Something...
House... Something.
Oh, come on!
The show starts in a half-hour,
and we still have to pick up manny.
Can -- can we just --
Come on, move this thing along.
Okay, this m is in crisis.
He could have a family-health issue
Or a personal-health issue
or a financial matter.
Okay, wait, stop.
You're getting all this from
"something house something"?
Let's just call gloria and
have her deal with it, okay?
"it" is a human being, mitchell!
Named caesar salad.
Okay, what's going on with you?
Cam, you -- mnh! You always do this!
It's like you're incapable
of hearing anyone's sad story
Without making it your job to fix it,
And then my needs -- my needs come second.
Your needs right now are a puppet show.
This man could have lost his
brother in a cable-car accident!
You understood "casa."
Okay, fine.
If it'll prove to you that I'm
not the obsessive help-aholic
That you make me out to be,
Let's go to the puppet show.
Cam...
Let's go.
Ay, ¿dónde está mi novio?
Su camión está aparcado fuera.
I think this has something
to do with the gardener.
You think?
Um, just down the hall to the right.
Ay, gracias, gracias.
Perdón. Okay.
Okay. Let's go.
Oh, no, please -- I know it's killing you
Not to get back there in the middle of that.
Oh, no, no, no, no. We are going.
These folks can find their own way out.
And now you'll know that I'm not
a manic mother teresa out there
Collecting lost souls.
Oh, come on!
Is manny ready?
Didn't you get the message? He's not going.
What?
Oh, some mandatory cleanup at school.
What's the real reason?
It's a puppet show, mitch.
Perfect.
All right, it's just you and me, then, lily.
How's the little fortune cookie?
Oh, she's -- she's good. She's good.
Where's cam?
We got into a fight.
Because of him,
I have a house full of latinos.
Welcome to my world.
So, trouble in gay paradise, huh?
Well, he just can't say no
to anybody who needs help,
And why do you have to always add the
word "gay" where it doesn't belong?
Hey, hey -- you're not mad at me.
You're mad at the old balls and chain.
Okay, dad, good talk. See you later.
Oh, come on. I didn't mean it.
Hey, I didn't mean it. I'm a little cranky.
I got into it with gloria a little bit.
Oh, no. What happened?
Ah, she hates barkley.
It's the same stuff I went over
with your mom all the time --
Get rid of the boat,
get rid of the motorcycle.
You know, I liked those things.
Why do you have to get rid of it, then?
You know, actually, I don't.
Anyway, I'm gluing his hand on over here.
His hand came off.
Rough day, dad.
Your hot, young wife doesn't like your doll.
yeah. Unlike your big problem --
"my boyfriend's too nice to people."
No, see -- mm. That's not all it is.
He -- he helps animals.
He's always volunteering for things.
T-trust me, it -
it - it's worse than it sounds.
Who are we kidding?
We both got it pretty good.
Hell, I'm probably fighting with your mom
More than I'm fighting
with gloria on this thing.
A bird fell out of a tree,
and he fed it with an eyedropper.
Just drop it, kid.
We're both with people different from us,
And that's gonna create stuff,
but you want different.
Your mom and I were perfect on paper,
And you know how that ended.
What I got now is a lot better.
Sure, people look at us sometimes,
And sometimes even I can't
believe we're together.
But we're happy.
At the end of the day,
There's no one I'd rather come home to.
You mean gloria?
Who else?
No one.
I'll see you later.
See you, kid.
Did you draw on my poster?
Yeah, I did.
Maybe you'll think about that
The next time you read my journal.
I didn't read your stupid journal,
And I waited in line to
get this signed, haley.
Oh, don't be such a baby.
It's just some dude with weird hair.
That's maya angelou, you idiot.
Ohh, sorry I don't follow the wnba.
You know what?
This is the worst thing you've ever done,
And I'll never forgive you!
You started it!
What are you looking at? Well, I just heard-
I was the one who read haley's diary.
I was playing on her computer,
and it just opened.
Okay, I opened it.
But I didn't mean for anyone to fight.
Oh. Home already.
Mitchell, hi! Hi!
Hi, cam. Hi.
Did you forget the tickets?
No. You know, I was never gonna
enjoy the show without you, so...
Oh, but you were so excited
To take lily to see the russian marionettes.
She's probably a little young anyways.
We can just prop her in front
of the dryer for a half-hour.
Listen, cam, I-I love that
you try and help the world.
And I-I'm very lucky to have you in my life.
Oh, mitchell.
How'd everything work out with the gardener?
Uh, great. Great.
Turned out it was his wedding day,
And he was just a little nervous.
But you know what?
There's no need to apologize to me.
No, I need to. I've been very selfish.
No, no. Sometimes I take things too far.
Okay, well, if that ever happens,
I will let you know.
okay.
Is there a reason I can't go inside?
No. No, no. No.
Y ahora te pronuncio hombre y esposa.
La puedes besar.
Mom, can I talk to you?
Sure, honey. What's going o
I feel bad about something I did.
Oh, sweetie.
Is this about the computer? Yeah.
Something you shouldn't
have been looking at? Yeah.
It was just so freaky.
I couldn't stop looking.
I know, sweet pea,
Buthe important thing
is you did stop looking.
Yeah.
After about an hour.
Okay.
Well, it's perfectly normal to
be curious about these things.
Some parts were funny. Mm-hmm.
And some parts just seemed crazy.
Well, I hope you realize
That some of those parts weren't real.
Obviously.
But they can be totally real, right?
Hmm. Like anne frank's?
What?
All I know is, it really
made me wonder about haley.
That's disturbing, sweetie. Why haley?
It was her journal.
You read my journal?
You little creep!
I'm sorry! I couldn't help it!
Wait, haley's journal, too?
Luke, you are now banned from the computer.
What?
What happened? Who's in trouble?
Luke read my journal!
I told you it wasn't me!
I'm gonna kill you!
Haley, calm down.
What, you're not even gonna yell at him?
That was private! Oh, please.
The most shocking thing in
there was your spelling.
You read it, too?
Am I the only one who hasn't read it?
I was looking through the
computers in the house
For pornography.
sick.
Not for me.
I wanted to see what you
guys are looking at.
So you're violating our privacy.
When I find out that my children
Are looking at a naked picture online,
They don't have any privacy.
Who was looking at naked pictures?
That doesn't matter.
I wasn't.
It wasn't me!
That's gross! I'm 10!
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you people?
If it wasn't you, who was it?
Mangia!
Rosa, thank you for coming. Gracias.
Carlos, let me know how it
works out with that dentist.
Victor, you owe me a dance.
Yes, I'm a caring person,
and without mitchell,
I would just keep giving
and giving and giving.
I'm like a big, runaway charity truck,
And mitchell is my of
f-ramp full of safety gravel.
He knows how to say no.
He always can put himself first.
He certainly can turn his
back on someone's suffering.
Um...
No, really, keep going.
He --
Don't keep going!
Gracias. Goodbye.
that was nice.
Oh, god! Dad.
Looks like I missed the party, huh?
What I-- what is that doing here?
He is a gift for you and cam.
Thank you. He lost his monocle on the drive.
Head was out the window.
Well, they love that.
I'll just put him here for now.
I don't want that.
I think he's cute. Let's give him a chance.
I came as soon as I heard your message.
Did you say that somebody
was getting married?
Gloria, there you are!
I've got good news!
What's the matter?
Honey?
Hey.
I'm really sorry.
That picture was just something
that someone sent me.
Doesn't matter who.
Gil thorpe.
Anyway...
I don't do that stuff.
You're all the porn I need.
that's --
Honey, it's fine. It's fine.
Aah!
Now it's fine.
I couldn't care less about the picture.
I was just upset when I thought it was luke.
Haley, honey, I really wish
you would give me a hand
With all this laundry.
Never, ever...
Haley's off in her own world.
Alex has never really been a kid.
But luke is my baby.
Is it really too much to ask
That he stay a sweet, innocent kid...
Forer?
Hey, buddy.
Um...Here, sorry.
We'll -- we'll dribble later.
Um...I just, uh,
I just want to say I'm sorry.
I never meant to blame you
for that whole picture thing.
Your mom sort of thought it was yours,
And I-I should have stopped it,
but I didn't.
So what was the picture of?
Well, it was a woman on a tractor,
And she had her shirt off.
Was it hot?
Okay, we're being honest here.
Um... This particular woman --
Well, my tastes do run to the curvy,
And the cowboy hat did not hurt one bit.
Couple that with the cut-off jeans --
And you were asking about
the weather, weren't you?
Yeah.
Well, this is good. This is good.
You're gonna be going
through some changes soon,
And I think now you can feel safe
Talking to me about whatever.
sadly, I've been summarily dismissed.
From the employ of masters
cameron and mitchell --
The former being an utter delight,
And the latter being a humorless snoot.
Just -- come on, get him in the car.
The thrift shop's closing.
What is this exciting
thrift shop you speak of?
Many of my relatives were
taken out of their homes
To be released into the green
pastures in their maturity!
Did you just say "maturity"?
Unhand me, you brute!
I regret nothing!
I'll pay you. I'm a comfortable man.
I've been stealing from
your father for days.
Oh, is there any better feeling in the world
Thanaving your ears flap in the wind?
You know what? Get out.
You mean it? Sweet freedom?
No. No, not you, barkley.
Cameron. Out. Oh.
SYnc by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net