A gang fight.
I just want him
to fit in.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Do you care to join me?
You know, honey, there's a gun
in the footlocker in the garage.
If I ever say "no"
to that question,
I want you to use it
on me.
[ chuckles ]
[ haley speaking
indistinctly ]
[ footsteps approaching ]
Shh, shh, shh!
What's wrong?
[ continues speaking
indistinctly ]
Why aren't they trying
to hurt each other?
I don't know,
but I'm afraid to move.
[ laughing ]
you're really good at this.
Thanks.
What is happening,
claire?
Cameron: Mmm.
Mitchell:
What do you think?
Now, that is a scone.
No butter, nonfat.
Shut up.
[ doorbell rings ]
I'm gonna go check
on lily.
Surprise!
Mom!
[ laughs ]
[ thud, bird squawks ]
Gloria: What's that?
Sounds like a bird
hit the window.
Oh, god,
that's a bad sign.
Ow!
That hurt, jerk!
I'm gonna kill you, stupid!
Ow!
[ clatter ]
Wh happened?
Now I'm sad.
Uhh!
Hi, honey.
Hi.
I-I didn't know
you were in town.
You didn't call.
Well, I couldn't wait
to see your new baby.
Where is she?
Cameron:
Mitchell, who was that?
Uh, it's my mom.
Oh, yeah, right.
'cause the last time
she was here,
The refrigerator magnets
rearranged themselves
Into a penta--
Grandma!
Hey.
-- Sync by honeybunny --
www.addic7ed.com
Mom...Mom, what are you doing
to her legs?
Tai chi.
I did it every day in sedona.
Cameron,
you should try it.
[ chuckles ]
Mitchell's mother
has a problem...With me.
Last christmas,
for example,
She gave me
a piece of exercise equipment
And a lettuce dryer.
So, to recap,
I gave her a gorgeous pair
of diamond earrings,
And she gave me a hint.
Dede: And living in sedona
has been transformational.
I get up every morning, and I
go to a vortex meditation site
And work with a shaman
to finally understand
How to live
my spirituality.
Yikes.
And I've learned
that the only way
I can move to the next level
of my awakening
Is if we all can somehow
get past...
The incident.
Oh, no.
Oh, boy.
I would like to congratulate
jay and the lovely gloria.
I'm very happy for them.
I wanted a big, beautiful
wedding with jay
Because my ex-husband and I
got married
In a tiny, little office
of a judge in colombia.
Well, my mother
wanted to go to the wedding
To show everyone how okay
she was with all of it,
So I convinced dad and gloria
to invite her.
Who warned you that
that was the worst idea ever?
Anyone?
Oh. [ chuckles ]
Of course,
I've -- I've moved on.
[ chuckles ]
I was supposed to come
with a date,
But he just hurt his back,
Which is very ironic because
he's young and -- and healthy.
My mom started drinking
these cocktails
Called "horny colombians"
With some of
gloria's uncles,
Whom, apparently,
the drink was named after.
Phil: Oh, come on,
they were funny.
[ laughter ]
They kept
patting my butt.
[ chuckling ]
somebody's full of herself.
It's a -- it's a colombian
wedding tradition, they said.
[ glass clinking ]
I would like to make a toast.
Yeah,
nana got totally wasted.
Uh, it was really funny.
Then it was gross.
To the bride and the groom,
my ex.
35 years we were together,
And he couldn't wait 10 minutes
to run off with charo.
I'm kidding.
[ chuckles ]
[ rim shot ]
Seriously, I knew
they were perfect for each other
When I saw his wallet
and her boobs.
[ laughs ]
Take your hands off me.
Mom.
Oh, relax, mitchell.
What, did you take
your claire pill?
Okay, l-let's just --
let's get a little
fresh air, okay? Come on.
And then it got weird.
[ hispanic accent ] I'm gloria.
I'm gloria. Kiss me.
Oh, hey, kiss me.
[ guests gasping, murmuring ]
Nana is really strong.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi!
Ooh!
During my vows
to my first husband,
Drug dealers burst in
and assassinated the judge.
This was way worse.
What can I say?
I drive women crazy.
[ laughs ]
It's too soon,
I guess.
Everybody is going to be there,
mom.
Claire:
I don't care.
Your father and I
are not about to let you
Drive two hours
to go to a concert
And then spend the night
with a bunch of boys,
Especially that 17-year-old
hormone you're dating.
It's totally supervised.
Oh, really?
By whom?
By spencer patine's uncle.
Who's spencer patine?
You know spencer --
the guy with the arm.
Wait. What kind of arm?
What does that even mean?
His uncle
is uncle tobey.
Oh, uncle tobey.
I'll be sure to include that
in my amber alert.
Oh, my god.
Okaycan I step in here?
I think I can help.
Haley, what your mom
is worried about
Is you getting
your heart broken
When dylan goes off to college
next year.
He's not going to college.
That's not
what I'm even think--
He's not
going to college?
He's in a band, okay?
They're going on tour.
Oh, this just gets
better and better.
Why are you always on me
about everything?!
Because you need
to understand --
okay,
now, everybody, calm down.
Let's start
from the beginning.
What's wrong
with spencer's arm?
Ugh!
Mom, I'm home!
Gloria: Hi, baby!
Did you have fun
at the slumber party?
You must be exhausted.
No,
I'm not tired at all.
I was the first one
to fall asleep.
What's on your face?
A smile from having such
a good time with my friends.
No.
Come here.
Look.
Oh.
That's why
they were laughing.
I thought it was my funny take
on current events.
Why would they do something
like that?
Don't worry about it.
Guys pull pranks like that
all the time.
You just got
to prank 'em back.
Just got to show 'em
you're willing to give
as good as you get.
What do you think?
Hmm, revenge...
I like it.
Well, mom, instead of scratching it
down a wall,
Maybe we should just try
and repress it
Like a --
like a normal family.
I can't.
I need closure.
I'm about to embark on
a new journey.
I met a man.
Really?
His name is chas,
And he's asked me
to come live with him
In his foreign land.
Wow. Where?
Canada.
You're moving to --
to canada?
French canada.
[ plates clattering ]
oh.
Oh, that --
that's wonderful.
It is wonderful.
It just that when I think of
all the awful things
That I said
to gloria and jay
And you and claire,
I feel such guilt.
Give it time...
And see banff.
Cam, please.
I just can't give myself to him
sexually.
Okay, mom.
Did not see that coming.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
We satisfy each other
down there.
Oh...
Yeah, don't want to...
That's why I need
everyone's forgiveness.
I need your help,
mitchell.
Cameron:
Did you hear that, mitchell?
Your mom needs your help to
make love to her new man, chas.
That's not weird at all.
I -- [ chuckles ]
I'm just not really sure what
you're asking me to do, mom.
Well,
everyone's mad at me.
Oh...
Maybe you could pave the way
so that I can apologize.
Well, um...You know,
we are actually
All supposed to have
Sunday dinner tonight,
So maybe I could go around
and ask everyone
If it's okay
foyou to join us.
Oh!
I knew
I could count on you.
Oh, my beautiful boy.
I love you so much.
There's a fish in nature
that swims around
With its babies in its mouth.
That fish would look at
mitchell's relationship
With his mother
and say, "that's messed up."
Hey.
Boy [clears throat]
Things with your mom got pretty
intense down there, huh?
All like
east coast/west coast.
You feelin' me?
Act like a parent,
talk like a peer.
I call it "peerenting."
I learned it from my own dad
who used to walk into my room
And say, "what's up, sweathog?"
[ chuckles ]
Honey...
I would love to let you go
to the concert.
Are you kidding me?
I think concerts are rad.
Hello!
I was a hall-raiser.
A what?
I followed hall & oates
around the country one summer.
"rich girl"
just spoke to me.
I was dating this girl.
Not -- not dating.
I guess I was following her,
too, kind of.
Okay, mom just doesn't trust me,
and it's not fair.
She trusts you.
It's just that weird stuff
happens at concerts.
Boys get urges.
Ew.
Dad, is there something
you want?
Yes, there is --
To connect with this girl
right here.
Now, come on.
Pretend I'm not your dad.
We're just a couple of friends
kickin' it in a juice bar.
What's a juice bar?
Okay, a malt shop,
whatever.
Dad, I don't --
no.
Who's dad?
Who's dad? I'm --
I'm marcus from biology.
Hey, haley.
How's it going with you
and dylan?
Has he tried anything
inappropriate with you...Girl?
[ cellphone rings ]
Hey.
No, nothing.
Just talking to some dork I met
in a malt shop.
[ doorbell rings ]
Hey, mitchell.
What's up?
Hey, just --
just in the hood.
So, do you --
do you remember
How mom gave up a career
to raise us?
Promising career.
Oh, god.
Claire?
Mom.
Why so long?
Mm, I know.
I know, it's weird when
we haven't talked for a while.
I mean your hair.
Mm...
Well, if I can't tell you,
who will?
So, mom wants you to know
That she's very sorry
about the incident
And -- and she wants us
to forgive her.
Oh, very nice of her
to say that through you.
Do you see?
The sarcasm
is so hurtful --
Like a whip.
Yoow how growing up, we l
have that voice inside our head
That tells us
we're not good enough?
Well, mine was outside my head,
driving me to school.
So -- so, anyway,
mom really wants
To smooth everything over
with dad and gloria,
So I was thinking,
would it be okay
If she maybe joined us
for dinner tonight?
Because it may be the last time
you ever see me.
Well...
Okay, wait.
What are you
talking about?
Well, I'm --
I'm moving to a far
and dangerous place.
Canada, but -- uh, she met
a man named chas. Yeah.
He's a logger.
Like a --
like a lumberjack?
No, he logs blood samples
into a cholesterol study.
Anyway, until I'm past
this whole wedding debacle,
I can't be intimate
with him.
Oh.
We do things
to each other.
We use our hands.
Mm...
Oh, my lord.
Haley: Hey, nana.
Oh, my little comet.
Hey!
Oh, look at you.
You're all grown up.
Hmm, tell mom that.
She won't even let me go
to a concert.
Overnight
with her boyfriend.
[ laughs ]
What are you laughing at?
Oh, karma's a funny thing,
that's all.
Remember ricky?
Oh, god.
Oh, who's ricky?
No one.
Ricky was
your mother's boyfriend,
And he looked
like charles manson.
And one night, she didn't come
home until 4:00 in the morning.
4:00? Wow.
Wow, mom, what were you
and ricky doing?
Nothing.
We were doing nothing,
and he was a very sweet boy,
Which you might have known if
you bothered to get to know him.
Dylan's a sweet boy.
[ scoffs ] dylan.
Dylan is no ricky.
Ricky -- ricky was a poet.
Dylan writes songs --
awesome songs.
And maybe
you would know that
If you
"bothered to get to know him."
Ha!
[ laughs ]
Okay, you know, first of all,
I am not my mother.
I don't judge people before
I get a chance to know them.
So you invite dylan over
to dinner tonight,
And if he's as sweet and as kind
as you say he is,
Then I have no problem
Considering letting you
go to the concert
After I do a background check
on uncle tobey.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, mom.
Okay,
I'm gonna go call him.
Okay.
That's very revealing.
That's my parenting style.
No, I meant your blouse.
Mom.
Claire, wait.
Come -- [ chuckles ]
Not making this easy.
Claire, come on.
Stop, stop, stop.
Just let her
come to dinner,
Apologize
to dad and gloria,
And she and chas
can live happily ever after.
In canada.
[ sighs ]
Wait, why don't you make her
fix this
Instead of you doing it,
as usual?
Whoa.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, you know,
mom makes a mess,
And there's mitchell
to clean it up.
Okay, that is so not true.
If -- if anything,
you're the one
With the screwed-up relationship
with mommy --
With -- with -- with mom.
Wow, "mommy"?
No, I didn't say it --
damn it.
Ooh.
Fine.
Fine, she can come, but she's
got to clear it with daddy.
"Daddy"?
I did not say "daddy."
You said "daddy."
Hey, dad.
Mitchell,
what are you doing here?
Uh, I'm sorry to bother you.
Uh, could I talk to
you and gloria for a second?
Oh, she's out dealing
with a manny situation.
He set a kid's bike
on fire.
Why?
Oh, I might have told him
to get even with some kids,
And he went all rambo
with it.
Not my best parenting
moment.
[ chuckles ]
not your worst.
What's up?
Uh, well, you know,
mom's in town.
Your mom?
No. No, your mom.
She's back from the grave.
Yes.
Yes, my mom,.
My mom
would be less scary.
Listen, she's a wreck about
what happened at the wedding,
And she wants to come
to dinner tonight
To apologize to everyone.
Still her little errand boy,
I see.
No. Why does everybody
keep say-- no.
I -- I'm just trying to piece
this family back together.
So you'll talk to gloria
about mom coming to dinner?
Oh, gloria would never go
for that in a million years.
She's still furious
with your mother,
Which is why
I'm not talking to you.
What did I do?
This conversation
never took place.
Well, that's not very nice.
I drove all the way here.
No, you didn't.
You were never here.
In fact,
you never even called.
I would have called,
but I thought it would be better
To talk about th--
what -- what's happening here?
Listen...
I would love to get
this thing behind us,
But gloria
would never forgive me
If I pulled a fast one
on her.
That's why you're going to pull
a fast one on her,
And I'm not going to like it
one bit.
Okay, that's just great.
No, that's great.
So it's all up to me.
I can't hear you
because you're back home
And I'm taking a nap.
[ sighs ]
[ doorbell rings ]
D-money. There he is.
Hey.
Come on in.
Hi.
Hey, how you doing?
Good.
Um...
Uh, hey, everybody,
this is dylan.
Hey.
Hi.
He has
a very gentle soul.
You got that from "hey"?
So, dylan,
I see you brought the ax.
Yeah, yeah,
I just came from practice.
Sweet.
Miss those days.
Oh, you were in a band?
Could have been,
but in high school,
I was really
all about my magic, so...
Oh, my god.
[ doorbell rings ]
Oh, that's gonna be
dad and gloria.
Oh, mitchell,
I know it's silly, but...
I'm a little nervous.
Oh, no. That's not silly.
You should be.
[ door opens ]
Hey.
How are you?
Manny.
Phil.
Nice mustache.
Thank you.
Don't make fun.
He may burn your house down.
Oh, boy.
Dede.
Hi, jay. Gloria.
What is she doing here?
What does she mean,
"what is she doing here?"
Mitchell told you
I'd be here.
Lies!
I couldn't tell her
because she wouldn't come.
Gloria, my mom wants
to apologize for everything.
So you just spring it
on gloria like this?
Mitchell, what the hell
is wrong with you?
I don't want
her apologies.
And who could blame you,
honey?
Which is why this is
a terrible idea by you!
Jay, manny, let's go.
Oh, wait, wait, gloria.
I d--
I just want to tell you
How sorry I am
for ruining your wedding.
I was struggling
with being alone.
Meanwhile, jay moves on
so easily.
And -- and not with
just anyone --
With a...
Young and smart
and beautiful woman.
I don't expect
to forgive me.
If I were you,
I'd want to punch me
right in the mouth.
I think we've had
enough revenge
In this family
for one day.
Oh, okay. Y-y-you see?
Yeah, we're all gonna
move past this.
And because of me, who --
who's not a mama's boy,
But is a caring person with
wisdom and emotional insight,
So make a note, bitches.
That's not a good color
on you.
[ sighs ]
I forgive you.
Oh. Wow.
I am not prepared
for this.
I just -- I wa--
I want
to rip your head off!
[ indistinct shouting ]
You ruined my wedding!
I got gloria!
[ indistinct shouting
continues ]
I got gloria.
Stand up like a big girl.
Come on.
Jay: All right, all right,
all right.
Stop it, stop it, stop it,
the two of you!
I am so sorry
about this.
No, it's cool.
It's cool.
This is ridiculous.
Gloria didn't steal me, dede,
and you know it.
We grew apart for years.
And you left to find yourself,
remember?
I thought
I could handle this.
I'm so sorry.
You don't say "sorry"
anymore!
That word means nothing
in your mouth!
I got gloria.
I don't know
what just happened.
Dylan: I do.
I mean,
it seems pretty simple to me.
You're reaching out, trying
to hold on to something awesome.
Um, maybe --
maybe you shouldn't --
Look, look, look,
I'm noused to this,
The whole big-family thing.
In my house, we don't even talk
to each other.
You know, it's funny.
The first time I saw haley,
I knew I liked her.
I mean, she's beautiful
and everything,
But it's --
it's not just that.
It's that she's got
this killer confidence --
You know,
the kind of confidence
That you get
from having a family like this,
That's passionate
and accepting of hot foreigners
And gay dudes
and nutty people --
You know, a family
that actually loves each other.
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this,
But maybe we should let her
go with him.
He's perfect.
Everybody, haley says
that dylan is a musician,
And he writes
some great songs.
Play something, bro.
Well, I guess so,
if you want me to.
We could all use a nice tune
right now.
This is actually a song
I wrote for haley.
It's called
"in the moonlight."
Lovely title, dylan.
Thanks.
* the stars are falling
from the sky *
* and you're the reason why *
* the moon is shining
on your face *
* 'cause it finally feels
it's found its place *
* 'cause, baby, baby,
I just want to do you *
* do you *
* do you want to do me *
* do me *
* underneath the moonlight *
* the moonlight? *
* baby, baby,
maybe I will steal you *
* steal you *
* just so I can feel you *
* feel you *
* maybe that would heal you *
* heal you on the inside *
She's so not going.
Not a chance in hell.
* the moon is shining
* they doon your face *nd *
* and it finally feels it's *
* found its place 'cause *
* baby, baby,
I just want to do you *
* do you *
* baby, you can do me *
* do me *
* man, I will do you *
* do you *
* maybe it would heal you *
* heal you *
Both:
* from the inside *
Sync by honeybunny & bardwill
www.addic7ed.com
Never good at harmonizing.
* side *    that was good.
www.tvsubtitles.net