When the enemy attacked, you ran away.
That's treason.
Now it's time to splatter
your brains everywhere.
Please! Please, don't kill me!
Shut up! Die like a man!
But I have a wife and family.
That's what happens to cowards.
Hey. You have to keep it down.
There's an important
meeting going on.
Sorry.
I'll set you up
in the copy room.
You won't be in the way there.
This is gonna be a close vote.
Most of your colleagues
are not gonna want to spend this
amount of money in just 25 districts.
Try persuasion first.
Talking points
are in your packets.
And if you want more detailed
information, research, statistics,
you can contact
Gillian or myself.
And when it comes to doling
out favors, talk to Doug.
If favors don't work, come
to me directly. Peter.
I'll be campaigning
in Pennsylvania.
All my events this week will be
in counties within the watershed,
so I'll be working
the media angle.
But if you need me to get
on the phone with anybody,
reach out to Christina. She'll
work it into my schedule.
I have to say, Frank, $200 million
is going to be a hard sell.
The natural gas lobby's already
putting up a big fight.
We need to make
this about jobs.
But the drilling industry can offer
far more jobs than this bill can.
This bill doesn't
threaten those jobs,
it just makes sure the
drilling is done responsibly.
It adds more jobs
on top of that.
I've already been approached by
SanCorp with re-election funds.
I have too. They offered
me a donation package
from eight different
drilling companies.
Remy Danton? Yep.
How many of you been
approached by Remy?
Look, I know it's not
easy to turn down money.
But if the Republicans control
redistricting in Pennsylvania,
we lose the House
next election,
and all of you lose your
committee chairmanships.
This is a feather that
we need in Peter's hat.
A loss on this bill endangers
his chance of winning,
and we are fighting to
keep our majority here.
Any other concerns?
I want a first vote count
by 4:00 tomorrow afternoon.
Thank you all very much.
It's brutal. Twenty-two
stops in three days.
It's a lot of sleeping on the bus.
No sleeping.
That bus is the only place
I can get work done.
You know, Francis did a
big bus tour in 1998,
and the bus lost its
brakes going down a hill
and we landed in
a tobacco field.
He gets out of the car,
knocks on the farmer's door,
writes a check for
all the damaged crops,
and then borrows his pickup so
he doesn't miss the next event.
And it was actually fun.
He was driving. I was shotgun, and they
had the whole staff in the flatbed.
We actually got
there 10 minutes early.
I think I should be here
to help drum up votes.
Careful, sir. It's very hot.
Look, you and
the Vice President
are gonna get
national coverage.
That's gonna help us
with the count.
I reached out to him. He
never got back to me.
I don't know if he even knows the
talking points about the bill.
I don't think Jim wants to go.
He's doing it as a favor
to the President and I,
so it doesn't matter if he
doesn't know the talking points.
People wanna see him
be folksy, you know?
So just humor him. Show
him some degree of...
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
It was an accident.
Okay, it's time for us to go.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right. I just need to
run it under some cold water.
I'm not going to lie.
I despise children.
There. I've said it.
You can't act
like that in here.
You have to be
a big boy.
I know.
Peter, we really
need to get going.
We've already missed one flight
because the meeting went over.
I booked us another
one at 9:25, but...
We have to drop
the kids off at school.
It's going to be really tight.
If we miss this plane, we have
to cancel our first event.
Nancy, can you take them?
I've gotta get packets ready
for the lunchtime subcaucuses.
Peter, I'd do it, but we have a meeting
with Greenpeace in 20 minutes.
I gotta get their
rating on the bill.
Where's their school?
Connecticut and Q.
Oh, I can take them. You sure?
Yes. It's on the way
to my office.
This Watershed Act
proves that once again
the anti-capitalist agenda is alive
and well in the Democratic party.
Let me show you
what's really going on.
Here are the Democrats eating
up all of their soft science,
"organically
homegrown" propaganda
that the eco-fanatics
are force-feeding them.
And over here, at the tail-end
of all those jackasses,
are middle-class Americans.
People who just
want to work hard
and rely on jobs in
the drilling industry.
And what about
the hypocrisy, folks?
Does Peter Russo
honestly have the gall
to lecture us on
the purity of our rivers,
when he has been polluting himself
with chemicals for years?
He's not just been eating
grass, he's been smoking it.
It's the only major bill
he's sponsored in six years.
I know, but they already have national coverage.
What's the angle?
If it doesn't pass,
I think he'll lose support from
the Shipbuilders' Association.
So they lose support.
It's not that juicy.
They're a huge part of his
get-out-the-vote effort in Philly.
It sounds like inside baseball.
Not if I get the vote count.
Black and white numbers.
Nobody has that.
But when I called the campaign,
they stone-walled me.
Same thing at
the Whip's office.
Do you know anyone over there?
In Underwood's office?
No, I don't.
Nobody on staff?
Mm-mmm. Oh.
I just figured because you
gave me the Russo profile.
No, that didn't come from them.
But Underwood
organized the campaign.
I'm sorry.
I don't know
anybody there.
Okay.
Hey, it's me. I just wanted
to fill you in on something.
I should be back home at 10:00.
Meet me there.
- Sarah made
this one.
- It's a frog.
And I made this one. Can
you guess what it is?
A lobster?
No. It's a scorpion. They're for you.
For the ones you gave us.
Oh, they're beautiful.
But maybe you should bring
them to school, no?
For show-and-tell? Or give
them to your friends.
No. The other kids will
just make fun of us.
Why?
Everybody hates us at school.
They say Dad's a crackhead
and that we're crack babies.
I looked up "crack baby" on the computer.
I don't look like that.
You know, they say Dad's
gonna OD like Amy Winehouse.
Well, you tell them
that your dad
doesn't do that kind of
thing anymore, right?
Yeah, we do,
but they don't believe us.
Did you try going
to the teachers?
We can't do that. Everyone
would just hate us even more.
Well, you can't worry about
what other people think, right?
I wish Dad wasn't
running for governor.
You ever been to Allentown before?
I have not.
What do you think?
Compared to New York,
the parking is easier.
Finding a decent bagel,
not so much.
We'd make up for it
with the cream cheese.
Shall we? Ready when you are.
Your Watershed Bill.
You've ticked off the
Republicans, oil, gas...
Sometimes you gotta upset a few
people to do the right thing.
Not just a few. There's
a sizable coalition
that wants to
see your bill fail,
including environmentalists
from your own party
who don't think
the bill does enough.
We wanted a passable bill.
That's why we aimed
for a middle ground...
Do you actually care about
the Delaware River?
I don't sponsor legislation
I don't care about.
Until recently, you hadn't
sponsored any legislation at all.
I spent my time in Congress
focusing on things that were
important to my constituents.
The shipyard.
Kept it open
as long as I could.
Okay. That's one thing.
What are the others?
I'd love to
provide you a list of
all the things
I've done in Congress,
but we've got 15 minutes...
Your opponent has
linked your inactivity
to your fondness
for single-malts.
I've been very
open about my past,
and I've done everything
I can to overcome it
in a responsible,
permanent way.
And I preferred
vodka to scotch.
You should get
your facts straight.
Is your Watershed Act just a
ploy to jump into the spotlight
and pad your transcript while
you apply for governor school?
It's real money.
It's real jobs.
And when the Delaware River is less
polluted than it's been in 50 years,
it's holding up a real glass of its
water and seeing how clear it is.
That's what my
bus tour is about.
The Vice President is
joining you later? Correct.
Why has it taken him this
long to endorse you?
He didn't think I was worth it.
But then he heard I had a
one-on-one with The New York Times,
and, boom, he was on board.
I might print that.
The more of my words,
the fewer of yours,
the better off we'll both be.
If I didn't think you were such a
liability to yourself, Congressman,
I might even like you.
If your circulation was as high
as The Wall Street Journal,
I might like you back.
Hit me. Next question.
I have to
put up a fight, Frank.
Tell them they're
wasting their money.
It's gonna pass. Are you sure?
When was the last time
I got a count wrong?
If you were certain, you wouldn't
be trying to neutralize us.
Well, SanCorp has been
good to me.
I'm just trying to do you
and them a favor, Remy.
Then why propose the legislation
in the first place?
You must've known
they would oppose it.
The regulatory
restrictions are minimal.
There's a bigger
battle here, Frank.
SanCorp is against any
step toward regulation,
no matter how small.
Russo's planted his feet on
the wrong side of the fence.
How much are you
giving his opponent?
Check the FEC filings.
How much are you
actually giving?
It's a $10 billion industry, Frank.
There's money to spend.
If the Democrats lose Pennsylvania,
you know what that means.
We don't want you
to lose leadership,
but that's up to you, not us.
You don't have the same kind of
relationship with the Republicans
that you have with me.
Then we'll adapt.
We both have votes
to count. Good luck.
You tell SanCorp
they're being foolish.
I'm not gonna do that.
Well, then,
you're being foolish.
Come on, Frank. Let's
not make this personal.
I can't compete with
SanCorp's war chest.
My only option is asymmetrical.
To pick off the opposition one by
one like a sniper in the woods.
There will come a time to
put Remy in my crosshairs,
but not right now.
As we used to say in Gaffney,
"Never slap a man while
he's chewing tobacco."
Congressman, how are you?
I deeply appreciate you taking
the time out of your schedule...
Hank, I need to eat.
See if you can rustle up a
club sandwich, extra bacon.
Fuck me.
Ta-da.
Thai cuisine again.
The green curry is for you, and
the other green curry is for me.
I was actually
just on my way out.
I bought you dinner.
You have to eat it.
Or at the very least, you
have to watch me eat mine.
I'm gonna be late
to meet someone.
Who? Like, a date?
A friend.
The mysterious fuck-buddy who you
get all of your stories from?
Lighten up. I was just teasing.
Not that I would judge.
We've all done it.
I used to suck, screw and jerk anything
that moved just to get a story.
Really? Like who?
You want dish?
No. It's just...
The Comm Director on Ben
Schroeder's Senate race.
A staffer in
the Defense Department.
My very own White House intern.
He was a real blabbermouth when
he wasn't eating me out. Wow.
And I even had a fling
with a Congressman.
Which one?
You tell me yours,
and I'll tell you mine.
I've never been with any.
Oh, come on. You're hot.
You're telling me that none
of them have come on to you?
I haven't really
been in those circles.
You are now.
I guess I don't really
give off that vibe.
You mean the slut vibe?
Look, I don't
do that shit anymore.
'Cause once word got out,
it was like I hit a wall,
and nobody took me seriously.
So, a piece of advice, as far
as career strategies go,
it's not worth fucking
your way to the middle.
Chopsticks or fork?
Look, if you go, I am gonna
have to eat both of these,
and that is not cool.
No. I'll eat with you.
Good.
Things have gotten underway
in Eastern Pennsylvania
for the governor's seat left vacant
there by Vice President Jim Matthews.
After a political career that
has lasted 42 years so far,
the genial Vice President and the
former Pennsylvania Governor,
faces the most critical task
of his new electoral life
helping his home state fill the vacancy
of his departure from Washington.
However, Matthews
seems reluctant
to hand over the spotlight
to Peter Russo.
Back home, Meechum.
Sir.
Francis...
How's your hand?
Fine.
You should change
the bandage, no?
Later.
I thought you were
gonna be out late.
No.
You seem upset. I'm not.
What happened? Nothing.
Can I get more than
two words out of you?
I'm just trying to relax.
Claire, I love you.
I love you too.
Did Zoe expect me to twiddle
my thumbs until her arrival?
Perhaps she's
making the mistake
thinking her time
is as valuable as mine.
Proximity to power deludes some
into believing they wield it.
I put an end to that sort of
thinking before it begins.
And if I'm not mistaken, the
last time I was in Tannersville,
Buddy Corcharan pulled me aside
and told me I was
wasting my time,
because the Republicans were gonna
sweep Monroe County in a landslide.
Well, Buddy had to eat his
hat and both his shoes
when I won the county
in a landslide.
And let me tell you,
that man has big feet
and an even bigger head,
so that was quite a meal.
My daddy used to tell
me a story about people
who count their chickens
before they hatched.
Although, to be fair,
he probably didn't know
what he was talking about,
because he grew
up in Pittsburgh.
And I certainly never saw
a hen around my house,
unless you count my mother.
Do you want me to do something?
But, seriously, folks...
No. Let him talk.
I do love this town.
I don't know if he's ever
going to introduce you.
He will. Just give him time.
It's been an hour.
We were supposed to leave for
Carbondale 10 minutes ago.
I can't interrupt him.
He's the Vice President.
We're not on the edge
of Penn's Woods.
We need economic development
flowcharts for the Watershed Bill
sent over to
Terry Womack's office.
Hard copies, 20 of them.
I'll do it right away.
How's everything
going with Rachel?
I think she's
a little down in the dumps.
She got a waitressing job last
week, and then they let her go.
Why? She wouldn't tell me.
All she said was
her boss was a creep.
Thirty minutes ago, I
received a text from Zoe.
She intends to apologize,
no doubt.
I respect that she wants
to atone in person,
even though it's taken her over
16 hours to build up the courage.
Janine Skorsky is digging
into Peter Russo.
What in particular?
The Shipbuilder's Association.
She have an angle?
The Watershed Bill is a consolation
prize for them losing their jobs.
That's not
an unfair assessment.
She thinks if the bill fails to
pass, they'll withdraw support.
Not unfair speculation.
Well, I know how hard you've
been working on his campaign,
so I wanted to
give you a heads up.
Well, let me know if she
expands her inquiry.
Into what?
Anything you deem
worth telling.
Well, can I throw her a bone?
She might be more talkative if
I have information for her.
What sort of bone?
The vote count for the bill.
I don't have a vote count yet.
Should have a preliminary
one this afternoon.
You'll let me know?
As soon as I have
something solid.
There's one more thing.
About last night...
No need to apologize.
I'm sure you had
a very good reason.
I do.
I think we should end it.
Not professionally,
the other thing.
Why now?
We have a really good
working relationship.
I don't wanna
overcomplicate that.
All right.
You're okay with it?
Completely.
It's over.
And it won't change things
in terms of our arrangement?
Oh, please. I don't punish people
for making adult decisions.
Thank you, Francis.
She was never more than a
faint blip on my radar.
We've served
each other's purpose.
If she wants to be an adult,
let her see how she can fly
once she leaves the nest.
Claire. Hi. Catherine.
Thank you for fitting me in.
I can always find time
for you and Frank.
Well, the reason I'm here
is the CWI has a large shipment
of water filters
stuck in South Sudan,
and they've been in storage
for the past four months,
just sitting there, and the
Sudanese government...
Won't release the shipments
through customs.
My deputy briefed
me on the latest.
Right. And I know that Francis spoke
to you about this not too long ago,
but lately we haven't heard
much from the State Department,
so I was wondering
if you could help.
We've done our best, Claire.
I put my top people on this.
The Sudanese are
just not responding.
Well, is there
anything else we can do?
There's over $200,000
worth of equipment.
I wish I could. I know how
important this is to you,
but we're about to cut
off diplomatic ties.
It's a directive straight
from the President.
We can't ignore their human
rights violations anymore.
What about back channels?
Well, once we cut ties,
I can't contact their government
officially or unofficially.
Well, is there someone you
could put me in touch with?
I'm sorry, Claire.
My hands are tied.
I would move mountains for you and
Frank, but I've done all I can.
Of course.
Okay. Good to see you. You too.
Congressman,
you have a major bill
going to the floor
later this week.
Are you optimistic it'll pass?
I'm very optimistic.
The Delaware
River Watershed Act
not only protects
large portions of
the state's
freshwater resources,
it also creates
thousands of jobs.
I'm confident that my
colleagues on the Hill...
There's only one way
to create jobs.
I did it during
my administration.
The answer is tax credits
for small businesses.
You've got to encourage
self-starting entrepreneurs
to start new ventures,
hire employees...
But specifically, about
the Watershed Act...
Small businesses,
that's the solution.
Everything else
is window dressing.
Thank you all very much.
Thank you.
Good night, Mr. Vice President.
Hello.
I need to talk about Matthews.
Yes. I've read
the press reports.
He's not being
very helpful, is he?
No, he's doing
more harm than good.
I want to ask him to leave.
Well, that wouldn't make
for a very good story.
It's better than him
torpedoing the whole bus tour.
Have you tried to talk to him?
No, I wanted to ask
your advice first.
Well, maybe there's a way
to keep him on the tour
and inspire his support.
We have fundamentally
different views.
Well, look, you're not going to
be able to change his ideology,
but dig deeper.
Jim is a proud man.
Tap into that pride.
I just wish he was gone.
Well, you do whatever
you think best.
But whatever it is you decide,
be firm and stand up
for yourself.
He'll respond to that at least.
And call me back
if you need anything.
What was the reason he gave you?
Were you messing up?
No. The head waiter said I
was doing a really good job.
He even started letting me take
my own tables on the second day.
And the manager...
What's his name?
Leon.
He propositioned you?
Called me into his office,
said couldn't afford to
start taking anyone new on,
even part-time.
Put his hand on my knee,
said he might be able
to make an exception.
So he starts sliding
his hand up my thigh.
So I stood up and I tell him
I should get back to work.
He says, "Stay."
He unbuckled his belt.
Did you?
No, I walked out of the office
and got back to my tables.
Next day, I came into
work, told me to go home.
I was fired.
Tell me the name
of the restaurant.
You're home early.
I needed a breather. I didn't
have breakfast this morning.
I might head back
in a little while.
The vote count?
It's going to come down
to the wire on this one.
I spoke to
Catherine Durant today.
She's unable to get the
shipment out of South Sudan.
Yeah, we're cutting
all diplomatic ties.
Foreign Affairs is
up in arms about it.
Yes. Which is why she can't lift
a finger, according to her.
It's what she said, anyway.
Anyway, I need you
to talk to her.
I don't think that would
make any difference.
I thought she owed us, Francis.
She does, but there's limits.
She's Secretary of State. She
can't break diplomatic protocol.
Well, can you make some calls?
If she can't, I can't. Plus I have
to focus on the Watershed Bill.
I'm taking time out of my
schedule to help you with that.
Because you drafted it.
Because you asked me.
I didn't want to do this.
All I'm asking is
that you give me
a little bit of
your time in return.
And how am I supposed to
fix a problem I can't fix?
What about Remy?
Glendon Hill must have
contacts in South Sudan.
He's fighting us on the vote.
Those are two completely
separate issues.
They are not. He does you a
favor, he hangs it over me.
So what you're saying is my
goals are secondary to yours.
That is not what I'm saying.
I think you don't
want to go hat in hand
to somebody who
used to work for you.
I will not be lectured to the
moment you walk in the door!
I called Catherine,
as promised!
Her inability to deliver is
not my problem or my fault!
I cannot control changing
global landscapes!
And I will not be cornered into
making promises I cannot deliver!
I'm sorry I yelled.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
You're right,
I didn't think it through.
I just can't go
to Remy right now.
He's poaching too
many of my people.
I've got two congressmen
who will not commit.
I was hoping you
might speak to them.
Who?
Vanderburgh and Abrams.
What is it you want me
to say to them?
They're big on the environment.
They don't think
the bill goes far enough.
They respect your opinion.
I wanted you to walk them
through the bill step-by-step.
Put them at ease. I need to
get them in the yes column.
I meet with them tomorrow.
I'll deliver the bruises.
You meet with them later
and patch them up.
That might just do the trick.
Of course.
I think I broke the bowl.
We have contacts there
through our oil interests.
I'm going to need
government intervention.
Wherever there's a
government, we know people.
Even when there's only the
illusion of a government.
Will you help me?
I'd like to.
But for something like this, I'm
afraid there's a price tag.
The CWI will endorse
SanCorp as eco-friendly.
They can use our logo on any PR
or marketing
materials you want.
We'll need more than that.
They were willing to donate
over $1 million for that.
These filters are only worth $200,000.
I'd say that's a bargain.
You turned down that offer.
Landscape has
shifted since then.
The Watershed Bill?
That's right.
You want it amended?
I want you to kill it,
the whole thing.
CWI has publicly
backed the bill, Remy.
What you do publicly
is your concern.
Gentlemen. Please, have a seat.
So, have either of you changed
your mind since we last spoke?
We're still undecided, Frank.
Leaning one way or the other?
If Congress is going to
allocate $250 million dollars,
we want to make sure
it goes towards a bill
that does more
to protect the...
We've been through all that.
I know your concerns.
So if the protection
standards don't change,
we would rather see that money
spent more effectively elsewhere.
That sounds like
you're both leaning no.
We've been very clear
about what we're asking.
Okay.
This is you, Abrams.
And this is you, Vanderburgh.
And over here
is the majority of
the Democratic Caucus.
See, you're over there
all by your lonesome.
Now, you don't mind
being the black sheep.
You're the liberal wing
of the liberal wing.
Most of the time you can vote what you
want, we still pass things anyway.
But this time it does matter.
And what the two of you
aren't taking into account
is between this end of the
desk and this end of the desk,
is me.
Now, I'm going to say to you
what I say to every congressman
that sits where
you're sitting now.
Vote your district.
Vote your conscience.
Don't surprise me.
And the most
important one of those
is don't surprise me.
Now, you're both to meet
with my wife tomorrow.
And you're to hear her out.
She will go through your
concerns point-by-point.
And I am certain after that
that the two of you will
make the right decision.
This is the part
where you leave.
I have often found
that bleeding hearts
have an ironic fear
of their own blood.
One drop and they seize up.
But offer them a caring hand
and massage them back to life
and they soon start beating
to the right drum.
Hello.
I've just spoken to
Abrams and Vanderburgh.
Let them toss and turn tonight,
but they're all yours tomorrow.
I'll reach out to their
offices and set a time.
Thank you, Claire.
Of course.
Whatever I can do to help.
Here you go, sir. Enjoy.
Excuse me.
There's a hair on my steak.
I am so sorry, sir. Where?
Right there.
I don't see it.
Are you telling me I'm blind?
No, sir. I'm so sorry.
I'll have the kitchen...
What's your name? Stephanie.
You can leave the plate,
Stephanie.
I'd like to talk
to the manager.
Yes, sir. I'll go get him.
Thank you.
Good evening, sir.
Stephanie tells me there
was a hair on your plate.
No.
There wasn't any hair. Leon, right?
That's your name?
Yes.
Stephanie is a hot little
number, isn't she?
Nice ass.
Did you make her blow you
before or after you hired her?
Sir, I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Sit down, Leon.
Sir, I want you to go.
I said sit. Don't make
me call the police.
I'll tell you what.
You call the police, I'll call
the Department of Immigration
about the four
undocumented employees
you have working
in the kitchen.
A felony, Leon.
And I might also mention your
girlfriend, her mother, and her aunt
who are also undocumented and
living in an apartment you pay for.
Prison time for you,
deportation for them.
Not a pretty picture, is it?
Let's talk about Rachel Posner.
How close is it?
I should have the last two
votes I need committed today.
I just want to make sure
no one changes their mind.
I'd prefer not to get embroiled
in environmental
issues at this time.
But it's also
a jobs creation package.
It's antagonizing oil and gas.
We can't afford
that sort of battle
after all the capital
we spent on education.
All I need is one public
statement of support.
I won't do that. How about
you take Linda tomorrow?
You set her up in your offices.
Any meetings or calls you
might need to whip up votes,
you've got her there.
Well, I can't afford to spend a
whole day lobbying on the Hill.
Well, you've got deputies.
Yes, I do.
Well, you're telling me you can't
manage them from 10 blocks away?
Of course I can, sir.
Look, if it's too difficult...
No, no, no. We'll help you out, Frank.
Won't we, Linda?
Yes. If you'll just excuse me,
I have a few things to
rearrange on my schedule.
What else, Frank? Tell
me what Birch is up to.
No, I know I've
already canceled twice.
They start next week.
Sweetie, I'm trying
to figure this out.
Linda. Excuse me. Yes?
I just wanted to thank you
for agreeing to pitch in,
I know you have a full plate.
Of course, Frank.
Is everything all right?
It sounds like...
Yes. What time do you want
me to come by tomorrow?
Can we talk?
Can I just call you back in one second?
I will call you. Yes.
Linda, I am so sorry that the
President has forced you into this.
It was not my intention.
If you would like, I can
talk to Congress...
No, it's not that. It's a personal matter.
Don't worry.
Well, what is it?
Maybe I can help.
Just, my son didn't
get into Stanford.
I was supposed to meet
with the Provost tomorrow
to see if I could get
him to change his mind.
I asked the President if I
could go, and he said yes,
but he must have forgotten.
You should go. I'm sure the
President will understand.
No, no. I don't let
personal matters
get in the way
of my job, Frank.
Linda, you can't put your
entire life on hold.
And certainly not at the
expense of your own son.
Well, it has been at
the expense of my son.
It's my fault he didn't get in.
I was on the campaign and
I wasn't there for him.
His grades suffered.
His application was...
I wasn't there, Frank.
But I figured if
I could just meet
with the Provost
face to face...
Okay, look, you are going
to Stanford tomorrow.
If you show up at my office,
I won't let you in,
so don't even consider it.
Frank, the President
wants me to be...
He doesn't have to know.
I'm going to have one of my
schedulers buy you a ticket.
The bill will be fine.
Frank.
You don't have to do this.
We may have our
disagreements, Linda,
but that doesn't mean we can't
look out for each other.
You tell them you're coming.
Okay. Give that a try.
Test, test, test.
All right, Zoe. This is Dave, the
senior producer in New York.
We'll go live in four minutes.
Sounds good.
The first topic will be the Congressional
agenda for the fall session,
then we'll move
on to the midterms,
then we'll wrap it up with Peter
Russo's race for governor
and his Watershed Bill.
Okay, great.
Taking you off
mic until 30 out.
Hey, Janine, I have to talk
about the Watershed Bill.
Do you have a one sheet?
Yeah. Hold on.
Thanks.
Any word on the vote count?
Still no luck.
I've called every Democrat in the
House to cobble together a number,
but no one's
getting back to me.
So what can I say?
That there's a lot in
flux, and it'll be tight.
Okay. Thanks.
Yeah. Sure thing.
Hey, Francis, it's me.
Call me back.
Yes.
Congressman Russo.
He says it's urgent.
Fine.
Good morning, sir.
I'd like to talk about
how the tour's going.
Well, let's talk on the bus.
Don't we have an event at 11:00?
There won't be any
events until we talk.
You're hijacking
the microphone.
You're contradicting
everything I say.
We need to be promoting
the Watershed Act.
Well, I appreciate your
being so forthright.
Let me tell you what
I don't appreciate.
The DNC is running a man
with zero track record,
except for substance
abuse, to fill my shoes.
I realize you don't
want to be here, sir,
but it seems like you're deliberately
trying to sabotage my campaign.
Despite my better judgment,
I'm trying to save it.
I know the people of this
state better than you, Peter.
They don't want to hear about watersheds.
They want to hear about jobs.
Well, this week,
they need to hear both.
Well, then,
maybe I should just stand
quietly beside
you at the podium
and watch you lose.
You don't think I can win, do you?
I'm not optimistic.
You lost the first two times
you ran for governor.
The third time, nobody
thought you had a chance.
By September, you were 15 points down.
You were out of money.
You had to mortgage
your own house
just to keep your
staff on payroll.
I'm well aware of what I did.
I was there.
My point is you kept going.
You hit 67 counties
in less than 20 days,
and you proved everyone wrong.
Like it or not, it's my name
on the ticket this time,
and I got the shot, and I'm
gonna prove everyone wrong,
just like you did.
Including you, sir.
I would like your support,
but if you won't give it, fine.
It won't stop me.
You think it's easy
for me to be here?
I left the Governor's
mansion right in my prime.
To be what? Vice President.
I thought that was a step up.
But you know what? I don't have a
fucking shred of real influence.
I'm trotted around like a goddamn
mascot, and this is my home state.
I'm offering you
influence, sir.
I'd like your guidance
and your expertise.
But if that's not on the
table, then, well...
With all due respect,
Mr. Vice President,
you should head
back to Washington.
Your husband was very explicit.
I would categorize it
as a threat.
What did he say exactly?
Not to surprise him.
Didn't he also tell you to vote
your district and your conscience?
He did, but those seemed far
lower on his priority list.
Well, he would never fault you
if you had a compelling reason
to do what you think is right.
I'm confused.
Aren't you for this bill?
CWI is publicly for it.
Privately, I have my doubts
for the same reasons you do.
I was under the impression
that we were here
so you could
persuade us to vote yes.
I'm not trying to
persuade you of anything.
I will say this.
If the bill fails, it's
not the end of the world.
We can always
sponsor new legislation.
You know, something with
stricter regulatory standards.
Just to be clear,
you're telling us
you don't mind if we
vote against the bill?
I'm simply saying
what my husband would...
That you should
vote your conscience.
How are we looking?
We're short a vote.
I just got off
the phone with Claire.
Vanderburgh and Abrams
are on board.
Those are definite yeses?
Definite.
We should be good.
Yes?
I've been trying to reach
you since yesterday.
Well, I've been a bit
busy counting votes.
You said you'd
have a number for me.
Well, you should try
my press office.
I did.
They won't return
my calls.
Well, the official word
is it will be close.
I'm trying to get
the unofficial word.
I can't appear to be playing
favorites now, can I?
This isn't because of
the other day, is it?
What other day?
You said we'd keep our
professional relationship.
Well, this is what
professional feels like.
The Vice President of the
United States, Jim Matthews!
Thank you.
It's good to be
back in Bristol.
Go, warriors!
Now, you all know me.
I'm a windbag.
I can go on until
you all fall asleep,
get eight hours of shut-eye, and
wake up to find me still yapping.
And there's a lot I could say
about this young man to my left.
The truth is, I've had a lot of
doubts about him and his ideas,
about his past,
about his youth.
But if you'll remember,
a lot of you had doubts about
me the first time I ran.
And the second and the third.
But over the last few days,
traveling around
the state with Peter,
I have to admit
he's won me over.
He's smart, he's energetic, and
most important, he's a fighter.
Now, it says "A fresh start!"
on that bus over there.
And that's the real truth,
because this young man
will give our state
the fresh start
it so desperately needs.
Ladies and gentlemen, the next
Governor of Pennsylvania,
Peter Russo.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
How's it going, Bristol?
Today I'd like to talk to you
about economic recovery.
Now, as many of you
may be aware,
mostly because my opponent
feels the need to spend millions of
dollars on TV ads about my past,
I know a thing or two
about recovery.
I've learned a great deal
through my personal struggles.
I've learned how to harness
my strength and my resolve,
make them work for me,
much the way your
Bristol watermills
harnessed the power of
your beautiful Otter Creek
and the mighty
Delaware River years ago.
Let me tell you how
the Delaware River
will reinvigorate your
economy for years to come!
We're going to get the
shipment out of Sudan.
That's great.
It might take
a few weeks,
but I think you should start
making arrangements for Botswana,
where you're gonna set up
base camp and the depot.
Just send me a budget as
soon as you've got one.
Claire, is there any way we
can send someone in my place?
I thought you wanted
to be on the ground.
I would, but I can't this time.
Why not?
I wasn't sure how to tell you this,
but I passed the 12-week mark.
You're expecting?
Gillian, that's wonderful.
That... When did this happen?
Who's the father?
There was this guy I met overseas.
Doctors Without Borders.
We had this thing. Then I left.
But he came back to the
States a few months ago,
and that's when it happened.
Anyway, it didn't end well.
But I want to keep the baby.
And does he know?
He's married.
I shouldn't have. It was stupid.
You don't have to explain.
I'll need some time off at
the beginning of March.
Of course.
And absolutely, we'll send
someone else instead.
I appreciate it, Claire.
Sure.
You said medium rare?
Just let me know if you
guys need anything.
Who would you guess
texted me just now?
I thought she'd last
more than a couple days.
Going somewhere?
Just for
an hour or two.
I got one last
hold-out to whip.
What's the vote count
on Russo's bill?
Don't you wanna shower first before
we dirty ourselves with business?
I'll shower after you leave.
What's the vote count?
Your tone doesn't inspire
me to be very forthcoming.
The fuck wasn't enough? You
need a special tone too?
Ooh...
Someone washed her mouth out
with acid this morning.
Whatever it is
you're grappling with,
I am sincerely not interested.
You're almost twice my age.
You said that
didn't bother you.
I lied.
If you had a daughter,
she'd be older than me.
In 20 years, I'll still be
younger than you are now.
Well, I can't argue
with basic arithmetic.
You don't find that disgusting?
I think you want me to.
But I've never considered
this any more or less
than a transaction between
two consenting adults.
If you just want the girl who
will do your bidding for you,
you already have that.
Why do you need to fuck me?
I would remind you that it was
you who initiated our affair,
and it was you who came knocking
at my door last winter.
And it was me who asked that
we stop what we're doing now.
Which I respected until
you picked up a phone
and asked me to
come over tonight.
Because you wouldn't give me
what I wanted unless I did.
So tell me,
why do you need this?
You don't seem to get
any pleasure out of it.
I know I certainly don't.
I seem to always
leave you satisfied.
How do you know
I'm not faking it?
Are you?
Doesn't it say a lot
that you can't tell?
What do you think about when
I'm up against the wall?
A great man once said that
"Everything in life is about sex...
"Except sex.
"Sex is about power."
So you need a whore,
which makes you a pimp.
I'm not a pimp.
Just a very generous john.
Fine.
As long as we're clear about what
this is, I can play the whore.
Now pay me.
The bill will pass. We
have it by two votes.
You can pass that along to
your friend, Ms. Skorsky.
If she must say such things in
order to sleep at night, so be it.
Her loyalty costs me nothing but
the occasional crumb of news.
Her hatefulness
takes no toll at all.
You don't compensate a working
girl so you can cuddle after.
Final voting...
A lot of small towns,
some really great crowds.
No buses losing their brakes.
Final call for voting.
Please, no.
When do you head back?
Tomorrow. We wanna do a press
conference when all the votes are in.
Members, please cast
your votes now.
Are you all right?
I'm just a little nauseous.
It'll pass. I'm okay.
You said you're due in March?
March 14th.
It must be so exciting.
How's the morning sickness?
I think I'm over the hump. I
have to pee all the time.
Weird cravings.
It was good
to be on the road again.
Invigorating.
Our internals are showing a
nice bump in the numbers.
You made a big difference, sir.
The President
is grateful,
and so am I.
Well, it's a team
effort, right?
Excuse me. I have yet to say
hello to your better half.
How'd it go at Stanford?
Well, I think.
The Dean's a Republican, so there
was not a lot of small talk.
But he seemed open
to considering it.
We'll know more next week.
That's terrific.
I appreciate
your helping me out.
I didn't do anything. Anybody
could book a plane ticket.
That's not true.
You covered for me.
Well, we have to keep the important
things in perspective, right?
Don't think it's
bought you any favors.
Kindness isn't kindness
if you expect a reward.
The man of the hour!
Not yet. The votes
are still coming in.
Hey, how'd you vote?
I voted yes.
Voting.
I knew I forgot something.
We got this.
There's some sparkling grape
juice there to celebrate.
Thirty seconds remaining.
Thirty seconds. Looking good.
Come on, everyone. Let's go.
Everyone's voting
along party lines.
See? This is what happens
when we all stick together.
This is an easy win for us.
Fifteen seconds.
Vote now.
Ten seconds.
Fuck. This can't be happening.
Members, please cast
your votes now.
Voting is closed. H.R.
4913 is defeated.
Doug. I thought we had it.
So this means it's dead?
It's such a shame.
All of that hard work.
I wanna know who lied.
www.tvsubtitles.net