What was that?
A faucet.
It wouldn't shut up.
Did you sleep last night?
No.
I'll call Nancy and tell
her to call a plumber.
Absolute discretion.
Can I count on that?
Always.
Raymond Tusk.
The President wants to
tap him as the new VP.
You and I cannot
let that happen.
Why not?
Because a third of his fortune
is tied up in nuclear energy.
SanCorp does not
want a pro-nuclear
businessman in the White House.
Market is shifting toward
natural gas anyway.
But Tusk wants to stall
that shift or reverse it.
Vice President doesn't have
that kind of influence.
This one would. He and
Walker are very close.
And it's in neither
of our best interests
to see SanCorp's position in
the marketplace diminished.
What's the ask? Tusk won't
accept the nomination
if he thinks
his holdings are at risk.
SanCorp needs to initiate
a hostile takeover.
He's worth three times
what SanCorp is.
I'm talking about
the subsidiaries.
We go after the companies that
refine and ship the uranium,
the support system that...
Come on, Frank.
There's stockholders to take into
account, huge financial exposure.
We just need to distract him.
Send a few token salvos and
intimate there's more to come.
All I'm asking is that
you speak to your client
and see if this is something they
might be willing to consider.
The President
announces Tusk on Friday,
so we don't have a lot of time.
I'll make some calls.
Thank you, Remy.
If he doesn't deliver, I'm
an invader without an army.
If he does,
I've got a fighting chance.
I just didn't feel
that we could work
together constructively
any longer.
I think that's a perfectly
legitimate reason...
Of course it is.
But what you can't do is fire
someone for being pregnant.
Is that what she's saying?
Ms. Cole claims that you said,
quote, I need employees,
not mothers,
and, quote,
go focus on your baby.
Can I see that?
It's completely false. I...
I never said that.
She claims you did.
It's her word
against mine, right?
Well, juries are very sympathetic
with expecting mothers.
This is extortion.
We don't want this
going to trial, Claire.
You and your husband
are public figures.
This will result in
some very bad press.
I suggest we go back to them
with a settlement offer.
We need the arrest record.
There isn't any.
They let him go.
Then we need to know
who got him off.
If Underwood was involved,
we are talking abuse of
powers and corruption.
I checked. There's no files,
no mug shot, nothing.
Then we need to find the
cop who pulled him over,
or somebody who saw him
come into the station.
But D.C. cops?
They look after each other.
We need to be careful.
Do you have any
sources on the force?
Not that I would trust
with something like this.
You know, Lucas started
out on the crime beat.
I can see if he knows anyone.
Would he help us? I don't know.
Maybe. Help out a competitor?
We stayed in touch.
You've gotta be kidding me.
This town is way
too incestuous.
I know it's a lot to ask.
I'm still trying to wrap my
head around the affair, Zoe.
If you could just give me a
contact and maybe vouch for me...
Did you wait to bring this up
until now because you thought
it'd be harder
for me to say no?
What do you mean?
In bed, right after we...
You don't actually think I
would do something like...
It sure seems that way.
This is huge, Lucas.
I'm trying to avoid
fucking up what we have.
Whatever that is. And you're
making it really hard for me.
I don't know that I'll ever be the
kind of person that makes it easy.
I'm not looking for easy. But I
don't need to be reminded of him.
I can't erase what I did.
I know you can't.
But this is really
fucking manipulative.
Did you mean what you
said the other night?
That you probably...
I don't know what to do when
I hear something like that.
That's why I was so quiet when
you drove me to the airport.
I was angry.
I just blurted it out.
I wish I hadn't.
At least not like that.
I'm not trying to take advantage
of you because you did.
He hasn't said a word. And
you haven't brought it up?
I just asked him if he was
still considering Tusk.
He said yes, but that he wanted
to speak to you first.
That's it.
I wish we knew if
they'd spoken at all.
Well, he has his private line.
I can't track those calls.
Frank. Mr. President.
Tell me about St. Louis.
He's a hard man to read.
I did my best to probe him,
but I don't think I left any
wiser to which way he's leaning.
I must say, though,
I think he is
by far and away
the best candidate.
Why do you say that?
Doesn't it make
sense for you to
nominate someone
you know so well?
I don't know him. That's why
I sent you to St. Louis.
Forgive me, Mr. President.
I didn't mean it that way.
I meant that
the world knows so well.
You, me, everyone
knows Raymond Tusk.
We don't need to convince
anyone of his worthiness.
But you said
he still seems ambivalent?
Which is why I think you should
make a personal overture.
Invite him to the White House.
Well, I don't want
to appear desperate.
I agree with Frank.
Inviting him is
a very good idea.
If you're serious about Tusk,
you should wine and dine him.
Make him feel very special.
I'm sure we can find
time in the schedule.
Let's give him a few more days.
We have less than a week, sir.
I wouldn't wait
any later than Friday.
We can make Friday work, sir.
All right. Well,
see if he's available.
What are you doing?
Give me your phone. Why?
Just give it to me.
Have you noticed
anything weird in here?
Stuff moved around?
Anything missing?
No. Anyone following you?
What did you find out?
This is serious, Zoe.
It goes way up, as high
as the Commissioner.
I had to beg my contact
at Metro to give me this.
No record of Russo
getting pulled over,
but he remembers there was a
call girl brought in with Russo.
That's a file on one of
her previous arrests.
I've investigated
police cover-ups before.
I got death threats for a year.
Are you willing
to take that risk?
Yeah.
How long?
The next board of directors
meeting is three weeks from now.
That is too late. Remy, look,
the President is gonna nominate
Tusk in a week or less.
I've urged Scott Cunningham
to call a special meeting,
but that doesn't
happen overnight.
There's a lot of machinery in
a corporate attack like this.
I want to meet
Scott Cunningham myself.
I'm not sitting you down with Scott.
You know the rules.
These are extraordinary
circumstances.
Frank, SanCorp's officers do not
meet with politicians, period.
You talk to me, I talk
to Scott Cunningham,
and vice versa.
That's how it works.
All right, Remy.
Whatever you think best.
I'll call you when I know more.
Nancy!
Of all the things I hold in high
regard, rules are not one of them.
I will not place my fate solely
in the hands of a middleman
if I can go
directly to the supplier.
Book a flight to Atlanta. Tomorrow morning.
Let Meechum know.
Yes, sir.
She grew up in Lynchburg, Virginia,
went to Lorimer High School
until she dropped out
sophomore year,
and then after that,
there's no public record.
But all it says here is
that she was fined $300
for loitering on April, 2012.
One of us has to
go to Lynchburg.
Parents, classmates, teachers.
I'll do it.
Okay. Well then, you and I
have to call escort services.
I'm willing to
lend a hand,
but not
by making cold calls
12 hours a day
just to get hung
up on by hookers.
Where was she arrested?
Connecticut Ave. 2460.
That's the address of the
District Grand Hotel.
I'm not a fan
of surprise visits, Frank.
Remy wouldn't
arrange a meeting.
Remy Danton exists so
we don't have to meet.
I needed to speak with you.
There's a congressional
travel report
that puts you on
a trip to Atlanta
the same day I was pulled out
of an investors' briefing.
Those are the sort of
coincidences we want to avoid.
Were you briefing your
investors on Raymond Tusk?
Meechum can be trusted.
Why would I be speaking
to them about Tusk?
I thought Remy filled you in.
No.
He didn't say anything about the
Vice Presidential nomination?
He didn't. And I have a feeling
I'd rather not be told.
Trust me, you want to know.
I've appeared in front of
grand juries before, Frank.
It's much easier when
you can tell the truth.
Please, don't put me in a
position where I have to lie.
If Tusk has
the President's ear,
you will see this administration
shift its support
toward nuclear energy and
away from natural gas.
His subsidiaries and his suppliers.
Go after them.
Frank, we should end this
conversation right now.
He will not accept the
nomination if his assets
are in a blind trust and he
can't fight off the threat.
Okay, we're done. Scott...
I don't wanna
hear another word.
Go back to the airport.
Figure out a good reason you
needed to be in Atlanta today.
You can pull over at the next corner.
I'll have my car pick me up.
♪ When Sunny gets blue
♪ Her eyes get gray and cloudy
One last one? Another.
♪ Begins to fall
♪ Pitter-patter, pitter-patter
♪ Love is gone, so
what can matter? ♪
Can I get
you something?
White wine.
Put that on my tab.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
They're about to
call last call.
That's all right. I don't
have much of a tolerance.
One more?
No. I'm good.
Hey.
You should head upstairs.
I was waiting for you.
Is that the new faucet? Yeah.
How'd it go?
Not good.
Remy's up to something.
He's not returning
my phone calls.
What can I do?
Tell me what you were dreaming.
Oh, it was so awful, Francis.
He's not letting
me sleep either.
Yeah. It's not him.
It's the kids.
I was playing with them
in the backyard,
and the girl was
climbing on the vines,
and I kept telling her to
stop and get down, and...
The vines just took hold of
her, and they wouldn't let go.
And she was screaming so loud,
and I just kept
pulling harder and harder,
and she just ripped in half.
Come here. Come here. Okay.
Ow!
Jesus!
You wait until after 2:00 in
the morning to return my call?
You trying to get my voicemail?
The conversations we're having we
can't be having on cell phones.
Where are you?
Claire is sleeping upstairs.
You shouldn't have gone
to see Cunningham.
He says you
didn't bring up Tusk.
You really think
he'd admit to that?
If we go through with this,
it's insider trading.
He didn't strike me as a man hearing
the news for the second time.
You want to believe
I'm playing games,
I can walk away
from the whole thing.
But I'm all
you've got right now.
I'm the one doing you and SanCorp a
favor, not the other way around.
I can tell when I'm being used, Frank.
I just want to know what for.
I don't use people unless I can
throw them away afterwards.
I'm trying to
strengthen our partnership.
Smells an awful
lot like bullshit.
Don't condescend.
Eight years
I worked on your staff.
And never once made it further
than your front doorstep.
Well, now I'm in
your living room, Frank.
It's not because of
what you taught me.
It's because I finally woke
up to what my value is,
and how undervalued I was,
slaving away for you.
This is business. Keep your
sob story to yourself.
I want to
maintain the influence
that I have worked to
achieve in the White House,
which translates
into the influence
that you have
in the White House,
through me.
I'll get in touch with
Scott again tomorrow.
See if we can push
this forward faster.
Thank you, Remy.
But you gotta let me
do this my way.
The message was very clear.
She doesn't want a settlement,
no matter what the figure.
Even if we give
her WorldWell back?
She wants to go to court.
They said we can expect a
formal summons next week.
This is ludicrous.
Her lawyers agree.
They'd much prefer a settlement,
too, but she's not playing ball.
I'll keep pushing them.
But in the meantime,
you should start
gathering all the
correspondence you
ever had with her.
Emails, notes,
every scrap of paper.
Okay. Thanks, Oliver.
All I'm trying
to do is find her.
I've got an arrest
record from April, 2012,
and I know she was pulled over
with a client in January.
That girl.
She had so much potential.
Why did she drop out?
Like I said, it's
an ethical breach for me
to discuss anything
that has to do...
I spoke to her parents.
Her father was very combative.
Was there trouble at home?
The father. Did he...
I won't speak about Rachel.
Can you talk to me about
your job in general,
the sorts of cases you deal
with in an abstract way?
When I'm concerned
about a student,
especially if there's possible
criminal activity involved,
it's my duty to
contact the DA's Office.
Now, if the DA pursues charges,
the student has to testify
against their own parent.
That's a difficult decision
for a young person to make.
Extremely difficult.
It could be easier to run away.
It's set for tomorrow.
Tusk lands at 7:30
and then heads straight to the White
House for dinner with the President.
Is it on
the official schedule?
No.
We need it to be.
Well, I can't do that.
The President specifically
asked that I leave it off.
Actually, that's good.
We can make that work.
Can you set up a meeting between
Birch and the President?
About what?
So he can give him his 2 cents
about who he will nominate.
I don't think we want
Birch getting involved.
He'll never get the chance.
What are you planning?
Can you set up a meeting for later today?
Yes or no?
I'm sure I can squeeze it in.
Good. I'll talk to Birch.
Get him on the phone.
This has to stay off the books,
just like the dinner with Tusk.
Okay. And finally.
Do you have a scheduler
that you can fire?
Janine,
I've got something for you.
What is this?
The President's OTR schedule
between now and Friday.
How'd you get this?
It doesn't matter.
Look who he's meeting
with this afternoon.
Bob Birch.
And look at Friday night.
Raymond Tusk. These aren't the craziest
meetings for him to be having.
Then why aren't they on
the official schedule?
He's considering them
for Vice President.
I'd say that's reason
enough to keep them secret.
Get this out, right away.
Mr. Speaker, I'm hearing
that you're gonna
be considered for
the Vice Presidency.
Slugline is
reporting that you're
heading to
the White House
right now.
I'm... No. You're not
headed to the White House?
Yes. The President
just wants my input.
But there's
the possibility that you
might be under
consideration yourself.
Not that I'm aware of.
Excuse me.
How did the schedule get out?
It got leaked, sir,
by someone in
the scheduling office.
On purpose? Accidentally.
A wrong attachment to an
email that went wide.
Well, whoever it was,
I want them out.
I already let them go.
Is Birch here yet?
He's waiting outside.
Well, cancel the meeting.
Tell him something came up.
I don't want to
feed the frenzy.
Yes, sir.
Give me
the private line,
please.
There are three satellite
trucks on my street.
I'm trapped in my own home.
Somebody in the scheduling
office fucked up.
Are you seriously
considering Birch?
Absolutely not.
We are losing control of
the process, Garrett.
Every time I've spoken to you,
you've never spoken back.
Although given
our mutual disdain,
I can't blame you for
the silent treatment.
Perhaps I'm speaking
to the wrong audience.
Can you hear me?
Are you even
capable of language,
or do you only
understand depravity?
Peter, is that you?
Stop hiding in my
thoughts and come out.
Have the courage in death
that you never had in life.
Come out, look me in the eye
and say what you need to say.
There is no solace
above or below.
Only us.
Small, solitary, striving,
battling one another.
I pray to myself, for myself.
Hello?
Who is it?
My lawyer said I shouldn't
be talking to you.
Mine said the same thing.
I'm not gonna
change my mind, Claire.
I made a mistake. I got upset,
and I acted impulsively.
I was the one
who made the mistake
by partnering with you
in the first place.
Well, then,
can we please both admit
that it wasn't meant to be, and
we can find an amicable way...
No, we can't.
What do you want?
To send a message.
Organizations like yours get
90% of the grant money,
then cozy up to corporate sponsors
who destroy the environment.
The things you're
claiming are lies.
I never mentioned
your pregnancy.
I got in touch
with Evelyn Baxter.
Remember her?
We had a long conversation.
It seems that
you have a history of
axing people
who disagree with you.
She'll be
testifying on my behalf.
So will eight of the people
that you made her fire.
If you want an apology, I'm
here to offer you one,
and to give you whatever
you think is fair.
This case is gonna
get national attention
because of who
you're married to.
I'll have a platform to
say what I want to say.
That's worth more than
anything you could offer.
Listen, I know we have
different philosophies,
but what we're trying to achieve
is exactly the same thing.
We shouldn't be
fighting each other.
Do you feel that? The kicking?
I won't let
people like you fuck up
the world my child
has to live in.
If I have to tell
a few lies to do that,
at least I learned one
valuable thing from you.
♪ Call me
♪ Irresponsible
♪ Unreliable
♪ Go on and throw in
What can I get for you?
Glenlivet, neat.
♪ Do my foolish
alibis bore... ♪
The lawsuit?
And other things.
What other things?
You know,
I cannot guarantee you
that all of this
is gonna succeed.
Oh, it's not that.
You can tell me,
or I can keep guessing.
You'll roll your eyes.
Not at you.
I was thinking about
when one of us dies.
Whether it's you first or me...
Well, if it is me, and
I'm sure it will be,
you won't be alone for long.
No. I mean,
what will we leave behind?
We've accomplished
a great deal.
And I intend for us to
accomplish a lot more.
But for whom?
For each other.
But if we're not...
I'm being silly.
Have you ever been published?
Many times.
I guess that's
a stupid question.
You don't seem like
a starving artist.
Don't judge
a book by its cover.
You have a nice laugh.
Really?
It's very attractive.
Are you staying at the hotel?
You want to come up to my room?
That depends.
Well, how much
would that cost me?
That seems about right.
Close your eyes.
Put out your hands.
Now open them up.
I'm trying to find this woman.
If you make me
pull out my badge,
I have to take you in.
But I don't want to do that.
Let's not make a scene.
I used to see her around.
She left the business, though.
We haven't really kept in touch.
Any idea where she might be?
A friend of mine
saw her waiting tables
at a restaurant in Georgetown.
I guess the question I'm
trying to ask is...
Is it even worth that step?
The bottom line is that for a woman
your age, it's extremely hard.
Have you ever
had a miscarriage?
No. I...
I've been late before,
but I don't...
You know, I don't know.
I don't know exactly.
Have you had any abortions?
Three.
That can make it
more difficult.
I'm not trying to dissuade you,
but please make sure you think
long and hard before you decide.
But it's possible?
Assuming you and your husband
fit all the criteria?
Yes, it's possible.
Okay.
What? Well,
that's hardly my problem.
No, you get on it. It's...
I have to call you back.
What is it?
SanCorp's stock.
It's up 35% in
the last four hours.
It's all over
the financial news.
Tusk is making a play.
Get Remy on the phone.
Congressman Underwood
on line three.
I was just about to call you.
I need to meet with Tusk before
he sees the President tonight.
He's already here.
At the White House?
He decided to come in
a few hours early.
His plane landed
half an hour ago.
Do you know where he is?
I don't know.
He had his own car pick him up.
I just found out.
Remy's not in his office. I left
word there and on his cell.
Look, you need to call me the
moment you know where he is.
Okay.
It's just the lunch menu right now.
I hope that's okay.
Yeah. That's fine.
Your server will
be with you shortly.
Is Rachel working?
No. I don't think she's
scheduled till Sunday.
Stephanie will be
with you this afternoon.
Thanks.
Should we come back Sunday?
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
Can I help you
with something?
Yeah. I was just
looking for the bathroom.
The bathroom is out this door,
to your right, down the hall.
That way? Thanks. Yeah.
Unless you want to use the
restroom in the office.
Who are you calling?
Rachel.
Rachel Posner?
My name is Zoe Barnes. I'm a
reporter at slugline.com.
I know about Peter Russo.
Rachel?
Come on, Rachel.
You shouldn't
have mentioned Russo.
She'll write back.
I wouldn't if I was her.
How much do you know?
That you were with him
when he was pulled over.
Who else knows? Just me.
I can keep it that way,
but I need more.
There is no more. You're lying.
Yeah, I was with him
when he got pulled over.
They took him away
and let me go.
I don't know
what happened to him.
He was never charged.
You know more than me, then.
No one ever came
to talk to you?
About what? To keep you quiet.
You don't kiss and tell
in that business.
Not even when
it's a congressman?
Especially when
it's a congressman.
Frank Underwood
never approached you?
Who's that?
You're too smart to
play dumb, Rachel.
You know who that is.
Name rings a bell.
I try not to follow the news.
Too many familiar faces.
How about Douglas Stamper?
Never heard of him.
I've told you
everything I know.
I know about
what your father did.
If you don't help me,
I'll write about Russo.
I'll write that
you were a prostitute,
and I'll write
about why you left home.
Go to town, bitch.
So?
She mentioned both
you and your boss.
What exactly?
She didn't say.
All she seemed to
know was that I was
in the car with him when
he got pulled over.
And you didn't
admit to more than that?
No. I said everything exactly
like you told me to.
You really think
I'd spill my guts?
Calm down.
Why didn't
you tell me he was gonna
hurt himself?
I never would've done it.
How could I have known?
I just want all this
to go away.
It will.
All of it.
I promise.
Do you want me to
order you dinner?
Where's Doug at?
I don't know. He left early.
Call him for me, will you?
Yes, sir.
Thirteen minutes from now,
Tusk will meet
with the President,
if he isn't there already.
You've never been an ally,
have you?
Pressing on with your
slow, incessant march.
Time would've killed Russo
if I hadn't,
just as it will
kill me someday.
Kill us all.
Sir, I just
got Doug's voicemail.
I wonder where he's at.
Well, maybe this is him.
Freddy?
Sorry, Frank.
I had to trade up.
SanCorp's a big fish, but
Raymond Tusk is a whale.
Can I get you something, Frank?
Nothing right now.
Thank you, Freddy.
I'll leave y'all to it.
I hope you don't mind
that Remy told me
about this little
secret of yours.
I wanted a place where
you'd feel comfortable.
Shouldn't you be
at the White House?
How could I pass up the chance to
eat the best ribs in Washington?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Remy told you about SanCorp.
As of closing bell today,
I own 3%.
By the end of next week,
I'll own over 10%.
Enough to make sure they
can't cause me any trouble.
A valiant effort, though.
I respect that.
So why are we here?
I told you I'd give you until
today to think things over.
I'm a man who keeps my word.
And I'm still not interested.
You wanted me to be more
specific back in St. Louis.
That would be a good start.
Why did Britain go to war
with China 150 years ago?
I'm in no mood for riddles.
Humor me a moment.
Opium.
It was bigger
than opium, Frank.
That was simply the excuse.
Peking wanted to call the
shots instead of the West.
It's the same problem
we're facing now.
But nobody wants a trade war,
much less a military one.
And what's your opium?
Samarium-149.
I need it for my reactors.
China controls 95%
of the world's supply.
And you're worried
about the imbalance
in our currency,
our foreign debt...
All of it.
You already have
the President's ear.
Trade tariffs are
controlled by Congress.
You have a lot more influence
there than Garrett does.
It's the reason I wanted you to
stay there in the first place.
And what exactly
would you want me to do?
Well,
that part I don't know yet.
We'll have to wait and see how
things play out with Chinese.
I've already told you I
will not do a blank check.
I must say I'm surprised,
Frank.
You have a reputation
for pragmatism.
And I also have avoided a reputation
for indentured servitude.
I never make an offer
more than twice, Frank.
Tell me now if I can count
on your cooperation.
You're not offering cooperation,
you're demanding tutelage.
So let me make you a proposal.
I am absolutely willing to
work together as equals.
I will take your opinions seriously,
just as the President does.
But I will not bind myself
to them in advance.
If that doesn't
interest you, fair enough.
Good luck finding a Vice
President in the next four days
who will prove
as pragmatic as I.
You can't purchase
loyalty, Raymond.
Not the sort I have in mind.
If you want to earn my loyalty,
then you have to
offer yours in return.
And if we can agree to that.
Well, you're a man
with imagination.
Wait.
If Stamper was there himself,
this goes much deeper
than a lost arrest file.
Well, let's think about this.
What did Russo gain him?
A mansion in Harrisburg.
Uh-uh.
Underwood thinks
bigger than that.
Then what?
I don't know.
He controls Pennsylvania.
He has influence
in the White House.
Walker needs the state
for re-election...
No. No,
it can't just be Walker.
The President backstabbed him for
the Secretary of State nomination.
It has to be something else.
The President would owe him.
But what?
They already meet once a week.
The Education Bill? I mean, what?
What specifically?
He could be after
the VP nomination.
That doesn't
make sense, though.
The VP slot is on the table
because Russo tanked.
Underwood wanted him to win.
Unless he didn't.
Maybe he wanted
Russo to self-destruct.
To force Matthews to run.
Exactly. And then next week,
when Matthews wins...
The President taps Underwood.
Mr. President.
Mr. Tusk.
Thanks for coming
on such short notice.
Have a seat, Frank.
I have a confession to make.
Raymond and I have known
each other for years.
We don't publicize it, but he's
been a trusted advisor to me.
And I sent you to St. Louis so
he could spend time with you,
give me his 2 cents.
On what, sir, if I may ask?
Offering you
the Vice Presidency.
I told the President that,
in my humble opinion,
both he and the country
would be well-served
by a man as experienced,
intelligent, and loyal as you.
So I'm officially
asking, Frank.
Sir, I...
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
Yes.
It would be a great honor,
Mr. President.
Meechum.
I take care of my own,
and you've proved yourself
to be very valuable.
I would like you to be
part of my security detail
once I get confirmed.
That's the Secret Service, sir.
I'm Capitol Police.
Then I'll put you
on the Secret Service.
If you're interested.
I'd be more
than interested, sir.
Good.
And I'm extremely grateful.
Keep being valuable.
That's the best way to
show your gratitude.
I will.
Mr. Vice President.
Did the plumber finally come?
No. I fixed it.
Francis.
So proud of you, Francis.
But I didn't do it alone.
I got here as
quickly as I could.
Is something wrong?
I need you to be completely
honest with me, Christina.
About what?
The other day, when I said
that you should tell me
if anyone from the press
started harassing you?
Zoe Barnes?
You said you wanted to talk
about something on the phone.
Oh, no. That can wait.
No. Come on. Tell me.
I... Earlier today...
The rowing machine,
I saw, is broken.
Oh, it's my fault.
The cable broke.
I haven't been able
to replace it yet.
What about going
for a run with me?
She's trying to smear
Congressman Underwood.
It's a coordinated campaign
by everyone at Slugline.
But she knew things.
Like what?
About Peter.
Something to do with Kern
losing the nomination.
And?
Want me to drive
alongside you, sir?
No. You stay here.
Yes, sir.
You ready?
Yes.
www.tvsubtitles.net