Hey, excuse me. I'm Paul Capra.
I'm here to see Christina.
Oh, right this way, Mr. Capra,
she's expecting you.
Paul. Hey, Christina.
Hi.
It's good to see you.
Yeah, you too.
Can I get you anything?
No, I grabbed some
breakfast on the way down.
Okay, have a seat.
I asked you down here because I
spoke to D-trip and the DNC.
We'd like you to
run for Peter's seat.
As you probably know,
the election
has been set for the
first week of February.
You want me to run?
With your stature
in the community,
your grass-roots
organizing experience...
Christina, hold on...
I know it's a lot to consider.
It's only been a month.
We still have to govern, Paul.
I thought you
asked me down here
because you wanted
to talk or something.
I do, about the election.
I mean about Peter.
How come you didn't
go to the funeral?
I couldn't.
How you been holding up?
I'm all right.
It's been hard keeping
the office on track.
Jesus. Screw the office.
What about you?
You're allowed to grieve,
Christina.
Paul,
there are 600,000
people counting on us.
I can't let my feelings
get in the way of that.
Will you hear me out about
running for Peter's seat?
Well, you've passed the vetting
process with flying colors.
Is there anything
we might have missed?
No, sir.
Tell me about your
experience as the Chair
of the Oversight
and Reform Committee.
It's been very rewarding.
What are the biggest
challenges you've had to face?
Partisanship.
Well, I suppose a room
filled with 435 big egos
isn't the most hospitable
place for oversight.
Do you want to be
Vice President, Tabitha?
It would be a great honor, sir.
We'll be in touch.
That's all? For the time being.
Thank you, Mr. President.
We have to cross her off.
I agree.
She could put
a crack addict to sleep.
Then what is she doing
on the goddamn list?
Tabitha's a very
gifted legislator.
I don't want people who
make sense on paper.
I need at least
one viable option.
The two of you've
created this list,
and have proceeded to cross off
every name you've put on it.
It's just a first pass, sir.
We need time to
fully vet all...
Jim is going to win this
thing in Pennsylvania.
And we're no closer to naming his
replacement than we were a month ago.
Let us take
another crack at it,
and give you a few
more names to consider.
I just want one name.
We'll have something for
you by tomorrow morning.
Thank you, Mr. President.
He's ready to say
yes to anything.
Yeah, for this to work, I
don't think you can be there.
Not when I first
mention it.
I agree.
You bring it up in
your morning brief
and when I show up,
I'll act surprised.
Assuming he's open to the idea.
Look, all we have to do tomorrow
is plant the notion in his head.
I'm sure you'll be persuasive.
Hello?
Mr. Capra? Yeah. Who's this?
Janine Skorsky from Slugline.
We spoke when I wrote the piece
about Congressman
Russo's passing.
I'm done giving interviews
about Peter, okay?
He was a troubled
guy, end of story.
This is not about his death.
I'm calling you because my sources
at the DCCC are telling me
that you might be
running for his seat.
I'm not talking about that.
But you did have
a meeting this morning
with Christina Gallagher,
correct?
I'm driving right now. I really
shouldn't be on the phone.
If you do run,
I would like to know
about your involvement
in the closing of the
Philadelphia Shipyard.
That decision was
made in Washington.
The Association
wasn't consulted.
Forgive me,
I find that hard to believe.
I read all of the transcripts
from the BRAC Commission.
Congressman Russo didn't
give any testimony.
So are you saying that he didn't
consult with you once before he...
Somebody was strong-arming him, okay?
It was politics.
Do you know who would
have pressured him?
I don't know. He just said
people up the food chain.
Did he say anything
more specific about...
You know what? There's traffic.
I gotta go.
Mr. Capra, I would love to...
Should I be prepared
to do press?
If he's amenable.
What do you think
our chances are?
Better than 50-50,
if I had to say.
We won't announce until after
Matthews wins, though.
I hate to admit it,
but I'm nervous...
So am I.
It's just that last time
we found ourselves...
That's my fear, too.
All right.
You call me,
either way?
In no more than nine hours.
Linda's been in
there far too long.
If the President takes this much
convincing, it doesn't bode well.
I can feel it, his hesitation,
on the other side of that door.
I know it's pointless to worry until
I know what cards I'm holding.
Perhaps he just got
interrupted by some...
He wants to tap Raymond Tusk.
What?
He thinks it's a bold idea.
That's an idiotic idea.
The man's never
held public office.
That's one of the things the
President said he likes about him.
The President wants to nominate
a multi-billionaire in
a struggling economy?
He'll alienate
half the country.
Which is exactly
what I said to him,
but he made it very clear he does
not want me to fight him on this.
So you didn't
mention me at all?
I never had the chance.
His mind was made up
before I could say a word.
Well, we have to un-make it.
Well, you can try,
but if you do,
my guess is he's gonna cut you
out of the process altogether.
He seemed adamant.
We should go in there.
Mr. President. Morning, Frank.
Will you give us
a few minutes, Linda?
Of course.
Linda fill you in?
I think Raymond Tusk...
Is an exciting, bold idea.
Well, I'm glad you agree.
Linda didn't think so.
He's a proven businessman,
brilliant but down-to-earth.
Do you know him personally?
I met him briefly
once at a fundraiser.
Last night when
I called him was
the first time we had a
meaningful conversation.
Did he seem open to the idea?
I sensed a good
deal of reluctance.
He wanted a few
days to consider.
Well, good, that gives us
time to start vetting him.
He's clean.
I had him vetted last year
when I was considering him for
Secretary of the Treasury.
And did he say
why he's reluctant?
No, didn't give a reason.
Just wanted to mull it over.
I want to send someone to St.
Louis to speak to him person,
convince him to accept
the nomination.
Who are you thinking about?
I'd send Linda, but there's so
much work for her to do here.
And she can be
abrasive at times.
Yeah, she can be a bit tough.
I want someone with,
uh, gravitas.
Birch is a possibility, but he's not
always been our strongest ally.
I'm not sure I would trust Bob
with something like this.
I would be happy
to go myself, sir.
I can use a light touch, and give
him the respect he deserves.
Good. I'll let his people
know you're coming.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Thank you, Frank.
Tell me, Francis.
It's good we were
prepared for anything.
I have to fly to
St. Louis tonight.
"Somebody was strong-arming
him." And when I asked him who,
he said, quote,
people up the food chain.
It's Washington.
Congressmen get
strong-armed all the time.
My gut says it
was Frank Underwood.
He had nothing to do with Russo
before the shipyard closing,
and then suddenly
he's propping him up...
That doesn't mean he was...
Let's cut the bullshit
once and for all, Zoe.
I know he's been
feeding you your stories.
I don't want to screw you over,
but I'm not going to
stop digging on this.
I won't say he was a source.
But you do know each other.
Show me your notes
and I'll talk to him.
These are the notes
from the Capra call.
And these are the transcripts
from the BRAC hearing.
When they get to the Philadelphia
Shipyard, Russo doesn't say anything.
That's fine.
Yeah, I would just put
both of them in that file.
Claire, I just got a call
from the PR office at SanCorp
saying they wanted
to send a film crew
to take footage of our
filtration project in Botswana.
Right. They're just using that
for promotional material.
SanCorp fought us on
the Watershed Bill.
They helped us get the
filters out of South Sudan.
I thought that was
the State Department.
No. You remember Remy Danton?
You met him in your office right
after you started working here?
The lobbyist.
I asked him
for his help.
We're just returning the favor.
That's all.
Claire, they're against
everything we stand for.
It's harmless.
They'll send the video to
a few of their investors,
and make some commercials.
This makes me very uncomfortable.
The idea...
They are sending
the film crew, Gillian.
So please work
with them on that.
One of my colleagues is
looking into Peter Russo.
The assumption is you strong-armed
him into closing the shipyard.
Where does your colleague
get their information?
I don't know.
Allocating the DoD budget
is always a free-for-all.
Did you pressure him?
There were certain people
that were gonna benefit
from the base closing
sooner rather than later.
I didn't strong-arm Peter,
I advised him to trade in a
losing hand for a winning one.
How did he stand to win?
He made allies out of enemies. That's
a very valuable thing in Congress.
I wish I could give
you something juicier,
but the shipyard closing was
just politics as usual.
I assume your colleague
is Ms. Skorsky.
She know we're talking?
No, of course not.
Be in touch.
More than you ever wanted to
know about Raymond Alan Tusk.
Companies he controls,
political contributions,
a GQ article entitled
"Backwoods Billionaire"
is about his humble
mid-western lifestyle.
Jesus.
There's also a copy of the
financial disclosure requirements
and details of the blind trust.
I think the trust is
where you want to focus.
Could Linda be behind all this?
To what end?
To get you out of
town for a few days
while they continue the search
without your interference?
The President has no
reason to mistrust me.
Unless Linda told him you
want the Vice Presidency.
No, she's in way too deep.
We misjudged her on the Secretary
of State nomination...
That was different.
She blindsided me. Now she
knows my eyes are wide open.
Do you want the Gaffney
bag or regular business?
Regular business.
Tusk can dress
down if he wants to,
but I'm representing
the White House.
And get Walter Doyle onto Tusk.
Let's see if we
can dig up anything.
I'll call him right now.
And keep your eye on Janine
Skorsky while I'm away.
She's been prying into Russo.
What does she know?
She knows the right
questions to ask.
I want to make sure she doesn't
get the right answers.
I'm on it.
McCuddin.
What was that?
McCuddin Air Force Base.
BRAC hearing was
there on April 12.
David Rasmussen stepped down
less than a week later.
Womack takes his place.
So maybe...
So wait... Slow down.
McCuddin is in his district.
Is that the shipyard thing?
Janine, call me back. I think it
was Womack who pressured Russo.
Russo was probably just earning
a favor he could cash in later.
I'm around.
Did you ever have to fight
her to kill a story?
Janine?
Yeah, when she worked for you.
Only when I knew she was wrong.
She's trying to draw up
this whole conspiracy thing
with Russo and Frank Underwood
and the whole shipyard closing.
But I'm pretty
sure she's wrong.
Pretty sure isn't
the same as certain.
No, I am certain.
How do you know?
I have sources.
Underwood? No.
No, never mind.
I'll figure it out.
Mrs. Tusk? Jean, please.
You must be Frank. Come in.
So nice to meet you.
The guest room is this way.
It is very kind of you to
have invited me to stay here.
Why waste the taxpayers'
money on a hotel
when we have
a perfectly good bed?
Well, both they and
I are very grateful.
I'm sorry Raymond isn't awake to
greet you, he goes to bed at...
I know, he's an early riser.
I understand.
Would you like a wake-up knock?
No, I have an alarm
on my phone.
Sleep tight.
Thank you so much.
I would say good morning, but
it's the middle of the night.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And you, too.
Was I making too much noise?
No, I smelled bacon.
Here.
Coffee? Booze? 2:00 a.m.
you can go either way.
Just water for now.
It's filtered.
Your wife would approve.
You ever been
to St. Louis before?
Just the airport.
What do you think so far?
Well, I've only
seen your neighborhood
and whatever I could see out
the window on the interstate.
Good enough. It's all
pretty much the same.
Excuse me.
Listen, I still
haven't showered.
My mind is on China here.
What do you say you
get a few more z's
and we try this again in a few
hours with our clothes on?
Sounds like a plan.
Meet me at my office at 9:30.
I'll have a driver pick you up.
Can I ask why you do that?
Do what?
Tap your ring
like that.
I've seen you do it on TV.
Two taps every time you get up
from a table or leave a lectern.
Something my father taught me.
It's meant to
harden your knuckles so
you don't break them if
you get into a fight.
It also has the added benefit
of knocking on wood.
My father believed that success
is a mixture of
preparation and luck.
Tapping the table kills
both birds with one stone.
Your father was a peach farmer?
Yes, he was.
Not a very successful one.
Lack of preparation
or lack of luck?
Lack of both.
He was better at giving
advice than following it.
Hmm.
Miss, your card.
Thank you.
Ms. Gallagher,
my name's Janine Skorsky,
I'm a reporter at Slugline.
I wrote the profile
on Congressman...
I remember.
Do you have a minute?
If this is about Peter, I...
No. It's about Paul Capra.
We know that he
might be running
for Congressman
Russo's old seat.
I can't comment on that.
We're just trying
to do some background
on the shipyard
closing last April.
Listen, I just want
to eat my breakfast...
We have sources that are saying
that the Congressman
was being pressured
by someone to not
fight the closure.
Who?
That's what I'm
trying to figure out.
This is completely off the
record, I promise you.
Hi, Christina.
Doug, hi.
How you holding up?
I'm okay. I'm good.
I saw you sitting over
here, you mind if I?
No, please.
Ms. Skorsky, right?
I believe we spoke a few times when
you used to work for The Herald...
Whenever I could get past the
press office gauntlet to you.
We do like to run a tight ship.
Hmm.
So what brings
you to the Capitol?
I was just asking Ms. Gallagher
who's running to fill the vacant
seat in Pennsylvania's 1st.
Well, the honest answer
is we don't know.
Thank you for your time,
Ms. Gallagher.
Anyone starts harassing
you with questions
you don't want to answer,
you let me know.
I'll handle them.
You got enough on
your plate right now.
Thanks, Doug.
I appreciate that.
Hang in there, okay?
Yes.
Ah!
Uganda, Peru,
Nepal, Indonesia,
Nicaragua.
Well, you are quite
the well-traveled man.
No. I'm the man
who stays at home.
Jean brought those back for me.
Mr. Tusk, I am... First names.
After all, we have
broken bacon together,
we can safely assume
that we're familiar.
Raymond, I realize that
you are a very busy man,
so I'm gonna cut
right to the chase.
The President sincerely
would like you
to become
the next Vice President.
That part I already knew.
And I'm here to
convince you to say yes.
Another thing I already knew.
Well, I don't know
that I can tell you
anything you
don't already know.
But perhaps you can tell me
what your hesitation is.
Speak.
Yes.
Now, I understand you
might have some concerns
about the financial
disclosures leading...
Speak.
No.
I have eight people
representing me
at eight simultaneous meetings
in six time zones right now.
I sit here and
answer their questions,
provided they come in the form of
a single yes or no proposition.
Well, then let me
give that a try.
Would you like to be the
Vice President, yes or no?
Hold on a minute.
I am very sorry.
Let me have 20 minutes to
wrap up these meetings.
And then what do you say
we get out of the office
and away from this damn phone?
Meet me at my car. Betty can
tell you where it's parked.
Go ahead.
He's deflecting.
What I can't tell is whether it's
because he's inclined to say no
or wants to be
wooed to say yes.
Either way I'll
have to ease him into
the conversation,
not be so blunt.
This trip may take
longer than I thought.
We've looked through
all the file cabinets.
They're not on his computer?
Not with the Congressman's
handwritten notes.
All right.
I'll check his office.
Ah!
There's a comfort
to these woods,
like they're my backyard.
Well, they are my backyard in a way.
I own them.
How much land?
6,000 acres.
You think I could get a tour of your
Fulton Plant while I'm in town?
If you like,
but I don't know why you'd want
to be there when you
could be out here.
I've never seen
a nuclear plant.
Not much to see.
Steel, concrete, lot of steam.
The President
hasn't exactly been
a big supporter
of nuclear power.
Is that part of
your hesitation,
that fear that
the Administration...
He's just being savvy.
Nuclear energy is a
tough sell after Japan.
But it's the only
option we have right now
that doesn't completely
trash the planet.
The argument against nuclear
power is an emotional one.
And you don't make decisions
based on emotion.
Decisions based on emotion
aren't decisions at all.
Instincts.
Which can be of value.
The rational and the irrational
complement each other.
Individually,
they're far
less powerful.
And which category
do your thoughts
on the Vice Presidency
fall into?
You hear that song?
It's a hermit thrush.
Can't see him.
"Solitary, the thrush,
"The hermit,
withdrawn to himself,
"avoiding the settlements,
"Sings by himself a song."
Do you know the poem?
No, I don't. Walt Whitman.
It's about the death of Abraham Lincoln.
He's over there, somewhere.
Yes, I know the damn poem. We
studied it at the Sentinel.
I said to my professor, "Why
mourn the death of presidents,
"or anyone for that matter?
The dead can't hear us."
And he asked if I believed in heaven.
I said no.
And then he asked if I
had no faith in God.
I said you have it wrong.
It's God that
has no faith in us.
Deeper into the woods.
I think you're being paranoid.
He came up right after I sat down.
It was creepy.
I'm telling you, it was Womack.
Is that what Underwood said?
He didn't name names,
but who else?
And what's the big deal?
Congressmen trade favors.
One of these congressmen
committed suicide.
I think you're
stretching here, Janine.
To try and connect...
I have gone after
big fish before.
I know what it feels
like to be watched.
Underwood's Education Bill went
to the floor just three days
after Womack
became Majority Leader.
You leaked the Education Bill. And
then there was the Kern article.
Those were two completely
different stories...
Wait, what was the guy?
What was his name?
He's the one who
told that Kern wrote
the article for
the school paper?
Roy Kapeniak.
You should go talk to him.
There's no link.
Except you.
Underwood's been using you, Zoe.
Don't you want to know why?
Hi.
Remy Danton's on line two.
He says it's important.
Hello, Remy. Hey, Claire.
I got a call from the
PR team at SanCorp.
They said Gillian Cole
isn't being cooperative.
Hasn't gotten back
to them, you mean?
No, told them point blank she
doesn't want the film crew there.
I'm looking at an email.
She wrote that they
would be "disruptive
"to the project and
local community."
Is that her, or is
that coming from you?
No, I made it very clear that I
wanted her to work with them.
Well, it seems like she's
doing the opposite.
I will speak to her.
And then I'll sort things out
with the PR team personally.
Thank you, Claire. You bet.
Is Gillian at lunch?
She didn't come in yet today.
She's not feeling well.
Let me know when she gets here.
What time is your flight? 6:40.
We should get going.
There's gonna be traffic.
Almost ready.
I've been thinking,
the, uh, older man you were
with, was it Underwood?
So what this is really about
is covering your own ass?
That is not true.
You don't want anybody to know
you were sleeping with him.
Not exactly objective
reporting, is it?
Don't fucking lecture me
on journalistic ethics.
How many of the stories you
brought me at The Herald
were because you were...
I'm not gonna have
this conversation.
Fine. Maybe you should
take a cab to the airport.
Don't punish me
for being honest.
You haven't been honest.
I had to ask. And you still haven't
given me a straight answer.
Yes.
It was him.
I...
I don't know if I can do this, Zoe.
Do what?
You fucked a congressman
to get ahead.
I'm not the first person to ever
do something like that, Lucas.
But I'm not sleeping with
those other people, am I?
What, so you just hate me now?
No, I probably love you.
That's the fucking problem.
Let's go, I'm parked illegally.
So I hear you went stomping
through the woods today.
We did, and then
Raymond was kind enough
to arrange a tour
of the Fulton Plant.
I'm sure you were wondering,
"When is this old fool gonna
get around to brass tacks?"
I'm here to simply
answer questions.
I figured that you would make
up your mind when you're ready.
There are two minds here.
We know all about
the blind trust.
Does it concern either of you?
The words "blind" and
"trust" are not among
my favorites in
the English language.
But I have no
problem with it in theory.
Not managing our
assets for a few years
could unburden us from a
great deal of stress.
Well, then what does your
reluctance stem from?
Why do you think
the President wants me?
Well, I can't speak on his
behalf, but if I were to...
Aren't you here
to do just that?
Speak on his behalf?
If I were to speculate, I
think the President would...
Speculation is
a poor form of investment,
and an equally
poor form of politics.
Tell me what you know.
I don't know what you mean.
Well, what do you
think I should do?
You personally,
Frank Underwood?
My opinion isn't
what matters here.
It does to me.
Should I do it? Yes or no?
Well, there's a great number of
things to consider, Raymond...
And I'm sure you've considered them all.
Yes or no, Frank?
No, I will not
answer that question.
Because you think I shouldn't.
Because it's not relevant.
All right, then, let me
ask you another way.
Would you take the job?
It hasn't been offered to me.
What if it were?
I have a distaste
for hypotheticals
just the same as you have a
distaste for speculation.
All right, all right.
That's enough business for now.
We can discuss
it more tomorrow.
Get in there, Bruce.
Sorry. Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
I'm looking for Roy Kapeniak.
I thought his trailer was over here.
Am I in the right place?
You're in the right place a month ago.
He got evicted.
Shooting off his gun
too much in the yard.
Do you know
where I can find him?
Why?
I'm a relative. His niece.
Skipped town is what I heard.
Had a girl living with him.
Maybe she knows.
Name was Echo. Echo?
What she went by, at least.
Works at the titty bar
over on 40.
Highway 40? Mmm-hmm.
Across from the Burger King.
Okay. Thank you.
Girls get in free.
I'm looking for Echo.
Who? Echo?
Roy was a fucking wacko. I was stupid
to live with him as long as I did.
Do you know where he is now?
I don't know and I don't care.
He ever talk about
the article I wrote?
All the time. He had it framed.
Bet it's still in the trailer, if
it's not in a junkyard by now.
Did he say why he called me?
Did he ever tell you?
I was there.
Where?
When the guy showed up.
Who?
I won't name names.
Fuck Roy Kapeniak.
You don't owe him shit.
Some guy who said
he was a congressman.
Was it him?
No, he was younger.
Tall. Not much hair.
Pretty good-looking.
Yeah, that was him.
You're absolutely sure?
He brought bourbon, blow,
stayed the whole night.
The whole thing was his idea.
What, to say that Kern
wrote the editorial?
That guy didn't write anything.
It was all Roy.
Okay, I know I said that
I wouldn't name names.
And I won't,
if that's what you want.
But you could be
famous overnight.
Talk shows, TV,
the whole country...
No way.
You wouldn't have
to dance anymore.
You could do
whatever you want...
Don't use my
fucking name, okay?
I already said more
than I should have.
Stamper, it's midnight.
Two things, boss.
First, Janine Skorsky ambushed
Christina this morning.
I intercepted her before
she could ask too much.
Should we be worried?
I can keep this contained, sir.
I just wanted you to know.
All right.
What's the other thing?
Doyle came back with his research.
I just emailed it to you.
The President told you he and Tusk
didn't know each other, right?
Yeah, he said they met once,
I think at a fundraiser.
That would appear to be a lie.
All right, I have it
in front of me now.
Doyle cataloged all the
instances he could find
in which the two of them were in
the same city at the same time.
Items in red are events
that they both attended.
And he found something else.
Back in Walker's
private sector days
he was the CEO of
Pioneer Airlines.
Guess who owned a third of the
stock when it was sold to United?
Raymond Tusk.
My guess is that he and Walker
know each other quite well.
All right, let me look this over.
I'll call you back.
I'm being played.
But why?
Did I wake you again?
No.
I'd like to talk.
Give me a moment.
Carolina Parakeet?
You're wrong, but you're close.
This is the Sun Conure.
They look very similar, but the
Carolina Parakeet is extinct.
Was killed off because it
was considered a pest.
Interesting species, though.
Voracious appetite.
And he was poison.
Cats who ate him died.
This bird is not
the only thing you've
misidentified since
you've been in St. Louis.
You and Walker are old friends.
I wasn't sent here to vet you.
Very good.
Tell me why I am here, then.
So I can vet you.
For the Vice Presidency?
The President values my advice,
and he tends to follow it.
Like when I advised him not to
make you Secretary of State.
That was very bad advice.
Yes, it was.
One of the larger
mistakes I've made,
and I rarely make
mistakes of any size.
You've proven yourself
to be quite difficult.
Kern, the teachers'
strike, now Matthews...
You attribute all that to me?
If I had to guess.
A smart man once
said to me that
speculation is
a poor form of politics.
Why don't you stick to
what you know, Raymond?
What I know is you are extremely
effective at what you set your mind to.
That is valuable to me,
and I've already told Garrett
that it could be valuable to him.
Somebody at his side with one
foot in the Executive Branch
and one in the Legislative.
He is very open to the idea.
My turn to speculate.
Your recommendation
comes at a price.
Fact.
I have something that you want,
you have something that I want.
Have I said something amusing?
I've just sat too many times
on your side of the table
not to enjoy the irony of finding
myself on this side of it.
Would you like to
hear what I want?
I don't shackle myself
to people I don't know.
What I want is one favor.
One and only one.
Which is?
I need to be certain
you'll grant it before
I'll take the risk of
being more specific.
A blank check.
Of sorts.
You would never grant
anyone a blank check.
No.
But I'm not sitting on
that side of the table.
We still believe in
handshakes where I come from.
Do they still mean anything in Washington?
Who are you calling?
Car service to get
me to the airport.
Frank.
I will tell the President
that I want until Friday
to think things over before
I make my recommendation.
Let me know if you
change your mind.
And let me arrange
the car for you.
Hi, I'd like to
arrange a car, please.
How are you feeling?
Better than yesterday.
But I might take off early
if the nausea comes back.
I find it interesting
that you stay home
the day after you blow
off the SanCorp people.
You weren't
feeling sick,
Gillian.
I find it extremely
offensive that you'd
accuse me of hiding
behind my pregnancy.
You knew what I wanted.
The Botswana project is mine.
Under my umbrella.
Using money I raised.
You promised me autonomy.
Um, excuse us
for a moment, please.
I promised to empower you.
That's not the same
thing as you doing
as you choose
without consulting me.
I'm not going to
allow a project
I've put almost three
years of my life into...
Your project wouldn't be happening
if it weren't for SanCorp.
I didn't ask for their help.
How about consulting me
before you struck a deal?
Let's get something very
clear, I run the organization.
You work for it.
Our agreement is
an affiliation, Claire.
WorldWell isn't your vassal.
Yes, it is.
Entirely. If we're going
to be blunt about it.
That's not what you
proposed six months ago.
It's what you signed up for
when you signed the contract.
There was a good faith
understanding that...
And you've dissolved that
good faith by disobeying me.
Disobeying you?
Yes.
I threaten you, don't I?
Nothing about you threatens me.
But maybe you should
take a leave of absence.
Are you firing me?
That's up to you. But right
now, you should leave.
Did you get her on record?
No. She wouldn't
talk to me otherwise.
Well, we need hard proof that
Underwood was behind it.
This whole thing is
making me really nervous.
That you'll be exposed?
Not that.
It's Francis.
If this really goes
as deep as we think,
and he's already
watching you...
You think he's dangerous?
I know he is.
Then that's why we
have to keep going.
He crushes people, Janine.
Hey, Callum. Hey.
Look, if you weren't afraid, you
wouldn't be doing your job.
The only articles
that I have ever written
that truly mattered scared
the shit out of me.
We need to know about anything
that might've happened with Russo.
Something Underwood could
have held over him.
We have to go back to
Christina Gallagher,
see if she'll
give us something.
It can't be me.
If I go back for a second time...
I'll do it.
You honestly had no idea that the
President and Tusk were close?
He never showed up once on
any call sheet, phone log
or schedule during the campaign
or since we've been in office.
I'd love to believe you, Linda,
but I'm finding
it very difficult.
What would I gain by
keeping you in the dark?
I am as shocked
as you are, Frank.
Well, don't let on
that you know.
Of course not.
What's the President saying?
He wants to meet with you Tuesday
to get your report on Tusk.
That's a farce.
Should I come up with a
reason to delay the meeting?
No, maybe we'll learn something.
What time?
2:00 p.m.
All right, I'll be there.
Thank you, Linda.
We have one week.
To accomplish what exactly?
To force Tusk's hand.
He wants me
beholden to him? No.
We have to make him to
come crawling to me.
What's his weakness?
His fortune.
Wouldn't you say
that's his strength?
Not if it's slipping away.
How do you make $40 billion
disappear overnight?
We can't,
but maybe we can create
the illusion
that it's in danger.
The brief you gave
me on his assets,
how much of his total net
worth is in nuclear power?
About a third.
Sixteen reactors here in
the States, 37 worldwide.
Well, that's what
we hit him with.
We go after his
nuclear interests.
Even so, he's got $25 billion
in other investments...
Doug, this is a man who built
his fortune from nothing.
The money doesn't mean anything to him.
It's what it represents.
Which is what?
His life's work.
Get Remy Danton on the phone. Set
up a meeting as quickly as you can.
Tusk understands the difference
between power and money.
That's precisely what
makes him dangerous.
He doesn't measure his wealth in
private jets, but purchased souls.
I've worked too hard to get
within arm's reach of the prize
only to have my hand cut off
just before I seize it.
Zoe Barnes, here to see
Christina Gallagher.
I'm sorry,
I don't see
an appointment.
Oh, there must be a mistake.
I have an 11:30.
One second.
My name is Zoe Barnes,
I work at Slugline.
You spoke to my colleague,
Janine Skorsky.
Miss.
We're fine, thanks.
You can't just come in here...
There are things you
don't know about Peter.
I wrote the article
about Roy Kapeniak...
Please leave. Right now.
It was Peter who convinced
him to talk to me.
What? I don't understand...
Why would he...
Somebody pressured
him to do it.
The night of January 24. That's
when he went to speak to Kapeniak.
Do you remember
anything strange
around the time of
the inauguration?
Anything that could have
been held over him?
No, I don't.
If he was mixed
up in things that
in any way
contributed
to his suicide,
wouldn't you want to know?
I'm not trying to cause
you any more pain.
I just want the truth.
And you deserve
that more than anyone.
What was the date?
The 24th of January.
www.tvsubtitles.net