"A prince should have
no other aim or thought -
- but war and its organization
and discipline. " - Machiavelli
Hanne Holm, political observer,
what kind of game are they playing -
- The Liberals' Lars Hesselboe
and Labour's Michael Laugesen?
- Election day is only 3 days away.
- It's a chess game.
The end game is all about
making things simple.
Getting a few key messages across
and making your opponent look stupid.
Yes.
No, we don't want to talk EU.
That's not sexy election material.
Will Denmark's next prime minister be
Laugesen or Hesselboe?
It looks like it could be
the Opposition leader, Laugesen.
He's had the initiative
throughout the election.
Hesselboe tries
to preserve things as they are -
- but Danes are hungry for change,
albeit they're unsure as to what kind.
Laugesen looks more like
an advertising guy than a politician.
- Collect autographs, do you?
- My daughter does. She loves them.
- Get Birgitte Nyborg's for her then.
- She's more into real celebrities.
- Film and rock stars...
- Are we good to go?
You're on in eight. They'll ask
why you support Laugesen -
- and you can tell them how cool
we in the Opposition are.
Conceal any signs of her
lack of sleep this past fortnight.
She looks fantastic.
HESSELBOE BEHIND
Christ, Lars.
- You're still on these?
- It's the election.
I'm surprised you have a heart.
Hi. Let's do it out here.
In front of Parliament.
Ask me about asylum seekers only,
got it?
As always in Danish politics,
the fight is over the center.
The coalition with the centrist
Moderates benefits the Opposition.
Our next guest is Moderate leader,
Birgitte Nyborg Christensen. Welcome.
Kasper.
Oh, it's just business as usual.
We need to break the old patterns...
Zoom out on Katrine, 3.
- Where's Parliament?
- On 4.
- 4?
- 4, yes. Yes, get her shoulder, 3.
- Is that a live feed?
- Yes.
- Cue it up.
- We're running out of time.
So drop a few features. Cue it up.
Katrine, have Nyborg comment on
this interview just in with Laugesen.
At 11 she has a debate meeting
with some Labour hillbilly.
Overby, right.
She's gonna wipe the floor with him.
Do you share your coalition partner's
vision for the future of Denmark?
Yes, it's the very foundation
of our coalition.
I'd like your comments on this fresh
interview with Michael Laugesen.
Many Danes are worried about
the rising number of asylum seekers -
- in the wake of the Iraq war.
Let me make one thing clear:
Most of them will be sent back home -
- and until then
they'll be confined in refugee camps.
But you said they could work...
Look, we don't want them
taking Danish jobs.
We can't have employment hampered
by refugees already burdening us.
- So, will they be allowed to work?
- No, they won't be allowed to work.
Birgitte Nyborg, isn't Laugesen
going back on a deal here?
- It might be taken out of context.
- No, he's replying to a question.
Katrine, pile on the pressure.
The issue here is immigration policy,
a key issue to you and the Moderates.
If Laugesen goes back on his word, do
you still prefer him as prime minister?
Yes, of course we do.
- I need to find out if Laugesen...
- Dodge! Change the subject.
- Dodge!
- Laugesen is going back on his word.
Do you still support Laugesen,
yes or no?
Yes.
No. If that's Labour's new policy,
Laugesen no longer has our support.
Thank you, Birgitte Nyborg.
They're changing their policy
this late!
The train scandal continues...
GOVERNMENT
Episode 1
You own welfare and tax reform.
Jesus Christ!
It was in the news one minute ago.
Birgitte Nyborg rejects Laugesen.
- They won't let me buy anything.
- Honey, it's not...
Help me. My card keeps bouncing,
and I'm not leaving without that bag.
- I'm talking to my husband, damn it!
- Where are you?
Mulberry near Burlington Arcade.
It's all because you always desert me.
- You bastard!
- Honey, get a cab back to the hotel.
- I'm not leaving without that bag.
- Calm down, honey.
I deserve to have it good,
do you hear?
- I'll try to get a plane later.
- See you back home.
I'll handle this on my own.
- What's up, honey?
- Fucking store. I want this stuff.
- Let's come back later.
- No!
- You've bought for 12,000 dollars.
- And? I take so much crap from you.
How about giving something back?
- Lisbeth, please...
- Why can't you be nice to me?
- I forgot my wallet.
- Oh, shut up.
- Call that good journalism?
- Yes.
Birgitte Nyborg's spin doctor is
gonna have your ass.
- It comes with the job, Ulrik.
- Sure it does. Good luck.
You broke our deal. We demanded
to know your questions and angle.
- Ever heard of the free press?
- You know how this shit works.
- We're in the news business, Kasper.
- So, when can I see you?
- Soon.
- You never call.
Are you seeing someone?
- Is Birgitte Nyborg angry?
- No, she's a pro.
You don't pounce on your interviewee
three days before the election.
- Go for your prizes some other time.
- I'm sorry you feel that way.
We're here to cover the election,
not to support you.
Changing our policy three days before
the election calls for a new strategy.
I have that debate meeting in
20 minutes. We'll meet this afternoon.
- Is the car waiting?
- Yes. I'll talk to their head of news.
Katrine Fønsmark won't interview you
ever again.
Torben, Kasper Juhl speaking.
- Why can't we meet at the office?
- Something happened in London.
- Yes, you forgot this.
- I'm talking about Lisbeth.
- Popping pills again?
- She bought for 12,000 dollars.
Her Visa card bounced, and I was
afraid someone might see her.
She was about to make a scene,
so I panicked.
I only had my official Eurocard.
I know it was stupid.
Maybe you never should have brought
Lisbeth along to London.
I'll take these
and settle it with the Ministry.
You made a Party purchase
and didn't bring the right card.
It won't be charged to your account
for another two weeks.
We're sticking to the plan.
The Moderates will come crawling,
after Nyborg rejected the Opposition.
- She's rejected us so far.
- She needs new friends.
Besides, we owe her one. She just
gave you four more years, Lars.
See you.
I'm staying in town tonight to work.
How bold of you to change your policy
three days before the election.
I thought Nyborg was a smart girl.
How about a serious talk
when we've got a handle on things?
Why would we want to talk to you?
You need an alternative to the
Freedom Party to ensure your majority.
We need to talk immigrants and taxes.
We need 90 seats, and right now
you look like shit in the polls.
Round up your party for a charm
offensive this weekend. Call me.
And have fun.
- You should have dodged the bullet.
- Like we always do in this party?
- Like professional politicians do.
- See you.
- The Party is gonna have your ass.
- Nope.
I just talked to Nørgaard, Gjervig
and Lindholm. They're all behind you.
- This was bound to happen anyway.
- Laugesen isn't our natural choice.
Natural? We're not picking members
for the softball team here.
We're running for office here.
Did you see the latest polls?
- There's more to politics than polls.
- Not three days before an election.
We listen to the polls,
but they don't dictate our policy.
I know the Liberals want to talk to us.
I think we can keep the Freedom Party
out of power.
You scold her for leaving Labour. Now
you want her in bed with the Right?
- I have a birthday party to go to.
- Are you taking this seriously?
I work 16 hours a day,
or haven't you noticed?
I'm not going to make ouvertures
to the Right until after the election.
That is the Moderate Party's policy
as decided by me, their leader.
It's Saturday. I promised my children
the next four hours three weeks ago.
Never let your children down, Kasper,
because they grow up to be voters.
Hi.
- I missed you today.
- Boy, you look fantastic.
It's fake. I'm still in makeup
from this morning's show.
It was great! Just think, a politician
changed her policy on live TV.
- It was crazy.
- This is for you.
- Thanks. What is it?
- They said it's 150 years old.
- I bought it in London this morning.
- I thought you were too busy for that.
We were, till the Prime Minister's wife
popped a handful of tranquilizers.
- I thought we didn't talk about that.
- We don't.
If we do, I have a lot of questions.
I want to be with you all the time.
But...
- But?
- I'm lying to Nina and the kids.
- I have to make a choice.
- So does everyone in three days.
- I've made my choice.
- Was that a farewell gift?
No. I'm going to leave Nina.
I want to be with you.
All the time. Officially. No bullshit.
Get it?
- Is that ice skating thing tomorrow?
- Yes. Dad's taking me, right?
- Yes.
- I'm going to practice my piano.
Put on your headphones,
so you won't wake Magnus.
Hasn't she been playing
"Let it Be" for two months now?
How's it coming along?
I don't see an international career
in the cards for her.
Honey, you really buy
too much dessert.
And pastry for breakfast. I know it's
for the kids, but I end up eating it.
You always gain weight
during an election.
Hey, you!
Did I ask for honesty here?
"Voluptuous Birgitte Nyborg
in an elegant black dress. "
- They wrote that after that premier.
- So?
Black slims.
Black is sophisticated and sexy.
- Voluptuous in black is bad.
- Look, honey.
You get the most fantastic ass
during an election -
- and I try to live with that
in my own slightly primitive way.
Keep going.
I can't. You've cut off
the blood supply to my legs.
You used to be so funny.
You're losing your touch.
Michael Laugesen wants me to drink
champagne with Labour tomorrow.
When I was young, champagne
and Labour ruled each other out.
- Should I go?
- How tactical do you want to be?
I'm trying to salvage the remains,
but I don't want it to look that way.
Go. Make him retreat. Tell your voters
you'd rather topple the government -
- than sacrifice the Opposition
over a key issue.
- That's gonna take some swallowing.
- Wash it down with some ice cream.
- But you are funny.
- A scream.
Kasper, my usually smart ex,
asked me if I was seeing someone.
I just ignored the question.
I'm turning into a fantastic liar.
My mom doesn't even know you exist.
She will soon, though.
"Meet my new boyfriend, Mom.
13 years older, married with kids. "
I've never been happier.
I just thought you should know.
Meanie! If you're asleep, you're not
getting any sex the next month.
Ole.
Ole... look at me.
Ole, say something!
Come on, damn it!
It's not funny, okay?
Svend Åge Saltum, the Freedom Party
applauds Laugesen's remarks.
It's no secret that Labour needs to get
back in touch with their voters -
- many of whom are switching to us.
- Taking notes, Kasper?
- Good evening, Svend Åge.
No, your rhetoric is
crystal clear as always.
What is it you do, Kasper?
My constituency wants me
to hire a guy like you.
But I don't quite know what you do
to earn your no doubt grand salary.
What do they call you again?
Spin doctor, huh?
- Yes.
- But who's sick, Kasper?
Oh, excuse me.
- Kasper Juhl.
- Kasper...
What did people like you do
before they invented the cell phone?
- Katrine, what's up?
- I think he's dead.
- Take a breath. What's up?
- I don't know what to do.
He's just lying there
with his eyes open.
- I've tried everything.
- Where are you?
Tell me where you are,
and I'll be right over.
20 Bredgade, please.
He just went and died.
I guess he must have been sick.
So the guy you kept a secret from me
was the Prime Minister's PR advisor?
How long have you been dating him?
Grab your stuff.
Katrine, grab your stuff.
- You'll get fired, if this comes out.
- I don't care.
- You'll be accused of pillow talk.
- We never told each other anything.
Okay. The cab's waiting outside.
Go home and leave this to me.
- His wife and kids mustn't find out.
- Lots of people mustn't find out.
- We can't just leave him here.
- Katrine, let me handle this.
Go and take the cab.
I'll call you later.
You were home all night watching TV.
You weren't here, okay?
You were never here.
Hurry! Get going.
Emergency, how can I help you?
Hello.
Turn it down!
Hello! Hello!
- Do I look okay?
- Your scarf's crooked.
Thanks. People are in shock here.
The Liberal Party Secretary agreed
to an interview later about Ole Dahl.
- I think we should let Katrine do it.
- I can't reach Katrine.
- The broad's gone off the radar.
- But that's unheard of.
- I just texted her those exact words.
- Hi, Hanne. Ulrik speaking.
I don't mean to criticize, but Katrine
isn't the most stable person around.
- Let me do the interview.
- First of all, did we ask you? No.
Secondly, if you don't mean
to criticize, what was that then?
- You're not doing the interview...
- Fuck you.
Katrine has a different approach.
And I don't mean to criticize, Ulrik.
- Was that really necessary, Hanne?
- He can't get his head out of my ass.
- He's a great reporter.
- No, he's available. That's different.
He's a mediocre reporter, devoid of...
- Turn her off. I can't stand her.
- Here comes the Prime Minister.
Good day to you all.
I have a sad announcement.
My close associate and friend
of 11 years, Ole Dahl -
- died last night of a heart attack.
The election is coming up in two days.
I request of you not to use
this tragedy to question -
- my own and the Liberal Party's
capacity to carry on our campaign.
You'd be questioning
the professionalism -
- we should remember Ole Dahl for.
- Have you got a minute?
- Sure.
What will happen after the election,
do you think?
I'm finished as party leader,
don't you think?
What if I had some information
that could get you into office?
That sounds strange, but intriguing.
The Prime Minister uses state funds to
finance his private overconsumption.
- Who started that rumour?
- I've seen the evidence.
I've seen a Mulberry receipt
for 12,056 dollars -
- charged to his official account,
and two annulled Visa Card receipts -
- proving his wife tried
to make the same purchase.
Where did you see them?
Have you got them?
I can get them.
Either we tell Hesselboe we have them
and ask if he's ready to negotiate -
- or we go to the media and join
in the unified Opposition's outcry.
We're no longer part
of the unified Opposition.
Or we leak it anonymously
and wait for him to resign.
- And he will.
- Maybe it's all a misunderstanding.
Hesselboe billed the state
for an extravagant bag and coat.
- His wife is unhappy.
- He committed fraud.
And you want me to blackmail him?
The Prime Minister just lost
his best advisor.
- How dirty do you think I am?
- We stand to take a beating.
This is war. We can't let a chance
like this slip through our fingers.
I'd never forgive myself,
if I came to power that way.
In that case
I doubt you ever will.
Lindenkrone. Who says left-wingers
can't be drop dead gorgeous?
Dunno. But that's not your problem,
because you're not a left-winger.
You're fast. Aicha, good to see you.
You'll find cold sodas in the bar.
- Help yourself. It's free.
- Great, thanks.
Hi there, and welcome.
Birgitte, my dear. Boy, have you been
on my mind these past 24 hours.
- You too, Michael.
- Sounds like the start of a romance.
- Got a minute?
- You bet.
Help yourself to drinks.
It's on the house.
Off to battle
the red flag in hand
in these times
full of turmoil and strife
Close the door. Jesus, the songs
are the worst part of this job.
The old party dinosaurs
are putting the pressure on me.
These suburban bigots are ready to
sell their votes to the Freedom Party.
But I can't let them do that, because
then I won't become prime minister.
You and the coalition have got
to give me some space.
I can't when you go back on our deal.
We agreed to allow asylum seekers
to work after six months.
Stop nitpicking. They come here from
banana republics torn by civil war.
They've been through hell and can't
even clean the floor in a resthome.
I'll ignore that. You broke a political
deal three days before the election.
All this talk about emotions
is making me thirsty.
Birgitte, I need you
to support my candidacy.
- Your statements make it hard for me.
- I'll repay you.
Two more cabinet posts
than your seats warrant.
Apart from Treasury
and Foreign Affairs, take your pick.
Come on. Tomorrow we'll hold a joint
press meeting where you support me.
And I promise you we'll find jobs
for a couple of asylum seekers -
- as long as you don't
go about telling everyone.
I understand your interest
in a marriage of convenience.
But I'm an old-fashioned gal,
so my answer is no.
Talk to you after the election.
- No deal. He won't take it back.
- You're making my job difficult.
You'll probably be out of it soon,
Kasper.
- Yes?
- Don't you recognize me?
- We met at the coast.
- Right.
Let's get you some champagne.
- You're back early.
- I couldn't do it.
If we lose one or two seats,
I'm gonna resign at the convention.
- More, and I'll resign on the spot.
- Who says it's gonna be that bad?
It's time for you to pursue your career
now. My five years are up, remember?
- I thought you'd forgotten our deal.
- Hardly. It was my idea.
Very modern of me,
if I do say so myself.
Five years of career for you and five
for me. Even if you did find it silly.
Well, it implies you're able to put
your career on hold every five years.
- We've managed.
- We've been lucky.
What if Bill Gates had asked me to be
CEO of Microsoft five years ago?
- You'd have turned him down.
- Sure I would.
Somewhat more dignified than being
voted out by the Danish people -
- like me the day after tomorrow.
Are you gunning for some pity sex,
or what?
You'd be so much better at this job.
No, because I wouldn't have been
able to turn down Laugesen.
Coming through.
Everyone speaks highly of you,
Kasper.
Only because they don't know me.
- Promise me not to go away.
- Promises are alien to my racket.
When a Cuban delegation
came to visit us -
- we had to send them outside
to smoke. Coming?
To smokos un cigaros
Havana Cubana.
If I were a cynic, I'd take a picture
of that and sell it to the media.
- You pissing on Parliament.
- Know what's worth pissing on?
This naive idea of a nation run by
the people. The people don't run crap.
A tiny privileged circle of people
rule Denmark.
From the corporate world, the media
and a few politicians.
As long as I'm part of that circle,
they can call it anything they like.
What have you got for me, Kasper?
I apologize on behalf of my leader
for the no deal.
- So sneak something in the back way.
- She's not fond of the back way.
She's a nice girl, you see.
How about you? Wouldn't you like
to work for the Prime Minister?
I doubt Hesselboe wants me
to replace Ole Dahl.
You think Hesselboe
is prime minister after the election?
- Not necessarily.
- Not necessarily?
I know something.
I know something that could make
the right person prime minister.
If used wisely.
I'm a wise man, Kasper.
I've got an unpleasant announcement
regarding Hanne Holm.
As you may know,
she used to have a drinking problem.
Yesterday I received an e-mail
that Hanne is drinking again -
- sent from one of our open computers.
TV1 can't have a drunk hosting
the pre-election party leader debate -
- so I've been forced
to discharge Hanne as of today.
Now, we have an election to cover,
so get to work. You, my office, now.
We need to talk.
Hi there.
Where the hell have you been?
Sick? Answer your calls!
I should fire you, but we can't afford
to lose any more good reporters.
Look, this may sound like a promotion,
but it sure as hell isn't.
I want you to host
the final debate tonight.
Did you read my speech
for the final debate tonight?
- Yes, it's fine.
- Good. Wear the black suit.
It looks good on TV, and it slims.
Want to run through it?
It comes off as a smart attempt to save
a tactically difficult situation.
I don't want to waste what might be
my last appearance on tactics.
Want a farewell speech? I can deliver.
And if I asked for a speech on capital
punishment, you'd say: For or against?
- I wasn't hired for my convictions.
- I'll be speaking to you tonight then.
Congratulations.
Or aren't congratulations due?
Look, I've always respected girls
who fuck their way to the top.
At least it's a talent.
I mean, they're good at fucking.
But snitching on people
who do theirjobs -
- is such an ugly little Danish
tradition, for which I hold no regard.
- You think I told...
- Drop it! Who won us the debate?
- Hanne, I'd never...
- Let go of me!
The worst thing is...
I really quite liked you.
- Give it up, Mom.
- Get lost!
Dad, talk to her.
She's too fat for that skirt.
- The cab will be here in five minutes.
- It'll just have to wait.
There.
If I push it down here,
it doesn't show, does it?
- Do I look okay?
- Want the truth or the loving version?
- The truth.
- Your ass is too big for that skirt.
- And the loving version?
- The dry cleaner shrunk it.
Oh.
Okay, it's back to the old dress then.
Nothing else fits. But I can't
wear this to a debate. Look.
The other day the kids and I
were watching you on TV.
Afterward Magnus asked me:
"Dad, am I gonna be as smart
as Mom when I grow up?"
We're so proud of you.
You do know that, don't you?
- Anyway, I need to put this on.
- So put it on.
Attagirl.
Katrine, you're 29 years old,
and you just snagged the final debate.
Get in there and knock
their socks off. I know you can.
- I keep crying, and they wonder why.
- They'll put it down to nerves.
Let's go. It's the final debate. I'll
drive you there in the Black Lightning.
Come on.
Check positions. Keep an eye
on background and audience.
- Does my panic show?
- You're one sexy lady.
Did you hear anything out there?
The Liberals and the Freedom Party
seem cocky. Beware of Laugesen.
The Labour guy. He's wired.
He groped my ass.
We'll slap a sexual harassment charge
on him. Talk to me.
750,000 Danes may vote differently
this time. Laugesen is after the...
- They're drawing lots now.
- Katrine, two minutes.
You're gonna be great,
because you look fantastic -
- and you're a brilliant reporter.
If you aren't, it's my ass on the line.
- The black suit's at the cleaner's.
- You look good.
Just relax and be yourself.
And stick to the speech.
Got a minute?
Don't use that info now.
Are you crazy?
In ten.
Katrine, you look hot.
Four, three, two, one.
Roll camera 3.
- Dad, it's on now.
- Coming, coming.
We're going to debate
the key election issues.
Each party leader will get two minutes
to deliver their closing remarks.
We'll shut off the mikes after two
minutes, and that goes for all of you.
Don't give me that look.
I promise to behave tonight.
That would be a first, Svend Åge.
- There's Mom.
- Dad, that dress is embarrassing!
We need to send Mom positive vibes.
Lars Hesselboe has been
Prime Minister these past seven years.
Michael Laugesen is after his job.
You're both
full of big election pledges -
- but let me just say on behalf of the
women voters: Size doesn't count.
Welcome to the Final Debate, 2010.
This is it. It's time for the closing
remarks from each party leader.
We'll begin
with Anne Sofie Lindenkrone.
I'm ashamed to be a Dane in this
selfish nation Hesselboe has created.
- Amir Diwan is on camera 3.
- Is Diwan with a W?
Yes.
A vote for us is a vote for a green,
financially sound Denmark.
Denmark needs a modern,
well-trained military...
Hesselboe on 3.
Individual freedom and initiative
is what keeps Denmark going.
Can we still take care
of our senior citizens -
- when we have to take in criminal
immigrants who travel 4,000 miles...
Next up is Birgitte Nyborg.
Roll 3.
Thank you, Svend Åge Saltum.
Last but one is Birgitte Nyborg.
The floor is yours.
All of us here have become
ever so professional.
We know every question, because
we check them off with the reporters.
She's improvising. Katrine, that isn't
her speech. She's going impro.
All this decides our actions.
I'm shocking my spin doctor right now
by not sticking to my speech.
I upset him by not wearing
the right clothes either.
The trouble is
I've gotten a bit too fat for them.
Zoom out and let's see the dress.
Great, stay with that.
I believe we must
own up to our mistakes -
- and admit it when
there's something we don't know.
I became a politician -
- because I once held strong views on
how this world should be. I still do.
I believe we're losing
what keeps Denmark together.
I believe, unlike the Freedom Party,
we do live in a multiethnic society -
- so it's a waste of time
to discuss how to avoid it.
I believe it's a myth that we're all
equal and share equal possibilities.
These past seven years have seen
the gap widen between poor and rich.
The Prime Minister will say: "Oh, but
everyone is a master of his own fate. "
But to believe that the free market is
the best cure for social inequality -
- is like saying cars will cure the
climate crisis. It's not good enough.
If we're to create a new Denmark
together -
- we have to invent a new way
of communicating and doing politics.
Words like socialism, liberalism
and solidarity just might be words -
- describing the world of yesterday
and not the world of tomorrow.
A modern world is manifold,
and so must our democracy be.
A vote for the Moderates tomorrow is
a vote for a new Denmark. Thank you.
Christ! Nyborg has really got it tonight,
hasn't she?
That's your mom.
You can be proud of her.
- So, Michael Laugesen, top that.
- You bet I will.
I prepared a speech like, well, almost
everyone else. But I can't deliver it.
Not after having seen proof of the
Prime Minister's arrogance of power.
For seven years, he's been preaching
financial responsibility to the voters.
How does that add up, Hesselboe -
- when you let the state finance
your own overconsumption?
- What are you talking about?
- This is a receipt.
You billed the state 12,000 dollars
for gifts to your wife, Prime Minister.
- Christ!
- Zoom in on the receipts.
What's going on? Keep going.
- 12,000 dollars, Lars Hesselboe!
- Don't the rules apply to us all?
- Let the Prime Minister reply.
- Katrine, over to him.
Let's give Lars Hesselboe
a chance to reply.
I don't know what receipts he's got,
but this is not the place to air them.
- Is this your signature, Hesselboe?
- Stop that!
I won't stand for
your fabricated accusations... No!
Talk to my lawyer.
I'm leaving this debate now.
- If that isn't an admittance...
- Follow him out.
All the way out.
Screw aestethics!
Thank you, Michael Laugesen.
The debate is over. Thank you.
This debate came to a somewhat
surprising end. Tune in later for more.
I wish you all a good election.
- We're off.
- Alright! Jesus Christ!
That was fucking great TV,
girls and boys.
You were great. I'm sure my daughter
wants your autograph now. Later?
Sure.
Where did Laugesen get
that information?
Come in at nine tomorrow
and clear your desk.
Bye-bye.
Today, the Danes will decide -
- who is going to rule Denmark
the next four years.
The polls aren't painting a clear
picture after yesterday's debate -
- dubbed the most chaotic ever.
THE PRIME MINISTER
STANDS ACCUSED
We'd have made a good pair
in the long run.
Spare me the emotions.
That's my field.
My keys.
And your phone. The computer, and
the campaign documents are there.
I told security I'd take your ID card
before you leave Parliament.
Thank you.
Birgitte! The Labour top brass are
washing their hands of Laugesen.
The dramatic debate is sending shock
waves throughout the Labour Party.
Respected former leader
Hardy Eriksen -
- calls Laugesen's behaviour
at the debate a disgrace.
"I no longer support Laugesen's
leadership," Hardy Eriksen says.
This can go any which way.
We'd better look sharp tonight.
According to the first exit polls -
- the Moderates are tonight's winners
with over eight seats in Parliament.
- Mom, you're eight points ahead.
- Seats, you moron.
- Don't tease.
- It's true. It just came in.
I hate this.
I hate this, I hate this, I hate this.
- Not now, Phillip. I'm in hell.
- Birgitte.
I made the dry cleaner buy you a new
one, seeing as he shrunk the old one.
I love you.
Things are heating up.
We expect Labour leader...
We're still waiting
for the key figures...
Are you waiting for me, or...?
- No, wait. Let him go in first.
- Why?
Mom deserves to go on TV too.
Prime Minister Hesselboe just arrived.
How do you feel about the result?
I'm shocked that this misunderstanding
had such grave political implications.
Your lawyer hasn't
repudiated the claim -
- that your wife billed the state
12,000 dollars for clothes.
- I assure you, there's nothing in it.
- Are you still Prime Minister?
Okay.
Hesselboe hasn't been able
to rebuff my evidence.
He committed fraud and must pay.
I don't regret a thing.
I'd like to direct your attention
to my wife's dress.
Ten years old,
63 dollars at the local market.
Here comes one of tonight's winners,
Moderate Leader, Birgitte Nyborg.
Remember this, honey.
The Moderate Party is sky-rocketing.
They've gained ten more seats.
This is insane!
We've gained ten seats, Birgitte.
What if they're useless,
because Hesselboe has enough?
He lost 12 seats.
He has to resign. The door is open!
- We're going home.
- I want to see the result.
You look beat.
Just look at your brother.
- Are you okay with this?
- Sure. You look like a statesman!
Come along, kids.
And the success continues.
Two more seats...
We now have the national result.
Tonight, Denmark has seen
a landslide victory.
The two major opponents, Laugesen
and Hesselboe, are the two losers.
The winner is without a doubt
the Moderate Party.
15 seats. I just don't get it.
You hit the zeitgeist. This is
the beginning of something new.
Now, thank them and lead them,
because they want to be led by you.
- What if I don't know how?
- You'll learn it along the way.
We've come a long way.
Commentators say the voters voted
against Labour and the Liberals -
- because of the showdown
between Laugesen and Hesselboe -
- and that void was filled
by Birgitte Nyborg...
Coming? Torben is asking for you.
He's about to make a speech.
I'll be right in.
Katrine, come on.
I'm singing your praise.
What's up?
There, there...
DENMARK ELECTED FOR DECENCY
Thanks.
Hi.
- I didn't buy pastry.
- They want me for prime minister.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst