Darling,
you've bought for 12,000 dollars.
I only had my official Eurocard.
I'll settle it with the PM's Office.
Kasper, my usually smart ex -
asked me today
if I was seeing anyone. Ole!
Come on, damn it!
It's not funny, okay?
I think he's dead.
- Where are you?
I know something that could make
the right person prime minister.
This is a receipt proving -
that you billed the state $12,000
for gifts to your wife, Prime Minister.
Come in at 9 tomorrow
and clear your desk.
You look like a statesman tonight.
Birgitte! Birgitte!
- They want me for prime minister.
"It is much more secure to be feared,
than to be loved. " - Machiavelli
The Solidarity Party,
The Green Party, Labour and us -
together we have 91 seats.
You have the seats you need.
Think anyone's got cold feet?
- You have enough seats.
What about Labour?
- Laugesen just got KO'ed.
Nervous?
Her Majesty is waiting to give you
the mandate to form the cabinet.
The people gave me the mandate.
- Posing as a republican, are we?
You're loving this.
Cabinet-forming negotiations
with the Queen is a nice tradition.
The election winner
meets with the Queen.
It's the least we can do after
they put the people in power in 1849.
Why is she keeping us waiting?
Maybe she went out
to get cigarettes.
More coffee while you wait?
- No, thank you.
Her Majesty will see you in a moment.
Something's wrong.
They're trying to win time.
God damn it! Everyone wants you
to chair the negotiations.
Don't swear at the Palace.
- This isn't the hard part.
The hard part is controlling
the process the next couple of days -
so that you end up presenting
your new cabinet. Remember that.
Yes.
Look, we've got 91 seats.
Can't the bitch count?
Her Majesty will see you now.
- Thank you.
GOVERNMENT
Episode 2- Count to 90
How was the Queen?
- Polite in a royal way.
Did they live like on TV?
- Yes.
Did you curtsey?
- You have to.
Good morning.
Hey, the Prime Minister
is eating her cereal in our kitchen.
Good morning, Bent.
- I've lined up today's meetings.
Solidarity, the Greens,
the Liberals and the Freedom Party.
What about Labour?
- I'm banking on them coming first.
Mom, you're on TV.
- Hang on.
Bent, we're on TV.
Is Denmark going to get
its first female prime minister?
Yesterday, Birgitte Nyborg was
appointed royal investigator.
Torben Friis, welcome.
What kind of game are we witnessing?
It's the game
for political power in Danmark.
It proved a dramatic 24 hours
for Hesselboe.
Indeed, and as a result thereof -
- he had the cabinet step down
yesterday.
He had a bad election,
and I'm betting this nasty affair...
It's been seven good years, Lars.
- Thank you.
Laugesen is partly to blame.
Labour -
- suffered their worst election ever.
Laugesen's very aggressive attack...
When can you see the radio news?
- Bjorn, get the hell out. Get lost!
Laugesen is fighting
for his political life.
His party takes exception to him
and his campaign methods.
Let's look at the distribution of seats
in the new parliament.
- 91 and 88.
- A clear majority.
Birgitte!
So, the Prime Minister bikes?
- You'd better ask the Prime Minister.
When will you form the cabinet?
- No comment.
Good morning.
- Birgitte.
Congratulations. It's fantastic.
We've got a historic chance
to get Denmark back on track.
I'm meeting with Labour first, Amir.
It's a great day for democracy,
Birgitte.
Good morning. Let's switch to fruit
during meetings. I gave this up.
Labour won't come until this
afternoon. They're being tactical.
Or falling apart.
Let's reschedule another party then.
The Freedom Party's got time now
and then Solidarity, we hope.
Tell Laugesen it's crucial
that he shows up today. Anytime.
Tell Laugesen we're forming
a cabinet without Labour.
Look, we need to close this today.
- No chance.
Everyone gets a fair treatment. I've
made a list of items for each party.
Aicha Nagrawi.
- Good morning.
We can meet at 11.
We have a list of items -
crucial to a potential collaboration.
Congratulations on being elected.
The lady got a new head scarf, I see.
Hello there.
My mom wore a head scarf, too.
She was from a fishing town.
Hello, Bent. Congratulations
on your fantastic election.
And congratulations to you.
You did well, too. Sit down.
Thank you for coming. We've got
quite a political bridge to gap.
Still, I'd like to find out
where we see eye to eye.
Landslide-shocked are we, Birgitte?
Let's begin with tax policy.
Look, I followed Glistrup
back in 1971-
when the Conservatives
refused to let him run.
After that, Glistrup formed
the Progress Party.
One and a half years later
he gained 28 seats in Parliament.
He didn't hesitate for a second.
He was a winner.
Your party just doubled its vote.
Why don't you sound like a winner?
Glistrup went to jail...
- Look.
You and I differ on immigration,
economy, taxes -
culture, environment.
Everything you stand for
I'm against.
I am evil incarnate
in your little intellectual world.
You don't have time
to drink coffee with me.
But let me give you a piece of advice.
Take the head of the table
when you chair the negotiations.
Don't mind if I make it
a pastry to go, do you?
Have a nice day now.
Lots of people would like to fuck
the prime minister if it were Nyborg.
I've never heard that said before.
- She's a babe.
Did Hanne Holm congratulate you
on hosting the final debate?
Give me a smoke, Dan.
- I thought you quit.
We've got a hectic schedule, but we
need to cover the Ole Dahl funeral -
which is today.
It's going to draw a huge crowd.
Simon, bring a crew
and get some comments.
Pia, you got a scoop.
Lars Hesselboe and his wife are
guests on 'Focus' this Sunday -
to talk about the death of Ole Dahl,
marriage and the big downfall.
I'm thinking Katrine.
You're fucking good at emotions.
I don't have time to prepare for it.
- Say what?
I'm planning on attending the funeral.
Oh, you knew him?
- Through my talks with Hesselboe.
During the election
I talked to him lots of...
I'll take it. Let her anchor at six.
- Sure, if it's okay with Katrine.
Are you with us on this? The swap?
- Sure.
Have we got
any background info on Nyborg?
We're talking to her old classmates.
- Perfect, pile it on. See you later.
I just went upstairs
to sound out the Moderates.
Nyborg hasn't got a clue.
It's a waste of time.
Are you sure?
- Hi, Lars. See you later.
What ministries do you want?
- Environment and five or six more.
Maybe a new Ministry of Climate.
You're entitled
to four ministries, max.
Don't you want to be PM?
- Yes, but I won't be blackmailed.
Think it over and let me know.
An Inger Hansen is here.
Hi. I'm afraid Lars Hesselboe
couldn't meet with you personally.
I saw him in the hall half an hour ago.
Who are you?
- Inger Hansen.
I'm a member of the Liberals.
- Can you speak for the party?
Yes, during the initial meetings.
- There are no initial meetings.
We're forming a cabinet here.
If Hesselboe can't find the time,
we'll go on without the Liberals.
You just need Labour
to close the deal.
Laugesen will be right in.
- Don't bet on it.
He's leaving Parliament now.
Laugesen is leaving now. Have you
given Birgitte Nyborg your support?
I haven't met with her.
I have a meeting with my constituents.
- Are you still party leader?
- No comment.
Arrogant son of a bitch.
We agreed to meet half an hour ago.
Michael, call me.
We're watching you leave on TV,
and we have a meeting in ten minutes.
I expect you to call me back
and reschedule ASAP. Thanks.
What the hell is going on, Bent?
I'm stuck without Labour.
I can't form a fucking cabinet
with Solidarity and the Greens!
I'm losing control.
It's slipping away.
Take it easy
and go home to your family.
You lost the battle today.
You're going to win tomorrow.
Did everyone get that?
No. What does G stand for?
- At least pretend you've read this.
G stands for 'government'.
State funds or credits.
Page 27 in International Finance.
This is basic knowledge, people.
That's all for today.
- Please tell us about Friedman.
Milton Friedman, Nobel Prize winner,
Reagan's economic advisor.
Next time, people.
- How about...
Amina, go get a coffee
and find yourself a boyfriend.
Hi, kids. Hi, sweetie.
I thought you had to work late.
- We're stuck.
I need to make more random visits.
Good-looking students.
Stupid girl.
I know Laugesen is just
flexing his muscles -
but without Labour I'm dead.
I'm the smaller party. Why should they
agree to make me Prime Minister?
Because they took a beating.
Sure, they're the largest party,
but they've never been smaller.
If you want the job, just take it.
You've got to bluff.
Everyone does in the corporate world.
This isn't about qualifications.
Men lie themselves 50% better
atjob interviews.
Women make themselves 50% worse
by talking about what they can't.
Why do you think there aren't
any more women poker players?
They can't bluff. You've got
to take the head of the table.
If you show them you're a leader,
you're a leader.
Wannabe business coach!
I can take the head of the table.
- Great. What's the problem then?
Hey, you.
What's going on, Laura?
Leave him alone.
Kids, listen up!
Hey, we're talking. If you want to beat
each other up, go somewhere else.
See? That's taking
the head of the table.
We have to have a serious talk
with the kids if I make PM.
Not if... when.
Positive vibes.
I mean it. It'll change everything.
They know.
I'll talk to them.
You and I need to talk, too.
We made a deal back then.
- Sure.
But this is different.
Completely out of the loop.
Why?
I'm not going to tell my wife
I don't want her to be PM.
Who wants to tell his wife that?
What are you doing?
- Taking the head of the table.
Hi.
- Good morning, beautiful.
I thought you'd be out here
punishing yourself.
Water?
- Thanks.
What did you want?
- Nothing.
Just to talk.
Is everything okay?
No, everything's crap.
Sometimes I miss him so much
I don't know who I am.
How did you leave him
after I took the cab?
I just removed all signs of him
not being alone when he died.
Are you okay?
I don't work
for the Moderates anymore.
Just thought you should know.
You got fired?
- No way. I quit.
They're just too PC.
Officially, I left because
of a mutual disagreement.
Are you upset?
- No.
Know where Laugesen
got the receipts that nailed the PM?
He must have had a source
at the Prime Minister's Office. Why?
No reason. It's just that
I'm not in the know anymore.
I have to be at work in a hour.
This was nice of you. See you.
Breakfast sometime?
Good morning. The light was on
all night over at Labour's.
Laugesen is mounting
his strongest team.
Unless we have a concrete offer,
he'll smell blood.
I'm not bowing down on integration.
They can have the Ministries of
Finance, Justice and Foreign Affairs.
We'll take Economic and Business
Affairs, Education and Culture.
Are we early?
- Not at all.
Michael, Hoxenhaven, Marrot.
Sit down.
Congratulations again.
- Thanks.
Have you gone vegan on me?
Can't a guy get his pastry?
Let's get straight to work.
We met with the Greens
and the Solidarity Party yesterday.
I didn't want to get into the specifics
until we'd met.
Let me give you an overview...
I respect your position
as the royal investigator.
If Labour hadn't gotten back in step -
you'd have been an obvious PM.
Excuse me, but what is going on?
Labour and I want you to tell the
Queen your negotiations have failed -
so you're proposing me
as the new investigator.
Why on earth should I do that?
- I doubt you'll propose Hesselboe.
Besides, we're the largest party.
Of course
we should head the cabinet.
You've never been smaller.
Yesterday, I negotiated
with the Greens and Solidarity.
They're both proposing me as PM.
Birgitte, your day will come.
And we have a concrete offer for you.
Send the papers round, please.
Solidarity is out of the question.
It's down to us, you and the Greens.
Amir gets the Ministry of Environment
and Health and other little titbits.
We're offering you
Economy and Business Affairs -
Employment
and four soft ones.
You take the Prime Minister's Office
and Finance and Foreign Affairs?
Well, it's just a proposal.
- No way. We can't work with this.
I forgot. You get Justice, too.
- But we just agreed...
Troels, we'll work it out, okay?
Negotiations will continue -
as soon as Birgitte has proposed me
to chair the negotiations.
We need to think about this.
We're going to form the cabinet
tomorrow, with or without you.
You're going to get seven seats
in the cabinet. Hello!
You can still look your voters
in the eye, Birgitte.
That's all for now. Coming?
- Yes.
I'll just grab an apple.
Organic?
Have a nice day.
Hi.
Hanne came to clear her table.
Pity, but I've got the brass behind me.
Are you okay?
- Sure. Thanks.
Hanne?
- What do you want?
I'm sad to lose you as a coworker.
I don't know who sent that e-mail
about you. I was shocked.
I'm the one who's shocked.
You take over the final debate -
and become the prime-time anchor.
You're not ready.
Still, the most depressing thing
is the way -
this entire staff has treated
the outcome of the election.
Ratings and free premiere tickets
mean more to you -
than critical journalism.
You're newsreaders, that's all.
We've all got to start somewhere.
- Great, so start somewhere.
Why did Labour and the Liberals
avoid meeting with the Moderates?
How did Laugesen get hold
of Hesselboe's receipts?
You don't care about the crucial stuff
pertaining to how this country is run.
You rant about party strife
and churn out glossy articles -
about when Birgitte Nyborg
headed the student council.
I just came to wish you good luck.
Katrine?
Just to satisfy my curiosity.
Was calling me a drunk
enough to get my job -
or did you have
to fuck the Head of News, too?
So, what are my options?
You always ask that.
Tell the Queen you want
to propose Laugesen as PM.
With the support of the other parties,
he's the opposition leader.
If you propose someone else,
you'll lose your credibility.
He's an unscrupulous bastard,
and he'll be a bastard of a boss, too.
Still, we get seven seats.
Not bad.
Birgitte, you did your best.
Good night, sweetie.
Are you okay?
- Yes. Thanks.
Good night.
- Sleep tight.
It's tough to be comforted by your kids
because you didn't make PM.
So you made Minister of Economy
and Business Affairs. Not bad, either.
Still, it's not the same.
Magnus said not to feel bad.
His P.E. Teacher said
second place was just as good.
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
No more shit.
There, it's gone.
- He pulled a classic Laugesen.
He always pulls these maneuvers.
- I should've known.
Drink my wine, why don't you?
Amina?
Does she write as well as she flirts?
- She's far better at flirting.
Something really bugs me, though.
I had so been looking forward
to the PM giving me a blowjob.
I'll ask if Laugesen's game.
- Please do.
Hallo.
- Birgitte Nyborg?
I've got information
that could bring Laugesen down.
Who is this?
- Not on the phone. Let's meet.
I don't want to meet with you,
if I don't know who you are.
Both you and Bent Sejro will find
my information very interesting.
The future of the nation is at stake.
10 o'clock at the Marble Bridge?
Okay.
What was that all about?
A mint?
- No thanks.
Want me to come?
- No.
Troels?
I'm sorry about this,
but I'm not taking any chances.
What would you do, if Laugesen
were forced to stand down -
as leader of the party tomorrow?
But how?
Would you support a new party leader
to head the cabinet?
That depends on who.
If Laugesen stands down, he'll be
succeeded by a deputy leader.
You or Bjorn Marrot?
- Bjorn isn't cut out to be a leader.
He's got no popular support.
He's Laugesen's flunkey.
So you want to be prime minister?
How are you going
to topple Laugesen?
I've got an e-mail correspondance
between Laugesen and his cronies.
Read it for yourself.
The press is going to have a field day.
"The sight of Aicha from
the Solidarity Party makes me sick -
when she wears her fanatical scarf -
promoting a medieval
anti-democratic religion. "
How do I know these are real?
- I've got them all in my computer.
And that's only the beginning.
He's going to ban
head scarves in public -
if he comes to power.
He wouldn't dare.
- Are you willing to chance it?
This correspondance is more
than enough to topple him.
But I need your support
to make it worth the trouble.
I have to talk to Sejro about it.
- Let me know before midnight.
I want it to hit the news tomorrow.
We want Foreign Affairs, too.
- Deal.
I'll be in touch.
I knew I had some left.
This is one of the most insane
political tackles I've ever seen.
Hox has been a loyal party man for
20 years. Laugesen's avid supporter.
Caesar was murdered
by his friends, too.
I feel a history lesson coming on.
- I want to show you something.
We've got several old dynasties
here at Parliament.
Troels is
a fourth generation Hoxenhaven.
His great-grandfather Eugén
was a cabinet member in 1915-
and thought he was going
to be Minister of Justice.
Zahle had promised him so,
but the rascal went back on his word.
There's old Hoxenhaven.
See the bitter look on his face?
He was cheated. Zahle made himself
both PM and Minister of Justice.
That's the closest the family's
ever been to a ministry.
And Laugesen had in fact promised
Hox the Ministry of Justice.
Precisely.
Hox sees history repeating itself.
Laugesen is going to form his cabinet
tomorrow, so unless Hox acts -
he'll never make minister.
Well?
You're the party leader.
I don't want Laugesen to be
the next PM of Denmark.
Troels, it's Birgitte. We're in.
See you at the funeral tomorrow.
Katrine?
Hi, Mom. What time is it?
- Nearly ten.
What are you doing here?
- You don't return my calls.
You've looked a mess lately.
But we haven't seen each other.
- I see you every night on TV.
You can't tell anything on TV.
I'm going to make coffee.
- I've only got instant.
Got any milk?
- Sure.
No.
Have you got boyfriend troubles?
- No.
Who died?
Oh, sweetie.
I loved him so much, Mom.
He died right next to me.
He had a bad heart, but I didn't know.
When is the funeral?
- Today.
I can't go.
He was married, Mom.
He had a wife and two young children.
They didn't know.
You have to say goodbye.
Haven't you got a girlfriend
you can bring? A really good friend?
There's nothing about it in the papers.
What's going on?
Damn it.
- Bent, you're in a church.
Okay. So he got cold feet.
When someone is taken from us
far too early -
we are overwhelmed
by the senselessness.
But even when it makes no sense,
even in our darkest hour -
love prevails.
Resurrection prevails.
That is why Paul wrote in his
first epistle to the Corinthians:
"Death...
Death is swallowed up in victory. "
"0 death, where is thy sting?"
"0 death, where is thy victory?"
The widow would like
to say a few words.
Labour demands Laugesen's exit
after racist statements!
Ole's life was one of politics.
And so, clearly, is his funeral.
He wouldn't have wanted it
any other way.
He loved the battles and the game.
When you loved Ole like I did -
you always knew
you had an awesome rival.
Parliament.
Ole loved Parliament.
And Parliament could be
a demanding mistress craving him -
both day and night
now and then.
But Ole was a fantastic father to our
children, too, and a wonderful man.
They were internal and confidential.
So find out!
I'll call you.
Have you told anyone
about the info on the PM?
Just how important
do you think you are, fuckhead?
Who the fuck cares now, you idiot?
Michael.
Katrine?
I'd like to apologize
for that last remark yesterday.
What's the matter, honey?
Sorry. I'm okay.
You bastard!
You promised to stay with me.
Ready?
Laugesen just stood down
as party leader -
- thereby suspending
the pending cabinet formation.
Hoxenhaven doesn't answer.
Who keeps buying cake?
What if they don't choose Hox?
They will. Or else we're done for.
Hi, Katrine.
Katrine, are you up-to-date on this?
We expect to present the new leader
and potential PM at six.
Right now, we're compiling portraits
of both Hoxenhaven and Marrot.
Something's wrong with my
hydrangeas at the back of the garden.
They used to be blue,
but now they've turned pink.
Maybe the soil's gone sour, or...
Bent...
Just shut up, will you?
- Okay.
15 seconds. Katrine, dab your face.
You're sweating.
Mona, got a Kleenex?
- It's not like her to sweat.
And we're on in 5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1, go.
The results are just in
from Parliament.
Labour's new leader is Bjorn Marrot.
That is the result -
- after hours of debate
and a very close vote.
What's going on, Bent?
What the hell is going on?
- Easy, easy, easy.
Take it easy.
You did all you could.
Easy now.
I don't want to talk to the press
until all the pieces are in place.
Good evening.
Bjorn, congratulations. I've always
appreciated working with you.
Let's get Denmark back on track.
Sit down.
Birgitte, Bent and Amir.
You've all voiced your support for
a cabinet headed by Labour and me.
I have yet to draw up a proposal -
but I have a unified Labour Party -
behind me
and thus a coming cabinet.
We can go ahead with most of the
items agreed upon with Laugesen.
Amir, you know which ministries
you and the Greens were promised.
Bjorn, I can't support you.
What?
- You're not cut out to be the PM.
What are you saying?
Bjorn is a gifted politician,
but no leader.
Now is not the time
to become personal.
We're talking about the PM. It doesn't
get any more personal than that.
So who's going to form the cabinet?
Birgitte, you can'tjust walk out.
We have to work together on this.
The Queen will have to appoint a new
investigator. We can't support this.
I'm sorry, Bjorn.
Good bye.
Damn, you're a good man.
Why is it I don't spend more time
at home with you?
Because you're an ambitious bitch.
How do the kids feel about all this?
I only see them when they're asleep.
They're okay.
Magnus does think
you're away too much.
Maybe it's a good thing
I didn't make PM then.
What will you make?
- Nothing.
I'm the girl who got the Moderates
15 seats to no avail.
Okay. Are you going to wallow in the
Hesselboes along with the rest of us?
The former MP and his wife
are baring all on 'Focus' tonight -
about his wife's pill abuse
and whatever.
Yup.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
You do know Ulrik is hosting
tonight's show, I hope?
I'm afraid Hanne Holm quit last week.
I heard about that.
She had a drinking problem, right?
Yes, well...
You're not alone.
You start taking pills
because you're unhappy.
But it got out of control.
Lars has been a great support to me.
How does one lose control?
I snapped that day in London.
And it's in that light one must
consider my 'wrongdoing' -
when I used my official Eurocard.
I've long paid back the money.
Unfortunately,
Laugesen got hold of the receipt.
But that backfired on Laugesen, who
has now stood down as party leader.
Yes, and rightly so.
The brutalization he stood for
does democracy no good.
Not that that acquits me.
My position as prime minister -
caused me to neglect
Lisbeth's problems -
- and for that I owe you an apology.
Still, our wrongdoings aside -
I have no doubt that we've come out
of this a stronger couple.
And on that note
we bid you goodbye.
Stay tuned for the News.
Have a nice evening.
I think they came off well.
In an eeriely controlled fashion.
Promise me it's not us in ten years.
- We can get there much faster.
Hello.
- This is Lars Hesselboe.
I promised my wife
not to talk all night.
Would you like to pop by
our office tomorrow at ten?
I gather It didn't work out
with Marrot, so I think we should talk.
Fine. See you tomorrow.
Birgitte Nyborg?
You're meeting Lars Hesselboe?
He told me to ask you
to come to the PM's office instead.
Okay. Sure.
Let me take your coat.
- Thanks.
Thanks. Hi.
Birgitte, I'm so glad
you could come at such short notice.
Sit down.
- Hello, Birgitte.
Yvonne brought her
frighteningly good cookies.
Spéculoos.
It's a Belgian recipe.
Let me get straight to the point.
The left wing is paralyzed.
You caused the card house to collapse
when you refused to support Marrot.
A very brave decision -
which has, however, left the country
in a political vacuum.
I feel a great responsibility.
Denmark deserves a strong new
cabinet after these turbulent days.
We want to form a right-wing
liberal three-party coalition cabinet.
We have a concrete offer for you.
We're offering you Health,
Education and Culture.
You yourself get
the Ministry of Business Affairs -
in close collaboration
with Yvonne's Ministry of Economy.
We'd also like you to set up a new
Ministry of International Development.
I'd be honored to bring national
politics back where they belong -
at the center of Parliament.
I have to discuss it with the Party.
- Of course.
We weren't expecting an answer now.
At 4 this afternoon?
I can't wait to get to work.
Now, let's have one of those cookies.
You did it again.
Okay, Bent. Half an hour ago
I met with the PM.
The PM?
- Well, acting PM Lars Hesselboe.
He offered us to form a cabinet
with him and get five seats.
As I see it,
this is our best chance.
We push the Freedom Party aside and
start doing some real political work.
You can't be serious, Birgitte.
Excuse me for a second.
You met at the PM's Office?
Why not at the Liberals' own office?
Hesselboe had some errands up there.
Hesselboe just happened to round up
some cookies and heavy ministers -
for a little chat with you?
He looked quite the PM, didn't he?
He pulled a power bluff on you.
Hesselboe is crap
without your support.
His is a minority party.
It's just like the man
who went to market with a cow -
and came back with a chicken.
How long have you been here?
You let yourself be duped
by a new ministry?
They constantly cut back
on international development.
Come here.
All this can be yours.
But power isn't a cute little lapdog.
You have to grab it and hold on to it,
or it'll be gone before you know it.
The only relevant question is:
Who can count to 90?
Who can count to 90, Birgitte?
I can.
Do you dare?
From now on you don't have
any friends in Parliament.
You must be able to fire anyone
without hesitation.
Can I keep you as my friend?
Sure, I'm a thing of the past anyway.
What are your options?
I'm going to call in Labour
and the Greens right away.
How does your list of ministers look?
- It looks good.
I'm not sure we can accept that.
You don't have a choice.
We want to form a coalition with you,
but with me as the PM.
Or else I'm going to go
with Hesselboe.
I'll be PM.
Sejro Minister of Finance -
Bjorn Minister of Foreign Affairs,
Amir Minister of Climate and Energy -
Hoxenhaven Minister of Justice.
50% of the cabinet seats go to women.
We want the ministries we asked for.
You get the ministries we agree upon.
This is my proposal.
I was supposed to get back
to Hesselboe some time ago -
so we haven't got all day.
Is that a yes, Bjorn?
- Yes, we're in.
Amir?
- Three ministries are not enough.
I can't go back to my party with this.
Oh, it should say four ministries.
The new Ministry of International
Development goes to you, too.
Okay.
- Have we got a deal?
Hesselboe says you had
an appointment seven minutes ago.
Ask him to come down in 15 minutes,
and then we'll go next door.
No thanks.
Hesselboe is here.
- Thanks.
Birgitte. I rather prefer my ministers
to keep their appointments.
I apologize.
- No matter. This is a great day.
We've gone over your proposal,
and I'm afraid I have to let you down.
We're going to support another PM.
Who, if I may ask?
- Me.
Okay.
PREGNANCY TEST
Katrine Fonsmark,
please go to the studio.
I don't know where the hell she is.
Katrine, you can't come this late.
We get nervous.
- Sorry.
We're on in 5 seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1, go.
Today, Denmark got
its first female Prime Minister.
Birgitte Nyborg just presented
Denmark's new cabinet -
- a coalition between the Greens,
Labour and the Moderates.
The cabinet is younger than ever.
50/% of the seats are held by women.
Here we are. Boy, have I been
looking forward to saying:
Denmark has got a new government.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst