All this can be yours.
But power isn't a cute little lapdog.
You have to grab it and hold on to it.
The only relevant question is:
Are you game?
Clear your desk.
You got fired?
- No, I quit.
Ole! Come on, damn you!
It's not funny.
I loved him so much.
He had a bad heart.
When is the funeral?
- Today.
He was married. He had a wife
and two children. They didn't know.
We're going
to support a different PM. Me.
3, 2, 1, go.
Today, Denmark got
its first female prime minister.
Here we are.
Denmark has got a new government.
"Democracy is the worst way to run
a country - except for all the others. "
It took Nyborg's cabinet just two
months to negotiate the budget bill.
If the budget is passed in two days,
the PM will have passed her exam.
Hanne Holm, political observer.
What's this all about?
The budget is
what makes Denmark tick.
If the budget bill falls,
so does the cabinet.
How did you carry through
the budget negotiations so fast?
Sometimes things just go your way.
What are you going to change?
- I'm announcing it in 30 minutes.
Briefing with the Ministers for Finance,
Foreign Affairs and Climate in five.
Press conference at 10. And at 11...
The meeting with Danish Industry.
- That's tomorrow.
At 11 you're meeting with
the Director of the National Gallery.
She's going to help you
choose paintings for your office.
The PM always gets to choose.
I want something more modern.
- At 12...
I need to concentrate
on the press conference now, Sanne.
Did she just curtsey?
- We'll get rid of her.
Nobody else wants her, you see.
- So the PM gets her.
We need your New Year's speech
in four days.
And you need a new media adviser.
- I don't need a spin doctor.
Guess who's the new
editor-in-chief of the Express.
Laugesen.
And he wants your head on a platter.
I didn't fire him.
His party did.
But who made PM instead of him?
He hates you, Birgitte.
Who's it from?
Hanne Holm is with the Express now.
They take all the undesirables.
Good morning.
I'm going to tell you
about the budget bill today.
The passing of this budget bill marks
a change of system in Denmark.
Any questions?
Hanne Holm.
Has the PM secured
a broad majority?
Unfortunately, the bill will be passed
with the narrowest majority possible.
But how? Two Labour members have
just refused to vote for the bill.
What do you mean?
Parly Petersen and Vagn Fousing
won't vote for it.
Their press release looks genuine.
It looks like you just lost
your majority, Birgitte Nyborg.
GOVERNMENT
Episode 3- The Art of the Possible
I've never been so humiliated
in my life!
What's going on?
- I don't know.
Get them in line.
I want them to vote for it tomorrow.
Okay.
- My office in an hour.
Why are you going against party line?
It's just great that the PM
and her elitist friends -
want to help the poor in Africa.
But what about the poor in Denmark?
- Why this protest now?
- My conscience rules my vote.
Convene the Finance Council.
- We're meeting in an hour.
The press is all over us.
- They'll have to wait.
Who's going to deal with them?
- I'll hire a media adviser, okay?
Get the Party Secretary to help us.
Postpone the rest of my meetings.
Are you withdrawing the bill?
- No. We're sticking to the plan.
There's something fishy going on.
Why didn't they raise
their objections earlier?
It's an ambush.
- What are your options?
Is this a test? 1. Marrot gets
them in line. The bill is passed.
2. They demand concessions,
we comply.
3. We withdraw the bill
and lose all credibility.
Yup. And we're not the first ones
to reach that conclusion.
Laugesen just commented
on the situation on Express TV.
The Director of the National Gallery.
- I told you to cancel my meetings.
Tell her to pick something modern.
Something modern, Sanne.
I want a new secretary.
The PM is not up to thejob.
That's the plain and simple of it.
She masters political correctness,
but is devoid of political flair.
This isn't a question of gender.
She's simply incompetent.
Express asks you:
Is Birgitte Nyborg the right PM?
You need a media adviser. Now.
Hi, beautiful.
We're co-workers now.
I'm your new political analyst,
because I know Birgitte Nyborg.
Congratulations. Can I just...
- Jesus, don't go overboard.
You're still mad at me because
of what happened at the funeral.
I forgive you, Kasper.
- Thanks.
You've been to hospital?
- Don't go through my stuff!
It stuck out.
It was just a routine screening
for cervical cancer, okay?
Katrine, what's up?
Nothing.
I have to get to make-up.
Why are you pushing yourself
when you feel like shit?
Look, I know you.
- Maybe you don't anymore.
3 YEARS EARLIER
Hey, save some for me.
- Nope.
Save some for me!
Hey! Ego.
- Ego?
I bet you haven't told
your parents about me.
Sure I've told Papa about you.
Papa? Oh, sweet prince,
how is Papa?
Why don't you call him 'dad'?
- He lives in France.
Okay, then.
So he lives there with Maman?
Mama. Oui.
Or Sandrine, as she's called.
How come you call her 'mom',
when she isn't your mom?
My real mom's dead.
So Mama is a housewife, and Papa
gets rich from making helicopters.
For the French army.
I don't want to talk about them.
When can I meet them?
- Soon.
You've been saying that
for six months.
You met my family.
- They live only a few hours away.
Mine lives in the South of France.
- We were supposed to meet at Easter.
Then during the summer.
And then... when?
Then during the fall... and winter.
I mean it. When can I meet them?
- I really mean it, too.
Come on, give me a kiss.
- No. When can I meet them?
Just a tiny kiss.
- Okay.
Didn't you want a kiss?
- I didn't say where.
I hear you want Tore Gudme from
Save the Children as your spin doctor?
Yes, he's in line with our policies.
Have you seen his CV? He's the
youngest professor of rhetorics ever.
Look, who would you rather
send into the ring?
Someone who can kick ass
or a professor of rhetorics?
Bjørn Marrot is here.
- Did you talk to Parly and Vagn?
I gave them an ultimatum.
But they're not bowing down.
They can't stay in your party, then.
They already resigned.
- They've gone independent?
NEWS EXTRA
The cabinet is losing its majority,
and the budget drama is escalating.
After Parly Petersen and Vagn Fousing
got a bawling out from their leader -
they have resigned from the Labour
Party and are now independent.
Stick to the script.
"Bawling out!"
She looks like shit.
- Get Tanja to dab her face.
When am I back on?
- In 28 seconds.
What's up?
What the hell are you doing?
You're on in 20.
Where is she?
Roll headlines
if she doesn't make it.
Is there anything I can do?
- No, I'm fine.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go.
The budget bill is not
the only political drama.
Former PM Lars Hesselboe
may still be subject to an inquiry -
- into his use of public funds
during his time in office.
Jesus! Well done.
Well, ask the AB Group
to come over tomorrow. See you.
There's a beautiful man
waiting outside. Tore Gudme.
Send him in, please.
Go ahead.
- Thanks.
Hello, Tore. Thank you
for coming on such short notice.
I am aware of the urgency.
- Sit down.
I know you hold
a very important position -
but I'd still like to ask you...
if you'd...
I get your drift.
This job is confidential, and you want
a simple yes or no from me.
If I answer yes,
I'll drop everything and start at once.
What do you need?
- A media adviser.
Spin doctor.
- Yes, but not a "prince of darkness".
I won't let my spin doctor
control my policies.
My spin doctor controls the press.
I could sell myself for hours,
but you don't have time for that.
You obviously
know my qualifications.
I believe in you as a person
and in your political message.
Do you regard that as a prerequisite
to being a good spin doctor?
I guess that depends
on how professional you are.
I have no desire
to be that professional.
I have a question.
I've read your CV.
Impressive. The youngest Danish
associate professor of rhetorics ever.
Educated at Harvard and Princeton.
You've always played
on the winning team.
How are you going
to deal with adversity?
Analysis, consequence, execution.
I know it's short notice,
and you need to think it over.
I have. My answer is yes.
Can you start next week?
You need me tomorrow at 8.
Make that 7:30.
- Deal.
Thanks.
Hi, honey.
There goes my new spin doctor.
You hired him for his looks, or...?
- Hi.
Great to see you.
Are you out for stroll?
Oh, my God, Christmas presents!
That's going to be tough.
Hi, Laura and Magnus. Would you
like to see the Hall of Mirrors?
The budget bill's pure chaos.
- Just like back home.
Your bodyguards invaded the garage.
Our bikes now go in the greenhouse.
The two independents haven't
confirmed the meeting.
Give me an hour. One hour.
- One hour!
That's just great, baby.
Magnus and I are off
on a secret errand.
Well, Laura and I are off
on a top secret errand, too.
See you.
Think we conned them?
That way?
- I made a list.
I knew you wouldn't be prepared.
- You're a sweetheart.
Magnus' list is huge.
He's getting expensive habits.
I'm sure they can wait.
- Go ahead, Mom.
Sejrø speaking.
The independents are waiting for us.
I'm on my way.
I have to go.
- I thought you said an hour.
Yes, and I'm really sorry.
Just go, Mom.
See you.
- Isn't Mom coming?
No, Mom's got a budget bill
to salvage.
Okay, let's go Christmas shopping.
Thank you.
- They're waiting.
What is your offer?
- A couple of million for pensioners.
I'm not going to cut back on
development aid or other key issues.
A couple of independents aren't going
to make me change my policies.
We appreciate your concern
for the pensioners -
so we've found
another DKK 210m for them.
You've done your utmost
to humor us, obviously.
Yes.
But I have another issue
of great concern to me.
And politics is all about
seizing the day.
What are we talking about?
A motorway to Ringkøbing.
Thank you for coming.
We'll be in touch.
They're insane.
But I'll see what I can do.
Maybe we don't need them.
That was Hesselboe.
The Liberals and
the New Conservatives want to meet.
When?
- Now. You, me, Hesselboe, Yvonne.
Forget development aid. They want
funds for the police and the military.
I'm not going to revise
the budget bill now.
If Hesselboe patronizes me,
I'm out of there.
Let me do the talking.
- Someone has to wake her up.
What an unexpected call.
- We don't support your policies.
But I don't want you to bring about
a crisis of Italian dimensions, either.
You lost your majority.
As long as I don't have a majority
against me, that doesn't matter.
You could rely on the independents.
- And base your budget on traitors.
They have neither morals nor brains.
You want to save the cabinet?
- If you're willing to negotiate.
We can't live with certain elements of
your politically correct little budget.
I call it social responsibility.
Let's not get emotional.
I've drawn up a proposal.
We want the first press conference.
- Give Birgitte time to look it over.
Let me guess.
Tax breaks, more police and military,
less green taxes -
and clamp-downs
on juvenile offenders.
Yes, we demand concessions.
Denmark has a new government.
We are not pursuing
a right-wing policy.
A government pursues the policy
necessary to its survival.
Think it over.
Lars, the answer is no.
I won't go down in history as the PM
who merely sat in for the Liberals.
The alternative might be
not to go down in history at all.
Negotiation was an option.
- These were ultimate demands.
Hesselboe wanted to come off as
the great saviour of the budget bill.
Our only options are Parly and Vagn.
Go home. I'll talk to Parly. I won't
give them more than necessary.
Am I a complete idiot?
Maybe.
But you're the bravest idiot I know.
Are you still PM?
Two days ago I had a budget bill.
Now, we're negotiating with two crazy
independents about a motorway.
Will it secure your majority?
- Yes.
Then give them their motorway.
- To secure the peace?
The kids want
to spend Christmas with you.
Even if it'll cost me
a motorway to the sticks?
Are they mad at me
for not tucking them in?
You promised Magnus a bedtime story.
He wouldn't let me read him one.
He's asleep,
and he'll get over it.
Would the PM like to help me
wrap the presents?
I managed to distract Magnus enough
to keep Santa alive for another year.
I promise to give them
a great Christmas.
And I'll do all the hard work.
- No, you won't.
Yes, you will.
We're still us, aren't we?
Good morning.
- The Minister for Finance is waiting.
The National Gallery wants
to know what style...
The Director decides, okay?
Good morning.
You slept here?
I haven't slept. The motorway issue
won't be solved before the vote.
Ask the President of the Parliament
to postpone the vote.
The Bulldog? She hates me.
- The Bulldog is your only option.
She won't postpone the vote.
We stand to get a vote of censure.
- This isn't Italy.
Parliament is split. Securing the
majority is all anyone thinks about.
So get me the majority.
- We can't agree on the motorway.
The Greens are against, because
it runs through a wading bird habitat.
I bet Amir puts his own survival
as minister before the birds'.
Solidarity is against, too.
We don't have a majority.
That motorway was dropped
a while back.
Why is Parly re-opening the issue?
- His constituency is up there.
Let's leak to the press that Parly
doesn't care about the pensioners.
All he wants is a motorway.
- Leaking confidential talks is unfair.
I bet Parly withdraws his demand.
- We're about to be outvoted.
I think we're past fair play.
Do it.
- Okay.
Let's see how far along you are.
Please unbutton your pants
and pull up your top.
Let's see if we can get an image.
Let's see if we can see anything.
Yes, there's your baby.
What's that flashing?
- The little heart.
I can print out
a picture for the father.
Do you want that?
- Please.
He really wanted to come today.
- He can come with you next time.
Our source tells us
you have new demands.
Now you want a motorway
to Ringkøbing.
Yesterday you wanted
to help pensioners.
Voters are getting confused.
Not once they see how this motorway
benefits pensioners in particular.
Please elaborate.
Do you know how long it takes
to get an ambulance in that region?
Three times as long as here.
- Oh, come on!
One could get the idea you'rejust
trying to please your constituents.
Tell that to 5-year-old Anna
and her family.
Her granddad had a stroke
and needed an ambulance.
The old main road was blocked by
traffic, so he died in the ambulance.
Had there been a motorway, he'd
have spent Christmas with Anna.
The PM wants to treat people from
developing countries as our equals.
Why is a Danish granddad worth less
than a person from Somalia, then?
I'll pass that question on to the PM.
Tame journalism!
Parly's arguments don't hold up.
Parly just won popular opinion
because Anna misses her granddad.
HESSELBOE INQUIRY PENDING
How will we survive the vote?
- Blackmail.
I see you kept the paintings.
- They're about to be changed.
Your budget bill
is causing you trouble.
I need a week.
- A vote of censure could topple you.
I'm the only realistic
cabinet leader at the moment.
And you don't think
I could make PM again?
Yes, and I'm offering you
just that chance.
You have an inquiry looming.
They won't find anything.
- I'm sure they won't.
But right now
you're a potential embezzler.
That bars you from becoming PM.
- What do you want?
Without the Moderates there won't be
a majority in favor of an inquiry.
I'll vote against the inquiry, if you
vote for a postponement of my bill.
Give me a week's respite.
Neither I nor the New Conservatives
will vote for your budget.
Can you speak
for the entire opposition?
Yvonne's been at my beck and call
the past six years. That won't change.
I'm asking for a week, that's all.
Yes?
- You don't answer your phone.
Maybe I want to be alone.
- I just want to see if you're okay.
Why do you want to be alone?
- I'm working.
I'm going back home for Christmas.
Is that what you want?
- You're going to France?
No, Mama and Papa are
in French Polynesia. Bora Bora.
It's their new thing.
- Don't they ever miss Denmark?
What's to miss in Denmark?
- You.
Mama and Papa aren't
the sentimental kind.
I'm going to eat Christmas dinner
at the St. Petri Hotel. Want to come?
I've got my family, Kasper.
Remember?
They live in the sticks
where it smells of Ajax and dung.
But that's okay.
You can come, if you're alone.
I'm not alone. I was joking.
I'm going to my uncle's in Skodsborg.
He's invited at least 25 people.
It'll be great.
I'm pregnant.
Excuse me?
No shit? Who's the father?
- Ole.
But you can't be.
- We didn't take any precautions.
It's none of my business anyway.
I guess you're going to get rid of it.
No.
- You can't have a child now.
Why not?
You can't handle a child right now.
You just made anchor on TV1.
Listen to yourself. We're talking
about a child, the fruit of our love!
You can have lots of children later.
- Yes, but not with him!
Katrine!
3 YEARS EARLIER
Sorry I'm late.
What's so important?
Who are you? Who are you?
Your dad's name is Peter Juul.
There's no Peter Juul
working for Eurocopter.
Your mom isn't buried in Slagelse.
- Talk about investigative journalism!
You lied to me!
- I didn't!
I just left out some of the details.
- Then fill me in.
My dad took his new wife's name.
He works for the French army who are
not about to divulge any information.
Even I don't know what the man does.
My mom... is buried
in an unmarked grave.
My mom committed suicide
when I was three.
I'm sorry, baby.
Let's go.
Are you coming?
The cabinet avoided
being outvoted today -
when the Liberals voted
for postponing the budget bill.
Parliament will convenejust after
Christmas. Kasper Juul, welcome.
You used to work for Birgitte Nyborg
as her spin doctor. What's going on?
The PM is under heavy fire.
Parliament is split, but Birgitte just
secured herself six more days.
How did Nyborg
win over the Liberals?
I think we're looking at a horse-trade.
Nyborg declared on the news at 12
she saw no reason -
for an inquiry to be held
into Hesselboe's doings.
She gets six more days to negotiate,
and he's off the hook.
In other words: Quid pro quo.
Hey, I've been Christmas shopping
for 11 minutes.
My bodyguards chose hubby's gift.
- Did you see this?
GIVE DENMARK A NEW PM
Did you see Tore's brilliant reply
to Laugesen in the paper?
Laugesen is turning
the people against you.
Your spin doctor fights back
with his pen. He can't protect you!
Then my results will have to protect
me. What do you want me to do?
I work around the clock.
We've lost our majority.
You're fishing for sympathy?
You're the PM, aren't you?
Are you going to resign?
- No way!
I'll be damned if I'll resign
before we've even gotten started.
Let's find the money for that motorway
and get to work.
I believe in this, Bent.
- Put that in your New Year's speech.
Hello.
- Sorry.
Isn't Christmas the time
to apologize and all that crap?
That's not like you.
- It is Christmas Eve.
Are you at your uncle's?
- Are you partying with the Smurfs?
My brother went a little overboard
with the Christmas decorations.
The moron. He says he'll throw me
a spinster party if I don't marry soon.
You'd better get a move on then.
- Yeah.
Sure you're doing the right thing?
- Yes.
They're calling me now.
Coming!
Dinner's served. Take care.
- Merry Christmas.
Hi, Mom.
They didn't see me.
Why so stand-offish,
Phillip Christensen?
I saw your old spin guy, Kasper,
on TV the other day.
He was on to your deal
with Hesselboe.
Why didn't you make him your
new adviser instead of Gudme?
I don't want to work with Kasper.
He has no morals.
Since when
did a spin doctor need that?
He was a great campaign organizer.
In my world you choose the best one.
In my world you choose the right one.
And I choose you.
You could thank me for your present.
That pen cost a bundle.
Yeah, but you gave me one
just like it three years ago.
Oh, how mortifying.
How lousy of me.
Oh, come here, babe.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Leave it. It's mine.
- It's your new friend, Tore Gudme.
Good morning, Tore.
- Did you see the Express?
Laugesen claims you and I are
having an affair. It's grotesque.
It's a vile mixture
of gossip and hate campaign.
But efficient. My neighbor asks
when I'm calling an election.
My mom thinks I'm getting a divorce.
Laugesen wants to meet us
in a live TV1 debate.
I'm game.
- No.
You're the PM.
He's an editor-in-chief.
You're not on the same level.
- I'll meet him.
The opposition will kill us for letting
a spin doctor take a political debate.
I'm not. I'm just going to respond
to his dirty attack on me.
If you cross that line,
all hell will break loose.
Laugesen is trying
to undermine Birgitte's credibility.
We have to make sure he fails.
That's the bottom line of it.
It's time to act.
- I agree.
I'll call TV1 right away.
Merry Christmas.
Laugesen is lethal.
Does Tore have any TV experience?
The guy is a professor of rhetorics.
I'll be there at six.
Check with Pia.
Brief me when I get there.
You are coming to Granddad's lunch
tomorrow, aren't you?
I have to do an important interview
tonight. My plane leaves in two hours.
You're letting Granddad down.
- I know.
Watch TV tonight at 20:30,
and you'll understand.
Weren't you sick last week?
- Yes, but it's nothing serious.
People die from stress.
- It's not stress.
You work all the time.
- It's not stress, Mom.
You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
You're pregnant.
My dear girl. How...
Almost 11 weeks.
- Why didn't you say?
Who's...
- Ole.
So the child hasn't got a father?
Ole's dead, Katrine.
You don't understand.
- What's to understand?
We're going to have a baby.
- No, you are. And you're alone.
Katrine, haven't you said
goodbye to him yet?
Why are you so hard on yourself?
- You want me to get rid of it.
I thought you believed in God.
- This has nothing to do with God.
You need to look after yourself.
- I have to go now.
Are you up to it? I can ask Ulrik...
- No way! I'm ready.
Have Tanja put some color
on your face. You're pale as a ghost.
And smile, Katrine. We're not
running a funeral home here.
What?
- You didn't tell him?
You want a baby,
but no one can know about it.
Is it because it's Ole's?
- Shut up!
Laugesen puts a picture of you
and the PM on the front page -
- with a headline
implying a flirt.
It's grotesque and unfounded.
It just goes to show -
- how low the Express is willing
to go to attack the PM.
The Express is a mishmash
of gossipmonger and people's court.
But we all know
what segment they cater to.
Watch your step!
- And what segment is that?
All the uninspired losers out there.
Oh, people who don't read
four foreign papers each day?
The Express appeals
to the lowest common denominator -
- by glorifying Parly Petersen
for criticizing development aid.
No politics!
- He has a right to speak his mind.
And doesn't the Express have
the right to criticize your PM?
I'd consider it a blessing if your
freedom of speech were curtailed.
No, no, no!
Are you, the PM's adviser, in favor
of curtailing freedom of speech?
Laugesen is using the paper
to promote his own political career.
His board ought to look into that.
The PM will look into the matter.
- Oh, shut up, Tore!
Are you threatening to have anyone
speaking out against the PM fired?
I'm afraid our time is up.
A shame, because I'd love to hear
about all these impending dismissals.
OLE DAHL
DEARLY MISSED
I know who you are.
You shouldn't be here.
There's something you should know.
- I don't want to know a thing!
Understand? He's my husband.
I want you to leave.
- I'm sorry.
Get the hell out of here!
2 YEARS EARLIER
Papa just got a call from Sydney
about a military conference -
the week we were supposed
to go and visit them.
Let's make it a winter visit instead.
- This isn't working.
You and I. It isn't working.
- What do you mean?
Kasper, I think you're wonderful,
but I don't believe anything you say.
I don't know what's fact
and what's fiction.
Things are never as you say.
Maybe you need to keep secrets.
- I don't need anything.
Okay, then. I just don't believe you.
And I don't believe in us, either.
I swear to you.
This is all a misunderstanding.
I don't think so.
I think this is what we are.
I haven't got any secrets.
It doesn't matter anymore,
because it's taken root in me now.
I think we love each other.
- I think so, too.
Good news. I got the six billion
for the motorway.
I've drawn up the terms.
- Impressive, Bent.
The press dubs Gudme an amateur.
- I fired him this morning.
That was a first for him.
- What are you going to do?
We're going to sell the motorway
to the independents -
and get that budget bill
passed tomorrow.
Who's going to handle the press?
Try calling a pro this time.
I have a meeting with the PM.
- I have to register you.
It's okay.
This way.
I'm impressed you found
the six billion for that motorway.
The cabinet parties and Solidarity
have come to terms.
The independents are on their way,
and then we'll close the deal.
Wrong.
- He's going to get his motorway.
Parly doesn't want a motorway.
He wants your resignation.
Parly is being used by someone
who's got it in for Birgitte.
Michael Laugesen?
- How much do we know about Parly?
Wasn't he nailed for embezzling
with his EU salaries?
Who saved him?
- Laugesen.
He made Parly go against party line?
- Sure.
When Laugesen resigned, he could
no longer help Parly. Parly's isolated.
He's not assigned any tasks.
He's finished in Danish politics.
So why not do a friend a favor
and get your 15 minutes of fame?
He's going to topple the cabinet
to return a favor?
I may be way out there,
but I think you should call him.
Parly speaking.
- This is Birgitte Nyborg.
Our meeting won't take long, because
you're going to get your motorway.
Let's not get our signals crossed.
We still have a large bridge to gap -
if I'm to vote for your bill.
I want a new hospital in Skjern.
I'll have to discuss that with
my cabinet. I'll get back to you.
The nerve of the guy!
And we can't do a thing.
Yes, we can.
- What?
We can do what we've stood for
the past 50 years.
Negotiate across the political center.
Let's enlist the New Conservatives.
We already tried to talk to them.
- We talked to them and the Liberals.
Yes, they're in cahoots.
- Are they?
Don't you see?
It would be a triumph for the cabinet.
The New Conservatives hate...
It would be a historic break
with bloc politics.
Be quiet.
- Meet her at Marienborg.
The old snob will love that.
- Hi, Yvonne. It's Nyborg.
Thank you for coming.
- I presume it's urgent.
Tomorrow I'm going
to postpone the budget bill -
and pass a temporary
appropriation act.
I want a broad conciliation across the
center with the New Conservatives.
Sit down.
Why should we refrain
from toppling you?
An new election would lead to chaos.
Dead against your party's policies.
Law and order.
God, King and country.
Let's break with political warring.
- There's a lot we don't agree on.
There's even more we agree on.
Tea?
I should have asked you to bring
some of your scrumptious cookies.
My support comes at a price.
- How much?
DKK 400m more to the police.
- Deal.
Another 600 million to the military.
As long as it's for equipment
and education, fine.
The industry doesn't like
the pollution tax.
We'll just have to help them
develop green technologies.
You haven't got the money.
Less that DKK 9b won't hack it.
Four billion.
- Eight.
Five.
- Seven.
Six billion. And I'm not
budging on development aid.
This is about principles,
not money.
Where will you get six billion?
From a motorway
we're not going to build after all.
Have we got a deal?
- Let me talk to Hesselboe first.
We have, after all, been
coalition partners for six years.
Well, he was right, then.
Hesselboe told me the other day
you were at his beck and call.
Oh, he did, did he?
Yesterday, the PM landed the budget
with the New Conservatives' vote.
Political observer Hanne Holm calls
it a decisive victory for Nyborg.
Not only did Nyborg get
her budget bill passed.
She managed to split the opposition
through solid political craftsmanship.
Thank you.
Are you staying on at Marienborg
after your New Year's speech?
Shit! The New Year's speech.
- I've drawn one up.
Is it good?
You look very sharp.
- Thanks.
Your choice of artwork
is interesting.
Well, it's modern.
Sanne, get me the Director
of the National Gallery at once.
Despite the crisis, Denmark is one of
the ten richest countries in the world.
Yet many criticize our wish
to double development aid -
instead of taking better care
of ourselves.
But I believe we take better care of
ourselves by taking care of others.
Let me explain.
For every 1,000 children
born in Denmark, 5 die.
In Afghanistan, over 200 die.
This inequity leads to despair,
it breeds war and terror.
So much for the
political security arguments.
The most important argument is that
200 dead children are 200 too many.
Everyone should be allowed
to see their children grow up.
I believe the meaning of life is
to pass it on.
Yes. Thank you.
Well done! Considering you're hung
over from New Year's Eve last night.
I may just vote for you next time.
- I want to show you something.
You wrote that speech? I thought
you were a cold-hearted bastard.
I am. But your wife pays me a bundle
to write that sentimental drivel.
Champagne!
- Great. Want a sip, sweetie?
I sent you a personal message
in the PM's New Year's speech.
An homage to life and babies...
I just had an abortion.
- I'm sorry.
How come we're never in sync?
- I have to go now. Happy New Year.
Kasper...
Here you are.
- Thanks.
You're good.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst