Perhaps it was naive of me to think I
wouldn't lie during my first 100 days.
What's up?
- I can't tell you.
Who was that on the phone?
This is going to be hard.
- Let's just keep it personal then.
Maybe you need to talk about
the child you just lost.
We haven't had sex in three weeks.
We could have regular days.
Tuesdays and Saturdays?
Scheduled sex with the PM?
"All armed prophets
have been victorious. "
"All unarmed have been destroyed. "
- Machiavelli
Jesus Christ.
Let me see if I've got this right.
You want quotas ensuring 50% women
on the boards of Danish companies.
It's old news, Bent.
- It just reads a little drastic.
It'll say 45% in the bill.
A mere technicality.
A board of 7 can't have 50% women.
- I don't get it.
It's simple math. 45% enables boards
to have an uneven composition.
Will you use force?
- We hope it won't be necessary.
It might be.
- I agree.
This has been part of our
cabinet policy from the very start.
I thought we might moderate it.
- We're introducing it tomorrow.
Surely this falls under my Ministry
for Social Affairs and Gender Equality.
I see it as
a political economy initiative.
Not simply a gender equality issue.
- You call gender equality simple?
This was just to brief you.
The final bill may look different.
Let's call it a night.
- Why wasn't I informed?
Ask Bent.
Don't oppose the bill
the night before the press conference.
Your Permanent Secretary
wasn't thrilled.
Permanent secretaries
are opposed to change.
So I cannot have other gods than you?
No thanks.
What's up with you and Henriette
Klitgaard? You keep looking at her.
How do you mean?
You don't see her as minister.
- I see her as a hot minister.
Let's go through
the press release again.
It's 10:30.
Get a life, okay?
Good night, Sanne.
- Good night. Bye.
GOVERNMENT
Episode 5- Men Who Love Women
Dad, where's my note book?
- I have no idea.
Well?
It screams state regulation.
- It is state regulation.
You're in for a beating.
What will they attack?
- You, for proposing it.
It's Henriette Klitgaard's bill.
- She's a woman, too, and what, 38?
She's got a PhD in market economy
and an MBA from Princeton.
How do you know?
- I worked with her at Simtech.
She was an intern.
- It's Henriette's show today.
They're going to rage
about your feminist agenda.
When women become executives,
they must apologize for being women.
They must be overly skilled
and promise never to favor women.
Men don't force you
to beg for their approval.
I've never asked for a man's approval.
How do I look?
Fine. Fine from the back, too.
- Thanks.
We expect to have the bill passed
before the summer break.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Any questions?
Will this be compulsory for boards
in the public sector, too?
The Danish laws apply to everyone.
To the composition of the cabinet
and Parliament, too?
My party meets the quota.
Parliament is composed by the voters.
I'm not messing with the Constitution.
You're both highly educated women
leaders. Isn't this bill redundant?
May I?
Only 1.5% of the top executive
positions are held by women.
The people elected our PM.
They must be far more progressive
than the corporate world.
And sit down.
Pedal hard.
I said: Sit down.
Excuse me. I'm Benjamin,
the new instructor.
If you want to do your own thing,
please sit at the back.
Hey, sure.
And remember to bring some water.
It's unhealthy not to drink anything.
Is that your breakfast?
- Yes.
I can help you with your diet.
- Gee, thanks.
I don't eat croissants to stay healthy,
but to clog up my veins.
Well, get him to call back, dammit.
Get Klitgaard in for an interview.
- The Clit.
That's what they call her.
We call her
the Minister for Economic Affairs.
She's a former model.
Four degrees from foreign universities.
The mother of four, and not yet 40.
- I bet she can't cook.
She's the only minister
not voted into Parliament.
The PM headhunted her from
a top position in the corporate sector.
We'll put her to the test tonight.
At 6 eller 8:30?
I'll take her in the 6 o'clock news.
- What makes the best TV?
What looks best? In terms
of journalism. You've got something...
It's a feminist bill. Do we pair her
with a woman and go girl power?
Or should I take her in the 8:30?
- She looks great. You've got a point.
Girl power? You want to postpone
the story, so a man can interview her?
It's a story about favoring women.
Pairing her with you is overkill.
Since when did gender
interfere with our reporting?
Hey, this case is all about gender.
- It's all about equality.
You won't let Katrine take it
because she's a woman. Come on!
It's grotesque.
- I'll gladly take her.
What'll it be then?
Ulrik, 8:30.
- No!
We expect to pass the bill
before the summer break.
Aren't quotas more for flounder?
- He's good!
Quotas are useful in areas
that don't self-regulate.
You have quotas for students,
and not all students are flounders.
Take that, Ulrik.
- So, women need a bill to get ahead?
We need to break down the closed
systems of the corporate world -
so highly educated women don't
have to wait for things to change.
We legislate on maternity
and paternity leave.
The Royals embrace gender equality.
It's nothing to be scared of, Ulrik.
Henriette...
- She has him eating out of her hand.
Well, that girl is sizzling!
The carrot is tax benefits
for the companies -
that quickly let women
onto their boards.
The stick is harsher taxation
of the companies that won't.
We may even take away their right
to operate in Denmark.
Hopefully the carrot will be enough.
- Give her hell!
Thank you.
Now, from quotas and bills
to speeches and battle songs.
Today is Women's Day -
and our reporter has hit
the streets... wearing a bra.
Hey. Long day.
- Yes.
Katrine... I want to apologize
for this morning.
I didn't mean to criticize.
You can eat whatever you want.
Yes, and now I'd like to go home,
if that's okay with you.
It's that tough to be famous?
- What?
That you won't even chat
with a mere fitness instructor?
I apologize,
and you treat me like a stalker.
But I'm not.
I didn't even recognize you
this morning. I don't really watch TV.
And I like that other news anchor
better... Ulrik Mørk.
Why do you like Ulrik better?
- He gives people a chance.
Hey, Benjamin...
What are you eating?
- Coco Pops.
I was no match
for his pester power yesterday.
Do you want the headlines?
- Hit me.
"Violent protests in Burma. "
"The National Bank
raises interest rates. "
And...
Okay.
Who's that?
- The Minister for Economic Affairs.
Why isn't she wearing any clothes?
Now it begins.
ONE FOR THE BOARD, BOYS?
Hi. Good morning.
I got you the breakfast complet.
- Thanks.
No croissant for me.
- Are you ill?
No. I'm just trying
to eat wholesome food.
I really just want some water.
- Water?
Things are that bad
in the TV business?
The staff meetings are a stag party.
- At my job it's a hen party.
Economy Henriette is hot. She gives
a girl an instant inferiority complex.
Pernille Madsen feels the same way.
Well, it ought to fall under
her Ministry for Gender Equality.
My lips are sealed.
She's mad as hell.
But that's confidential, okay?
Now tell me about yourself.
- The facts, or what you want to hear?
What do I want to hear?
- That I'm celibate.
And that I miss an old friend.
And that I don't mean Ole.
I liked Ole.
But you like the thought
of being hard to get over, too.
Bull.
I was a model, 21,
and I needed the money.
Is there more than that?
- I was never Miss Wet T-Shirt.
I only worked for the big agencies,
and I did a lot of lingeri shoots.
Let's meet and work out a press
strategy about your modeling past.
Rune can handle it.
The media is on this, so coordinate
all announcements with us.
"Let's meet and work out a press
strategy about your modeling past. "
"I'd so like to help you
with your press strategy. "
Birgitte, I'm not flirting.
- You're flirting. You are so flirting.
Sanne, am I flirting?
- Not with me.
Pernille Madsen wants to meet
with you. She's been very persistent.
I'll call her.
Pernille Madsen has got a point.
She's the Minister for Gender Equality,
and we're keeping her out of it.
Fire her.
I can't stand Pernille Madsen.
Why not?
- She's a stale old bra-burner.
She's the essence of redstockings,
hairy armpits and cold meatloaf.
I just can't stand her.
- Talk to your shrink about that, okay?
Those women are the first up against
the wall, when the revolution comes.
You asked, I answered.
Boy, you're a flirt.
I'm glad you had time for a chat.
Labour doesn't understand why you
chose Henriette to pitch your bill.
The party leaders can come to me.
- We are. I'm deputy leader.
Why hand a gender equality issue
to the Ministry for Economic Affairs?
I want to shift the debate focus.
My choice of ministry was tactical.
She has the corporate world's respect,
and that makes us less vulnerable.
You think so?
She's a former lingeri model.
They'd never have dug out
pictures like that of me.
Why don't you keep your own
promise about gender equality?
The Coordinating Committee has
only two women members.
You? The Minister for Social Affairs
has never been on the C Committee.
I've got lots of clout in Labour.
We'd hate to create unrest
in the government.
You owe me
for favoring Henriette with this bill.
What do you want?
- Access to all related meetings.
And I want to be first in line for the
committee at the next cabinet rotation.
Nice chatting with you.
We've been approached
by Crohne Industries.
He wants to meet with you.
How about at 6 this afternoon?
It's hard to set up a meeting
with the PM, isn't it?
And yet you offer him a meeting
the day he calls.
We always meet with Crohne.
- We?
This office.
I know Hesselboe met with him.
- They were on good terms.
The press said Crohne dictated
the government's corporate tax policy.
Crohne is one of the most
powerful people in Denmark.
Is 6 p. m. Okay?
- No, I'm eating dinner at home.
I can be here at 8.
- Good.
How did you do on the test?
- Fine. I got an A.
Great! Congratulations.
- I got an A on the last one, too.
Can I play my computer game?
- No, this is family time.
Got any homework?
Run along, then.
Can I practice the piano?
I promise to wear headphones.
Who the hell invented the concept
of quality time? Sick bastard.
You've been away a lot. Tonight
they'll be all over you on the couch.
I've got a meeting.
- Oh.
Guess who.
- Who?
Joachim Crohne.
Okay. He's used to influencing
our country's legislation.
My Permanent Secretary insisted.
- Of course.
He's a member of the same
corporate network as Crohne's CEO.
Corporate Group No. 3.
- Oh, I see.
Is that a bad thing for democracy?
Ministers and civil servants shouldn't
get intimate with the corporate world.
Do we have to get a divorce, then?
- I'm not a CEO. I just teach.
It provokes me to see you
doll yourself up for another man.
For Crohne?
He's about 600 years old.
You always liked mature men.
Hurry home.
Good evening. This way.
We do understand that you
being the first Danish women PM -
feel compelled to fight
for women's rights.
However, it's always been
an executive right -
to pick the board members.
It still is. Only now,
50% of them have to be women.
When a symphony orchestra
chooses a new violinist -
they place a screen on stage -
behind which the candidate plays.
At the end they choose the best.
Not the best man
nor the best woman -
but the best violinist.
But nobody picks board members
that way.
We do.
- Okay.
Then why hasn't the number
of women executives changed?
Women are better and
more highly educated than men -
and there are more competent
women to choose from.
All good things come
to those who wait.
How long then? It took women
almost 70 years to get the vote.
Many boards are made up
solely of men.
They call in one of the old boys,
when they need a new member.
We will not be forced
to give up our freedom of choice.
This country's laws apply
to all Danish companies.
Exactly.
So this could result in -
the Crohne corporation moving
its activities abroad.
I sympathize with your proposal.
But we are a billion dollar corporation
up against tough competition.
We can't risk our companies
being run by incompetents -
because of state intervention.
Is that a threat?
- Not at all.
Your business is standpoints.
We have to live with the results -
and as such have
to take our precautions.
Take some time to consider it.
I'd like to hear your response
within 48 hours.
I know my way out.
They have?
I thought it was Monday.
Fine. Bye.
I just met with Crohne.
He threatened to move
his activities abroad -
if we pass the bill.
Christ!
I warned you.
- We must take this seriously.
It's an unreasonable response
to a bill he doesn't know in detail.
I think it's a reaction
to the introduction of the bill.
I doubt Crohne is that rash.
Maybe the bill went too far.
We could have given them two years'
warning and only said 30% women.
Call yourself
the Minister of Gender Equality?
That would be admitting
men's first claim to the boards.
Are we talking equality or not?
- I think we get the point.
We have to change our policy, Birgitte.
We have to.
It's lousy PR to withdraw the bill
because of a little resistance.
Crohne accounts for 11%
of the Danish gross national income.
11%.
And when Crohne says 'jump', the
corporative world says 'how high?'.
So we should let Crohne
dictate the law of the land?
No, but that's just the way it is.
He's stronger.
We stand to lose DKK 170b.
Not to mention a lot of jobs.
It's going to be fun to pitch that
as a positive to the business dailies.
Crohne gave us 48 hours.
Let's go on as if nothing happened.
- Play it tough.
If we bail the first time
anyone raises their voice, we've lost.
Beware, Birgitte.
- I won't let Crohne rattle my cage!
We may have to make concessions.
Maybe we can create a public opinion
forcing him to give us a better deal.
Nice shoes.
Louboutin is a genius.
Oh, you know about shoes, too.
Read fashion magazines?
No, I'm a know-all.
What is that tattoo on your ancle?
It's the Chinese sign for woman.
- In case you're in doubt.
It's more to get know-alls
to reveal their ignorance.
Dropping your pen on purpose
was lame.
But thanks for the compliment.
Have you got a moment?
- Sure.
Poor Henriette.
The press is having a field day.
It gets to her.
- You think?
She's very strident.
But then there is a lot of talk about
her among reporters and spin doctors.
People talk about her quick success...
with men.
Very nasty for her.
- We can't take it seriously.
Just say so, if you need me to relieve
her of some of her responsibilities.
If things comes to a head.
I don't see any reason
to change anything.
Let's not listen to gossip, okay?
Sure.
But what do I tell the press?
TV1 wants to interview me tomorrow.
They want to hear how I feel
about her taking over my area.
You can't.
- But I have to.
You can't display
our internal strife like that.
I'm sick of being on display...
- I'm your boss. I forbid it.
Call it off.
That's masculine leadership,
if I ever saw it.
I thought we talked things over.
- We did, and I made my decision.
Kasper. Come here.
Door.
How did TV1 get wind of the conflict
between Klitgaard and Madsen?
Find out.
Katrine, please pick up.
Call me, dammit.
Katrine. We need to talk.
What's up?
- It's confidential.
Benjamin is my spinning instructor.
- Spin off and let the grow-ups talk.
Hey!
- I need to talk to you. Now.
I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Nice talking to you.
- See you.
Don't talk to people like that.
Are you seeing him?
- Stop it.
Did you invite Pernille Madson
in for an interview -
because I told you about the conflict
between her and Klitgaard?
It's a good story.
I told you in confidence.
I said so.
Pernille is not going on the news.
- I love it when you bully me.
That's nothing against
a cabinet crisis. Goodbye.
Kasper.
This is why I left you. Your world
ends and begins with you.
Your priorities,
your secrets.
I have no secrets.
- You have nothing but.
Oh, come on.
Crohne threatens to pull out
of Denmark, if we pass the bill.
Sure.
He's a tough old bastard.
You think it's tough of him
to blackmail the PM?
No, but I told you
you were in for a beating.
Come here.
- Babe, I've got 48 hours.
What are you doing?
Getting to know all about Crohne.
I guess you need to take it seriously.
It's not just the gender thing.
It's because you're meddling
with the way he runs his business.
It's just a gambit.
Exactly. It's just like when
people go all in in a poker game.
They may not have a good hand,
but it'll cost you to find out.
Pokerjust isn't your game.
- Why not?
You can't bluff. You're a girl.
Am I wrong?
Hell yeah!
Girls bluff all the time.
Really?
- Sure.
I just need to check something...
- No, baby.
Look...
If you must work,
you'll have to go next door.
Okay. Good night.
What's this?
- Oatmeal.
With grated apple.
- Yuck.
It's called healthy food, and you
should try it before you turn 18.
No way.
- Coco Pops is for the weekend.
Your minister's been around, huh?
- Get dressed.
MY MANY MEN
Did you finish your work last night?
"Henriette had a sure plan
for getting ahead. "
"She carried it out on her back. "
"Several of her acquaintances say -
Henriette targeted powerful men
and made them her sex partners. "
They can't write that about a minister.
They make her sound like a whore.
Laugesen is at the helm of
the Express. They're unscrupulous.
It's libel.
- She may have been a fast girl.
What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
What... Have you been with her?
- Stop it.
When you worked together.
You fucked her.
It's 17 years ago.
- You slept with my minister.
And you've been concealing it.
- We don't talk about all the...
About the people we've been with
before we met.
It was at a Christmas party.
We were drunk.
My Minister of Economic Affairs.
- She was a 21-year-old intern.
Go through my list of ministers and
check off those you've fucked, okay?
Sure.
Good morning.
Yes.
- This is completely over the top.
They've talked to some men
from your past.
It's classical chauvinism. It's okay
for a man to bed a lot of women.
If a woman does it, she's a whore.
- Well, did you? Bed a lot of men.
We have to come up with a response.
If we're going to sue,
we need to know...
It's personal.
- Not after 120,000 have read it.
I've had a perfectly normal
amount of boyfriends and flings.
At the odd Christmas party.
Laugesen hates this cabinet and me.
This time you took the flak.
Laugesen is acting under orders.
Who ran the story?
Three media within the last 12 hours.
First The Express.
And then the free newspaper CITY.
The Express is owned by CPH Press -
who in turn is owned by CITY Media
who publish the free paper.
"Stars and Royals"
are published by Orion House -
who is owned by...
Mermaid. Com.
...which is owned by Crohne Media.
Joachim Crohne.
It all adds up
Good work, Kasper.
Only we can't use it.
We can't prove a thing.
It's a great story.
- We're not going to use it.
We focus on the politics, and you're
shocked by these personal attacks.
I mean it. How are we
going to deal with the press?
We won't respond. We get Henriette
live on the news tonight, TV1 or TV2.
Let the Ministry for Economic Affairs
handle it, but run everything by me.
I'll set up an interview.
- I'll handle it.
I'm well-connected.
I'm very sorry
you have to go through all this.
I guess it's part of the job.
- No.
Now what?
- A gift.
- At what price?
- It's a gift.
Open it, and let's see if I want it.
- An interview with Klitgaard.
But she's refused to comment so far.
Why this sudden urge to go on TV?
I don't have a hidden agenda.
- Quote of the day, Kasper! Well?
Really? Okay.
Sure. Okay, Bent.
No, okay. Yes.
Am I interrupting anything?
- No.
Klitgaard is going on
the 6 o'clock news with Laugesen.
The network thought it would be
too tame to have her alone -
so Laugesen is going
to represent the Express.
Klitgaard cannot mention
our talks with Crohne.
Thanks, Sanne.
The Metalworkers' Union.
- That's tomorrow.
The Commissioner of the Faroe...
- The High Commissioner.
She's pretty incompetent.
- Yeah, but she's got a great ass.
Klitgaard can't reveal anything.
She must keep it on a personal lavel.
Sejrø just spoke to Danish Industry.
Five of our largest companies
are backing Crohne's threat.
If he pulls out of the country,
so will they.
So you're withdrawing the bill?
- They're putting the squeeze on us.
Don't tell Klitgaard.
Make sure she stays in line.
Coordinate with her adviser.
- Rune Holm is an amateur.
But you aren't, Kasper.
Rune, let's see to it
your minister doesn't screw up tonight.
Yes, let's.
How did you get so arrogant?
- Practice makes perfect.
Where's your adviser?
Since you insist on handling the press,
we might as well talk one on one.
The PM asks you to refrain
from mentioning certain issues tonight.
You cannot reveal
the PM's talks with Crohne.
You cannot use the argument
that Crohne owns the Express.
Don't mention Crohne.
- Please explain.
Laugesen has a way of making people
say things they wouldn't dream of.
So I stick to saying
that we're going through with the bill.
Don't mention the bill either.
Keep it on a personal level.
I don't get it. Is there something
you're not telling me?
Has Birgitte changed her mind
about the bill?
Just stick to our agreement.
You want me to go up against
an unscrupulous bastard -
who's peddling blatant lies
about me...
It goes with the job.
- Yours or mine? Have you no morals?
Act like a professional, dammit!
Now what?
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
Are you dropping the bill?
- Yes, dammit!
You have a meeting now.
You can see yourself out.
Say it like it is!
- How many am I up against here?
I love easy women -
- but it's not something I associate
with a minister for economic affairs.
Why should the public be interested
in the Minister's sex life?
The public has a right to know about
the morals of their politicians.
Your allegations are irrelevant.
- None of your men have denied them.
Maybe because the debate is low.
- Or because it's true.
Let's leave that debate for now.
Michael, in an interview last month -
- you talk about your college days.
"I spent all my time
doing as many women as possible. "
Are the rules different for men?
- You hate women in top positions.
I like beautiful women on top
and in all positions.
Does your crusade against me
as Minister of Economic Affairs -
serve other interests, too?
- Please elaborate.
- Yes, please do.
The corporate powers-that-be
are dead against my proposal -
- of putting more women
on the Danish boards.
Your paper is owned by Crohne
Media who want the bill dropped.
- What an absurd allegation.
- No more absurd than your story.
Let him answer.
- I'm afraid our time is up.
The nerve of her!
She didn't let him answer.
What did you tell Klitgaard?
- I told her to be careful.
Did you tell her
we might have to drop the bill?
Kasper, dammit! Crohne will be
over here within the hour.
He'll say we're accusing him
of leaning on the cabinet.
He is!
- But we can't say so, Kasper!
The Permanent Secretary
and the Minister for Finance.
Have Klitgaard come in tomorrow.
- Crohne is going to sue us, dammit!
I'm sure he can be dissuaded.
- Sure, if we drop the bill.
It's our most sensible option.
- It's our only option.
No! That implies
Crohne makes good of his threat.
He'll be here in an hour.
How much do we know about him?
Let's hear the facts, Kasper.
Denmark's most powerful
businessman. A Grand Cross.
Founder of
the Crohne Foundation -
which restores Danish landmarks
and finances hospital wings and so on.
Thanks. Doesn't Crohne
also play bridge with the Queen?
You know him well, don't you?
He has been known to.
Every three Thursdays.
And he's always invited to
her New Year levées and Royal balls?
And what do they sing each morning
at Crohne's head office?
"In Denmark I was born. "
- Is this Jeopardy?
I'm calling...
- Crohne's bluff.
He's the most powerful and richest
Dane alive. Hobnobs with the Queen.
Huge donations to national causes.
The man is going on 70.
Is he going to end his days
by leaving Denmark -
just because he has to let
a few women on his board?
You're gambling.
- It's a calculated risk.
Let me evaluate!
- You just did.
You let your guests shout it out.
You're set on crucifying Laugesen.
That was a lousy interview.
- Sharp questions, sharp answers.
The anchor must distribute
the verbal blows evenly.
Christ, it's the Director-General
calling to kick my ass.
I bet Laugesen complained already.
And whose fault is that, huh, Katrine?
Evaluation sure comes
in all shapes and sizes.
I always take a critical stand
toward my guests.
You're ranting.
- Hey.
How about some interval training?
Let me teach you how to run.
- I've been running for 15 years.
Women's races?
- And junior handball.
Show me tomorrow then.
- Aren't you going running tomorrow?
I'll pick you up at 8 a. m.
See you.
I never said
I was going running tomorrow.
He's a stud!
- I bet he can't spell IQ.
He's mad about you.
That guy's name is Yes Please.
Repeat after me: Yes Please.
Well, ma'am.
Have you got an answer for me?
No.
- You need more time?
No, the answer is no.
You run this country's largest
company. We make the laws.
And we don't mix those two things up.
That's a very nonchalant attitude
considering the consequences.
The consequences of giving in to you
would be far greater for democracy.
It's going to pain me to leave
Denmark after a lifetime here.
But you won't.
You're not going to move 10,000 jobs
just because of three women.
Oh no?
What am I going to do then?
You're going to reveal yourself
as a modern leader -
adjusting to new times
ahead of everyone else -
because you won't
let the law force you.
That way you'll also get the most
competent women for your board.
And what do I get in return?
The Prime Minister's gratitude.
The environmental taxes are
going to hit our plants hard.
I'd appreciate more time
for the transition.
Another two years.
Not bad.
- Thank you.
But you won't make a Moderate
out of me just yet.
Your wife just beat the most
powerful man in Denmark in poker.
Oh. Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Let's celebrate.
- No. Sleep tight.
Good night.
Good morning.
- What's up?
Large envelope, no sender.
We got Intelligence to check it out.
A bomb?
- Maybe.
Good morning.
Good morning, Kasper.
- We have a problem.
Henriette lied on her CV.
We just received a transcript
of her CV from Who's Who -
as well as proof that she hasn't
got the degrees she claims.
Does it hold up?
- I'm afraid so.
Two universities deny
her having gone there.
She never got her PhD.
Who sent it?
- I'm betting Crohne.
Not personally,
but some of his people.
Birgitte, this is a recognition
of your settlement.
He's sending you the weapon
he would've used against the cabinet.
Does the Express have this?
- Probably.
But they won't use it.
Crohne won't allow it.
I've given her my personal support.
I know.
Come in.
Are congratulations in order?
- Yes, we'll get the bill passed.
I should congratulate
all women, then.
I'm sorry I let my temper
get the better of me on TV.
Yes, well,
that's not what I want to talk about.
Do you know the amnesty rules?
Anyone guilty of a crime
can avoid punishment -
if they turn themselves in.
Let's say I told you
you could confide in me -
anything you think you ought
to have told me about yourself.
You have nothing to confide, even if
it will spare you the consequences?
About your past?
If you're referring
to my encounter with your husband...
That's irrelevant.
This is the Prime Minister talking.
This is far more important.
I have no idea what you mean.
I'm awfully sorry -
because that forces me
to ask you to resign.
These degrees
didn't make me minister.
It's a long time ago.
- You lied.
In public, to the cabinet
and to me personally.
This was necessary
to get the right jobs.
It's a trifle.
I've been a good minister.
I can't have a minister who lies to me.
Birgitte, this isn't necessary.
Believe me, it isn't.
We'll find a nice way to do it.
This won't get out.
I suggest you send me
your resignation this afternoon.
Yes.
I only did what hordes of
incompetent men have always done.
I embellished the facts.
Yes, but I don't need
an incompetent man.
I need a competent woman.
Henriette Klitgaard is resigning
because of the smear campaign.
She says she's resigning
because of her family.
The media campaign
has been a shocking experience.
I've realized that this job
comes at a price so high -
- that I neither can nor will
subject my three children -
- my husband nor myself
to anymore.
The new Minister of Economic Affairs
is Pernille Madsen -
- who also gains a seat
on the Coordination Committee.
Hi, Mom. Have you had a nice day?
- Fine, thanks.
I'm looking forward
to continuing your work.
Henriette Klitgaard
was obviously moved today.
It's hard to say goodbye.
Subtitles: Helle Schou Kristiansen
Dansk Video Tekst