What do you want?
I don't want to argue with you.
Hi.
- Are you?
You're drunk and very silly.
- Katrine, I think he's ugly.
She's asking you to leave.
- Take it easy!
We can't meet privately anymore.
It won't do.
Do you know that your wife loves you?
I love her, too.
But I'm not sure about the PM.
No more friends at the Castle.
You must be able to fire anybody.
Do you have a minute?
- Of course.
Once we would both have protested.
Before you became pragmatic.
I'm PM. Also for those who
didn't vote for me. Remember that.
"Trust is good, control is better. "
- Lenin
No, in that sense I don't have access
to the Prime Minister.
Well, we were sort of friends
in those days.
Yes...
I think I can bring that up
with Birgitte Nyborg.
Oh yes, we do have
our brief meetings.
What the hell is this?
Did you put this one in?
I'll call you back. Bye.
What is it?
It looks like a camera?
Magnus, stop that!
Birgitte, this is against the rules.
Your office hours are at 12, right?
Phillip, I can easily read a report
and plant some flowers.
No, you can't.
We'll do this together, okay?
Okay... Give it to me!
- Stop it!
We're doing this together.
- Birgitte!
Kasper, what do you want?
- I have a minor problem.
Social Solidarity claim
that we're bugging them.
But we aren't, are we?
- There are indications that we are.
GOVERNMENT Episode 7
- See No Evil, Hear No Evil, Speak No Evil
Lindenkrone, today you found
bugging devices in your rooms.
I'm shocked. This is
a breach of all democratic rules.
Do you suspect who put it up?
It wouldn't be the first time that
Intelligence go beyond their limits.
They are controlled by Parliament.
- The control doesn't work.
The control group is tied
to secrecy in most cases.
Hi, Birgitte. I thought you were
working from home today.
So did I, but somebody has
been bugging a legal party.
Which equipment did they find?
- That's what I ask myself.
So you don't know?
- I've asked Intelligence to report.
If it's Intelligence, the bugging
has been past your desk.
I can't remember them all.
There's more than 3,000 every year.
You can't remember if Intelligence
has asked to bug Social Solidarity?
Nobody is monitored without a reason,
and a judge would be included.
Intelligence follow strict rules.
- So it could be Intelligence?
I'm not 100% certain,
and I don't want to misinform you.
But I'll keep you informed.
- Good.
They already call it 'NørrebroGate'.
Relax...
I am not a crook.
Okay?
- Okay.
Bugged them?
But that's bloody illegal!
Jesus!
One moment.
Yes?
I'll call the Ministry of Justice.
How did they find out?
Okay.
Right.
Yes.
Let's talk at the editorial meeting.
I'll see you in a moment. Bye...
That's really good work!
Laura, why don't you help us?
- May I go to Emma's place?
No, we're working together here.
Come on.
Hi, Phillip.
- Hi, Freja. What are you doing here?
The application that we talked
about. Would you read it for me?
Well...
I really expected it in a mail.
I thought I'd just come by.
What job was it for?
- An internship at the National Bank.
I really want it!
- You want it?
You told us to write
a decent application.
You read so many bad ones
when you were a CEO.
If you mail me later -
I could come back,
so we could look at it together.
Right.
No, I'll just return it
with my comments.
Okay. Thanks a lot.
- No problem. Bye...
Bye...
Better late than never.
- My bike had a flat tire.
Is he good?
- What are you talking about?
He looks good.
That's a private matter.
We'll see him at the TV-festival.
You're shortlisted for a prize.
You're evading the question.
- Who will you bring?
We could go together.
- I'd love to.
I'm smelling blood here.
The bugging of Social Solidarity
sweeps the table.
I think that a minister
will have to go.
Meaning the Minister of Justice.
- Right. If Intelligence is behind.
Höxenhaven will join me
at 6 o'clock.
He only wants to say that
they're looking into the matter.
He will know if it's Intelligence.
- He won't comment on that.
They say he sleeps with them.
- Who wouldn't if they know his wife?
Somebody else could tell us whether
this equipment is Intelligence stuff.
We're on to an expert.
- Can we get hold of him today?
We could ask him,
if we can tape an interview.
I'd like to use it at 6.
- First you tell the Minister.
I don't think so.
We don't use methods like that.
- We're talking illegal bugging.
Well, we'll inform him...
...but not this time.
Fine.
Of course I take exception to the
bugging of legal political parties.
I've asked for an investigation.
Could Intelligence possibly
be the bugging agency here?
The present address
for Social Solidarity -
used to be the address for
'Reaktion', the publishing house.
And they sympathized with
many revolutionary movements.
Hence the interest of Intelligence?
- I can't comment on that.
He's under pressure now.
Move closer, but slowly.
So Intelligence isn't behind this?
- There are other possibilities.
We've talked to an expert in
bugging equipment. Listen to this.
It's one of the world's
smallest surveillance cameras.
A Hapac-Fischer U-46 CCD-camera,
transmitting on 2.5 gigahertz.
The mike is very sensitive. It will
pick up the slightest whispering.
If it's not Intelligence, it would be
people they should keep an eye on.
It's state-of-the-art equipment.
Who would be the owner here,
in your opinion?
I'm 90% certain it's Intelligence.
90% certain of Intelligence,
an expert says.
I can't comment on that.
- What the hell can you say?
Intelligence is your province.
- I don't know their expert.
His name is Hansen, and he's
considered to be a leading expert.
We won't get any closer than this.
- Thank you.
And now some good housing news...
Bloody good interview!
- Thanks.
Remember to thank you mom and your
boyfriend in your speech of thanks.
Ulrik will receive the prize.
Will we see little Benjamin
in a tight tux?
I don't think so, Tanja.
- He's only good enough for sex?
You were the one to suggest sex!
- You've been together for 2 months.
Everybody seems to have an opinion
about my private life.
What's so dangerous
about being seen together?
Bye...
Höxenhaven has been called in by
the legal affairs committee tomorrow.
I've asked for a report.
- You should stay out of this.
The media mustn't think they can
approach the PM on this issue.
Agreed.
It's a Minister of Justice issue.
Social Solidarity have called
all day. Don't open a dialogue.
I've agreed to meet Lindenkrone
in a moment.
Can she approach the PM
just like that?
They have a right to be furious.
I'm accommodating them.
Because Lindenkrone
was your invention?
No, Bent.
- Who is whose invention?
Birgitte got her into politics.
- Wrong.
I met her at a radio debate.
She was good, and
I encouraged her to enter politics.
You were her mentor, really...
- No, I was not, Bent.
I always thought our party could
agree with them on a few issues.
Bent never liked Lindenkrone.
As a principle.
Oh, come on... No, no.
He's a bit uneasy about
the red-haired company.
Would you discuss that over a beer
at the next party convention?
Right. The majority of the government
rests on Social Solidarity.
So a dialogue-friendly approach...
- Precisely.
What can we offer her?
- Offer her? What do you mean?
So she will not topple the
government, if it comes to that.
Hi, Birgitte.
- Hi, Anne Sophie.
Thanks for taking the time.
- Of course.
How are you?
- You ought to know.
Aren't you bugging us right now?
That must be a misunderstanding.
- Misunderstanding?
Didn't TV1 News establish
that they were your people?
My people?
This isn't a police state.
How is bugging a legal party
different from a police state?
In that you're here, you get
an explanation and an apology.
But that's not enough.
It's not that I don't like you
or your project.
No, and that's why I've contemplated
how to accommodate you.
And how would you do that?
Intelligence is Höxenhaven's area.
If a mistake has happened -
he will be rebuked. And
you will receive a formal apology.
And we'll establish a hearing about
the existing control of Intelligence.
Headed by
a former Intelligence chief?
No.
You tell me who you want.
That's a very generous offer,
Birgitte.
It is.
In return I hope -
that you're aware of your position
as the basis for the government.
I don't want to make life hard
for your government.
As long as you can accept that our
voters want a watchdog in Parliament.
What do you mean?
If it really is a misunderstanding,
no problem. If it goes deeper -
I will neither leave you
nor your government in peace.
Just to make our position
quite clear.
But of course.
Let's pretend you don't need this.
- What a boring game.
What's this?
- A galla performance invitation.
"We are pleased to invite you and
companion to a galla performance. "
Who's your companion?
- Nobody. I'm going on my own.
Because it's work.
Don't you want people to see us?
- Stop it. I see you all the time.
We never see anybody.
We have sex, and that's it.
Yes, but I'm very private,
when I'm private.
Let me ask you then: Would you
like me to be your companion?
Maybe.
Maybe?
Yes.
Yes, of course I would.
- Really?
Yes.
Hi, sweetheart.
- Hi, sweetheart.
Good morning. Isn't this nice?
- Yes, it's wonderful, right?
I slept like a log.
- Your minister didn't look good.
What's he up to? Letting
Intelligence bug competing parties.
Where I work it would be illegal.
- And in my business as well.
That's not what happened.
- Are you sure?
It says here we've got 250.000
surveillance cameras in Denmark.
Do you getter better grades, if you
put a photo on your assignment?
Yes, that's a straight A.
It's a job application.
Her hair is longer now.
She came here yesterday. She wants
an internship at the National Bank.
Maybe I should ask Intelligence
to tail you.
Well, you're already abusing
your power, so why not?
Ready for the consultation?
It belongs to Intelligence
and was installed by Hesselboe.
For which reason?
The rooms were used by people
on the EU terror list.
And you have names?
- Photos and info.
One is Massoud Bucak from
PKK's extremist wing. Also PFLP.
The publishers had lent them
the rooms, right?
Intelligence had
a very complicated task.
Social Solidarity took over
the rooms concurrently.
I have details, but the committee
will get the full report.
It's hardly a desirable situation,
if their criticism is justifiable.
There's nothing at the consultation
that I cannot explain.
This is really taking a long time!
Why don't you get us a sandwich,
Ruben?
Did you deliver what
the opposition had demanded?
Did the committee get the answers
they had asked for?
No. The Minister explained why
the equipment had been set up.
But he hasn't asked Intelligence
to remove it, when we moved in.
Shortly after Nyborg
came into office?
That's why
it's his responsibility.
Maybe the Minister didn't know
you had moved in?
The Minister had been informed
that we took over the lease.
When we moved in, we invited
all parties to our housewarming.
Any comments to the consultation?
It's a scandal, if the Minister knew
that a party was under surveillance.
The oppositionen is underway.
- You were PM at the time.
At the time the rooms were taken
by a publishing house.
Our government would
have removed it immediately.
I wonder.
- You want something to eat?
If it had happened in my time,
they would ask for my resignation.
How do you intend to react?
- We've asked for a consultation.
This consultation was a closed one,
but this must be made public.
The Minister must answer
to Parliament and to the nation.
I may call in the PM.
- This is enough!
Sanne! I need Höxenhaven now!
And no excuses, please!
The PM does not defend herself
during intense questioning!
That's bad media exposure.
- You don't have to tell me.
The Minister is in a meeting.
- I said: No excuses!
They're holding a press meeting
in a second. At 4 o'clock.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Welcome to you all.
Before we start, I'd like to say -
that there may be questions
we cannot answer -
due to the protection
of Intelligence work.
What do you think of the criticism
of the Ministry of Justice?
I don't understand it.
I've explained -
that 'Reaktion' used their rooms
for suspicious meetings.
Social Solidarity claim that
you were aware of their moving in.
The publishers used the rooms after
Social Solidarity's housewarming.
They may have been drinking wine
in the front rooms -
but other things went on in the
back rooms. I want to point out -
that Social Solidarity was never
a target for surveillance.
Is there an investigation against
a member of Social Solidarity?
I cannot comment on
ongoing investigations.
Is there an investigation
of any party members?
No comment.
You can't hold a press meeting
that hasn't been cleared by me.
I can explain everything.
Did you approve the bugging after
Social Solidarity took the rooms?
Listen...
- Yes or no?
I have information that justifies
the surveillance -
and which will change
everybody's idea of the matter.
In my office there is a secret
recording of Lindenkrone -
where she argues for kidnapping
former PM Hesselboe's two teenagers.
Anne Sophie?
- Yes.
When was the tapping done?
- About six years ago.
It can't be from those rooms then.
- It's from the old Youth House.
There's a lot of noise,
because there was a party.
But there is no doubt that
she considers the possibility.
I suggest we inform the media
already by tonight.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you want to press charges -
because of a bad wiretapping
from a party in the Youth House?
A recording that Intelligence
didn't take seriously?
It's Lindenkrone without any doubt.
- That's not a rescue plan, Höx.
You can hear it yourself.
- I don't want to hear it.
I forbid you to use it.
- You can't do that.
It's a very important argument.
What else am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
But you'll have to find out.
You are the minister responsible,
and tomorrow you'll explain yourself.
The Minister must explain whether
he was aware that a legal party...
Anne Sophie, may I have a word?
- Yes... We'll talk later.
Thanks.
- Bye.
I didn't know anything about this.
I'm shocked at the whole thing.
Höxenhaven will answer all
relevant questions tomorrow.
What will you gain by grounding him?
Even though he acted foolishly?
We're talking about
illegal surveillance.
Anne Sophie, it will be a major
defeat, if Höxenhaven resigns.
Never mind your party members, but
could you hold back a bit tomorrow.
For your sake?
- You could say that.
You have no political interest in
letting down my government. Right?
So tomorrow we belittle
a breach of the Constitution -
for old friendship's sake?
Good. Okay.
Keep me out of it
for as long as possible, okay?
I'll talk to you tomorrow, Kasper.
Bye.
Tell me something
that will make me forget my job.
I've had a visitor.
Hi.
I've gone through Freja's application
with her.
You're doing a great job as PM.
- Thank you.
Okay. I'll be off then.
- Okay.
Thanks for your help, Phillip.
It was really kind of you.
No, keep them.
- Okay.
See you later... Bye.
- Right. Bye.
Where are the kids?
- Laura sleeps over at Ida's.
Karsten asked Magnus to join
William for a circus performance.
They'll be here in a moment.
Are you hungry?
Hi, Mom.
Hi. So you went
to a circus performance?
Hi, Karsten.
Long time, no see.
Magnus, take care.
- Bye...
No, honey. It's too late for cakes.
Was it a good performance?
Look, what I had.
Are we having supper now?
- Yes.
She forgot this.
Spaghetti with meat sauce. That's
what we can offer today. Okay?
The PM's press conference.
- She won't say anything.
Could we make her come here?
- She's kept away from here so far.
Katrine has a special connection
to the PM's spin doctor.
And now to my private life again.
- Because it's so bloody secret.
He will come for the awards.
- The PM's spin doctor?
What is it that I don't know?
- My boyfriend.
Can we move on?
- See you later.
The Minister of Justice will face
the heat in Parliament today.
The opposition threatens
to call the PM as well.
Any comments from the PM?
The case belongs 100%
to the Ministry of Justice.
Do you think the opposition agrees?
- I certainly hope so.
And if it doesn't?
- That's hypothetical.
The Speaker decides
who can be called.
I think she knows
it serves no purpose to call me.
Lindenkrone won't reject
the possibility of calling in the PM.
I trust that the Minister
can answer for himself today.
If the Minister has overstepped
his powers -
will he stay
in the government then?
Not if he has failed
to recognize his responsibilities.
Höxenhaven knows that as well
as the other ministers. Thank you.
Can you guarantee he's out,
if he cannot answer for himself?
Thanks to Hanne Holm. That
was the end of our weekly meeting.
Katrine Fønsmark from TV1 News.
I have an appointment with Juul.
Why are you staring at me?
- Because you're cute.
What?
- What?
Hi.
- Well, well...
Distinguished visitors.
To what do I owe the honour?
I'd like an appointment with your
minister. Can we talk in private?
I thought that was over.
- Let's talk about the options.
There's nothing to talk about.
It's not the PM's responsibility.
You took a meeting with me
just to say that?
You asked for it. I looked into it,
and I'm sorry. End of story.
Thanks a lot.
Wait... Katrine!
- You're a waste of time.
Is it because of Benjamin?
- You think I'm that primitive?
Exactly.
- Well, the Smurf beats me at it.
Good conversations about politics?
He's so shrewd, isn't he?
I bet his analyses
are razor sharp.
Life is more than work.
- Not for you.
I thought we had a guard here.
Did the Minister know that
Intelligence tapped a legal party?
Doesn't Mrs. Lindenkrone know that
Denmark is targeted by terrorists -
and that Intelligence fights
on the invisible front?
So the Minister confirms that
Intelligence went too far?
No, but I'm familiar with
Mrs. Lindenkrone's sympathies.
He didn't say that!
- Would the Minister explain that?
There has been every reason
to tap those rooms.
An effective Intelligence is
our only guarantee -
against international terror.
Kasper, let's make overtures
on TV1 tomorrow.
I just turned TV1 down.
- Höx just got himself killed.
This could end in
a vote of no confidence.
We can't expect Höxenhaven
to draw the necessary conclusion.
Well, then somebody
must do it for him.
I'm ready to take responsibility
and react accordingly.
I'll apologize tomorrow and accept
a reprimand from you.
As a minister you couldn't answer
questions in Parliament.
You've exceeded your powers
in a crucial area.
We are beyond reprimands.
- Well...
Your morals must be more impeccable
than those of other people.
I see no other options
than asking for your resignation.
I beg your pardon?
Resign?
I can't do that. I haven't even
been minister for a year.
That would look strange.
There's another solution.
There are no other solutions.
- Yes. The Intelligence chief.
If Kruse resigns...
- No. Stop it!
Stop, before you make
an even bigger fool of yourself.
Go home and talk with your family.
And tomorrow you hand in
your resignation in a dignified way.
Right?
Birgitte, this is intolerable.
I'll do anything.
- It's no good, Troels.
It doesn't have to be
your last ministry.
If you resign, you can make
a come-back in a Cabinet reshuffle.
You are a good politician.
But if you don't want to resign,
I have to fire you.
You'll get a vote of no confidence
after your show in Parliament today.
Good. Okay.
Right.
Kruse, we have a situation.
Yes.
I have to ask for your help.
Where are you right now?
My apologies.
This mustn't be a problem for us,
and it will be -
when I can't get an interview,
because you dislike my boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
So it's official now?
Yes.
You've got your interview.
Okay?
The PM will be available tomorrow.
Thanks.
And no more talking about it now.
We're pros, right?
I just need to get used to the idea -
of you choosing a guy like...
Benjamin.
I'm sure he's marvellous.
But it was confirmed.
The PM will be on tomorrow.
Yes,
it pays off to have connections.
Right, Torben.
Bye.
God, that was sweet of you.
I'm starving.
I've been toiling away today.
- Me, too.
I've taken over Tina's advanced class
and will teach director's school!
Great. We'll have champagne,
if we topple Höxenhaven.
Who's he?
- Minister of Justice. You know him.
Not really.
Don't you know
who's Minister of Justice?
Why is that so important?
Because he's the most talked-about
minister at the moment.
I'm not really into politics.
Relax!
But you have to keep track
of what's going on!
I'm busy. I don't ask you
to keep up on amino acids.
We're talking of people
who run this country.
Why is your world
more important than mine?
It isn't.
- But that's what you say.
Yes, it is! Because we tell people
what's going on in the world.
And you talk about spinning bikes!
Is that how you see it?
- No, that's how it is, dammit!
Are you checking my mails?
- No.
Are you having an affair with Freja?
- Oh, come on!
She visits you twice in a week
and leaves all kinds of stuff.
She calls you 'sweet' in her mails.
- Are you jealous? She's 22.
I'm asking you.
- No. You're checking me.
No, I'm not fucking one of my
students. I miss adult companionship.
I'm with people her age all day.
That's not where I would go.
- Where would you go?
I can't be bothered to talk like this.
Loyalty is paramount to me.
- Loyalty? Okay.
You're only here when you sleep.
We're not counting on you anymore.
We all work our butts off,
so you can be Prime Minister.
The two of us are sacrificing
our love and sex life on this account.
Not to speak of my career.
We had a deal, Phillip.
It's no use crying over it now.
I'm not crying. We need you
to participate beyond a hobby level.
Would you like an update?
Laura got an A for her essay.
She deserved a small present.
I lied and said that you bought it.
I never asked you to cover for me.
I know what I'm missing.
Oh, shut up.
We both want for anything.
That's the price.
Yes.
- It is!
You have time to be with the kids.
That's something I miss.
Okay. Will you talk to the school
psychologist about Magnus?
About how we keep an 8-year-old
from wetting his pants.
Maybe he should wear a diaper?
- What are you talking about?
Did we wake you up, honey?
You're getting cold.
I'll tuck you in. Come...
Let's move that one up...
Pia, Höxenhaven is on his way out.
- What? Fired, or what?
It's only a question of time.
- I'm in a meeting.
Let me go and dig something up.
- You'd better be quick!
Can't you check it out?
- Who? I'll be right there.
Frederik Ravn, isn't he the weirdo
who monitors both right and left?
He's in the lobby with a package,
we'd love to see.
Sorry.
Easy now... Anne Sophie,
what are you suggesting?
I've said it before. Somebody could
grab Hesselboe's own children.
- Shut up! Lindenkrone is right.
- How?
Kidnap them. So he'll know what
it feels like to lose your children.
I know which school they attend.
Wejust have to plan it carefully.
And it stops here?
- Is that all?
It's Lindenkrone.
- How old is it?
It says 2005 on the tape.
- What do we do? It's spin, you know.
Leaked by the Ministry of Justice.
- But this is ass-kicking news!
Based on some old recordings from
a dubious source used by Intelligence.
The Minister is desperate.
Why else would we get this?
It'll divert the flak from Höxenhaven.
- It's a better story.
It will justify his bugging
Social Solidarity.
We can run both stories.
- But what will be the top story?
What do you think? We have
the story about the Minister.
He talks about terror attacks, and
he forgets dates, but it's complicated.
Then we have a party leader,
who wants to kidnap the PM's kids.
She's not planning it! Why does the
tape stop right here, do you think?
She's drunk, leaves to puke
and goes home.
Listen! A party leader
contemplates a kidnapping.
Do you really mean
that we shouldn't bring it?
Now you define our focus,
which will make Höx a hero.
Höx and Intelligence have tried
to protect democracy.
You can protect it so much
that it's no longer a democracy.
Save that for School of Journalism.
Here we make cool television!
And we're on in 81/2 minutes,
so let's move on.
Ulrik, get on with it.
- Fine... Good luck.
Is Magnus about to get up?
- Yes.
Has anybody seen the other
black shoe. Where could it be?
I'll take it.
Birgitte's mobile, Laura speaking.
Mom, it's Kasper.
- Tell him I'll call back from the car.
Sorry, Kasper. She's looking
for one of her shoes... Okay.
Eat your breakfast.
- What channel? Kasper told me to.
The case took a turning
when it became known -
- that Lindenkrone
some years ago contemplated -
- abducting former PM
Hesselboe's children.
Hesselboe had decided
that Denmark should invade Irak.
Another 10 seconds.
- Let's take Hesseboe's own children.
- How would you do that?
- Kidnap them.
So he'll know what it feels like
when you lose your children.
I know which school they attend.
Wejust have to plan it carefully.
The Minister of Justice
had this comment:
Lindenkrone's statement
is shocking.
A year ago some young activists
entered Christiansborg -
- as Lindekrone's guests and threw
eggs at the Minister for Integration.
It was suggested that an ongoing
Intelligence investigation -
- was relevant to the issue
of bugging Social Solidarity.
I can't comment on that.
- Damn! He did it!
It's shocking that she encourages
such a despicable action.
No matter when she did it.
They are my children!
Do you view the bugging of Social
Solidarity in a new light now?
As Mrs. Lindenkrone inhabits
the rooms, it may be reasonable.
Do you still advocate a kidnapping
of Hesselboe's children?
This was six years ago.
I was young and naive. It was a party.
But you encourage a serious crime?
Who wants to make this public?
The Minister and Intelligence
have leaked this information.
So they are responsible
for your statement?
I haven't got the time now.
I'm expected at a group meeting.
You contacted the New Conservatives,
The Liberals and The Freedom Party.
Yes, they won't support
Lindenkrone at all.
And they let Höx off the hook.
I don't care what he's doing.
I want to see him now! Thank you.
He knows he's about to be fired,
and yet he leaks a recording -
that I prohibited him from using.
I offered to let him resign.
He will be fired so badly that he'll
never become a minister again.
We have to call a press meeting,
so I can explain why he's fired.
Birgitte, you can't fire him.
- I can't fire him?
Höx managed to spin the story.
The media bought the connection.
Höx and Intelligence are now heroes
that protect our Danish democracy.
The oppositionen is satisfied
with a reprimand to Höx -
and a report about the bugging
of Social Solidarity.
We have to make use of the fact
that we just passed the buck.
The only tactical solution is
to keep Höxenhaven.
He ignored a straight order.
How can I ever trust him again?
Don't trust him then!
But don't fire him.
And he completely shattered
Lindenkrone's political life.
Remember what I said about
having friends in the Castle?
This is a political decision.
It's the only right thing to do.
The right thing, Bent?
Thanks.
Yes?
Anne Sophie Lindenkrone
wishes to see the PM.
Tell her I'm in a meeting.
For how long?
Very long.
I'd really like to talk to you.
- Sorry, I don't have the time now.
You know what the media are doing to
me? I'm being attacked by everybody.
They're unraveling everything.
- And what can I do?
I said it at a party. You know
I'd never do a thing like that.
I don't control the media.
- You could distance yourself from it.
You could say that it's
a trivial matter in your opinion.
For my sake.
- You said what you said.
You have to accept that.
Birgitte, I have no idea
how this tape was released.
There are a few things you need
to know and to take very seriously.
Officially you're still a minister,
but in my mind you were fired at 9.
You have broken every rule
in the book, and you let me down.
Never show up in my office
for no reason, and listen to this:
I consider you a dead man
in my government.
The Minister has guaranteed
that this will never happen again.
The committee will get the details -
and the Minister will answer further
questions in a new consultation.
There's nothing more to do
for me in this case.
So Höxenhaven keeps his post?
The Minister of Justice has
my full confidence.
Will Lindenkrone be prosecuted?
- I really don't think so.
She will continue as party leader
for the time being.
You have a close friendship with
Lindenkrone. Does this affect you?
If you get personally affected in cases
with friends in the Castle -
you couldn't be Prime Minister.
Subtitles: Allan Hilton Andersen
Dansk Video Tekst