All I had was my Eurocard
from the PM's Office.
I know something that can make
the right person PM, if used wisely.
This voucher proves
that the PM bought gifts for his wife -
for over DKK 70,000
at the government's expense.
You're only home at night.
And our sex life
is almost nonexistent.
At least you can be with the kids.
I miss that.
Take the appointment
with the school psychologist.
How to stop our son
from wetting his pants.
Katrine?
- Your father's name is Peter Juul.
There's no Peter Juul at Eurocopter.
- He took his new wife's name.
He works for the French military.
My mother committed suicide
when I was three.
"History is a nightmare from which
I am trying to wake. " - James Joyce
Thank you.
That was educational.
I'm sure the PM is against
the killing of pilot whales.
Aren't we wearing a tie anymore?
- It's summer vacation.
Who told all the crazies
that our diary isn't full, Sanne?
There's a society against the killing
of pilot whales on the Faroes.
It's cruelty to animals.
It's cultural cruelty to animals, and
it's not the government's business.
Anything else?
- An Irene Juul called.
She's very keen on talking to you.
Sanne, you know
you're the only woman in my life.
Would you like to see the mail?
- No. Anything important?
Ornithologists want to turn
northern Jutland into a national park.
Out.
The Danish UFO Society.
- Out.
Michael Laugesen has written
a book about his time in Parliament.
"A caustic and revealing description
of life in Parliament.
'Exit' tells the true story
about Danish politics.
The scandals, swindles
and dirty tricks. "
I'll be back in an hour.
That was quick.
- Do you have the book?
We've given 10 copies
to the critics for their eyes only.
Tell me what it says about me.
I've saved your ass many times
when you had unconfirmed rumors.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
Michael is down the hall.
Talk to him yourself.
Hi, Michael.
- What the hell do you want?
Can I have a word?
It's important.
- Okay. I have to piss.
You have two minutes.
Did you write about the vouchers?
- They brought Hesselboe down.
Would I write a book about Parliament
without mentioning them?
Did you say where you got them?
- Read the book.
I hate it when someone tells me
the ending.
Aren't you going
to wash your hands?
It doesn't make the smell
go away anyway.
And Kasper... Maybe you shouldn't
throw the want ads out these days.
You can't run away from the past.
You dropped something.
LIST OF CRITICS
GOVERNMENT
Episode 8- The Silly Season
We're at
the school psychologist's.
Thank you.
I'm here as Magnus' mother
and not the PM.
I hope that isn't a problem.
- Not at all.
Phillip told me
that Magnus had a few accidents -
and wet his pants.
His teacher feels
that he is a bit out of kilter.
I imagine it has something
to do with me and my job.
Everyday life obviously changes
when your mother is the PM.
Your job causes Magnus' accidents?
- He's trying to get attention.
Magnus has also wet his pants
at school. And you're not here.
I'm sure it's about something much
bigger than getting your attention.
The quantity of time
isn't always the most important.
In stressed homes, a child often
reacts to the tone and atmosphere.
Has the tone changed while you
have been busier in the past year?
Yes, it's more matter-of-fact.
Phillip and I talk
about practicalities.
Practicalities?
We're more professional.
There are more logistics.
We don't always
have time to be friendly.
Do they also see you happy?
- What do you mean?
Do you think
your husband is happy?
Yes, I do.
Nothing is going on in Denmark.
- How about abroad?
Laugesen's memoirs?
- The book isn't out yet.
I know what it says.
- But it won't be out till Friday.
Anything else?
- How about cold buttermilk soup?
The production of cold buttermilk soup
is going through the roof.
This summer is unusually hot.
So sales are up by 25%.
500,000 liters a week.
I have an employee
who can provide a perspective.
Excellent idea.
With plenty of meat and potatoes.
Shouldn't we report news?
- It's the silly season.
There are seven civil wars in Africa
we never hear about.
And cholera in Bangladesh.
- Shut up.
Shut your damn mouth.
We have to think of our ratings.
And management loves
a nice, happy story.
Cold buttermilk soup is today's
hottest and happiest news.
You can't possibly believe that
dairy products are qualified to...
No, I don't want you to give me the
book, but lend it to me for an hour.
Easy, Kasper.
I heard about Laugesen's book.
I'm getting hold of copy.
- What can it say?
A bunch of dirt about politicians
and this administration.
Are you in contact with the other
media advisers? How about you?
Laugesen must remember
the voucher thing.
I'll get the book. No problem.
I hope you're right.
Are you okay?
You don't look busy.
Am I right?
No.
- Can I buy you dinner?
I don't dare go out
with the great spin doctor.
And your big news was...
- Cold buttermilk soup.
We might as well have
a black screen till Friday.
Laugesen's book will be out.
- Oh, yes. I've heard of him.
Who has his book?
I know one of you has a copy.
It's confidential.
I'll just mention some names,
and you can shake your head.
Why is it so important?
- Does Torben Friis have it?
I don't know.
It's you, you nasty thing.
You have the book.
Is it Ulrik?
Sweetie, can we talk for a minute?
- What?
Are you happy?
- Am I happy?
What kind of question is that?
- I want to know how you feel.
Okay. Fine. I'm slogging away.
We'll survive. I'll survive.
That's how I feel.
Do you mind...?
Okay.
If you could have anything,
what would it be?
A different job.
I'd like to do something different.
I teach 22-year-olds
about the business sector.
I'd love to run a company.
I'm often asked to.
The other day, a headhunter asked
if I was open to offers.
At that moment,
I was actually happy.
You would like to have a job.
Fine. What would it entail?
Sending the kids to boarding school.
- Someone to bring and fetch them.
And cook and talk to them.
We could hire an au pair.
- No, we decided we wouldn't.
Do you want me to quit?
- No.
It's a question of priorities.
We're talking about you.
Damn, you're good.
Do you know that?
Yeah.
Could you have your boss
call me back?
You're his secretary! Just tell him
Kasper Juul called three times.
Hello?
A woman in reception
wants to talk to you.
Can't you see I'm busy?
- I'm sorry. He's not available.
Okay.
She says she is your mother.
Didn't I tell you
that I don't want to see you?
Then why are you here?
If you want to contact me,
call me.
Your father is dead.
Excuse me?
Kenneth, your father is dead.
I'm impressed
that you work here, Kenneth.
My name is Kasper now.
What are you plans?
It's just that...
- Do you mind?
What do you want?
- I need your help.
I don't know
who else to ask.
Just with the practical things
for the funeral.
The hospital asks
all kinds of questions.
I can't help you.
If you need help,
call the municipality.
But I don't know what to say.
Please come home.
I haven't been home
since I was 12-
and I have no wish
to go home now.
I'll contact an undertaker.
That sounds perfect.
Yes. Lovely.
Hi.
Didn't you want to show your mother
around the Prime Minister's Office?
It wasn't my mother.
It was our old housekeeper.
A rather senile old woman,
who thought I was her son.
Now I see why the guard said
that she called you Kenneth.
Actually, it's rather sad.
She just lost her husband.
- I see.
These are design proposals
for our homepage.
Do I need to be involved?
- Yes, it's our public image.
Let's take a seat.
When Parliament isn't in session,
the rest of us can get some work done.
Aren't you going on vacation?
- A long weekend in August.
We don't manufacture
children's shoes or ice cream here.
We rule Denmark -
and that demands total dedication.
Ministers always take vacation.
Hesselboe did.
Hesselboe pretended to.
A prime minister has to appear
to be a normal human being.
That doesn't mean
he actually goes on vacation.
There isn't time for any of us
to do that. Not even for me.
Does your wife understand?
My present wife does.
My two ex-wives didn't.
Phillip?
- Yes?
I put the country on automatic pilot.
We're going on vacation now!
Okay.
I think we can borrow Mads and
Malene's summer cottage in Skagen.
Should I call them?
It sounds lovely, but Intelligence
can't clear it on such short notice.
How about that house on Bornholm?
- Not right next to your father?
Doesn't the PM have access
to her own summer residence?
The coolest in the country.
Marienborg.
Your official residence.
It's a country mansion.
- What's wrong with that?
Welcome to Marienborg.
- Thank you. Magnus and Laura.
Hello.
Will the children share a room?
- No... thank you.
Fine.
They'll have separate bedrooms.
Maybe you'll sleep in the same bed
as some president.
Do you know all about the place?
- Not everything.
Would you like a guided tour later?
Very much.
Thank you.
I was thinking about dinner.
How about pizza?
I promised Magnus.
- Good idea.
Excuse me. I make dinner when
the Prime Minister is in residence.
We didn't know.
Can't we cook ourselves?
- It isn't customary.
Tonight it's pork tenderloin
in a creamy mushroom sauce.
Many ministers have enjoyed it.
Is 6 p. m. Suitable?
Fine, thanks.
Pork at 6.
Can't you ask her to take time off?
I don't know if I can.
- Really? I thought you were the PM.
THE DAY OF JUDGEMENT
"Everyone is anxious about
Laugesen's revealing book. "
Will that be a problem?
- No.
Kasper is getting hold of a copy,
so we can read it before it comes out.
What does it say?
- Who is doing whom.
There are always rumors.
Yeah.
Who are you doing?
- Excuse me?
Is there anything about you?
- I don't think so.
No skeletons in the closet here.
- No, you're a goody-goody.
Only top grades
and a demure dress.
You're so good that you don't dare
ask the servants to take time off.
Are you suggesting I'm boring?
- Not at all.
I just have a good wife.
Don't believe everything
you read in the papers.
I'm filthy.
I can't fall asleep.
I hear strange noises.
Come here.
Don't fucking touch me!
I want to borrow it for half an hour.
If you don't leave now,
I'm calling security.
Give me that fucking book!
- Leave.
You're history.
- Fuck you too.
What the fuck is up?
- What do you mean?
Did you tell Kasper
that I have Laugesen's book?
No.
Why has he constantly been calling
me and now threatening me?
You must have got it wrong.
- Got it wrong?
"You'll never get an interview with
the PM." Can you get that wrong?
Is Kasper mentioned in the book?
- It's confidential.
Right.
Can't you see that it's a problem
that you two are going out?
Don't take the driving test
if you're not ready.
Come by on Monday,
and we'll talk, alright?
I'm only going to Århus
for three days.
Come here, Kenneth.
We'll have a really good time.
When Mom isn't here,
we can be noisy and watch videoes.
We can have a guys' night.
And we'll have Dad's food, not Mom's.
I'll make burgers with fries
and the whole nine yards.
And ice cream.
Coffee?
Would you like some coffee?
- No thanks.
Has the undertaker been here?
- Lovely to see you.
Shouldn't he be here now?
Your father's shirts.
Would you like to go through them?
Some of them are new.
- No thanks.
I think you're the same size.
In the end he was thin as a rake.
I don't want any.
Take your time in making
the right choices for the deceased.
I just want to get it over with.
- I understand.
But there are decisions to make
about the service, cemetery, coffin.
Any final wishes.
It will be strictly private.
- I see.
Will the service be held in church?
- No, he didn't belong to a church.
Kenneth, he did.
- We agreed that I would handle this.
He didn't belong to one.
- Right.
Burial or cremation?
- Burn him.
How about a plot and a headstone?
- Do tombs of the unknown still exist?
I would like...
- You won't look after it anyway.
You know best, Kenneth.
- I do. The tomb of the unknown.
Right.
That's about it then.
There are documents for your mother
to sign. Possibly tomorrow.
We can meet here when you have
them, and I'll have her sign them.
And as I said,
as soon as possible.
Dad, are we canoeing together?
- We'll beat the girls.
I'll go get a sweater.
It's Mom's.
It's Kasper.
We'll hide it down here.
Are we leaving now, Mom?
- As soon as your father is ready.
That's my cell phone.
Where is it?
Kasper?
- Hello?
I couldn't get hold of the book.
But I'm sure
Laugesen isn't holding anything back.
Does he have dirt on my ministers?
I'm sure the book reveals that
I gave Laugesen the vouchers.
Do you have a strategy
if it's revealed?
No.
- We have to meet and talk.
See you.
The worst case is that he busts you.
That could be ugly.
I know.
One option is to remain passive
and let Laugesen take the blame.
You showed him
the vouchers during a party.
But he used them
and abused my trust.
But it doesn't seem credible.
No. What's the alternative?
- Taking the offensive.
You gave Laugesen them deliberately.
How will that get me off the hook?
You saw the vouchers
in an undisclosed place -
and were so appalled that you
thought something should be done.
So you suggested to me
that they be made public.
I refused. And in frustration
you went to Laugesen.
Because I thought Hesselboe's
actions were reprehensible.
And you fired me.
We couldn't work together
due to a moral disagreement.
If I ever become prime minister,
will you be my spin doctor?
What the hell are you...?
Look what I found.
- What?
A prime minister's favorite champagne
according to the housekeeper.
Have you tasted it?
- I cheated, yes.
The housekeeper
is watching the children -
so they won't barge in
for the next hour and a half.
So I think you should kiss your wife.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it like this.
- Should I do the other thing?
No, I don't mean that. I...
I'm not in the mood.
Okay.
So...
You're never in the mood.
Because you're never home.
- We spend every night together.
You come in at 3 a. m.
With a computer under your arm.
Yes, but now we're on vacation.
There's peace and quiet...
...and we have the time.
I wanted to have sex
for the first time in a month.
And that's fantastic,
and I'm sorry.
I can't participate
in the official program.
I miss my wife.
Why don't you answer your phone?
- Things are busy here.
You threatened Ulrik today.
Have you lost your mind?
Why is that book so important?
What does it say?
I don't know what you mean.
- That's why you flirted with me.
Stop it, Katrine.
It's ourjob to get information.
And you tell whatever stories
you need to get what you want, but...
But what?
You still don't get it.
If you just told me the truth -
I would do anything for you.
Can I get you a beer?
There's one piece of information
I never got Laugesen to divulge.
How he got hold of the vouchers
from my wife's shopping trip.
When did you last see them?
When I gave them to Ole Dahl,
who died that very evening.
Two days later, Laugesen showed
them to me during a TV debate.
I don't know how he got them.
- Did Ole give them to Laugesen?
- No, Ole was very loyal.
No, the truth lies somewhere else.
We'll see if the truth is revealed
in Laugesen's book...
Did you do it? Did you give Laugesen
the vouchers during the election?
Is that what he has on you?
Tell me what happened
on the night that Ole died.
Sit down.
Tell me the truth
for once, Kasper.
It's true that I took the papers
that night and gave them to Laugesen.
But I didn't go through Ole's bag.
I did it to save you
and your career.
The bag fell over,
and the damn vouchers fell out.
And you took them?
Katrine, those papers proved
that the PM broke the law.
It's your duty to act
when that happens.
Is that how you'll explain it
to the press?
That you did your civic duty?
You stole them from a dead man.
Here we are. I need
your name and address here -
and your signature here and here.
As well as here.
Here's a pen.
Name and address here.
- Come on.
Name and address,
signature, signature, signature.
Feel free to read it first.
I don't know where to start.
We'll take them one at a time.
Let's start with your signature here.
Can't you fall asleep?
Me neither.
I saw your light was on,
so I know you're awake.
Do you miss Mom?
She's coming home on Tuesday.
Do you remember that game
we played last time in Dad's bed?
I think I can fall asleep now.
Let's have some fun first.
When we're alone, we get
to decide when we want to sleep.
I'm tired now, Dad.
I want to go to sleep.
Excuse me,
do you have a minute?
The crematorium called. They have
a slot at 12:30 p. m. Tomorrow.
A slot?
- Yes. To cremate your father.
Would you prefer to postpone it?
- Tomorrow is fine.
Do you have any opinion
on what the deceased should wear?
No.
- Then we'll take care of that.
See you tomorrow in the chapel.
Excuse me...
Hang on a minute.
I'd like him
to be cremated in this.
A pair of pajamas?
The Minister for Climate
is an inept womanizer.
Bent Sejrø is having an affair
with Yvonne Kjær.
And Höxenhaven
has homosexual proclivities.
Several politicians are threatening
to sue Laugesen for libel.
Of most interest is that
it was Kasper Juul-
- who got hold of the vouchers...
Why are my top ministers talking
to the press without consulting us?
I can't gag them.
- Did you talk to their media advisers?
I did talk to them. Not every spin
doctor can control their politician.
When will you be in Parliament?
- At noon.
Laura, stop making that racket!
You've known for days
that the book would be out today.
11:30 a. m.
- Amir, any comment?
- No comment.
- Are the allegations true?
- He'll hear from my lawyer.
These allegations are groundless.
- We're sueing for libel.
If you do, you'll get into
a quagmire about truth value.
I don't have to prove -
that I didn't fuck every woman
in my group.
But they'll ask you. And Höx
will have to discuss whether he's gay.
I've been happily married
for 16 years.
Amir and Höx can't talk to the press.
- But someone has to.
TV1 has asked for a comment.
- You'll give them one.
Your vacation has been interrupted
by a trivial matter.
Put a stop to it now.
What about the slander
about you and Yvonne Kjær?
I did have an affair with her.
It was a right mess. But done is done.
Deny it.
If he denies it, he lends the book
value and importance.
This has to be hushed up.
- But it's in all the papers.
They all refer to Laugesen's book.
If we refrain from comment,
it will look like idle gossip.
Our strategy is not to comment.
- But we'll demand a retraction.
No retraction. If we want this
to work, we'll keep our mouths shut.
But you have to comment, Kasper.
The most serious accusation
is about you.
And the information on Hesselboe
that Laugesen got hold of.
That's damn specific. That was
what overturned the government.
I don't understand why
we should remain silent about that.
How do you feel about
Laugesen's revelations?
Very relaxed.
- Have you read it?
No, gossip doesn't interest me.
- Then why break off your vacation?
I have other things to do
than feed the press.
How about the accusations
about your spin doctor?
I was aware of the voucher case
when I rehired Kasper.
Can Kasper Juul keep his job?
- He'll make a statement to the press.
That's all I can say right now.
- Birgitte Nyborg...
Come on now.
I'm on vacation. Thank you.
I'll coordinate it with the Office
and get back to you.
Okay. Thank you.
TV1 wants me on the news.
- Do it.
We can't hush this part up
anyway.
Kasper, just so we're clear...
A media adviser must never be
a liability to the government.
I can't make political sacrifices
to save you -
so I hope you'll do a good job.
Today's menu is meatloaf.
- It looks delicious.
And it's a suitably light dish
for summer.
Laura, enough with the cell phone.
Come and eat.
It's hot, and I'm not hungry.
- Sit down.
Did you play tetherball today?
- No, I fell on the pavement.
The crybaby bawled for 10 minutes.
- Bitch.
Mind your language.
Let's have a nice dinner.
Why can Mom text when I can't?
- Because she's the PM.
How long are we staying?
Louise is having a party on Friday.
Ask your mother.
I don't know.
We'll see.
Didn't we both agree
to come here?
Yes, yes.
But it depends on
whether you have time to be with us.
You're not really here.
- What do you mean?
No!
Okay, let's go home.
Fine, let's go.
Come on, kids. Let's pack.
Can I invite Ida over tomorrow?
- Fine. Answer the phone.
Hello? Laura speaking.
Dad, it's for you.
Sascha Rousing
from some headhunter thing.
This is Phillip. Okay.
That sounds pretty damn good.
Tomorrow morning is fine.
Bye.
They're offering me a big position.
Of course I'll say no,
but I have to talk to them first.
If you like, I have some booze
for people who are camera shy.
No thanks. It's not my first time.
- No problem. It was just an offer.
Laugesen will be in
when you're done with Juul.
He'd like to talk to you on the air.
I only agreed to do this alone.
- I thought I'd give you the offer.
And now you have. Twice.
The answer is still no.
Lean back.
It's my daughter. Do you mind?
- Go ahead.
Hi, sweetie.
No, Mom is at work.
We're on in 20 seconds.
I'd like to apologize
for my behavior last time.
No problem.
It's fine.
5 seconds. 4, 3, 2, 1.
Kasper Juul,
the key figure in the case is here.
Laugesen claims that you gave him
the vouchers that toppled Hesselboe.
How did you get hold of them?
I can't comment on that.
I was led to believe
that you got them from Ole Dahl.
I can't reveal my sources. I'm sure
a journalist like you understands that.
How did Laugesen get them?
Birgitte Nyborg wanted
nothing to do with them -
but Laugesen did.
How can you defend approaching
the leader of another party with them?
I can't,
but I disagreed with her.
The vouchers proved that the PM
was abusing government money -
for private purposes.
I felt a moral obligation.
So you acted ethically.
If that's true -
I don't understand
why Nyborg fired you.
That's a widespread misconception.
I quit because of our disagreement.
We discussed the matter,
before we resumed our cooperation.
So you think you can continue
in your job?
It depends on whether you believe
an ethical person can be a spin doctor.
Thank you, Kasper Juul.
He isn't a spin doctor
for nothing.
I saw the interview.
You did well.
But then you're an ace
at telling stories.
I don't think
you understand.
You'd rather lie about everything
than look yourself in the eye.
You sound like a spoiled brat
that has never experienced -
how much shit there is
in the world. Goodbye, Katrine.
We were talking.
- So talk. I'm leaving.
Then leave. It's easier
than taking responsibility.
My father died. Okay?
- Oh, really.
Really died?
Or did he move to France again?
Hi.
- Goodness. Are you home?
I came home to change.
TV1 wants a comment from me -
about Kasper and the vouchers.
So you're having a beer
at 11 in the morning.
Are you becoming
a serious drinker?
I went to the headhunter meeting.
They asked -
if I would be the CEO of
Via Electronics in Northern Europe.
Wow!
That's a big deal.
I'm sorry.
You really deserved that.
I accepted it.
What was that?
- I took thejob.
But we agreed
that it would be impossible.
We did, but the problem was
that I wanted it.
I wanted the job.
Get it? I wanted it.
This is Kasper Juul.
Leave a message.
Hi, it's me. I wanted to talk to you
about yesterday. Give me a call.
The Prime Minister's Office.
- Katrine Fønsmark for Kasper Juul.
I'm sorry. He's not available.
He's attending a funeral.
He'll be in later.
Can I take a message?
No thank you.
Hello.
Hello?
The PM finds no cause
to take the matter further.
Kasper Juul is a trusted employee.
This case hasn't changed that.
- But you disagreed with him?
- True.
But Juul made an ethical call
and took the consequences.
And I respect that.
Isn't Mom coming home
at 11:30?
Kenneth...
You and I have to talk.
It's important that you and I
keep our little secret.
Mom won't understand.
She'd be upset and angry with you -
if she ever found out.
And you don't want
to upset Mom, do you?
Kenneth, look at me.
Do we have a deal?
Hey.
- Here comes Mom.
No more burgers for us now.
We have to be in the chapel soon.
Aren't you going to get dressed?
Mom, we have to go soon.
Get dressed so we can go.
I can't, Kenneth.
I can't.
Your mother?
- She's not coming.
Subtitles: Karen Margrete Wiin
Dansk Video Tekst