We're all very professional.
We must admit when we're wrong.
I became a politician because I know
what the world should be like.
My father died.
- Really? Or did he move to France?
You don't get it. If you told me
the truth, I would do anything for you.
I went to the headhunter meeting.
They asked -
if I would be CEO
of Via Electronics.
I'm sorry. You deserved that.
- I took thejob.
"You won't know what hit you before
it's too late" - American Arms Maker
Congratulations, Phillip. Well done.
We'll miss you.
Here, honey.
- Thanks.
Now we, Phillip's students,
would like to say a few words.
We wrote a speech -
called 'Ten Things
We Will Miss about Phillip'.
Number 1. We will miss
your fantastic lectures.
Few people can make
international finance exciting -
but you could.
Number 2. We will miss
how good your ass looks in jeans.
Number 3. We will miss the
great expectations you have for us.
It has been extremely inspiring.
Yes, Kasper?
- When are you coming in?
Defense needs a press release
approved on the new fighters.
I'll be there in half an hour.
- Super.
All your support when we don't
know why we took this course.
And finally,
we'll miss your nice ass -
after we see it
for the last time -
but we're sure we'll see it again
on the front page of the newspapers.
Congratulations.
A toast to Phillip.
Cheers. Thank you.
Here is the press release
from Defense.
The ministries aren't pleased about
you approving all press releases.
When was that rule adopted?
- While you were away.
That's incapacitation.
Höxenhaven held an unauthorized
conference about the wire tap -
and then Laugesen's book
caused embarrassing reverberations.
What does it say?
Hans Christian Thorsen recommends
the F26 Defender -
because it's the best on the market,
and our allies have chosen it.
The total investment
has been raised by DKK 10bn...
Stop. 10 billion?
- Military hardware is expensive.
Could you be more specific?
- The total cost has risen.
But it's definitely
the right type of fighter.
No. The two other were cheaper.
Withhold the press release.
The minister will have to account
for choosing the most expensive one.
Anders, give me the material
on all three fighters.
I'll go through them.
This won't go down well.
The Ministry of Defense
has struggled with this for a month.
What's up with her?
GOVERNMENT
Episode 9- Divide and Rule
Today's top story is that we finally
figured out which fighter to buy.
The press release is on its way.
The Minister of Defense is coming in.
Katrine, are you prepared?
- Yes. It will be the F26 Defender.
That will give industry DKK 9bn
in orders.
I have to take this.
- What's your angle?
Is it the best one for pilots
or for business?
"I'm afraid of the big, strong men
and cars honking in traffic. "
Our approach isn't that Denmark
should be a demilitarized hick country.
I don't get it.
- There's another angle.
New fighters give Danish companies
big business.
Yes! Let's all be spin doctors.
Strike a balance between a conspiracy
theory and hooray forjournalism.
I need some kick-ass pictures.
- It'll be pure 'Top Gun'.
We need to interview pilots.
- I'm going to Skrydstrup.
I'll be in the cockpit.
- Congratulations. Perfect.
That was the Ministry of Defense.
There'll be no press release today.
Why not?
- The usual. Details to iron out.
Now what, Friis?
- Right. Now what?
We bump up the story
about the bank managers' salary.
How come you have time for lunch?
Because your Minister of Defense
can't decide which fighter to buy.
You're not surprised.
So the PM is involved?
I didn't say a word.
- She's awfully busy these days.
She is the PM.
"We're all very professional. "
That's a quote from your boss.
I watched the party leader debate.
You flipped
when she deviated from the script.
"I think we should be who we are.
We can still be good politicians. "
Does that still apply to her?
- Again, no comment.
What about your father?
Still no comment on that?
There's nothing to say.
He's dead.
You didn't say a word when he was
cremated. You haven't said a word.
People are often quiet
when they've lost someone.
I thought we should talk about it.
- No.
Your father was cremated in a chapel.
It was just you and me.
It's hard to believe
he was a big businessman in France.
Tell me about him.
- No.
Didn't you like him?
Did you?
Kasper, did you like your father?
My father was a nasty, little wuss.
He lived a boring life in Korsør.
A godforsaken city. That's it.
Why did you lie about him?
- Because I hated my life with him!
So I made up stories about a life
I would have preferred.
I've seen a psychologist.
I know all the interpretations.
I can't take any more.
'THE FUTURE OF THE MILITARY'
'DENMARK'S NEED FOR FIGHTERS'
Do you really have to read that?
- What?
Can't someone summarize it for you?
- Yes.
I'm going to bed now.
- Goodnight, honey.
Goodnight, Birgitte.
Sleep well.
The F26 Defender is the next
generation from Triton Technologies.
It is built to deliver both
air-to-air and air-to-ground -
- thanks to its state-of-the-art bomb
and missile systems.
The stealth technology allows it
to strike without being noticed.
You won't know what hit you
before it's too late.
Thank you.
Hans Christian, will you go first?
- Gladly.
The future image of the enemy
indicates that we need aircraft -
that can't be picked up
on our present radar.
The F26 Defender is the only fighter
that meets this demand.
The literature says that the Defender
is the only one not in the air.
So there's a risk
of technical teething troubles.
The Triton factory
guarantees that won't happen.
Factories always say that.
Several analyses indicate
that soon radar systems -
will be able to trace
the Defender's stealth technology.
Who knows what the future will bring?
So let's concentrate on the present.
Bent, we approved new planes.
- You know more than I do.
But we need to justify
spending DKK 130bn.
Defense Command Denmark
has worked on this for years.
With all due respect, you have
purchased many things by mistake.
APCs that tipped over,
faulty helicopters -
and drones that never took flight.
We'll put it on the back burner
and check it out.
Gentlemen...
Bent?
Yes?
Do we have a meeting?
- No.
And I'm not here
as your Minister for Finance.
I'm here as your friend.
Do you have a minute?
Birgitte,
you need to see the big picture.
Be careful you don't get lost
in all the details.
DKK 130bn isn't a detail.
- Yes, in the big picture.
Thorsen is your Defense Minister.
- That's not reassuring.
He's in the military's pocket.
Take the CIA flights over Greenland.
If you take responsibility for
everything, it all falls back on you.
No PM can take that in the long run.
The Romans called it 'divide and rule'.
Let your ministers do their work.
If they screw up,
you can fire them.
In my experience, there's often
something to be said about it.
What if something happens
in the Ministry of Health?
Will you decide who is to run
the University Hospital?
Let the Ministry of Defense
buy those damn fighters.
Let's move on. Negotiations
have been ongoing for 7-8 years.
You happen to be the PM now
when the order was to be given.
Yes, and that will reflect on me.
Christ!
You have to trust the experts.
But I can't, Bent.
Then tell me something.
Who will be prime minister
while you do all ourjobs?
I thought you had quit. Again.
- Yes, so did I.
The press release arrived.
They chose the Defender.
The minister will be here
on the news at 6 p. m.
So we'll do what we agreed on.
- Of course.
I requested disclosure from Defense
Command about the selection process.
Christ! At least ten employees
dream of having yourjob.
They want to be on camera,
but they don't have what it takes.
Let them do theirjob.
Have faith that they can do it well.
I'd like a car home now.
Yes, I signed my contract yesterday,
but I won't start till next month -
so I have time to read everything.
Yes, but listen.
I have to go now.
Okay. Fine then.
Thank you.
Bye.
- This sucks, Phillip.
Your firm delivered for EUR 5 billion
won'th of hardware for the Defender.
So what? We're subcontractors
to another subcontractor.
Your hardware will be in the fighters
that my administration is buying.
You'll make money on my decision.
- Birgitte, you're seeing ghosts.
Via Electronics
isn't a partner of Triton.
We're just subcontractors.
We'll make peanuts
in comparison to the size of the order.
It's really not a problem.
Believe me.
Okay.
I'll just run it by Kasper.
It corresponds to you
buying gas for your state car -
- and Phillip happens to be
the CEO of the gas company.
So the press won't give us hell?
- No, your government is exemplary.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I promise you.
Thank you, Kasper.
You might have saved my marriage.
Don't forget to see Thorsen.
- I won't. Bye.
Most of our NATO allies
have bought the Defender.
That's an advantage
in all our international operations.
Danish industry will benefit
from the counter-purchases -
by the Triton factories.
Was that an incentive?
No, but is it a bad thing
that industry makes money?
Is it the best fighter for our pilots
or the best for Danish industry?
It's the best fighter.
I'd like to reiterate that...
Katrine, wrap it up after his answer.
It's a question of national security.
- Thank you for coming.
The purchase of new fighters
is part of the new Defense Agreement.
Now you've learned a bit
about fighters, little girl.
Back to the studio.
That's a wrap, Katrine.
The minister is hiding something.
- What could it be?
Something's not right.
- Or didn't you like 'little girl'?
Thorsen is army and a chauvinist.
That's refreshing.
Why is an army guy interested in what
industry gets out of buying fighters?
I see where you're going,
but believe me, there's nothing there.
Morning. Is this true?
- We're checking it out.
Get the Minister of Defense
in my office in an hour.
Friis,
Hanne Holm has documented -
that the Defense Minister went
on six hunting trips paid by Triton.
Holm is a watchdog for corruption.
Isn't that a good thing?
- Yes. It's a damn good thing.
Danes aren't interested in hearing
about ministers' expensive habits.
Grouse hunting is very exclusive.
It costs 25,000 per person per day.
Plus room and board.
- Let's get Thorsen in the studio.
Let Research find other participants.
- Yes, Dad.
Here are the files
from Defense Command.
Thanks.
That was pretty damn quick.
What's that?
- I told you I requested disclosure.
Katrine, you're a well-paid anchor.
You're not here to do research.
I know,
but I already requested them.
Is 'the little girl' still bothered
about Thorsen's comment?
Do I look like a sensitive person?
Defense Command, Lars Bang.
- Katrine Fønsmark, TV1 News.
Some documents are missing
from the files.
I'm sorry, but our archives have been
moved and aren't quite in order.
When will they be available?
- I don't know.
But you're welcome to visit
with any specific questions.
Great. When?
- How about right now?
I'm a big fan of your work.
You're very good.
Thank you.
When will the archives be in order?
I don't know, but perhaps
we can answer your questions.
We'd very much like to help.
It's this way.
Here are the tenders. The Chief of
Defense has taken time off to be here.
Thank you, Lars. The Defender has
key qualities, which led to our choice.
I'm not asking about
technical details.
But they determined
our choice.
I'm interested in the decision process.
Is it true that you attended meetings
in Scotland with the minister?
Correct.
It was part of my job
as Minister of Defense.
The meetings in Scotland
were of a technical nature.
Including eight-course dinners
and hunting trips.
Traveling is a necessary evil
in my job.
What's wrong with investigating
the fighters before we invest 120bn?
130bn.
Has the press seen these?
The agendas from the trip?
Can you give me details
of the meetings and trips?
Among other things, we were
informed about the weapons systems.
Is it true that expensive
hunting trips were included?
I must admit that I wasn't very
interested in the expense account.
How much hunting was there
compared to work?
A total of four hours of meetings
in three days.
The rest was hunting and meals.
Fried foie gras accompanied by
a 1998 Romanée-Conti. Christ!
I didn't organize the trips.
- No.
Despite your dislike of traveling,
the fine dining must have suited you.
I'm told that hunting trips like that
can cost 25,000 per person.
Did you have any qualms
over accepting that trip?
Good gracious, my dear.
Triton is a huge enterprise.
The amount was insignificant.
And I can assure you that nothing
covert happened at Glen Farlan.
Glen Farlan?
One of the estates where we met.
- May I see the agendas?
No.
If journalists want to see the agenda,
I can spill coffee on the right places.
What is your name?
- Henrik Mikkelsen.
Listen, Henrik Mikkelsen.
Don't ever take that tone with me -
if you want to keep yourjob.
Is that clear?
Hans Christian,
is there anything else I should know?
No.
Good.
Thank you.
Sorry we couldn't be more helpful.
- You were a great help.
Glen Farlan.
John McCoy speaking.
My name is Katrine Fønsmark.
I'm a Danish journalist at TV1.
I'm calling to ask about a guest.
- Sorry, we don't talk to journalists.
Hello? Jeff Carlyle.
- Katrine Fønsmark from Danish TV1.
John McCoy just gave me
your number.
How can I help you?
Are you the hunting guide
at Glen Farlan?
No! Some other time.
Jesus Christ!
I talked to an employee
at the estate in Scotland.
He told me something
very interesting.
Thorsen received two hunting rifles
won'th DKK 250,000 from Triton.
Jesus.
Can we document it?
What should I do?
- You're asking me?
Jesus! This is new.
It suits you.
Tell the ministry you're changing
the premise of the interview.
It will also be about the gifts
the Defense Minister received.
If they complain,
tell them we know about the guns.
But he can still cover his ass.
Otherwise he might refuse to answer,
and the interview will be useless.
Be glad I'm not chewing you out
for investigative journalism.
Is that because I made a scoop?
This conversation is over. Go!
We're doing our best to find
the best solution for the Air Force.
This is a matter
of national security.
So your decision wasn't influenced
by Triton's expensive hunting trips?
No, not at all.
- Did you also receive a gift?
That's true.
When a minister travels...
Let's hear a comment from
Jeff Carlisle from the estate.
The Danish minister received a pair
of guns with his name engraved.
- What kind of guns?
- A pair of Purdey shotguns.
- Do you know the price of them?
- About 25,000 pounds.
An expensive gift.
A minister receives official gifts,
but they belong to the ministry.
But when your name is engraved,
they must be personal.
Yes. When I realized the mistake,
I returned them.
When did you realize that?
- I don't recall.
You don't recall when you saw
your name on guns won'th 250,000?
No.
I believe I answered that question.
- Katrine, wrap it up.
Today? Yesterday? A week ago?
- I couldn't say.
End it, Katrine.
- Thank you for coming.
Super, Katrine.
The little girl learned
a bit about shotguns today.
Hans Christian, for fuck's sake!
You said you told me everything.
But on the news I hear
you received an expensive shotgun.
An oversight.
As long as Hans Christian
wasn't caught telling a blatant lie...
When did you return the guns?
- Earlier today.
Okay. It's vital that Thorsen
is brief and precise with the press.
It's a regrettable misunderstanding.
That's all.
We'll lay down a strategy
for the other ministries.
This is extremely problematic.
It taints the government.
I hope you can see that.
- I assure you, this is the end of it.
What good is that?
You've said that before. Thank you.
I'll let myself out.
- You'll be hearing from me.
What did I tell you?
- Forget Thorsen.
If you fire him,
you'll be in the spotlight.
We chose the fighter,
and the Opposition is content.
What do you suggest?
- Let him be. He closed the case.
There's something else
we have to discuss.
It's a more serious matter.
Phillip's new job.
You said it wasn't a problem.
- That was before this Thorsen thing.
The press are out to get us. The good
girl's government has dirty hands.
My colleagues
in other ministries say -
that the press smells blood.
Even a subcontractor to
a subcontractor would be enough.
There must be a countermove.
- Not the way I see it.
So far you've been squeaky clean.
It would be a scoop -
if they find something on you.
Nothing is trivial anymore.
They're going for thejugular.
It's a mechanism
that has nothing to do with reality.
What exactly are you saying?
I don't see how Phillip
can keep thatjob.
Hi.
You're home late.
- Phillip, we have to talk.
What?
We can't control this any longer.
Can't control what?
The Defense Minister's gifts
have made the press smell blood.
And?
- They'll dig up everything.
Everything.
Birgitte, I don't get it.
I'm terribly sorry,
but you can't take that job.
But I already took it.
What are you talking about?
They'll use it against me.
Even the smallest mistake
can bring down the government.
The deal was made
long before I took the job.
But the press
doesn't see it that way.
Your company will make money
on a decision I made.
I already took thejob!
It's been in the financial papers!
Do you realize how embarrassing
it would be to resign?
I understand how you feel
and your frustration.
Don't talk to me like
some HR person.
You're firing me because
you can't fire your Defense Minister.
The future of the government
is at stake.
We can't afford
that they find any fault with me.
No.
My husband can't take thatjob.
- Can you have a husband at all?
Kasper wrote a draft of a press release
that Via Electronics should send out.
Very nice indeed.
It's my idea to quit -
because I don't want to undermine
the PM's credibility.
What a great husband you have.
I have to know if...
- I'll quit.
But don't fucking count on me
lifting another finger for you.
Where are you going?
Will the PM fire Thorsen?
- No way.
Not in the middle
of a Defense Agreement.
All the other stations want
the clip of Thorsen.
Well done on the interview.
Have you talked to Research?
We're going through all
the government's meetings, trips, etc.
Excellent. Can we get the PM
to come in for an interview?
I've tried to contact her, but
we can only get the Defense Minister.
We could have Katrine call
her good friend Kasper Juul.
You said you like being
a investigative reporter.
Yes.
- Good. That's a deal.
The only solution is to keep
our mouths shut till this blows over.
No comment to the press.
It's like infidelity:
Deny, deny, deny.
What if we're like an open book?
We make diaries available.
Lists of gifts. Travel agendas.
Put everything on the net.
- It's a dangerous road.
Because the ministers will see it
as control on your part -
with the Danish people
as witnesses.
It's the people who voted for them.
- It'll be unpopular in the cabinet.
Can you put up with openness?
- Yes.
Phillip is resigning.
It's being released today.
How did he take it?
The after-school center called.
Your son hasn't been picked up.
And we can't contact your husband.
He must be running late.
This one is 388%.
I've done the first three.
Can you do the rest?
- Yes.
Where is Dad?
He's very busy these days.
The Defense Minister
has apologized.
It'sjust a misunderstanding -
- that shouldn't prevent the military
from getting their fighter.
The New Conservatives
can claim a lot of credit for that.
Hi, Kasper.
- The New Conservatives like us.
Yvonne agreed to vote for the budget
if she got 600m for the armed forces.
You can go on the news tomorrow
and present your plan for openness.
I'm helping Laura with her homework.
See you tomorrow.
How do find the average?
- Let me see your equation.
Okay. That's far too much.
Hi, Dad. Fine.
We're doing homework.
Or Mom is doing my homework.
Ask him where he is.
- Yes, pizza and coke.
He's out playing.
I'm here to see Kasper Juul.
- Go on in.
Hi.
See you.
- Bye.
My boss thinks I should make
professional use of our relationship.
Then let's keep it that way.
Coffee?
Just water, please.
You can have an interview
with the PM after all.
Birgitte Nyborg wants to be
totally open from now on.
So all diaries, travel agendas
and meetings will be on the net.
Thorsen has made life difficult
for Birgitte Nyborg.
She must be under a lot of pressure.
Did you watch the news today?
- I reported it.
Yvonne Kjær clearly stated that
the government isn't under pressure.
The cabinet will be transparent.
And Nyborg will say that
in the interview. What about Thorsen?
She has nothing to add
to the Defense Minister's comments.
I thought there'd be a catch.
- You get your interview.
And we have an opportunity to explain
our openness to you exclusively.
And the only catch is:
We could give the interview
to some otherjournalist.
Hi, Bent.
- Hi, Laura.
Thank you for coming.
I can't leave the children alone.
Would you like some coffee?
- Please.
Tomorrow I'm presenting
my suggestion about openness.
I've sent e-mails.
- Indeed.
The cabinet will be furious,
including me.
What's going on, Birgitte?
Reporters are lining up
to find dirt on us.
No, what's up with you
and your family? Where's Phillip?
Listen. Will you help me
convince the cabinet?
Where is Phillip?
- He won't answer his phone.
I even called our friends.
No one knows where he is.
Don't do that.
I'll just start crying.
I had to ask him
to resign his position.
He looked forward to that job.
- It's a terrible contradiction.
In Parliament we fight for the modern
family where both parents work.
But for an MP's marriage to work,
the spouse has to stay at home.
Is he having an affair?
- No.
Laura, I have to go to Parliament.
I'll be back soon.
Will you watch Magnus?
- Yes.
Call me if you need me.
- Okay. Goodnight.
Hi, Freja.
May I come in for a minute?
Thank you.
What's going on?
I'm sorry. I thought...
I'm terribly sorry.
Mom, it's late.
We have to get up now.
Mom?
- Coming.
I don't have any clean underwear.
Where are Magnus' trunks?
Why does he need them?
- He goes swimming on Fridays.
We're out of milk.
- Okay.
When is Dad coming home?
Good morning, Kasper.
- Are you on your way?
No, we're having breakfast.
- You're on the news at 8:30 p. m.
I'll be there in half an hour.
We can talk then. Bye.
Magnus! Time to get up.
The interview with the PM
is our top story.
Did you see that Phillip Christensen
resigned from Via Electronics?
Yes, but I promised the PM
that we'd only talk about openness.
And you know that Via Electronics has
delivered hardware for the Defender.
Nyborg's transparency in government
is affecting her own husband.
So what's the story?
- The great personal sacrifice.
Ask for permission
before asking private questions.
And we need to know before 1 p. m.
- I'll call them now.
I won't talk about my private life.
It's not a bad idea
to give it a personal angle.
Did you hear what I said?
- Yes.
Is everything okay?
I talked to Kasper Juul
about the interview.
No questions of a private nature.
- Why did you talk to Kasper?
Because it's important to the PM
that we stick to our agreement.
So he talked to the little girl's boss.
It shows that we're on to something.
- Yes, but a deal's a deal.
No mention of private matters.
- But it isn't private.
The government's demand
for openness is a big diversion -
that prevents Nyborg's
husband from keeping his job.
The Defense Minister's mess has
consequences for the PM's husband.
That's a clever analysis,
but where do you want to take it?
I want to get the story back on track.
Our Minister of Defense is corrupt.
Forget it.
- All this openness is a diversion.
Should her husband pay the price?
- Do not mention her private life.
This story isn't won'th
making an enemy of the PM's Office.
If he hadn't quit,
you could have fired away.
But that isn't the case.
- I strongly disagree.
And you're welcome to.
Here's confirmation
from the PM's Office.
If you're still in doubt, shout it
from the rooftops. We're used to it.
Fine, Kasper.
See you later.
Take your shoes off.
- You're not my mother.
Just take them off.
- Be nice, you two.
I'm on the news tonight,
so Trine will make dinner.
Hi, kids.
Hi. Did you miss me?
- What do you think?
Hello, gorgeous.
Hi.
Go up to Laura's room
while I talk to Mom.
I won't be long.
Where have you been?
Why didn't you call me back?
I talked to Freja.
You're damn lucky
she didn't go to the press.
I know.
But I was frightened, Phillip.
You can't disappear for days.
It scares me.
It made me think
you were with someone else.
I was.
I was so fucking angry with you
and your damn job.
So I...
I felt like breaking something
and...
Birgitte...
Christ, Birgitte.
Are you okay?
Mom, what happened?
- I tripped over my bag.
My God, I'm clumsy.
I need to clean up.
Did I frighten you, sweetie?
- How about some tea?
Are we ready for the news?
Wait. Stop.
Do we cancel?
- No, we can't.
What the hell happened?
Make something up.
Torben, this is Kasper Juul.
The PM took a fall.
We need your best make-up artist
if we're going to do this interview.
Good. Bye.
Are you okay?
- No.
Can you do it?
- I'll be fine.
Let's go.
Welcome to TV1 News. Tonight's
guest is our Prime Minister.
Can you conceal it?
- Not completely.
But you'll look fine.
Can you make sure that the PM
is only shot from the right?
I'll talk to the cameramen.
- And no one else comes in here.
Is that clear, 1 and 3?
- Only from her right side.
Katrine, stand on the other side.
Okay. Hi.
Welcome.
And thank you for coming.
Four seconds.
- 3, 2, 1...
My guest today is
Prime Minister Birgitte Nyborg.
Pan out. Not too close.
You're showing your hand. Diaries
and gift lists are going on the net.
Why do you find it necessary
to be open?
We have a responsibility
to the voters.
They mustn't lose confidence in us.
The initiative for more openness
isn't a new idea.
The Defense Minister's travels made
it necessary to speed the process up.
Will there be any repercussions
for the Defense Minister?
I consider it a slip-up
that he has apologized for.
He has the support of Parliament.
I see no reason to pursue it further.
Will the rest of the cabinet
have to pay for his slip-up -
since they'll be
constantly monitored?
No one is being punished here.
The public needs to know
what the politicians are doing.
That's only fair. This administration
has nothing to hide.
Katrine, wrap it up.
Yesterday there was a press release -
stating that Phillip Christensen
has resigned as CEO of a company.
Is that correct?
- Yes.
Katrine, stop!
- Sorry. Technical difficulties.
What the hell?
- She took off her earpiece.
Would your husband have resigned
had you not been forced -
to speed up
the process of openness?
Has your husband not paid
a high price for Thorsen's slip-up?
The consequences of
my administration's decisions -
do affect my own life,
just like any other Dane's life.
And that's the way it should be.
My husband and I aren't above
other citizens in this country.
My husband made the decision
to resign himself -
when the Defender
was decided on.
I'm very grateful
that I can count on him.
Damn, she's good.
Also when it comes down to giving
up something you're pleased about.
I'm very grateful.
Would he have made that decision
without this new openness?
Yes. It's a matter of my husband
not profiting by my politics...
At least as long
as he's married to me.
Thank you.
Now for the weather forecast.
Who the hell do you think you are?
- What do you mean?
You took off your earpiece.
- There was an echo.
Shut the fuck up.
An echo?
Was it a good interview?
It isn't about that.
You didn't stick to our agreement.
The PM's office will formally complain
to the director tomorrow.
I'm sick of being told off by you.
I've had enough!
Now you listen to me!
You have four weeks of vacation.
Clear your desk and go on vacation.
Think about whether
you're part of this team or not.
I'm very sorry
that question was asked.
But know this.
You were absolutely fantastic.
That really hit home.
- Great, Kasper.
See you tomorrow.
I'd like to go home now.
Hi.
I talked to the kids.
They're asleep.
Could you see my eye on TV?
No, not at all.
I'm so sorry about what happened.
I'm coming home.
We can talk and find a solution.
With you as head of negotiations?
- Stop it, Phillip.
The kids are counting on one of us
being here in the morning.
So if you want to come home -
I'll spend the night
at a friend's house.
What?
Why won't you talk to me?
Because...
We don't talk, Birgitte.
That was something
we used to do.
I'll spend the night here.
There's been a change of plans.
I'm not going home after all.
Do you want to go back
to the office?
No.
Take me to Marienborg.
Subtitles: Karen Margrete Wiin
Dansk Video Tekst