- This is my friend Wade Campbell.
- She's so British.
- We're a little more than friends.
- Good to meet you.
- Mackenzie: I'm sorry.
- No, this is exactly what was supposed to happen.
You two have broken up four times
and gotten together five times,
so there must be
a strong connection.
- Was that sarcastic?
- No.
You guys obviously
have something.
My suggestion is
stop breaking up.
Learn how to have a fight.
Lisa, are you still there?
That was him.
Will: The Tea Party
is being radicalized
and their original
principles obliterated.
The health care law
hasn't taken effect yet.
TARP was signed into law
by George W. Bush.
He's gonna tone it down
or I'm gonna fire him.
You'd manufacture
a reason to do it?
I've got a really good job,
Charlie.
In six weeks I haven't heard
anything from the 44th floor.
- How are they with this?
- Good. Good.
I'll tell you when there's
something to worry about.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
Hey.
I thought I saw you sneak in.
- You look nice.
- Thanks. So do you.
Oh, yeah.
I was at a party at Bloomberg's.
But you came here to be with
your News Night family at midnight.
Well, near them, anyway.
- Can I ask a favor?
- Yeah.
Can Wade have
two minutes with you?
He's got some facts
he wants to share.
- Sure.
- You don't mind?
No problem.
Wade?
- Happy New Year.
Oh, and Jim's putting together
the packet of stories you asked him to.
You want to give it five
minutes a night next week?
- Let's look at the stories first.
- Done.
I'll leave you guys alone.
- How have you been?
- I've been good, thanks.
- And I appreciate you taking a minute.
- What can I do for you?
You know I'm an assistant US attorney
for the southern district, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, right now,
my job's prosecuting
financial crime.
Well, you know, Wade,
feel free to start any time.
You've been pretty rough on us.
Countrywide?
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
You've got guys flooding
the market with bad mortgages,
lying to investors,
making billions of dollars,
but most incredibly,
discussing it by email.
I don't mean to insult you, man,
but how do you not get a fraud conviction?
Right there's what
I'm talking about.
This is the half of the story
you're leaving out.
- Are you ready for me to blow your mind?
- Gary: Sure.
- Bigfoot's real.
- Jim: No, it's not.
- Gary: Did you say--
- Bigfoot is real.
- No, it's not.
- Listen to me, skeptismo.
There are 1.7 million
known species on the planet,
and biologists estimate
this represents
only a quarter of the total
species on the planet.
The other three quarters
are microscopic.
- How do you know?
- I don't know.
But if the other three
quarters were Bigfoot,
they wouldn't be hard to see.
They'd be walking up and down the street.
We're gonna step
slowly away now.
Don't mention this to anyone
unless you know them really well.
- And even then.
- Pandas were thought to be a myth until 1869.
Gorillas were thought
to be a myth until 1902.
The giant squid was thought
to be a myth until 2004.
- What's up?
- Maggie, listen to me.
Apex predators--
species at the top of the food chain--
have the smallest numbers
and move in the tiniest packs.
Is this Bigfoot?
Species diversity is greatest
in the rain forests.
Stop. Just don't even--
Stop.
What are you doing?
Trying to work.
- Do you see there's a party happening around you?
- I'm okay.
Sometimes it's hard to tell
who the biggest nerd in the office is.
- Could there be an apex predator primate--
- Not today, though.
Kaylee.
You guys haven't met
Kaylee yet.
Is this a new girlfriend?
- Girlfriend's a strong word.
- Really?
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- Kaylee: Get me drunk.
- Neal: Done.
Boom!
- Come on, join the party.
- I will.
I just want to finish
this for Will.
- What is it?
- Stories we missed this year
or didn't give
enough attention to.
- Want some help?
- Sure.
Yeah, take this stack here
- and anything you think is--
- Anything we missed.
Jim: Or didn't give
enough attention to.
Bigfoot's real and
I don't think anyone reported it.
- Hey, Don.
- Jim: Circle it.
You look really nice tonight.
- Yeah?
- God, definite-- Yes.
Yeah. Definitely.
- Yeah, I don't mean to be--
- Shoot, Don's here.
- I'm sorry.
- It's no problem. I was almost done.
Well, don't, you know--
- Take a couple hours off.
- I will.
Will you?
'Cause it's a party.
Have you ever been to one?
I have been to
over three of them.
Maggie.
See you later.
- Oh, man. Look at you.
- You look at me.
I had to get a crew off the clock.
Did I miss anything?
Neal won't rest until
he gets Will to do a story on Bigfoot.
Did Bigfoot do something?
Bigfoot can't do anything.
He's not real.
That's what they said
about the moon landing.
I believe you've
had a cocktail.
Men have cocktails.
Carrie Bradshaw has drinks.
Nope, the other way around.
Doesn't matter.
I'm fun Don tonight.
I love fun Don.
- Where have I seen this dress before?
- On Lisa.
- She let me raid her closet.
- I think you should never take it off.
Except when you take it off.
Now, speaking of your roommate,
I had a great idea.
- Soundproofing her bedroom?
- Fixing her up with Jim.
Are you kidding?
I feel like I owe him one.
Then why would you
unleash Lisa on him?
- They'll get along.
- She works in a boutique.
- Here she is. Lisa.
- Wait, don't.
This is the worst
fix-up ever.
I'm not talking about
having him take a bride.
- I'm talking about starting off the new year...
- Getting him laid.
- With a bang.
- ...with a bang. See what I did?
- You made it.
- Yeah.
Am I wearing a huge sign
that says dateless on New Year's Eve?
- No, but that dress sends a message loud and clear.
- Do I look slutty?
- Absolutely. In the best way.
- No. Don!
I wasn't going for slutty.
I was going for--
♪ If you want my body and you think I'm sexy ♪
♪ Come on, sugar,
let me know. ♪
I like Rod Stewart.
Yeah. So,
I've got a guy for you.
- No, you don't.
- A guy here?
- Yeah.
- No.
Is it another loser
that doesn't have a date
on New Year's Eve?
- He's not a loser.
- Yes, he's a huge loser.
- What the hell is going on?
She works in fashion, Don.
No offense, Lis.
I don't even know what
I'm supposed to be offended by.
But I can talk about other things.
I don't have to talk about fashion.
- I know you can.
- Give me a topic.
What's happening with
the Greek debt crisis?
There's a huge crisis
in Greece.
- They're in a lot of debt.
- See?
- Are you serious?
- That's more than most people know.
You see the guy over there?
The cute, sweet-looking puppy dog guy
- with the stupid look on his face?
- He is cute.
- Why is he working?
- He has a job.
So right there,
he's a leg up on your usual diet.
His name's Jim Harper.
He's a senior producer.
He's a bright guy.
He's not the creative director
for an imaginary Internet start-up.
He calls his mother.
I'm sure he's nice,
but I don't think I'm in the mood for a fix-up.
- Why not?
- I don't know, I'm just coming off a relationship.
Of 10 days. I've bought milk
before your relationship started
- that was still good to drink after it ended.
- I don't think so.
No, it's true.
I can show you the milk.
She doesn't need to be fixed up,
honey.
I didn't say that she
needed to be fixed up.
No guy wants to be fixed up
10 minutes before midnight.
Besides, I'm not his type.
I can tell.
You're everybody's type.
You're the girl next door. Let's go.
Next door to what?
- Jimmy Olsen.
- That nickname's really gonna stick, huh?
It has endured. It's a compliment.
Jimmy Olsen was a go-getter.
Yeah, but strictly speaking,
he was a photojournalist.
In fact, when DC Comics
first introduced--
Yeah, shut up.
This is Maggie's roommate Lisa.
Oh, hey.
It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
- I've heard a lot about you.
I've heard a lot about--
Not a lot.
Maggie's--
She's mentioned you once, I think.
Lisa went to Parsons
and she works at a very high-end
boutique in the Village.
- Nice.
- So why don't you take Lisa out onto the terrace
where you can watch one million
people in Times Square
waiting for the world's
biggest nonevent?
Maggie and I are going to get some drinks
and we'll meet you out there.
- Jim has to work.
- Not at 11:50 on New Year's Eve.
Grab some coats.
- Tess.
- Yeah?
Kill me.
Kill me now.
- Do it now.
- Huh?
Congress cut our investigations
to 20% of what they promised.
We were supposed
to get 165 million.
But after rolling over to the GOP,
they only gave us 30.
- How's it going in here?
- Good.
Wade says the House cut 80%
of the DOJ's budget
- to fight financial crime.
- He was just telling me.
For every one of me
the Justice Department can hire,
the banks can hire 20
and afford to stay in litigation forever.
You think Big Tobacco
throws money at this shit?
Meet Goldman.
Meet Lehman.
Meet B of A.
And meet Countrywide.
Honey, are you saying the United States
of America is getting out-lawyered?
Don't call him honey.
It makes me crazy.
I didn't say that.
It came out of my mouth. Just words.
Yes, we are getting
out-lawyered.
That is a story we're missing.
Let me talk to Mac a second.
- All right?
- Great.
- I'll be outside.
You can't have your boyfriends
lobbying me to go easier on them.
Hang on, he wasn't lobbying for you to go easier.
He was pitching a story.
I've got a staff of paid
professionals to do that.
Mostly by using
inside sources like Wade.
And it's not boyfriends.
It's one boyfriend.
- So he's your boyfriend?
- I guess he is.
- I mean, that's what you call him?
- I call him Wade.
- When you introduce him, do you say--
- Yes!
How do you introduce the Netflix queue
of crazy divorced women
with digitally remastered breasts
you spend your nights with?
You see anyone
with me right now?
Of course not.
If you'd asked someone out on New Year's Eve,
that would mean you
were in a real relationship.
Oh, please. Please tell me more
about real relationships.
I'm not keeping myself
in jail anymore.
- What does that mean?
- He's my boyfriend.
We're serious.
I want a partner.
That is so romantic.
I'd set it to music.
- Look.
- I'm glad you're letting yourself out of jail.
- I meant--
- You owe it to yourself.
Congress defunded the DOJ
on financial crime.
I thought you'd want
to hear that.
I did.
Come on out to the party.
I will.
All right.
Fuck it.
- Nice tux.
- I just came from a different party.
- Was it good?
- Have you ever been to a good New Year's Eve party?
- No.
- I've never enjoyed myself on December 31st.
No one ever has.
I can tell you for me,
there was this one time
in 10th grade--
This is my thing
I'm talking about now.
Okay.
Why don't you talk to someone?
I don't need a therapist,
I just don't like New Year's Eve.
No, I'm saying
why don't you go up to someone
here at the party and talk to them?
- Do people really do that?
- Talk to people?
- Just walk up to them.
- I've seen it on TV.
That woman over there,
she's obviously here alone
and I'm getting
a good feeling about her.
You have good instincts
about these things?
I'm opening up to you.
I'm not good at this.
That's really sweet, Will.
You should let more people--
Yeah, yeah, yeah, what do I do?
Walk up to her
and introduce yourself.
- I'm gonna do it.
- You should.
- I'm gonna go talk to her.
- Talk to her.
- I'm going.
- Okay, but you're still standing here.
- Here I go.
- Haven't moved.
Shut up.
- Hi. Excuse me.
- Am I in your way?
No, I just wanted
to introduce myself.
- I'm Will McAvoy.
- I know that.
I'm Nina Howard.
I don't know what to do now.
- Did you come over to talk to me?
- Yes.
All right.
How'd you get in here?
I'm a friend of one of the producers
on ACN Morning.
Day side. Uh-oh.
Oh, day side and prime time
don't get along?
Jets and the Sharks.
Well, maybe we could
be like Tony and Maria.
Why is Will talking
to Nina Howard?
- You know who she is?
- She's a gossip columnist for TMI.
Oh, he shouldn't be
talking to her.
- I know. Why is he?
- I may have suggested it.
- Why?
- You were here with Wade and he seemed lonely.
Excuse me.
- Hi.
- I'm so sorry.
- Can I talk to you a moment?
- Really?
- Yeah.
- She wants to warn you that I'm a gossip columnist.
Oh, that's not it.
I promise.
- She's a gossip columnist.
- No, she writes features.
TMI had Jennifer Aniston
on the cover this week.
You know who they had last week?
Jennifer Aniston.
- Know who they had the week before?
- Are you a subscriber?
They have it at my nail place.
- Oh, do you go to Cuti-cles?
- Yes.
- Ba-Ling?
- I'm walking away from this.
- No, Will.
Yeah, my instincts
may have been wrong.
It's New Year's Eve.
I don't care if she writes for Mein Kampf.
Really?
You're setting up my boyfriend?
- Not my boyfriend. Just words. Hi.
- What about your boyfriend?
- Hey, handsome.
- Nice.
You know, it's only a few
minutes before midnight.
Yeah, we've got
clocks everywhere.
So I say you kiss me
at midnight
and we see what
happens from there.
I'm gonna start to walk
up to people more.
I got you a drink.
Now you seem lonely
and broken to me.
- I do?
- But don't worry, I can fix you.
Well, if there's one thing
a man likes,
it's a woman who tries
to fix him.
What are you
working on right now?
A piece on Brittany Giancarlo.
I don't know who that is.
Brittany Giancarlo.
She's the young one
on Real Housewives of New Jersey.
- Oh, I've got them all TiVo'd.
- She's a drunk gold digger
who's probably cheating
with her yoga instructor.
And why are you
writing about her?
I just told you.
No, I mean, sure,
but what did she do?
Nothing,
it's just a takedown piece.
- A what?
- A takedown piece.
I'm gonna take her down.
Why?
'Cause that's what you do
in a takedown piece, genius.
Crowd:
Nine, eight...
You actually call it
a takedown piece?
- Yeah.
- Crowd: Four, three,
two, one!
Happy New Year!
- Hang on.
- What?
You're just setting out
to be mean to somebody?
- And this was going so well.
- No, it could still go well.
Not if you're going to give me
a condescending lecture.
I think we both know
that's what's going to happen.
Didn't I just spend
the last six months
watching you take
down the Tea Party?
Okay, first,
thanks for watching.
Second, I obviously didn't take them down.
They won.
Third, the fact that they did
is an enormous danger to A:
- a great political party...
- Oh, there's subheadings?
Of which I happen
to be a member, and B:
An enormous danger to everyone
who lives in this country.
- Fourth...
- Fourth?
These are people who
are asking for our votes.
You and I do the same
thing for a living.
That's nuts, Nina.
I try to expose the truth about things
that are of national importance.
Well, I'm trying to expose
the truth about the fact
that Brittany might have had a daughter
when she was a teenager
who's now 10 possibly and being
taken care of by her mother.
Why is that the concern of
anyone except for Brittany?
It's not a concern.
It's entertainment.
Okay, well, here's the thing,
though, it shouldn't be.
- Is that right?
- Of course it's right.
You know it's right.
You know right from wrong.
Everybody said
you were like this.
No, no, look.
You can be part of the change.
You don't have to write gossip.
I work for a gossip magazine.
Are we gonna go back to flirting or
are you gonna keep putting me down?
I'm not putting you down.
I'm just saying that what you do
is a really bad form of pollution
that makes us dumber
and meaner and is
destroying civilization.
I'm saying,
with all possible respect,
that I would have more respect for you
if you were a heroin dealer.
And I'm speaking professionally,
not personally.
Okay, Will.
I'm speaking personally
when I say fuck you.
And you just passed up
a sure thing.
- Come on, hear me out.
- Don't touch me.
The real lives of people shouldn't
be used as entertainment.
- You can turn this around.
- I'm not interested.
What do you think he's doing?
Trying to civilize her.
Oh, that's not
gonna work out well.
Hang on, looks like
it's coming any second.
that you're on right now.
There it is.
- Will.
- Yeah?
I just wanted to introduce
my friend Kaylee.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Thank you.
I hate to bother you,
but do you have a second?
I've got all the time
in the world, Neal.
All right, Bigfoot is real.
- Let me start--
- Get the hell away from me.
- No problem. Sorry. Come on.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Have you read the New York Post?
No, my eyes
are connected to my brain.
I'm not sure about that.
Let's open to Page Six,
which for some reason
is on page 10,
and see what we find.
The headline, "Anchor Rancor."
- Anchor anchor?
- Anchor Rancor.
- Anchor anchor.
- Rancor.
Anchor Rancor.
Subheader,
"Will McAvoy gropes in the New Year."
What?
"ACN's newly minted
liberal bloviator
made a scene at a private
New Year's Eve party
at which our spies caught
the reengineered lefty firebrand
making a drunken pass at
TMI reporter Nina Howard."
Whoa, Nelly!
"But the Tea Party foe
got a face full of bubbly
- instead of what he was looking for."
- Ha!
"McAvoy was wearing
a $4,000 custom-made tuxedo
and a dumb look on his face."
There are a couple of factual
errors in that story.
Please let there be
more than a couple.
First of all,
I'm a registered Republican.
I only seem liberal because
I believe that hurricanes
are caused by high barometric
pressure and not gay marriage.
Second, I wasn't
making a pass at her.
I was rejecting a pass from her
while trying to talk her out of doing
what they call at TMI a takedown piece
of one of the
Desperate Housewives of New Jersey.
- Real Housewives.
- Who gives a shit?
- Definitely not me.
- And the tuxedo's off the rack.
- Did you grope her?
- No! I-I-I--
I gently touched her
to block her
as she was coming
in for a kiss.
I blocked her.
I was the victim of
an unwanted sexual advance.
But more important,
I was fighting the good fight.
Why were you
fighting any fight?
I was trying to get her to
not write the takedown piece.
- Why?
- Yeah.
- I'll tell you why.
Because I'm on a mission
to civilize.
- How's it going so far?
- Progress is slow,
but I'm in it
for the long haul.
You want Publicity
to draft a statement?
- About the mission?
- The Page Six piece.
- Absolutely not.
- Good.
- What did you call me up here for?
- Mostly to laugh at you.
But I also wanted
to share an observation.
- Go.
- You're dating.
I am. I've decided to live my life
as if I'm alive.
I am all for it.
But I've noticed that the women you date
all have one thing in common.
I am a leg man.
No, these are all women who,
in a million years,
you would not want to spend
any daylight hours with.
What do you make of that?
You're asking out
the wrong women.
- I'm not an elitist.
- Be one.
No comment on this shit, Charlie.
I'm not kidding.
And I'd also like to know who at my party
was tipping Page Six.
- I'll launch a full-scale investigation.
- Thank you.
How much was the tux?
It was-- It was like--
It was 4,000 bucks.
Mackenzie: Now!
What's happening now?
In this order,
Tess, Tamara, Gary,
Maggie, Kendra,
Martin, Neal, and Jim
thought it would be funny.
- And you?
- Peer pressure.
I didn't grope anybody.
I was holding her at bay
while I clarified--
It doesn't matter.
I'm on a mission to civilize.
- I'm Don Quixote.
Have you even read Don Quixote?
- In the original French.
- It was written in Spanish.
Not my copy.
I could have read it in Spanish?
You could have read
it in English.
Well, there's a year and a half of my life
I'm not getting back.
Sit down.
All right.
Jim was working on New Year's Eve
on stories we either missed
or didn't pay enough
attention to in 2010.
Not all New Year's Eve.
He found some time to take a little break.
- Pardon?
- Nothing.
We'll do five minutes a night
every night this week.
I've boiled them down to these and, Will,
you can boil them down to what you want.
I'm out there on the front lines
fighting for civility.
You picked her up at a party.
I didn't pick her up.
I walked up--
And can I say in my defense,
did you see her legs?
All right, that'll do.
First up, the Chilean miners.
We stuck with the Christine O'Donnell
debate in Delaware
instead of cutting away
to the rescue.
I'll let everyone know
that they came out all right.
You're the one
who wanted these.
- Next?
- Next.
I wouldn't mind following
up on the bribery charges
- Nigeria filed against Cheney.
- Next.
Conflict of interest with Virginia Thomas
and the voicemail message--
- Next.
- Tess?
- Now I'm frightened to say it.
- Say it.
May 27, the iPad was released.
Lines went around
the block--
- Get the hell out of the meeting.
- Yeah.
- Sit down.
- Where are the real ones? The lies. Lies.
Why doesn't the news ever call a lie a lie,
but we know it's a lie?
Jim, Maggie.
It was during the week of the midterms
so we were doing other things,
but the idea that Obama
spent $200 million a day
on a trip to India
is still in the water supply.
We could deconstruct
how that happened.
Sold. What else?
- Maggie: Guns.
- Will: What about them?
Everyone from Wayne LaPierre
to Glenn Beck is shouting
that Obama is coming
to get our guns
when there's no evidence
to suggest
that Obama's the least bit
interested in our guns.
Show me the lack
of evidence and I'm in.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
I don't know
how else to say this.
- Bigfoot is--
- Great.
Not because they don't
want to limit your rights,
but because they're afraid
of the political consequences.
- Coming back to you, Will.
- Don't doubt for a minute
that if they thought they
could get away with it,
- they would ban guns and ban ammunition.
- Stand by, 177.
That was former
governor Sarah Palin
speaking to the National
Rifle Association last year.
Here's Fox News host Glenn Beck on
the same subject.
Herb:
Go, 177.
Beck:
He will slowly but surely
- take away your gun.
- Herb: Stand by, 178.
And here's NRA executive
vice president
Wayne LaPierre
speaking at CPAC,
- the Conservative Political Action Conference.
- Go, 178.
But it's a big, fat,
stinking lie.
Just like all the other lies
that have come out
of this corrupt administration.
Would you put
this guy on a list
of the top 10 craziest
people in politics?
That's a tough list to crack.
Yeah, I know this looks like a big,
juicy rib-eye to you,
but show some restraint now
and let the facts speak for themselves.
- Any other tips?
- Try not to get distracted by his legs.
- Here we go.
- That's their agenda.
Will:
And radio host Rush Limbaugh
has repeatedly warned
to his listeners
to go out and buy guns before
President Obama outlaws them all.
The result?
In November 2008,
the month Mr. Obama
was elected,
there was a 42% spike
in gun background checks
as compared to the same month
the year before.
- Stand by, G-17 through 22.
- The country's largest anti-gun lobby
is called the Brady Campaign
to Prevent Gun Violence,
named for James Brady,
President Reagan's press secretary
who was shot in the head
during John Hinckley's
assassination attempt
on the 40th president.
The Brady Organization gives
grades to elected officials
based on their record and leadership
with regard to gun legislation
with an "A" being
the most anti-gun and so on.
In spite of Governor Palin,
Glenn Beck, Rush Limbaugh,
and the Director of the NRA
telling us emphatically
that Barack Obama has
a secret plan to get our guns,
here's the president's
report card.
Background checks? F.
Gun trafficking? F.
Guns in public? F.
Federal assault
weapons ban? F.
Standing up to
the gun lobby? F.
Not only has no attempt
whatsoever been made
to dismantle
the Second Amendment
during Barack Obama's
first two years in office,
the president has signed
into law more repeals
of federal gun policies
than George W. Bush did
during his entire eight years
in the White House.
In fact, these grades would
indicate that President Obama
is the best friend the NRA
has ever had in elected office,
to say nothing
of the Oval Office.
Why are Sarah Palin,
Glenn Beck, Rush Limbaugh,
and the head of the NRA
so colossally lying to you?
I don't know.
But I know when they do,
ratings go up,
political contributions go up,
membership in the NRA goes up,
the president's
approval rating goes down,
and gun sales go through
the freaking roof.
- We'll be right back.
- Herb: Cue music.
You'll need to get used to dating
a guy who gets off work at 9:00.
Hey, not dating.
One date.
- No, stop it.
- Maggie, I'm not--
- It's fine.
- It's not in the vicinity of fine.
Listen to me.
This is crazy.
- I agree.
- Nope, keep listening.
I have a boyfriend who I love.
And I should have fixed you up
with Jim a long time ago.
- Even if that were true--
- It is true.
- Even if it was-- Even if--
- It is. It--
- Let me talk!
- Sorry.
- He's--
- But it is.
He's gonna think I'm dumb.
No, he's not.
Who told you that?
Lis', you're not dumb.
Look at me.
You're not dumb.
You go out with guys
who make you feel dumb.
And Jim's not like that.
That's one of the things
that makes him--
Trust me. I've never been
on a date with him,
but I imagine...
You imagine what and how often?
That it would be fun...
is all I was gonna say.
You're not dumb.
I'm just nervous.
I know.
Your skirt's on backwards.
Damn it.
And this is my field of expertise.
Yeah.
Oh! Oh, my God. I'm freezing.
I've got a real fireplace
with real fire.
You do? Well, what about
some dry clothes I can change into?
Take whatever you want
in the bedroom.
It's right around the corner.
Not the yellow
taffeta sundress.
This is your fault.
I'm not the one who said,
"Let's walk off dinner."
I had to walk off dinner
because you made me order
the $135 macaroni and cheese.
I really wanted to see what $135 macaroni
and cheese looked like.
- This is a fun date.
- It is.
And it's the same as
Stouffer's macaroni and cheese
with $134 worth of
shaved truffles on top.
Sloan said you were fun.
Hey, do you like to get high?
I used to,
but I can't buy pot anymore
without it showing up
in a newspaper.
There's a joint in the side
pocket of my purse.
Get it out.
All right.
- Carrie?
- Yeah?
Can we talk about the gun
that's in your purse?
I'm a southern liberal, dude.
It's northern liberals
who are afraid of sex and guns.
Well, both at the same time
and I'm a Republican from Nebraska.
But you mind if I...
You're disarming.
Get it?
- Here's the thing--
- Yeah, yeah, I saw the show tonight.
I'm a liberal's liberal.
I worked for Hillary.
- You were dead wrong on guns.
- I didn't take a position on guns.
I took a position on lying.
I came out against it.
Well, if I'm walking the streets of Manhattan
at night and a guy your size
wants to rape me,
then this is gonna happen.
Actually, statistics show
that this is gonna happen.
Is it wrong that
I'm turned on by that?
Yes.
What'd you think of her?
Yeah,
what'd you think of her, Will?
Oh, sorry.
- She was packing heat.
- Didn't I tell you?
No, Sloan, she was armed.
Waverly Inn
to my apartment
with a loaded .38 caliber
Walther PPK/S.
- Are you going out with her again?
- No.
- Oh, you have to.
- No, I don't think so.
30 seconds.
Get your mics on.
No, she's gonna call me and call me
asking why you're not calling her.
That would happen after a second date,
too, wouldn't it?
Listen, just wait a while
before you show up
again in Page Six
with a different woman.
She's super jealous.
You haven't seen the crazy side of her.
You set me up with a crazy woman
who can shoot me.
Fatal Attraction with
a concealed carry permit.
- I'm tagging you back.
- That's totally fair.
You're supposed to be
the smartest person on the staff.
- You have two PhDs.
- In Economics.
This is an area
where I do not excel.
Oh, thanks for the heads up.
Herb:
In three, two...
Will: Terry Smith is coming up next
in Washington with the Capitol Report.
I'm Will McAvoy.
Good night.
Good show, everybody.
Good show.
Yeah, I don't know.
The economy, we're still
nibbling around the edges.
We can't get it all
done in one night.
They're gonna rip Dodd-Frank
limb from limb.
I don't know how many more
nights we have left.
Hey, speaking--
Speaking of nights,
I never asked--
I forgot to ask you how your date went.
It went fine.
Do you think you'll
be seeing her again?
- I don't think so.
- Why?
Just one of those things.
Not a love connection?
Broccoli, and combine
cauliflower and string beans.
- So, elephant in the room.
- Yeah.
When I told my friend
I was going out with you tonight,
she sent me Monday's Page Six.
Okay, I met a woman
named Nina Howard
at our New Year's Eve party.
It turned out she writes for TMI.
I asked her what
she was working on,
and she told me she was doing
what she called a takedown story.
I'm on a mission to civilize,
so I tried to talk her
out of it and she
didn't take it well.
- A mission to civilize?
- I walk a lonely road.
What was the story she was doing?
Um, Brittany DiFranklengonio
from the New Jersey--
the Real Naked--
- Wait, Brittany Giancarlo?
- That sounds right.
Yeah, she has a 10-year-old daughter
that she allegedly gave to her mother.
Shut up.
And they actually call it
a takedown piece.
That is so typically Brittany.
Yeah, it is.
She had a kid she gave up?
I have no idea.
I don't even know if the kid is real.
- What I'm talking about--
- I knew she was a liar
when she didn't invite
Wendy to her game night.
When she got busted,
she made everyone lie to cover her ass.
- What kind of person does that?
- I don't know.
Oh, and she's having an affair
with her yoga instructor.
- My therapist told me that.
- Your therapist really--
She knows I can keep a secret.
She's an awesome judge
of character.
- Brittany?
- Your therapist.
- 'Cause Brittany's a bitch.
- No, you are.
Okay, let's hold it right there
and review the situation
because when I said "you,"
what I meant was "we."
I meant I'm not
concerned about Brittany.
She signed up for this.
I'm concerned about the rest of us
who are being turned into a bunch of
old ladies with hair dryers on our heads
gorging ourselves
on the staged mis--
It's just-- God,
it's so plainly bad, Monica.
It's called a guilty pleasure.
The chocolate soufflé on
this  menu is a guilty pleasure.
The Archies singing "Sugar, Sugar"
is a guilty pleasure.
Human cockfighting makes us
mean and desensitizes--
Wait, are you saying that
I'm mean and insensitive?
You-- You are a smart,
accomplished woman.
- You work for a US Senator.
- Am I mean and insensitive?
Yes, but thank goodness
you met me in time.
Because now--
I can't believe
how often this is happening.
He said he wasn't
that into her.
Why are you so eager
to make this happen?
When did you get
interested in Jim's life?
Or Lisa's life?
I just asked
how did the date go.
But I'll tell you
what's strange.
- What?
- Jim's lying to you.
About what?
Lisa told me they were
going out again tonight.
That's Lisa saying she's hoping
they go out again tonight.
- Ah, I misunderstood.
- Yeah.
Why would Jim lie about that?
It's funny, I was
wondering the same thing.
Why don't you give him a call?
I'm not gonna call
and check up on him.
Then call him and tell him to
look on Politico 'cause I'm reading
that Spencer Bachus told
his hometown newspaper today
- that Washington is there to serve the banks.
- Seriously?
- Spencer Bachus is--
- I know. Is that a quote?
"Washington is here
to serve the banks."
I actually do have to call Jim.
It's an economic story.
That's what I'm saying.
Can I see that?
- Jim: Hello.
- Jim, it's me.
- Yeah?
- Did I wake you up?
No.
Is everything all right?
Go to Politico. The new Chairman of
the House Financial Services Committee
told his hometown newspaper
that Washington is here to serve the banks.
- Bachus?
- Yeah. Go to Politico and click on--
♪ If you want my body
and you think I'm sexy ♪
♪ Come on, sugar, let me know ♪
♪ If you really need me ♪
♪ Just reach out
and touch me... ♪
- Jim?
- Yeah?
You know, I'll talk
to you in the morning.
Something wrong?
She should really
change her ringtone.
I can't believe
what you just did.
There is no way I'm the bad guy
in what just happened.
At worst, I'm in fourth place.
Have I done something wrong?
No.
Good.
- "Serial Sleaze."
- I can explain this one.
"Will McAvoy is making more news
when he's not behind his desk.
For the second time in a week,
the ACN anchor
was humiliated by a drink to the face
from an unhappy date
- when the newly-come-liberal bachelor"--
- Registered Republican.
--"stepped out with a bodacious blonde
for a late supper at the Mercer Kitchen.
The formerly vanilla host
of Atlantis Cable's flagship program,
who many believe
has become unglued
since an appearance at the Northwestern School
of Journalism last April,
seems to like the ladies.
Unfortunately for McAvoy,
the ladies don't seem to like him back.
The kicker?
Our spies tell us that McAvoy,
who's reported to earn
a mid-seven figure salary,
stiffed the waiter on his tip."
Are you kidding?
We didn't get past drinks.
I threw $100 on the table.
How much is a vodka martini
and a pomegranate cosmo?
Please tell me it was you
who ordered the martini.
Of course I was the one who--
Yes.
Look, she asked me about New Year's Eve,
I told her.
And it turns out that she, too,
really seems to care about the life of Bethany--
- Brittany.
- DiLaguardiosa.
- No.
- How does it get in the paper so fast?
God, these guys are good.
Well, now we're putting
out a statement.
- No.
- Not from you.
- From your spokesperson.
- Not from any person.
Mr. McAvoy has been the victim of
a comical series of misunderstandings.
No way. However,
I want to depose every waiter,
bartender, doorman, and valet
to whom I have ever given a tip.
That might be unrealistic.
I am beloved in
the service industries.
Hey, I've been meaning to ask you,
how's the dating going?
You know what?
How many women did you date
before you finally found the one?
Doesn't matter
how many I dated before.
I didn't date anyone after.
It probably helped that
she didn't pull your heart out,
throw it into an oven
preheated to 450 degrees,
bake it in a light honey glaze,
and serve it to you
on a bed of rice.
That's vivid.
But you don't hold onto things.
Why is it taking you so long to--
Because it is.
It doesn't work
like in the movies.
It doesn't work at all.
- How sure are you about that?
- Please.
On the off chance that you're
not going to live forever,
why not take a shot
at being happy now?
Can I go do the news?
Yes.
- Hey, stupid.
- Yeah?
- What'd I say?
- When?
I said don't show up in
Page Six with another date.
- You think I phoned this in?
- Carrie is freaking out.
- Who's Carrie?
- Two nights ago!
Oh, God.
What did she say?
That you're a womanizing asshole
and she hates you.
I wasn't womanizing.
I was dating.
Well, William, she has a gun
and she's going to shoot you.
She's going to have to
shoot you first, Sloan,
because I'm going to use you
as a human shield
because you set me up
with Annie Oakley.
- You mean Ado Annie?
- I mean Annie Oakley.
Annie Get Your Gun.
Ado Annie's Oklahoma.
- "I'm just a Girl Who Can't Say No."
- I can't help you anymore.
Damn, 'cause your help's
been invaluable up till now.
Hey!
Are you sure about
Annie Get Your Gun?
Yes.
Back in 15 seconds, Will.
Try not to date anyone
before you're on the air.
Copy, Mac. Try not to sleep with your
ex-boyfriend while I am.
In three...
He got the better
of that exchange.
Mark Twain said a lie'll
get halfway around the world
before the truth has time
to pull its boots on.
That was literally the case
in this story
we didn't pay enough
attention to in 2010.
President Obama was scheduled
to travel to Mumbai
to meet with the Indian Prime Minister
about loosening US trade restrictions,
a successful trip
that would net our country
$10 billion in export deals
and 50,000 jobs.
And these overseas trips
routinely cost in the area
- of $5 million a day.
- Hey.
- But on November 2nd of last year,
the website for New Delhi TV
quoted an anonymous official
of the Maharashtra Government
saying that President Obama's
trip would be costing
$200 million a day.
The Drudge Report posts
a link to the story,
either believing it to be possible
or not caring that it isn't.
Rush Limbaugh knows this figure
can't possibly be right.
But Mr. Limbaugh
runs with it anyway.
507 rooms at the Taj Mahal,
40 airplanes,
$200 million a day
this nation will spend
on Obama's trip to India.
In spite of there being no
source for this information,
to say nothing of
the absurdity of the figure,
- Fox News grabs the baton.
- Ready, SOT 1.
So he's traveling with 34 warships,
an entourage--
Oh, yeah,
and he added 34 warships,
or 14% of the US Navy.
So he's traveling
with 34 warships,
an entourage
of 3,000 people--
Nope.
Beck: He's staying at
the Taj Mahal Hotel,
which they have booked
every single room in.
And he's doing it--
$2 billion for 10 days--
Why?
So on November 3rd,
Matt Lehrich
of the Office of White House
Media Affairs says,
"The numbers reported
in this article have no basis in reality."
Congresswoman Michele Bachmann,
founder of
the Tea Party Caucus,
who herself has a difficult
relationship with reality,
ignores the statement
from the White House.
I think we know that
just within a day or so,
the President of the United States
will be taking a trip over to India
that is expected
to cost the taxpayers
$200 million a day.
I think people who willfully,
purposefully,
and gleefully lie
to the American people
in order to damage
someone's reputation
should, like
a registered sex offender,
be required by law to come
with that warning label
for the rest of their lives.
- Hello?
- Will, it's Charlie.
I'm sorry to call early
on a Saturday.
- What happened?
- Can you come into the office at 11:00?
- Yeah. What's going on?
- I'll see you at 11:00.
Welcome back to
Red Carpet Roundup
where we continue our review
of last night's fashion winners
and losers at
the People's Choice Awards.
We'll throw it back
to our studio in Hollywood
and Paulita Maya and her team
of fashion experts.
Paulita?
Man:
And we're clear.
He's here.
Against all instincts
of what sanity sounds like,
I'm here at 11:00
on a Saturday.
- Neal: You won't regret it.
- Jim: Too late.
Thank you all for coming.
Let me begin.
There are 1.7 million
known species.
Biologists estimate
this represents
only a quarter of the total
species on the planet.
Species diversity is greatest
in rain forests,
and 75% of all species
live in rain forests.
So, the argument is
could there be
an apex predator primate,
a missing link if you will,
between six and 10 feet tall,
weighing up to 500 pounds
that lives in a dense
temperate rain forest?
- Jim?
- No. Is that it?
Careful.
Sometimes when Jim says no,
what he really means is,
"I'm sleeping with your roommate."
What's going on?
I didn't know you were coming.
- I was told to come.
- Really?
Charlie called me
at 7:00 this morning.
I wonder how that happened.
Was I called in on
a Saturday for Bigfoot?
I think you're gonna
find this interesting.
I think you don't know
what that word means.
- What are you doing?
- You told me to come in.
Not for this.
What is this?
I'm glad you asked, Charlie.
Bigfoot is--
Ah.
Follow me.
- I called you in for this.
- Oh, shit.
We need a whole team for this?
Don's a good advisor
on damage control.
- When's it come out?
- It's out. This is it.
You keep guns in your house?
Yeah, a vast collection.
Sometimes to relax
I go to the park and shoot dogs.
- I'm just asking.
- She had the gun.
Some crazy fucking
friend of Sloan's.
I took out the bullets.
The highest incidents
of Bigfoot sightings have all come
from the temperate rain forest
region that stretches
from Northern California
to Alaska.
Here we find local myths like
the Sasquatch and Ts'emekwes.
Here we find local myths
like Jim not being a liar.
Come with me, please.
- I'm learning things.
- Now, please.
First of all, you can't talk to me like that
in front of the staff.
Oh, listen to Mr.--
- Mike.
- Yeah?
You got the rest
of the afternoon off.
Maggie's taking your shift
on the assignment desk.
- You sure?
- Go home.
Nice to throw
your weight around?
Yeah. Sit your ass
at that desk until 4:00.
That's number one.
Number two,
I'm sorry that I lied to you.
I didn't want you to be upset.
- Why did you think I'd be upset?
- Because you are!
Not because you slept with Lisa,
because you lied about it!
Excuse me!
This isn't soundproof glass!
It is because
I slept with Lisa.
You've never lied to me in all the time
we've been working together.
Is that not a little bit--
Just a little bit
a good feeling?
That it feels weird
that I lied to you?
And isn't it a little bit
a good feeling
that my instinct was to lie?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
It was Don's idea to
fix me up with Lisa, right?
Maggie:
Yes.
And Don was the one who called Lisa
when she was at my place?
- Yes.
- Then I'd ask Don.
'Cause he has every idea
what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry I lied.
It won't happen again.
Don: Did you know
she was married?
She's been separated
for over a year.
- Did you smoke pot with her?
- Yes.
Did you level
a .32 caliber gun at her head?
I was demonstrating--
Fuck this.
You'd just done
a gun rant that night.
Is that what it was, Mac?
It was a rant?
Don: Does she have
a text message from you?
Listen to me.
She got jealous 'cause she read
that I went out with
someone else the next night.
Then she went to
Nina Howard at TMI,
who was just waiting
for a chance--
I knocked Jennifer Aniston
off the cover?
This isn't funny, Will.
We're trying to do something here.
All of us.
There are guys in here
on a Saturday doing--
What the hell are they doing?
They're learning about Bigfoot.
Which, by the way,
is what used to be in the tabloids.
- Bigfoot and Elvis sightings have been replaced--
- Whatever.
We signed up with you and
no one's going to hear a word we're saying.
- Tell me what I did wrong?
- How about drugs?
I took a hit of a joint
in my own home.
- The text message.
- I'm not telling you what it says.
Just tell me if you'd want
your mother to read it.
Yeah, she died 10 years ago
and I wouldn't mind seeing her again.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna go on ACN Morning.
They are going to ask the questions we want them to ask
- and you're going to give the answers we want--
- I'm not doing that.
- Will.
- No, I'm not playing.
This is News Corp using
their gossip trash
to fuck with an anchor.
News Corp doesn't own TMI.
We do.
- I'm talking about the Right coming after me.
- Wait.
- I'm talking about--
- Wait!
Wait.
The tuxedo.
The $4,000 tux.
You didn't buy it off the rack,
did you?
- What does--
- Just tell me.
You're my boss and I make
a lot more money than you do.
That makes me uncomfortable.
- No, the tux was made for me by Armand--
- Armand Felini.
Yeah, how did you know?
'Cause Leona Lansing gave me
the same Christmas present last year.
A custom-made tuxedo
from Armand Felini.
This isn't News Corp.
It's us.
It's AWM.
That's how Nina Howard
knew how much the suit cost.
Why would our parent company--
I had a meeting
I never told you guys about
the day after election night.
Leona's really pissed that you're
shooting at Tea Party congressmen
and senators she has
to do business with.
How pissed?
I'm not asking him to lie.
I'm not asking him
to cover anything up.
But he's gonna tone it down
or I'll fire him.
Well, best of luck trying
to program against him.
I won't have to.
He's got a non-compete clause
in his contract.
He's got to stay off television
for three years.
- That's a death sentence.
- It is.
How would you possibly
explain firing
the second most
watched anchor on cable?
By creating
what we call a context.
His firing would be viewed
as an honorable step
by a corporation willing to sacrifice
ratings for integrity.
How could you not
tell me about that meeting?
- I should have.
- You think?
- This is a huge line that's being crossed.
- I made that clear to her.
- A huge--
how many times
in the last six months
have I asked if we're
all right on the 44th floor?
Will, I love you,
but you've got clay feet
and I needed to
keep you in the chair.
Oh, thanks for the confidence.
Don: Can we get back
to damage control?
- ACN Morning Monday.
- Hang on.
You'd never allow a non-compete clause
in your contract.
You couldn't stay off the television
for five minutes.
It got... put in.
When?
When, Will?
When I renegotiated
my contract.
To be able to fire me
at the end of each week.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ,
how much do you hate me?
- I don't hate you.
- You allowed a non-compete clause in your contract?
Three years? You were willing to stay
off TV for three years?
When was the last time an anchor
stayed off TV for three years
and ever came back?
Have revenge sex with
every woman in the Tri-State area
for all I care, but keep it out of
the goddamn newspapers.
- Some of us have moved on.
- Yeah, you mentioned that.
I can leave. You can do the
same show with another producer.
- We can have that discussion.
- Why don't we have it now?
Yeah.
Yeah, some of us moved on
three and a half years ago
and forgot to tell me!
Neal:
Uh, ahem.
The vast majority of this rain forest
is unexplored
despite almost 100 years of commercial logging.
I would add that renowned primatologist
Jane Goodall is also a believer,
given the cryptozoological history
of the lowland gorilla.
But she's not alone
in this scientific field.
Due to frequent
yeti sightings...
Heads up!
- What's going on?
- All hands!
There's been a shooting
in Tucson and a congresswoman,
Gabrielle Giffords,
has been shot in the head.
This is Martin
at the ACN newsroom.
I was wondering if you have
a comment on the shooting?
- Get me our Tucson affiliate.
- It's Charlie Skinner.
New York Control is
breaking in in 15 minutes.
- Tess!
- Yeah?
- I'm giving you a phone number.
- Okay.
Quickly.
Lt. Harvel Shansky,
Tucson PD. 8-4-6...
Gary, I need to be able to talk
to a goddamn correspondent
on the ground.
- The shooter's in custody.
- Who is he?
How'd they get him?
Everybody up!
Up, up!
recording their
next album without Maines.
We'll get the inside scoop
from Natalie herself.
Will: We're cutting into our
program with breaking news.
A local Tucson newspaper is reporting
that Arizona Congresswoman
Gabby-- Gabrielle Giffords
has been shot
while holding a public event
in Tucson outside a grocery store.
Possibly as many as 12 others
have been rushed to an area hospital...
We're now learning that three members
of Gabrielle Giffords' staff
were among those wounded and rushed
to University Medical Center in Tucson.
Does he have an arrest record?
They've had him for over an hour now.
How can they not know who he is?
He's not going on
the air with maybe.
- Jim. Jim.
- No, an arrest record.
Okay, can you tell me if the congresswoman's
district office has received any threats?
Jim, NPR is saying she's dead.
- Anyone else?
- No.
Then she's not dead yet.
If you're just joining us,
a gunman in Arizona...
Fox, MSNBC,
and CNN are all calling it.
Let me hear MSNBC.
Reporter:
...a sole source of information
that reports that
the Arizona congresswoman
Gabrielle Giffords
has been killed
in this heinous attempt
on her life.
Joey.
Get me some official confirmation
or I'm not calling it right now.
Why hasn't he called it yet?
I don't have time right now.
Jim, why hasn't he called it?
- Gary, I need him in the hospital.
- He's there.
CNN, MSNBC,
and FOX say she's dead.
They're all going off
the same NPR report.
- I'm not satisfied.
- I don't give a shit if you're satisfied.
Mackenzie:
What the hell is he-- Hey!
We're going to show you now an interview
Gabrielle Giffords gave just last year.
This is Congresswoman Giffords.
- Herb: 30 seconds.
- What's going on?
- I'll call security.
- Every second you're not current,
1,000 people are changing
the channel to the guy who is.
That's the business you're in.
MSNBC, Fox, and CNN all say she's dead.
Don, tell him.
Don!
It's a person.
A doctor pronouncers her dead,
not the news.
Back in five, four...
What we know so far is that
Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords
and 12 others were shot
when a gunman opened fire
at a local town hall
in Tucson, Arizona.
Is he overhearing it
or is he at the hospital?
- She's alive!
- Who's telling you that?
The anesthesiologist.
She's being prepped for surgery.
- I've got her alive!
- NPR called it wrong. She's alive.
She's alive.
Will.
All right, we're learning now
that Giffords is being
prepped for surgery
and we have our ACN affiliate
at University Hospital now.
- What can you tell us?
- Will...
Mac, get in here
with Charlie right now.
- Is everything--
- Right now!
You tell Leona that if she
wants me out of this chair,
she better bring more
than just a couple of guys.
That's exactly what
I'll fucking tell her.
I'm not fucking around, Charlie!
Feet of fucking steel.
- Mac.
- I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- I fucked everything up!
- It's gonna be all right.
- What the fuck is going on?
You're a fucking newsman, Don!
I ever tell you otherwise,
you punch me in the face!
Okay, but you're back in 30.
Back in 30.
Joey.
Just breathe regular.
This is a sketchy description
of the procedure they'll be trying.
Hey.
When this is over,
let me see the Bigfoot
presentation.
Really?
I think I need some consulting
on what's real and what's not.
Okay, I think you'll find that there's
some striking evidence--
- Not now.
- Herb: Stand by, camera 1.
- Right.
- In three, two...
Thank you, Tom.
Let's put together what we know.
A little after noon today,
Congresswoman Gabby Giffords
was shot while holding
a town hall meeting
in Tucson, Arizona.
Along with Giffords...
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net