I want some sort of document about
what we've been trying to do here.
I get to pick the writer.
I'm going with New York Magazine and you.
What about our history?
- You dated him?
- Brian Brenner is the guy I cheated on Will with.
- Wow.
- Tell me about this new debate.
The RNC is looking at Will
to possibly host a debate,
and Will and Mac have an idea for
a new debate format we want to show them.
Whose idea was it to not cover
the Casey Anthony trial?
- It was mine.
- It was hers.
Half our audience changed
the channel in one week.
I want the debate.
If that means we have to be Jerry Springer
for a few weeks,
I'm willing to pay that price.
The night we got bin Laden
I got a call from an anonymous source.
He works in software
engineering at the NSA.
We have to start vetting him
and the documents.
You got some tweets
from Congressman Weiner.
And I've got copies
of them right here.
We can do a pre-tape.
- Will.
- Yes, I'm sure I want to do this.
God, please give me a sign
I'm not doing a big thing badly.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
Backup generators should
have come on already.
Maybe it just
needs a minute.
It doesn't just need a minute.
It's an emergency generator
that's supposed to make
a seamless handoff
so if this happens
during a show-- Herb?
Power's out
in the whole building.
It's been explained
to me 19 different ways
how we can never
lose power in the studio.
What about all
the redundancies?
There was a round of budget cuts
before you got here.
- And they cut some of the redundancies...
- Don't say it.
- because they thought they were redundant.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
- That's a good sign, right?
- Those are battery powered.
- When should I start to worry?
- I'd have started already.
Electricians are on their way.
We lost power in the studio.
What makes you say that?
Everybody, listen up.
It's the whole building.
We've sent for maintenance
to check on our generator.
They should be here in a minute.
They've got to walk up 25 floors.
Okay, they should be here
in a couple of hours.
Neal, I want you
to be in charge
of rationing battery life
for laptops and cell phones.
- I have a question.
- Yes?
What if the power
doesn't go back on?
I don't think that's
a realistic possibility.
I don't mean ever. I mean what if
the power doesn't go on by showtime?
Do we have a contingency?
No.
Mac?
A miracle.
A miracle happens.
We become a team again.
We all hate this, right?
We're gonna hate it more after
10 minutes of no air conditioning.
No, not the power outage.
We hate what we're doing.
We hate that we're covering
Casey Anthony
and Anthony Weiner.
We hate that we have to do it
to save the ratings.
We hate that we have
to bump important stories.
And we're starting to be
not very pleasant people to be around.
Guys, this is real.
I'm not making this up.
Just a minute ago when
I was prepping for a pretape
with that idiot who's
still sitting in the studio--
- Are you talking about me?
- No!
Yes. When I was prepping
for her pretape I said,
"God, please show me a sign
that I'm not doing a big thing badly."
And right that second
all the power went out.
And so obviously I thought,
"There's my answer."
Raise your hand if Mac's
freaking you the hell out right now.
No, listen to me!
Just tell us how we do the show
if the power doesn't--
By being a team again.
And that was God's plan.
Keep God out of this
and talk more about electricity.
We do the show outside
right in the plaza.
- How?
- Yeah, we can do this.
What do we need?
A desk, a camera,
some microphones,
and a way to beam a signal into space.
The grips take apart the anchor desk.
And carry it down 25 flights?
You bet your ass they do.
We can use a single
tripod-mounted handheld.
- We park a sat truck out there.
- That's right.
- Run the video and graphics through Washington.
- Yes!
I'm in your sight line the whole time,
in your ear and standing next to camera.
I'll have a laptop with
a constant iNews connection.
How do we get power to
editors to run the Avids?
What did they do in Apollo 13?
They shut down all the power
in the command module
and siphoned it into the LEM.
I don't think that's gonna work here.
What would they have done if
there was a hardware store in space?
- Buy a generator.
- We're gonna buy two.
One goes in an Avid bay
and the other stays downstairs.
- What time does the sun set tonight?
- 8:37.
Why in the world
would you know that?
One of those things.
We'll need HMis with gels
for the top half hour
and incandescents for the bottom half.
We need the NYPD for security
and we need to trust each other.
Does anybody think
we're not good enough
- to pull this off?
- No!
- Should I still be sitting here?
- I'm so sorry, Sandy.
I know you had your heart
set on entertaining us
with private details of a man
you were sexting with
and maybe a Playboy spread,
but we're not able to do pretape.
So if you want to do the show,
you're gonna have to do it live.
I already committed to Fox,
and no offense,
but it's a bigger audience.
Shoot!
Does anybody think we can't do this?
- No!
- This is a blessing in disguise.
I say the power going out
is the best thing that
ever happened to us.
I say the power going out
is what is gonna save this--
Son of a bitch!
You're a freaking riot,
you know that?
I meant to tell you,
you should use the word
bombshell more
in the Casey Anthony
coverage tonight.
Sandy, you're back in business.
- Great.
- Let's go.
Bombshell after bombshell today
in the trial of Casey Anthony
for the murder of her
two-year-old daughter Caylee.
Casey's brother,
Lee Anthony, took the stand
to testify about the events
of the night of July 15, 2008,
when Caylee was reported missing.
- Watch and listen. It's riveting stuff.
- Roll five.
When you asked your sister
why won't you allow us
to see Caylee,
what do you recall her saying?
I told Detective Edwards that she said--
I'm paraphrasing--
"Because maybe I'm a spiteful bitch."
Lee Anthony described
his odyssey that month
trying to find his missing niece.
Oddly, he was never questioned
about the defense's claim
he molested Casey.
For the latest,
we're joined live from Orlando
by ACN's Selena Machado.
- Can you describe how you're feeling right now?
- No.
Selena, how did Casey seem today
during her brother's testimony?
Well, her demeanor
was different with Lee
than it was with her mother.
The normally outspoken
Democratic New York congressman
is suddenly tongue-tied and evasive.
Here he is again today with
The Today Show's Luke Russert.
- Roll 16.
- That's not a picture of you?
You know,
I can't say with certitude.
My system was hacked.
Pictures can be manipulated.
Pictures can be dropped
in and inserted.
Someone committed
a prank on me.
Somehow got access
to my Twitter account
and right away put up a picture
that made fun of the name Weiner.
Hey, we can be doing
mock debate prep during this.
Hey, debate prep.
You don't have to watch this.
We don't know for sure
what happened here.
I spoke earlier today with Sandy Witless,
- a bartender--
- Whiddles, like carving wood.
Excuse me, Sandy Whiddles,
a bartender here in Manhattan
who had been tweeting with
Congressman Weiner for the past several months.
- Here's that interview.
- Roll 22.
- Thank you for speaking to us, Sandy.
- Thank you.
When did you become a
Twitter follower of the congressman?
Let me say first that
I was more than a follower.
We had a relationship,
which is obvious when you read the texts.
Does he usually smoke at his desk?
I have copies of
the texts right here.
I know you're eager to read the tweets.
- We'll get to those in a moment.
- Okay, because--
Did the congressman ever
talk to you or tweet to you
anything that he was working on
in one of his committees?
No. I have copies
of the tweets right here.
Two minutes and 20 seconds
in the C block
to educate the public on the most
irresponsible economic inaction in my lifetime.
I know, it's all upside down
because of Casey Anthony.
- Once ratings are back up--
- We're committing journalistic malpractice.
Fortunately,
there's no such thing.
How great would it be if there was?
I can understand your frustration.
- What's your thing again?
- It's a website for trolls.
They get together and talk
about their conquests.
And I want to produce a story
and Mac's given me the go-ahead
- to go to the next level.
- Go on the website?
Yeah, but I can't get
in the conversation
till I can point to another
website and show how I've--
- Been an asshole?
- Yes.
I have to go onto a message board
and disrupt the conversation
to the extent that havoc ensues.
Then I can go on the troll website
and brag about it.
But you don't want to do
something or say something
- that would hurt someone you don't know.
- Right.
You want to say things
that would hurt me.
Yes.
What website?
You've heard of EconomyBrain.com?
Yes, it's a financial news aggregate blog
and discussion forum
that attracts an intelligent
level of debate.
And the commenters have
a very high opinion of your analyses.
So you'd like my permission to--
Jump in there and invent heinous
and incendiary lies about you,
end the intelligent debate,
and start a whole new one
about, say,
whether or not you're a whore.
My dad has friends
who are economists, too.
So with Father's Day
just around the corner,
- this'll save me the trouble of shopping for him.
- I know.
Just print out the whole whore debate
and put it in a nice frame for him.
It would be my first story.
And I really think it's a good one.
I think so, too.
Just let me know when it's over.
- You're the greatest.
- I really am.
This is Hang Chew's.
The staff adopted it as their hangout
'cause they get cheap
food and drinks until 9:00.
- Can you spell that?
- N-I-N-E O-C--
Okay.
Is it important that you
treat me like I'm an asshole?
I wouldn't say
important so much as
- it just sort of feels right.
- I know you'd agree it would be better
- to keep our personal past out of this.
- Yeah.
That said, I'd like to point out that
you broke up with me, too.
- Listen, Brian--
- I broke up with you, we got back together,
and then you broke up with me.
Those are the facts.
I sure hope we're
on the record for this.
And during the second act,
you were with Will behind my back.
Once again,
I was with you behind Will's back.
Yeah, and it makes me feel great
when you say that,
but I do think we should
stick to the story.
The story is this:
Will is a heavyweight.
And for a long time he was
pretending to be a lightweight.
- Because lightweights get higher ratings.
- Yes.
Will's a lonely guy, isn't he?
- Is he--
- He's lonely.
He doesn't care about ratings
because of the money.
He cares about ratings
because the audience
makes him feel less lonely.
What do you plan on
writing about, Brian?
I don't know yet.
I have to talk to Sloan.
Excuse me one second.
He is a lonely guy.
I don't know if that
started around the time
I told him I'd been
sleeping with you,
but I'll bet it didn't help.
Governor Pawlenty,
the possibility exists
that New Hampshire
will become the 23rd state
to pass right-to-work legislation.
As president, would you support
a federal right-to-work law?
- You should have this.
- Give me a second.
Try: for much of my life
my father was a Teamster truck driver.
My brothers and sisters were in unions.
- I was in a union.
- We grew up in a blue-collar town.
We live in the United States of America.
Governor, we know where we live.
Would you support--
People shouldn't be forced to belong to
or be a member of any organization.
Yes, I strongly support
right-to-work legislation.
That's what
an answer sounds like.
- Can I talk to you a sec?
- Yeah.
Just the fact that they're debating
- whether or not to raise the debt ceiling--
- I'm trying.
I need to find a Casey Anthony guest
no one else has.
And hopefully I won't be able to do it.
- I'll be rooting against you.
- Good.
- You doing all right over there?
- With him?
- Yeah.
'Cause you give me the signal
and I can just get in there
- and, you know.
- What?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
- Debt ceiling.
- Yeah.
Just hang in there
one more day.
It's not one more day.
It's another month.
The mock debate's tomorrow.
And once that's over,
we need the numbers to protect you from Leona.
Not if Charlie's guy can do it for us.
And if he doesn't
turn out to be credible?
Then-- I don't know.
Let's take it one day at a time.
And get a guest
that's promotable.
What are the flowers?
Nothing.
- Who are they from?
- I don't know.
They didn't come with a card?
- They did.
- The card wasn't signed?
- It was.
- Was it another threat?
- No.
- What am I missing?
Do you really want this
on your plate right now?
The flowers aren't for me,
they aren't from me,
they're just living in
my office for a little while.
Can you be satisfied with that?
- Are they for me?
- Let's go.
- Speaker Gingrich.
- Yes?
As a candidate for the
Republican nomination for president,
you signed a fidelity pledge
promising to be faithful to your wife.
- Now hold it right there.
- Didn't you also make that same pledge
at your three marriage ceremonies?
I find it absolutely disgusting
that the liberal media--
- Fine.
- No, that would be his answer.
I know. Are these guys gonna
be ready for tomorrow?
- Absolutely.
- We blow the mock debate,
we've been doing Casey Anthony
and Anthony Weiner for nothing.
They understand.
The debate is the only reason
we're scared of the numbers.
- Right.
- The only reason.
Right.
We need a Casey Anthony guest
no one else has.
Let me start here.
By any chance does anyone
know anyone who knows anyone
who knows Casey Anthony?
Who?
My roommate Lisa
went to high school with her.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
Why didn't you--
Get her on the show.
She's already been approached by
everyone including the agent.
- Dylan Kagin.
- She doesn't want to talk.
- Convince her.
- She really doesn't want to talk.
Be a producer.
Do you want me to talk to her?
No, I can do it.
When you've got her booked,
let me know so they can start the promos.
Do whatever you have to do.
Okay.
I like it. I do.
But does it say Tonys?
Well, it's the Tonys. You're gonna be
the youngest person there by about 50 years.
You know what I mean, right?
I think it looks spectacular on you.
It's so hard.
I'm just not sure it's for the Tonys.
What about Galliano?
We, um--
We stopped carrying Galliano
after he, you know,
came out in support of the Holocaust.
I mean, I don't agree with him,
but that's no reason to condemn him for life.
If only the Germans had had the same attitude.
I told you on the phone--
- I know, that's why we came in person.
- We?
- I'm just here in charge of morale.
- I'm with a customer.
- We're not in a hurry.
- We're actually in a huge hurry.
And I'm actually at my job
where I work on commission.
And I'm with a customer,
so I'll be done when she's done.
- Is that her?
- You mean the only person in the store?
- Yeah.
Miss, I'm just a random
heterosexual guy
from off the street and I think
that dress looks great on you.
Don't even look at anything else.
Buy that dress and wear
it out of the store.
He's just a--
Don't worry.
- It would have meant more if you'd said you were gay.
- Why is that?
I think I'm gonna try on the Di Santo.
Sure. Can I get you
another glass of wine?
Ooh, I'd love that.
Thank you.
They're counting on me.
You'd be a big exclusive.
It's what's called a get.
It's promotable.
And we need things
that are promotable
so we can get daytime viewers
to stay with us for the story.
Not for nothing, but you've never used
any of those words before.
Well, sure, I have.
But not in that order.
Guys, it makes me sick.
It's an unspeakable horror that's happened.
It's not a television show
and I'm not joining the cast.
And by the way, a week ago you guys
would have said the same exact thing.
- A week ago we weren't fu--
- This is bananas!
Well, the bodice hugs
your body perfectly.
Look how it shows off your legs.
See that?
- I do.
- You just got two inches taller.
- Okay, but the big question--
- Does it say Tonys?
- Miss.
- Oh, God.
That dress screams Tonys.
You're gonna win in that dress.
Oh, God, no.
I'm not a nominee.
That's how good the dress is.
You wear that dress and they'll just start
throwing Tony Awards at your head.
You, I promise,
will have skull contusions
if you wear that dress to the Tonys.
I'd be terrible at this job.
Yeah, I have a McQueen
that you may love.
And you know what?
If you take it right now, it's on the house.
- I'm afraid it's not.
- Well, then it's on me.
- It's $11,000.
- For a dress?!
Once again, I work on commission.
That's three times
what I paid for my car.
- Let me know if you need any help in there.
- Thank you.
A week ago we weren't screwed.
I knew her, that's it.
We cut third period together.
Will's gonna treat you very gently.
Well, guess what--
Did she kill children during Spanish?
- You can provide insight--
- No, I can't.
No, I can't.
I can't provide insight.
I have no earthly idea how she--
How this could have happened.
I can't provide insight and I can't stand
the people who think they can.
Lisa, I need a little help
with these buttons.
Sure.
You know what
these pants cost me?
- $30.
- That's right.
And they look just as good
as the ones that cost $40.
You think they're
kissing in there?
Do you think
they're kissing in there?
If I was a woman,
I'd spend the whole day kissing other women.
I don't understand gay men
or straight women.
You know you're talking out loud, right?
Take a look.
I think it's whimsical and romantic,
but it's still chic.
- I love it.
- Look how it defines your waist.
- I love it!
- We have a winner.
- Can we accessorize?
- No, I'm sorry, miss.
We need to speak to Lisa
for just one minute.
You can browse in the accessories section
and we'll give her right back to you.
This isn't her fault, it's ours.
- Please patronize this store.
- What?
Take a look at the jade earrings
and I'll be right with you.
- Okay.
- Am I not making myself clear?
Lisa, look at me.
You know that there is
no way we'd be asking you
to do something like this
if it wasn't important.
We got ambushed by the trial
at the worst possible time.
There's a new debate format we want to
show to reps from the RNC tomorrow.
And if we can't keep the ratings going up,
it's not gonna matter.
We've been working on this for months
and it's important.
And it's a good thing for everybody.
We can debate whether the ends
justify the means--
Will and Mackenzie are counting on you?
I don't have anything to say.
You won't be asked anything
you don't know the answer to.
Okay, what do I do?
Come to the newsroom at 7:00 tonight.
Oh, thanks. I owe you one.
I owe you more than one.
Let's go.
Um, I don't know if it was clear
from my e-mails and phone calls,
but I've been wooing you.
Still trying to get that second first date.
And yet I can tell from
the way you're staring at me
right now that this
isn't the best moment.
You see that?
I was able to tell without your saying anything.
Our minds are in sync.
But there's not
an ounce of quit in me,
- so I'll woo you when--
- What the hell are you doing?
All right, then.
7:00, it's a date.
Not really. I'm not crazy.
Thank you.
Yeah?
You wanted to see me?
It's 100 degrees outside.
You're wearing a jacket?
Because it's Ice Station
Zebra in my office.
- If you have any fresh fish you need to store--
- Those are yours.
They were delivered
for you this morning.
Jim signed for them
and looked at the card,
which you can see
isn't in an envelope.
Jim signed for them?
He said Maggie didn't see.
She wasn't around.
Maggie and I have broken up a lot
in the last year and a half.
I've--
I've gotten that sense.
- When we break up--
- You go out with other women.
Isn't that what I'm supposed to do?
- I'm not judging you.
- Then we get back together.
Do you tell the other women
that you've gotten back together
with your girlfriend?
We're talking about people that
I've been on one or two dates with.
Does Maggie know that you've been
out with other women?
No.
Does Gina know
that you're with Maggie?
- Jenna.
- Hmm?
Jenna. These are from--
Her name is Jenna.
You remember when
I didn't care at all
about the lives of the people
who worked here?
- Yeah.
- Those were the days.
- Time to go.
- Yeah.
Uh, I can't walk through
the newsroom with these.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thanks.
- Hey, Don.
- Yeah?
I'm doing the right thing, right?
To do a little wrong to do a big right.
Get the debate.
- Was that Shakespeare?
- Almost.
- Okay.
- And I'm doing the right thing?
No. You're either lying to Maggie
or you're lying to Gina.
Jenna. And I just backed you up
with almost Shakespeare.
You couldn't throw me a bone?
I've got to go.
- That was a cliché.
- I know.
But if you stand in the rain without a jacket,
you're gonna get a cold.
And if you have
a physically abusive father
who abandons you
and your family,
you're gonna be 1,000 times
more sensitive to betrayal
than the average person who's already
extremely sensitive to betrayal.
I miss encyclopedias.
I always wanted to have
a full set of encyclopedias.
You know, you pull down S
off the shelf,
flip to a page,
you read about, I don't know,
Salic law and why a woman can't inherit
the French throne.
- You can Google it.
- That's my point.
You have to know
what you're looking for.
You can't browse
for anything anymore.
Anyway, last night I was looking up
signal intelligence intercepts
and whether they leave
a fiber-optic footprint.
Is it important that
I know what that meant?
No. We've got a whistle-blower who's giving us
a big story and we have to vet him.
But what happened was
I was reading about fiber-optic footprints
and a couple of clicks later, I was on
a relationship advice website
called "Help Me Rhonda."
A woman wrote to Rhonda saying that
her husband was cheating on her
and Rhonda suggested that
the woman had to examine
what her role was in the cheating.
It made me crazy.
Do you think it could possibly
have been the woman's fault?
Are we saying that now?
What I don't believe
is that a couple clicks
took you from fiber-optic
footprints to "Help Me Rhonda."
If you went to a relationship
advice website, just say so.
It was the middle of the night.
There was nothing else to read.
Except the entire rest
of the Internet.
Do you and Rhonda honestly believe
that I share some of the blame
or even a small part of the blame
for Mackenzie cheating with Brian?
- Do you?
- No.
Fine.
'Cause that's about
the dumbest thing I've ever read.
And I'll tell you what else,
I don't even think Rhonda's her real name.
- Yeah, look--
- Maybe it is.
I don't know. But she's a moron.
You weren't part of the equation.
Ruined a perfectly good Beach Boys song.
Wait, what do you mean?
I can't really assess
someone I haven't met.
Then why did you say it?
Because I can assess
someone I haven't met.
My father left me volumes
on the two of you.
I had to get an extra filing cabinet.
How was I not part of the equation?
Mackenzie got dumped by Brian.
She got rejected.
People react to that in different ways.
When Brian started calling her again,
she saw the chance to get
unrejected and she took it.
You weren't even part of the equation.
But once she got unrejected,
she realized
that she wasn't in love
with Brian in the first place,
that she was in love with you,
and she confessed the whole thing.
- Not right away.
- Who cares about not right away?
When she thought you were
going to propose to her--
Do you remember when I came
in here yesterday without an appointment
and interrupted your session
with another patient?
I do remember that.
It was yesterday.
And you said that the trick was
to forgive Mackenzie.
- Yeah.
- I actually know that.
Intellectually, in my brain,
I know Mackenzie deserves to be forgiven.
I understood everything you said.
I understand she's taken every
punishment I've given her,
including having Brian hang around
the office and write his story.
I understand she's completely
devoted to the show.
I understand mistakes.
I understand time has passed.
I understand all of that.
So why can't I forgive her?
Because you weren't rejected.
You were betrayed.
How's it going, Sampat?
Well, the problem with people
who post on EconomyBrain
is they're not easily distracted.
Damn those economists
and their adult attention spans.
They're not making it easy for me.
But a popular discussion at the moment
is a recent article projecting
US credit rating fallout
as a result of the debt ceiling standoff.
Yes, I heard that on the news.
No, wait, I didn't.
I heard about Casey Anthony instead.
Well, that's where I jumped in.
I said if I can balance my checkbook,
why can't the government
balance its budget?
Mary, Mother of God,
am I sick of that insane analogy.
Balancing your checkbook
is to balancing the budget
as driving to the supermarket
is to landing on the moon!
See?
Ah.
- I got you a little upset.
- Yes.
So once they were hooked on
telling me how stupid I am,
- I steered things in your direction.
- How?
- You really want to know?
- No.
- Good.
- Tell me anyway.
I said the media and government
are in a conspiracy cahoots--
- Conspiracy cahoots?
- I have to sound authentically moronic.
How are the media and the government
in a conspiracy cahoots?
By shoving your breasts in our face.
- Many angry posters came to your defense.
- Good.
- So I created a second user account.
- Of course.
And asserted it wasn't your breasts
that were so compelling,
- it was your blatantly slutty body movements.
- What evidence do you use--
I posted a link on your Wikipedia page
detailing your rise
from small-town stripper to big-time
financial news reporter.
- My Wikipedia page doesn't say that.
- Check again.
You're going to see an emotional response
on my face and a physical
response directed at yours.
It worked.
After two hours,
I had economic PhDs posting in all caps.
And then the site administrator
froze the thread.
All right.
And this is enough to get you accepted
- into the fraternity of the pitiful?
- Almost.
There's a sort of pledge process
for the fraternity of the pitiful.
And this will get me to level one.
Once I do that, I can get to level two
and swim with the professional trolls.
You're gonna be a good reporter.
And I like that someone
is working on news stories.
Well, for what it's worth,
I could really get behind a government
that was in a cahoots conspiracy
to shove your breasts in our face.
Aw.
Re-edit my Wikipedia page!
Soon.
He's on his way.
All right, what do you know so far?
- You got Lisa for tonight.
- They've already started promoing it.
What do you have on the NSA source?
He's not rock solid.
Shit.
He didn't do well on
his latest psych assessment.
- Oh, Christ.
- They lowered his security clearance.
He also violated a restraining order.
- An ex-wife?
- Yeah.
And he was arrested for solicitation in 1979.
- If you had this guy on a witness stand--
- I wouldn't put him on a witness stand.
Wait a minute.
He didn't score well on his psych exam,
but they didn't fire him.
They just lowered his security clearance.
Yes, he's stalking his ex-wife and, yes,
he tried to pick up a hooker,
but that doesn't mean
he's lying about the NSA.
All we have are the transcripts
of his testimony
and his testimony
doesn't mean anything to me yet.
Keep working.
- Excuse me.
- Which one of us?
Both.
- I'm gonna speak in code.
- Why?
Because neither of you
can suggest to a guest
what they should say on the air.
- Okay. I understand.
- You do?
We've got Lisa.
We've promo'd her.
- She's done her job.
- She still has to show up.
But you don't care what she says
once she does.
I don't.
So do me a favor.
This is for me.
Get some statistics on the number
of missing children cases this year?
Yes, please.
And leave them for me
in the hair and makeup room.
- You understood that?
- Yeah, I cracked your code.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Jim, tell her she needs
a little blush to accentuate
those gorgeous cheekbones.
She refuses to listen.
I'm not auditioning for Dancing With the Stars.
My cheekbones are fine.
She's fine.
Could you give us the room a second?
We're in a Vulcan mind meld again.
I can tell this is a bad time to ask--
Maggie's my best friend.
She's actually my only friend, I think.
And I'd chop off my ears
before I'd hurt her.
You're basing this all
on the premise that--
Don's a good guy
who's not in love with her.
She knows it.
You're on deck, pal.
I've been on deck for a year.
I'm nobody's second choice.
Neither am I.
- Well, I-- I wasn't implying--
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
- Fine.
Listen, why don't you
take a look at this?
You can take that out there
with you if you want.
Keep it right on the desk.
Will and Mackenzie won't mind?
I'll see you after.
- I was gonna say--
- I want to learn this.
Please.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You don't have to say
anything you don't mean.
Okay.
I'm joined now
by Lisa Lambert,
a friend of Casey Anthony's
from high school.
- Good evening, Lisa.
- Good evening.
- Did you know Casey well?
- I didn't.
And neither did any of the other people
showing up on TV claiming they did.
- But you took classes with her?
- Wow.
- Yes.
- Did she ever lose her temper?
Yeah, and when she did,
we all said,
"Oh, my God,
she's gonna kill her baby one day."
Fair enough. Let me ask you--
There were 80 million children
reported missing last year.
Actually,
I think you mean 800,000.
Yes.
80 million would be way too many.
And I understand.
But this one involves a murder.
Olivia Garcia was one year old
when she mysteriously died
at her babysitter's house.
But Olivia Garcia had brown skin,
so we're not that interested.
Same with Triumph Skinner,
a seven-month-old
African-American who was rushed
to the hospital with a crushed skull.
For some reason he's not keeping
Nancy Grace up at night.
Where are you getting these facts?
Google.
Jariel Alexander died
after being knocked unconscious
by his mother's boyfriend,
then scalded with boiling water
after soiling his pants at dinner.
But Jariel's mother isn't pretty,
so what do we care?
I think you're making a very good point.
- Then I'd like to make one more.
- Mm-hmm.
What if Casey Anthony
had wanted an abortion?
- She didn't want an abortion!
- Don't.
- She told you that?
- No, I haven't spoken to her in years.
- I'm just asking.
- Is this you?
- No.
- Do the people who care so deeply
about the life of a microscopic
piece of biology
with no ability to experience physical
or emotional suffering
care at all about a two-year-old
who was born to a mother
who didn't want the child
and was unable to care for her?
Help her out of this.
Lisa, I just want to be
clear for the viewers
that you're not saying
Casey's only two options
were abortion
or murdering a toddler.
I'm saying that
there's an undiscussed
and unappreciated cruelty
in forcing a child
to be born to a mother
who doesn't want the child
and isn't capable
of raising the child.
Okay, let's get back to what
Casey was like in high school.
Where's a power outage
when you really need one?
What's wrong?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- How'd they know where you were?
- Her Facebook page.
- Shut the page down.
- I'll take care of it.
Hey.
- Is she all right?
- Where's Lonny?
You shouldn't be out alone.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Are you mad I didn't tell you
I was gonna do that?
No.
I know you're pro-life.
I'm not pro throwing
a brick through a window.
There are gonna be local
news trucks here any second.
- Get her out of here.
- You, too.
Is that your boss?
The owner of the shop?
I'm gonna talk to her.
This should have been me
and not you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Teddy, is there something
different about these pants?
Different from what?
Every time I wear that suit,
I mean every time,
I put both my legs
into one side of the pants.
One side of the pants?
I stand up, I put one leg into one side,
and then I take my other leg
and I'm certainly aiming
for the other side of the pants,
but I get stuck.
And I'm asking
if there's something,
not so much wrong,
but different about those pants.
You can't put your pants on
and you think
there's something wrong
with the pants?
All right, get out.
- Adam Roth is here.
- Yes.
- Adam!
- Rock star.
- How you doing, man?
- I'm good.
- How's Emily?
- The whole family's great.
David got into Stanford,
so thanks for the recommendation.
I wrote him a pretty bad recommendation.
I'm surprised they took him.
They must not care that much
about what you think.
This is my partner at the RNC,
- Tate Brady.
- Nice to meet you.
- How do you do?
- Excellent.
Charlie Skinner, Mackenzie McHale,
this is Adam Roth.
Will talks about you like you were
bunkmates at summer camp.
Well, we were,
but the summer camp was the White House
and there was no bunk
or sleep of any kind.
I was Bush 41's body man
right out of college
and Will was writing greeting cards
or something in the communications office.
I wrote serious policy speeches.
For the Muncie Chamber of Commerce.
They were good speeches.
And the president adopted Will
as the fourth son he never had.
The president knew my name
and that's thanks to Adam.
I'm sorry.
This is his partner Greg Brady.
- Tate.
- I'm sorry, Tate.
Everybody sit down.
Anybody need coffee or anything?
- I'm okay.
- I'm good.
So we're glad to see your numbers
rebounded from last week.
We hadn't been covering Casey Anthony
and half our audience went to HLN.
But we started covering it
and things stabilized.
Well, good, because we were about
ready to offer a debate to Nancy Grace.
So the rules of the debate
are pretty simple.
There is some room for you to make
a few choices, but not much.
Everybody gets an opening statement.
Everybody gets at least two questions
with 60 seconds to answer
and it's up to you whether you want to
offer someone a rebuttal.
We had something different in mind.
What'd you have in mind?
Adam, how many hours
did you and I spend
talking about how flawed
the debates were?
Especially the primary debates?
A lot of hours.
Well, now you and I are in a position
to do something about that.
Follow me.
The questions have to be tougher.
They have to be able to square
their campaign rhetoric with facts.
They have to be stopped when
they're not answering the question.
And they have to be called out
when their answers contradict the facts.
Guys, get in place.
Our job is to find the two candidates
who'll give the voters
the best competing arguments,
and I don't believe we're seeing that.
We have to put the candidates
on a witness stand.
- Would you have them swear an oath?
- Just let 'em do it.
If baseball players testifying about steroids
in front of a House Subcommittee
are subject to perjury,
I don't know why presidential
candidates aren't.
But I'm not reaching for the stars,
I'm reaching just an inch higher.
Welcome to Princeton University
in Princeton, New Jersey,
for the fifth debate in the
2012 Republican primary race,
cosponsored by Atlantis Cable News
and the Republican Party of New Jersey.
At which point we'll explain the rules,
which is there are no rules.
I question a candidate until I'm done.
They can each make
an opening statement.
Beginning with you,
Congresswoman Bachmann.
Hi, my name is Michele Bachmann.
I'm a former federal tax
litigation attorney,
the owner of a successful company,
and also a member--
Hang on. Is that supposed to be a
Michele Bachmann impersonation?
No, nobody's doing impressions.
This isn't an SNL sketch.
These people have spent two months
studying stump speeches,
interviews, on-the-record statements,
previous debate performances
in order to come as close
as possible to answering
our questions the way
the candidates would.
After the opening statements,
we'd move to questioning.
Senator Santorum,
you said that your campaign
is about freedom
and that 20 years from now
you don't want to be
telling your grandchildren
how America once was free.
Name three freedoms
you had the day before
President Obama was sworn in
that you don't have now.
Obamacare, to begin with.
Obamacare is the most egregious--
Have you had to
change doctors?
- May I finish?
- No, sir.
- Have you had to change doctors?
- No.
Has anyone in your family
had to change doctors?
Has there been any change at all
in health care for you or your family?
I'm talking about
Obamacare now.
My question was name
three freedoms that you had
the day before the president was sworn in
that you don't have now.
Mr. Speaker, you just said
that if you're elected,
the price of gas will be $2.50 a gallon.
How does the US President
control the price of oil?
Governor, you've said that as president
you will never apologize for America.
This question is in two parts.
Name an instance
in which the president
has apologized for America
and can you imagine no instance
in which a US president
should apologize for America?
Mr. McAvoy, I find it reprehensible
that the liberal media would try to pit
Republicans against one another.
And I, for one,
won't stand by while it happens.
This is the Republican primary,
Mr. Speaker,
and you're running for the nomination.
It wasn't my idea to pit you against anyone.
It was yours.
Congressman Paul,
I'd like to discuss the newsletters
you wrote and sold
starting in the 1990s.
I've already said
everything I have to say.
I never wrote those letters
and I never even read them.
They had your name on them.
They had your signature on them.
You made money from them.
And in 1996 you defended them
to the Dallas Morning News.
- I don't like pretending--
- Stop. Everybody stop.
There's no need to go
along any further.
I see where you're going.
- Adam.
- Listen--
Is there someplace we can talk privately?
Take my office.
Adam.
I think they really liked it.
You did a good job, everybody.
Give me a minute.
- I told you, this guy--
- This guy what?
Wasn't on the team.
- He's on the team, okay?
- Hang on.
The team I'm on is the voters'
and smart, qualified people
disagreeing about issues.
Your plan was to embarrass
the candidates.
I want candidates who can
answer those questions.
And if they know they're going to be
held responsible for the nonsense
they're shouting on the stump,
they'll be forced to stop shouting nonsense.
- This guy has lost his mind.
- He hasn't.
Adam, this is exactly what
we always talked about.
This is what we dreamed of.
We said we need
real campaign reform
and a way of letting Americans hear
the two best competing arguments.
Nobody could stand up
to that kind of questioning.
- You think that was brutal questioning?
- It really wasn't.
And you honestly believe the candidates
would submit themselves to this?
- They should welcome it.
- I don't believe what I'm hearing.
Any candidate who can handle a cross
is gonna find himself at the top of the polls
in the morning.
And we should welcome
it 'cause it'll clear out the clown car
and give us a serious discussion
among serious candidates.
The only person who would
welcome it is him.
This is about him.
He wants to look tough
by making the candidates
look like idiots.
No, he doesn't. I have known this man
for 25 years and I vouch--
I don't care what you vouch for.
I am not allowing the goddamn press
to make fools out of our candidates.
I'll remember that the next time you bitch
about how the press never vetted Obama.
We're not agreeing to this format.
You are going to abide
by the rules that we give you
and I don't want Mackenzie McHale
producing it for you.
What are you talking about?
I want the old Will McAvoy.
Not the thing she turned you into.
I know all about that lady.
- Get out.
- Will, come on. You need the debate.
Of course he can use Mackenzie.
These guys have been compromising
and compromising all week
so we could host a debate that made
some sense and did some good.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that,
because it was all for nothing.
- We need ACN.
- No, we don't.
They've got the independents.
He's not the only anchor at ACN.
- Don Keefer.
- Yeah?
How would you and Elliot Hirsch like
to have one of the debates?
Eat me.
- Mr. Skinner, I'm trying to be as--
- When Don says, "Eat me,"
that's usually the end of the conversation.
Sloan Sabbith.
- You want to be a star?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Fuck you.
I hate these guys.
I don't know why you don't.
And I'll be in the car.
I'm really sorry.
I can't be out of work.
- Tuition at Stanford is--
- No, I know.
It was good seeing you.
You, too.
All those things
we talked about...
Yeah.
Don't let 'em push you around.
You take it easy.
I'm sorry, everyone.
We lost the debate.
I'm sorry.
We've got about an hour to air.
Let's put it together.
He'll cave.
He'll agree to the debate on their terms.
- No, he won't.
- You romanticize Will.
- Mm-hmm.
- That mock debate was about him.
He was the star.
He attacked his--
He didn't attack anybody.
He asked questions that the candidates
should be able to answer
and that the voters should
be able to hear them answer.
He didn't cower
and he wasn't Ed McMahon.
Thinking there was
even a remote chance--
- Maybe it was naive.
- It wasn't naive, it was hubris.
It was gutsy
and you're just jealous.
Jealous of what?
You know, fuck you, Mac.
I've spent this week
letting you kick my ass
from here to the Chrysler Building
because you were selling out
every 15 minutes to get your hands on
something you didn't get.
And you were embarrassed
by it in front of me.
He doesn't want you.
Please don't talk
about my personal life.
I'm sort of a key player in it.
Is it all right if I talk
about my personal life?
Yes, I broke up with you.
I'm the first guy ever
to break up with a woman.
And then I came back.
Also unprecedented.
Did he come back?
I don't know yet.
Seriously?
After four years?
In Castaway, Helen Hunt got remarried
in less time than--
I never would have gone
with the Casey Anthony story.
I don't care how much
of my audience I was losing.
And he's gonna cave
on the debate, too.
- Are you sure about that?
- I am absolutely sure about that.
You know what I like about Will?
He's not absolutely sure about anything.
He struggles with things.
He's never certain he's right
and sometimes he's not.
But he tries hard to be.
He struggles with things.
God!
Will, are you all right?
Could somebody help Will
put his pants on?
I don't think this is gonna work out.
- The story?
- Yeah.
That's Will's call.
Excuse me.
How's it going there?
There's something off
with these pants.
I think maybe considering everything
that's gone on here
this week, you should reconsider
having Brian write the piece.
- Can you handle him being here?
- I can handle him being here.
- But I think--
- I brought him in here to punish you.
- I know.
- I think I may have also brought him in here
- so you could see a side-by-side comparison.
- You're an idiot.
- Hey, these are really hard pants.
- Not the pants.
I have cooperated with
and been the engine behind
an instant dismantling of everything
we've built and everything we stand for.
I've ignored serious stories
so we can get down in the gutter
with the Casey Anthony circus
and the Anthony Weiner distraction.
And I've done it all
while Brian's been standing
over my shoulder
because you put him there.
And you pass on the debate
because that guy insulted me?
Who are you?!
I don't know where your head is at
at any given moment!
I am this close to losing it!
I think I have!
I think it's happening right now!
- Settle down.
- I will not settle down!
I should, though. I should settle down.
Remember your first day here,
the BP spill?
Yeah.
Remember when I said
throw out the rundown?
- Yeah.
- Did you think that was cool?
Yeah.
Throw out the rundown.
Wait, no.
We still need the numbers.
We've got to protect you from Leona.
Yeah, I can't live with a 15-year-old girl
being the toughest guy at my desk.
- Are you talking about Lisa?
- Yeah.
- She's 26.
- They all look 15 to me. Sloan.
- Are you sure about this?
- Not at all.
- Yeah?
- If I ask you the right questions,
can you talk about the debt ceiling
for two segments tonight?
- I don't even need the questions.
- Get ready.
Can you handle Brian being here
a little while longer?
I can handle anything.
- Jellyfish.
- I don't like jellyfish.
- Brian.
- Yeah?
Just write the truth, okay?
Just write the truth.
We're throwing out the rundown
and leading with the debt ceiling.
- You get all that?
- Yeah.
Is it working?
No.
They're laughing at me.
They think
I'm a small-time troll.
- That's got to hurt.
- It does.
It's too bad you're not the guy
who left the death threat for Will.
That's a dangerous area.
Yeah.
Jim?
Yeah?
Whatever happened with you and Lisa?
Uh, she doesn't want to go out with me.
I gave it a try.
A try?
Yeah.
"Gather ye rosebuds."
You know what that means?
It's the first half of the first line
of a poem by Robert Herrick.
What's the second half?
"While ye may."
"Gather ye rosebuds while ye may."
I'm gonna.
"Then be not coy but use your time,
and while ye may go marry.
For having lost but once your prime,
you may forever tarry."
- I won't.
- Okay.
- First we have to do the show.
- Yeah.
You're 100% sure?
It was a year ago.
It was over a year ago.
He was the new guy in the office
and Don and I were in a terrible place.
So I had a stupid crush on him
for five minutes.
He was nice to me
even though I was mean to him,
so I thought maybe
he liked me, too.
But that's just over,
and he's really trying hard with you.
- So if you like him...
- Of course I like him.
There's no way to fix
the air conditioning.
Your choices are
90 degrees or 30 degrees.
Who's here at midnight?
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Jim.
Come on up.
We never got to the God question.
Bachmann said that God told her to run
and Maggie wanted Will to ask her
what God's voice sounded like.
I think it would have sealed it for us.
If every network said,
"We're not playing by your rules.
You're playing by ours,"
we'd raise the level of debate overnight.
It wasn't as crazy as it sounded.
It was exactly as crazy as it sounded.
Good luck.
- Hi.
- I wanted to talk to--
- Hey, man.
Hey, Don.
- I did-- I didn't know that you'd--
- Maggie talked me into it.
I'm sorry?
You don't have to pitch me.
Maggie talked me into it.
- Let's go for a walk.
- Listen--
Let's go.
Nice ending, don't you think?
He had a whole speech
he didn't get to use.
Don?
Hmm?
What is it?
He said,
"I wanted to talk to--"
and then I cut him off.
What are you--
Lisa wasn't the one
he came here to see.
I don't--
He signed for the flowers.
What?
I have to explain something.
Congresswoman Bachmann, to you.
Elvis or Johnny Cash?
Oh, that's really tough.
That's really-- Both.
Both.
- Both?
- Yeah, I've got "Christmas With Elvis" on my iPod.
All right, now we know what's
on the congresswoman's iPod.
This is Lonny.
- Lonny, it's Neal.
- Yeah?
I'm sorry to call you so late,
but I need to tell you
about something that's
on my computer right now.
I've been working on this story,
and without going into too many details...
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net