Will, there's a comment on
your website you need to see.
"I got a bullet for you, too.
You think I'm fuckin' around?"
Charlie, I want a body on him
until this guy's in handcuffs.
- No way.
- You're not gonna have a choice.
- The insurance company makes that call.
- How does this work?
I'm with you any place that isn't
your home or your office.
Speaking of your roommate,
I had a great idea.
I'm fixing her up with Jim.
This is Maggie's roommate Lisa.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
We're not in a relationship.
She calls me at night and she says,
"Should I come over?"
- And what am I supposed to say?
- You say yes.
- Am I losing Maggie?
- No.
Are you good at knowing
these things?
No.
This whole file here.
Every page is about Mackenzie.
You've had a lot going on
for a long time.
Very serious stuff.
You're being hunted.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
How did you get this number?
- That's not important.
- It's important to me.
Charlie, this is the first
of several calls
and its only purpose
is to demonstrate
- my credibility as a source.
- How about you tell me your name?
- Call me Deep Throat.
- I'm not calling you Deep Throat.
That's a sacred pseudonym.
And by the way, Deep Throat
gave Woodward his name on the first call.
He said,
"Hi, this is Mark Felt.
I'm the deputy director
of the FBI
and I want to talk to you about
this story you're writing."
- So who is this?
- I don't care what you call me.
Call me late for dinner.
I'm not calling to give you a tip.
I'm simply establishing
my credibility.
But you're not establishing
your credibility.
- I'm about to.
- Go ahead.
In roughly 90 minutes,
you're going to get an email
from the White House
telling you to get to work.
- I am?
- That's it.
Should I be telling people
to get to work now?
- And do what?
- You tell me.
If I could,
I would have already.
I'm not trying to play a game.
I have 7:30.
At 9:00 Eastern,
you're going to get an email
from White House
Press Secretary Jay Carney
telling you to get to work.
And when that happens,
you'll know that I was for real.
- Is anyone in danger?
- No.
If someone's in danger
and you're not telling--
No one's in danger, Charlie.
This isn't a scary call.
I'm just establishing
my credibility.
Why? Why do you need me to
believe you're credible?
Hello?
- What was that?
- I don't know.
You should probably say a few words.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What do I say?
- What do you want to say?
"Please get out of my home"?
Everyone, Will wants
to say a few words.
I really don't.
But here you all are
in my apartment, socializing.
Coworkers, friends, family...
in my apartment
just like in my nightmares.
This is a party to celebrate
the one year and one week
anniversary of what we used
to call News Night 2.0.
Remember that?
I think we're up to about
News Night 174.0,
but I'm confident we're gonna
get it right one of these days.
So have a good time
at the party.
And please, please know,
from the bottom of my heart,
that I'm not gonna think
it's rude if you leave early.
- Good?
- Goose bumps.
Resume being here.
Okay, this is
an Australian actress.
- Nicole Kidman.
- No, she was in Spiderman.
- Time.
- Let me see. It's Christian Bale.
English, Batman, and a man.
Who am I thinking of?
♪ Sunshine go away today... ♪
- Up chickens.
- Down chickens.
- It's not there.
- Not there.
♪ How much does it cost?
I'll buy it. ♪
♪ The time is all we've lost,
I'll try it. ♪
♪ He can't even run his own life. ♪
♪ I'll be damned if he'll run mine. ♪
♪ Sunshine... ♪
♪ Sunshine go away today. ♪
♪ I don't feel much like dancing... ♪
Just to be clear
for you youngsters,
this isn't recreational.
It's medicinal.
When I was a junior in high school,
I was already throwing
a 74-mile-an-hour fastball,
which puts a lot of stress on your landing leg.
I also have epicondylitis in my elbow
due to my mess-you-up breaking ball.
You know, if you just want to bake,
that's okay with me.
You don't need to go to WebMD
to come up with symptoms.
I don't want to bake. I'm telling you
I was an awesome high school athlete,
but it's left me in constant physical pain
in my knee and elbow.
And experts say that medical marijuana
relieves the pain and inflammation
with fewer side effects than
prescription pain killers.
- Which experts?
- The ones on WebMD.
Anyway, thank you and thank your friend
in LA for getting this for me.
No problem.
He said they're pretty strong.
So you should just break off
a quarter and eat that.
And when this guy says they're strong,
they're strong.
I ate two.
Okay.
Well, enjoy yourself
and we'll see you
in 12 to 14 hours.
It's fine.
I have incredibly high tolerance.
That's why I can't feel
the Vicodin.
You took Vicodin
and then ate two cookies?
- Mm-hmm.
- He's fine. You're fine.
Just stay away
from anything dangerous.
Electricity.
You know, outside.
I'm fine.
I don't feel it at all.
- You will.
- We'll see.
My body has the physical
tolerance of 10 men.
Doctors have called me
a medical marvel.
Yeah, I'd just lie down.
But if you want
to see a real marvel,
Kaylee is going to play
Jim at Guitar Hero
and Kaylee is gonna
be blindfolded.
- You should come watch.
- I will.
Look at this.
It's from Mike Tapley.
"I'm available. Call me."
That's how you ask someone out?
What time do you have?
8:25.
Ooh, boo, I just buzzed.
Can you check my phone? It's in my back pocket.
It might be Jim's mom
begging me to stop.
I can play an actual guitar.
All you have to do is declare
my supremacy and I'll stop.
It's your incoming Twitter feeds.
Oh, read them to me.
And someone tell me if Jim's holding back tears.
Someone named Monster has a link
to some epic photographs.
- Steve Martin says, "I like my antiques new."
- Funny.
And the Rock's tweeting,
"Just got word that will shock the world.
Land of the free, home of the brave.
Damn proud to be an American."
Guess Fast Five
just won the weekend.
No, that means
he's coming back.
The Rock is coming back to lay
the smack down on Triple H.
Stop playing.
You lost like 10 minutes ago.
Hey.
Somebody said you were in here
working on a Sunday night
during a party and
I had no trouble believing it.
I was just securing
the video overnights.
It's okay.
It's weird how
the video overnights
look so much like
the Mets-Phillies game.
Isn't it?
- It's Lisa. You should take it.
- It's okay.
She's supposed to be here.
Maybe something happened.
I'm sure she's just
blowing up her hair.
- Blowing out her hair?
- Is that what it is?
Yeah.
Take the call.
I think she's gone.
Hi, Lis'.
Hey, did I call
the wrong computer?
No, your man is right here.
- He was just watching some porn.
- Nope.
- Where are you?
- Five minutes away.
I'm walking. I've got FaceTime on my phone.
Can you see me?
You should be looking in front of you
while you're walking or you're gonna--
- What? I'm-- Oof!
- Whoa, sorry.
- Are you okay?
- No worries. No worries.
- Okay, have a good night.
- You okay?
Yeah, I walked into a pedestrian
who also has FaceTime on his phone.
Please don't cross any streets.
I was gonna call you and then
I saw you were online.
- Aren't I coming to a party?
- Absolutely.
- I just needed to do some work.
- Watch some porn.
- Mets-Phillies?
- Only to check the score.
Hey, check it out.
I've got a new expression I want to try.
You ready?
It's a gas.
- I like it.
- Try it.
- It's a gas.
- Nope. Terrible.
You can't do it.
I'm almost there.
- It'll be a gas.
- Seriously, no.
- All right.
- All right, I'll be there in a minute.
- I love you.
- And I do, too.
Yeah, maybe if you stare at
that piece of paper long enough,
the time will reverse itself
and the last 10 seconds will
be erased from the universe.
All right, first of all,
can we agree
that sometimes being this connected
by technology does more harm--
I love you and I do, too?
Here's what happened.
Lisa told me she loved me last night.
- She did?
- Yes.
- She does that too early.
- I completely agree.
Save your agreement 'cause I don't think
we're gonna be on the same side on this one.
How do you feel about that?
Her? How do you feel about her?
- I don't feel the same way.
- You don't?
I like her.
She's really nice
and really funny
and incredibly sexy.
Really very sexy with
the sexiness that--
- I get it.
- And I like the new expression.
- It's a gas.
- Don't even.
- But I don't love her.
- You don't?
No.
So what did you say when she said,
"I love you"?
- I said, "I love you, too."
- Of course you did.
- Anything else seemed rude.
- And then you just told her again.
No, what I said was,
"And I do, too."
Which means that I love me.
And I do. I look in the mirror
and I like what I see.
I've been on a journey of self-discovery
to answer the question who is Jim Harper--
- Shut up.
- Okay.
You can't keep telling her
you love her if you don't.
Which is why, frankly,
I would have preferred not to take the call.
You think blaming me is gonna
be a winning strategy?
- No.
- What are you gonna do now?
Well, obviously I have
to leave the country.
- You have to break up with her.
- Why?
You can't have a relationship
where one person's here
and the other person's there.
Really?
Where's Don?
Don's on a plane back from DC
- and was that a dig wrapped in a metaphor?
- No.
- I think it was a dig wrapped in a metaphor.
- I have to break up with her?
Yes.
You don't think that's going to come
as a surprise after I told her I loved her?
I do, yes.
I think it'll be a surprise.
I'll write her a nice letter.
- No!
- Everybody likes getting mail.
You're not overseas
fighting World War I.
You have to do it in person
and you have to do tonight.
- In the middle of a party?
- No.
When she gets here,
you'll tell her you'd like to take a walk.
Hang on.
- And she's not that sexy.
- Yeah, she is.
Just because of her sweet face?
Yeah, that's it.
- I think--
- It's from Mike Tapley.
"I'm available. Call me."
Why would Tapley
want me to call him?
I mean, I get that she has
physical attributes that are prized by--
Hey. Tapley?
Our own National Security analyst.
Stay here and look around and
find out what he's talking about.
- Where do I start?
- Start by emailing him back
and asking,
"What are you talking about?"
Do not take a tone with me,
American Gigolo.
I wasn't tak--
- Hey, listen.
- Sing more.
No, I just got a strange email
from Mike Tapley.
- So did I.
- It said, "I'm available. Call me."
Why is he hitting on both of us?
He's not hitting on either one of you.
He's saying he's available
to go on the air.
- For what?
- When?
- Now.
- What are you talking about?
Wait for it.
- "Get to work."
- Who's it from?
The White House.
What does yours say?
"POTUS to address
the country at 10:30 EST
on matter of national security."
Hang on.
- It's Kaylee, right?
- What's wrong?
The Rock,
he has a cousin who's a Navy SEAL?
- Yeah.
- And tell me what his tweet said.
Um...
"Just got word that will
shock the world.
Land of the free, home of the brave.
Damn proud to be an American."
- He's coming back to avenge Triple H.
- No, he's not.
Everybody, quiet down.
Will, turn off the music.
Turn it off.
Martin, throw me the remote.
It's right next to you.
You're fine.
Martin, throw me the remote.
It's right next to you.
The president's speaking
in 90 minutes on a matter
of national security.
That's all we know right now.
30 minutes from now,
I want to know a lot more than that.
Four people to a cab.
Let's go.
What do you think it is?
It could be Gaddafi.
It could be Iran.
They could have fired
on a ship in the Gulf.
Jimmy Carter just got
back from North Korea.
He could have learned something.
We could be under attack.
But what do you think it is?
I think we got bin Laden.
- How many people does your lift hold?
- What?
Your elevator,
how many people can it hold?
- Six.
- Call down to the doorman.
- Just up and down, no stops.
- Yeah. Lonny!
I'm bringing the car around.
You stand in the lobby.
- Do not go out on the sidewalk.
- Yeah.
Guys, get Lonny in the elevator.
- Right.
- What is going on?
There's breaking news
and we don't know what it is,
but the president's
gonna go on TV at 10:30.
- You don't know what it is?
- No.
Can I come watch?
I'll sit in the corner.
Sure. Yeah.
But once you're there,
you can't leave and you can't
communicate with anyone.
Okay.
What do you think is going on?
We don't know.
But I have to be honest,
it can only be very good
or very bad.
It's almost, I don't know.
It's almost--
- Like she's trying too hard.
- Yeah.
Like she's trying too hard to
show you everything's fine.
It's almost like that.
It's right near being like that.
What are you guys
talking about?
- Don thinks that Maggie...
- Too loud.
- is trying too hard to create the appearance...
- Way too loud.
- ...that she's happy in their relationship.
- Full plane. Man right here.
You've been yammering about
your love life for two weeks.
- Wow, also bizarrely loud.
- Including last night's Correspondents' Dinner.
I'm a financial news reporter and
the Secretary of the Treasury
turned around and said,
"When's he gonna shut up about Maggie?"
That was really
embarrassing for me
and it came right after
I accidentally set him on fire.
Hey, don't turn on your phones yet.
- We haven't touched the ground.
- I turn mine on at 500 feet.
I turn mine on when I see
someone else turn theirs on.
It messes with the navigation.
The runway is right
in front of him.
Do you use your car's
navigation system
to get from your driveway
to your garage?
I don't have a driveway,
a garage, or a car,
but why don't we assume
the pilot knows--
Hey, sir, can you
take his phone away?
He's endangering your life and
the lives of the other passengers.
I'm not. I'm not.
She set the Treasury Secretary on fire.
- It's true.
- Why?
Just to show the other
cabinet secretaries that I could.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to New York's LaGuardia Airport
where the current time is
seven minutes past 9:00.
- We ask that you...
- You okay now?
Or are you worried
he can't find the airport from here?
I'm all about safety.
Yeah, I'm sure if we
went to the burn unit,
Timothy Geithner would say that--
Damn it.
My phone was on the whole time.
It's out of juice.
Could you guys scroll
through your messages
and see if there's
anything I need to know?
It's my daughter.
"Daddy, are you the smartest man in the world?"
- Yes.
- Scroll.
"Miss Sabbith,
a lady always buttons her top button.
If you buttoned your collar on television,
you would be a lady.
If you spilled water all over your front,
I would like that, too."
It's a fan.
- Scroll, scroll.
- Shit.
Jesus.
Hey, do you have this?
Excuse me, would you mind just
switching seats with that woman?
- We're almost at the gate.
- I know it sounds crazy, but would you do it for me?
Well, can I get your number?
- No.
- Sure. I will give you her number.
- If you'd just give me a chance--
- How old are you?
- I'm old enough.
- I will give you a chance.
Your first test is will you switch seats
without asking for anything in return?
- Yes.
- Excuse me.
You have to stay seated
until we're at the gate.
- Points for trying?
- Throw me your phone.
- You think they're still at the party?
- Not anymore.
Guys, wait till
we're off the plane.
There's just too much
we don't know
and too many words
we don't want to say out loud.
- What's going on?
- See?
No, I mean the plane's stopping.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the captain.
Well, no good deed
goes unpunished.
We arrived 10 minutes early and ground
traffic control doesn't have a gate for us.
No, no, no.
It'll be just a few minutes and
then we'll have you on your way.
All right, you guys
mind switching seats now?
Remember, I've already proven
myself with the first test.
Excuse me.
- You have to stay seated.
- But we're stopped.
We're still on the taxiway.
You have to stay seated until the captain
turns off the seat belt sign.
Ma'am, this is a bit
of an emergency.
Sir, FAA rules require
passengers to stay seated...
- Sure.
- ...with their seat belts fastened
until we're safely at
the gate and the captain...
- Got it.
- ...has turned off the seat belt sign.
It's not just for your safety.
You could fall into one of the other passengers.
- Understood, ma'am.
- Please don't make me tell you again.
If I can just say this:
We're stopped. Right?
And the pilot just said
that it would be a few minutes.
Now, if the plane does start moving
while my colleague and...
- Lester.
- ...Lester are changing seats,
it'll be going two miles an hour.
Up there, you let us stand and move around
and we were going like 550.
So I thought maybe
we could apply logic
and see where that took us.
Insulting me is not
gonna help you out much.
- I wasn't insulting you.
- I can't get anybody to answer their phone.
You're calling people
who are on the subway.
Call people who are in taxis.
You have to let us
off this plane.
I'm not letting you
unbuckle your seat belt.
You think I'm
letting you off the plane?
If you know what we know--
which is nothing--
you'd be behind us
and they'd be behind us
and I think later on tonight
you're gonna be saying,
"I wish I'd been more cooperative
with that passenger."
I think later on tonight
you're gonna be saying,
"These handcuffs hurt my wrists."
All right, she's not easy.
I need information now.
If they knew more,
they'd be telling us, right?
We'll keep calling the desk,
but I think we're just gonna have to wait.
Waiting, patience--
Words like that, always my last option.
Borrow somebody's phone
and start dialing.
Lester.
Andy, listen,
most of my staff are kids.
Five years ago, half of them were
editing their college newspapers.
- Will, we can't--
- You just got to give me a little guidance.
We think it's bin Laden.
If we're wrong, just wave me off.
I can't do any waving.
All right, we're gonna do a Carl Bernstein
from All the President's Men.
I'm gonna say it's bin Laden
and I'm gonna count to 10.
If you don't say anything,
that's what we're pursuing.
Ready? One...
Two...
Wait a second.
That's where they fucked up in the movie.
- I've got to go, man.
- No, he didn't--
The guy misunderstood
the directions.
Andy?
We're not moving.
- There's construction.
- On a Sunday night?
They do it on Sunday night so they
don't inconvenience people.
This is gonna be a great city
once they finish building it.
Just sit tight.
What are we, 22 blocks away?
I'm gonna get you there.
I'm gonna run.
- No, you're not.
- I can run fast.
You can't get out of
the car without me.
I see you thinking about it.
Do not do it.
What are you putting
that in your pocket for?
Motherfucker!
Get back here!
You are not safe out here!
McAvoy, get back!
God damn it.
- Sir, is there a problem?
- There's a guy running west.
- He's gonna go north on 5th.
- Just calm down.
I'm calm, Officer.
But that man cannot--
- Please step back in your vehicle.
- The keys are inside.
Could you just move it
over to the side?
- I'm private security.
- Calm down and step back.
- Please, listen to me.
- Turn around and place your hands on the car.
- Officer.
- I'm gonna kill him.
- What was that?
- Officers, I'm armed.
- He said he's armed.
- Put your hands on the car.
- I'm licensed to carry.
And there's a weapon
currently on your person?
Under my jacket
on my left side.
It's loaded with the safety on.
My carry permit's in
my back right pocket.
I work for Blue North Security and
my client is at large.
You're a big guy, okay?
Don't do anything that's gonna make us nervous.
Nothing I can do about being big and
black at the same time.
You guys,
you can sit anywhere over here.
The kitchen is back there with...
- with, uh...
- Pop-Tarts.
Why did you choose Pop-Tarts?
I don't know, but you were never
gonna finish that sentence.
Just sit tight.
And remember,
you're not gonna hear.
Please and thank you a lot.
How long does it take
to get the studio warmed up?
15 minutes. And the control room
is warming up right now.
You talking to DC?
They'll start rolling
coverage in 20 minutes.
- Of what?
- A live shot of the White House.
Let them know New York's running this
and they don't say a word
- until Charlie says okay.
- Any idea when we're breaking?
President speaks in 45 minutes.
If we know something
before then, we'll go.
Gary.
Have you tried Gary?
Quiet. Quiet!
Let's get organized.
What exactly do we know?
And I mean know.
The president is speaking at 10:30
on a matter of national security.
- What else?
- That's it.
Okay, that's exactly
what we knew 20 minutes ago.
Just to be clear,
he's breaking into the networks, too.
That's Desperate Housewives,
Celebrity Apprentice, Brothers and Sisters.
That's a ton of money
in ad givebacks.
- This can't wait till the morning.
- It's bin Laden, Mac.
We want it to be bin Laden.
Let's not let the wish
be the father of the thought.
Obviously we're
pursuing bin Laden.
But let's just talk about
what else it could be.
- Gaddafi.
- Follow it. Put together a team out there.
A foreign attack.
No one at State or DOD is talking, right?
If they're not clamming up,
they honestly don't know anything.
Who did the Santa Tracker story at Christmas?
Anyone?
When we get the guy from NORAD
on the phone, they report
they're tracking
a big sled with reindeer.
- I did.
- Get him on the phone.
You think the Santa guy
is gonna know something?
I'd be pretty surprised,
but I'm not doing nothing.
What about outside the box?
Way, way outside the box?
- Ahem, all right. Here I go.
- What?
A study published in the
Astrophysical Journal estimates
there are 10 trillion planetary systems
in the known universe.
- Which one are you from?
- She said outside the box.
Then she added way,
way outside the box.
Besides the near certainty that intelligent life
exists outside this planet--
Are you suggesting that we've made contact
with beings from another planet?
Is that your suggestion?
- You said way outside the box.
- Come back in the box.
- The birth certificate.
- What about it?
What if the long form's a forgery and
the president's resigning?
I think it's more likely ET is standing
on the Truman Balcony.
- So should I follow--
- No.
Where's Will?
Okay, where's Elliot?
Elliot, Sloan, and Don--
We're able to communicate with them,
but they're stuck on the tarmac at LaGuardia.
All right, Maggie, dust off the obit
packages for bin Laden.
- Tess, you're on Gaddafi.
- Okay.
Jim, do what you do
and get us new information
and get the bookers to line up
our National Security guys.
You can start with Mike Tapley,
who's available.
Let's go.
What?
The president's gonna tell us
what's going on at 10:30.
He's going to tell us.
What's the virtue
of breaking it
five minutes early?
America thinks bin Laden's alive.
If I can make him dead
one minute sooner,
my entire life in journalism up until this
point will have been worth it.
All right.
I got a White House usher
who says they're bringing
a backup generator
into the East Room.
Mac, he's speaking
from the East Room.
Presidents don't announce
bad news from the East Room.
They do it from the Oval Office
or the Briefing Room.
All right, good.
Listen...
You don't think there's any
chance it's a UFO, do you?
Keep it together, would you?
- She's in the bathroom.
- Thanks.
- What do you have?
- What, is this your boyfriend?
- Yes.
- No. Yes.
Look, I'm not the kind of guy
that likes to play games.
- He's with Maggie.
- Thanks, Pete.
- What'd you find?
- According to FlyersRights.org,
we can download a petition demanding
we be allowed off the plane,
but it's not clear how
many signatures we need.
We don't have time to circulate a petition.
What else you got?
A website that lists seven ways
to get kicked off a plane,
- including shouting loud, unpopular political views.
- I can do that.
Being dressed in an inappropriately
revealing manner.
- Take off your clothes.
- You take off your clothes.
I guess I'm stuck
with the tiebreaker.
Lester, I'm gonna
lose my shit on you.
- Generator in the East Room.
- It's not bad news.
Uh, Elliot, let's try--
Boy, that Genghis Khan
had some pretty good ideas.
- You see what happened?
- Yes.
The worst thing that
could possibly happen.
I fell down and guess what,
nobody died.
Get in your seat,
fasten your seat belt.
Sure, but I might need to see
that demonstration again
'cause I've never seen
a seat belt before.
He's stopping.
The gate's right there.
It's right out the window.
I can see it.
I'm practically touching it right now.
- Take it easy.
- It's right there!
Well, folks,
this is the captain.
- Good news-- Our gate has opened up.
- Thank you.
- But this is a tow-in gate.
- No!
So it'll be just
a few more minutes.
Let me out!
Let me out
and I will push the plane
to the gate.
Maggie's a lucky girl.
No one's asked us to switch over to
the Emergency Broadcasting System,
so there isn't a North Korean missile
headed towards San Diego.
No one knows anything
at the CDC,
so a vial of smallpox
hasn't been dropped
in the middle of
Madison Square Garden.
We have a computer that monitors
all the police scanners
and listens for certain words.
There's been no act
of domestic terrorism,
though there is a frat party
at Michigan State
that's about to get broken up.
You guys know it's bin Laden,
don't you?
Believe me, when we know
it's bin Laden, you'll know.
I'd have expected it
to be a lot more chaotic.
Since the first day
Mackenzie got here,
we've been practicing this once a month.
We do dry runs.
Obviously there are always
wild cards you can't predict.
Hey, little buddy.
- Oh, boy.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Mac's been worried.
We got stuck in some traffic,
so I ran here.
We've been calling.
I thought it would be better to
keep running than answer the phone.
What's that?
I stopped to get a falafel.
I'm just gonna...
Good. Thanks.
Anything new?
It's bin Laden or Gaddafi.
And the White House pushed
it 15 minutes to 10:45.
God. Have you ever noticed
how we've never been able to agree on
a way to spell Gaddafi?
"Q-A," "K-A," "G."
Will, are you able to--
Gaddafi would have been
a NATO operation.
I've spoken with Wesley Clark,
who called NATO HQ in Brussels.
They don't know anything.
You've already spoken
to NATO HQ?
When I was getting the falafel.
Kaylee.
I need to be able to count
on your discretion.
You can't imagine
how important this night is.
You're gonna be great.
Just keep drinking water.
All right.
So I'm gonna go
in my office and...
take it from there.
So if it's not Gaddafi,
doesn't that mean--
Like I said, when we have it confirmed,
you'll know it.
- Go back to work.
- Yeah.
You can see the Press
Briefing Room is empty.
The White House Press Corps is
starting to arrive on the scene,
but they're staking out positions
near the northwest
executive entrance.
- Mac, can you hear me?
- Yup.
Keith Urbahn,
who's the Chief of Staff
for Donald Rumsfeld,
has tweeted the following:
"So I'm told by a reputable person
they have killed Osama bin Laden.
Hot damn."
- We got the tweet.
- We want to report it.
- You can't do it.
- We're not gonna say confirmed.
We just want to report the tweet.
Jane, this is double
confirmation territory,
- and we don't even have one yet.
- The tweet is reportable.
Do you know how many tweets
there are out there?
Just one from the Chief of Staff
to the former Secretary of Defense.
I'm sorry, you're gonna
have to keep vamping.
We've got a package on past live addresses
from the East Room.
- We'll shoot it to you.
- Mac, we're eight blocks from the White House.
- We'd like to report some news.
- Then go get some, Jane.
Will's here.
- Mac?
- Back to you, Jane.
The president was scheduled
to address the nation at 10:30.
But we have been told it
will be closer to 10:45.
If you're just joining us,
I'll recap everything
we're able to report.
It shouldn't take long.
Thank God.
Where have you been?
There was construction.
I have to get on the air.
- What do you want to say?
- It's not Gaddafi.
We've got NATO
saying it's not Libya.
And we've got London and Paris
saying it's not Gaddafi.
- It's not Gaddafi.
- So who's saying it is?
Continuing what we have
assumed that Gaddafi--
It has something to do
with Gaddafi.
Do you agree with the general
that the war in Libya
will continue or do you think
that the death of Gaddafi--
Jesus Christ.
Let them know
New York is ready.
I'm just gonna go on,
say it's not Libya,
and then throw it
back to Washington
- until we have a double confirmation.
- Good.
Okay, so let's let them
know New York is ready.
I'm just gonna go on,
say it's not Libya,
and then throw it back to Washington
until we have double confirmation.
- You just said that.
- Hmm?
You all right?
I just think this
is some kind of trick tie.
- I can't get it to--
- What's the problem?
I can't remember
how to tie a Windsor knot.
I can tie a square knot
and a sheep-shank.
- Will?
- But that's not useful right now.
What is wrong with you?
I'm wasted, okay?
- I'm completely baked.
- What?
- I had-- Okay, listen.
- Oh, no.
- No, no, it's okay.
- Oh, my God.
Listen, Neal's girlfriend--
and you should see her,
she can play
Guitar Hero blindfolded.
- Oh, my God.
- No, you're right. It doesn't matter.
Let me back it up.
When you're pitching,
you have your push-off leg
and your landing leg.
That landing leg,
as you can see,
takes a lot of force when you
come down on it like that.
Boom. Like that.
And marijuana--
This isn't happening.
You can't do this.
- I'm a medical marvel.
- You can't go on the air.
My body has the
melatolical tolerance--
- Metabolical.
- What did I say?
- Will!
- Mackenzie, listen to me.
There is no way--
No way
I'm not reporting this story.
You understand, right?
Of course.
I'm not gonna let you down.
I know.
Hey, we got Obama.
Bin Laden.
I got that one out of my system.
Let's think of the people
who would know.
- Well, POTUS.
- V-POTUS.
- Head of JSOC.
- Bill McRaven.
- Gates.
- Panetta.
- Guys.
- It was either Delta, SEAL Six,
- or a bullet from the CIA.
- Guys.
- What about a drone?
- I don't think they'd use a drone.
They'd want
an immediate positive ID.
Guys!
What does EKIA mean?
It means "enemy killed in action."
I have the first confirmation.
With the White House
now telling us
that the president's address
has been pushed back
another 15 minutes to 11:00.
You will know everything we know
as we know it.
And in the meantime,
let's go back
to Jane Barrow in Washington.
Jane.
Don just called.
We got the first confirmation.
- From who?
- Chris Harkin at CENTCOM.
CENTCOM in Tampa.
That's one.
- Mac, we got the second confirmation.
- From who?
- New York Times.
- You're kidding.
Helene Cooper just posted
she has it from two sources.
Maggie.
We've got Chris Harkin
at CENTCOM
and Helene Cooper
at the New York Times.
- We got him.
- Let's go.
- No.
- What do you mean?
- We're not going yet.
- We've got double confirmation.
First of all, we don't.
We have Harkin at CENTCOM
and a reporter saying
she has two sources.
- I don't know who the sources are.
- It's Helene Cooper.
- It's solid.
- We're not going.
- Charlie.
- There's nothing wrong with waiting for the White House
to tell us it's reportable.
This isn't Watergate.
They're not the enemy.
We don't know what's going on.
We sent military assets
into sovereign airspace.
Maybe they're not out yet.
Maybe someone's
injured on the ground.
been taken prisoner
and the rescue operation
is underway.
Maybe we're at war
with Pakistan.
Guys, in '91,
I was cheering on
my guy in Tel Aviv
who was reporting where
the scud missiles were landing.
Turns out the Iraqis didn't know
where the missiles were landing
and I was helping them
range their targets.
Three killed,
96 injured in that operation.
Geraldo's probably
still up the street
saying we're in
a dogfight with Finland.
Whatever happened tonight,
I promise you,
lives and a presidency
were put on the line.
We're going to get
this one right.
And if we're two minutes late,
let that be a small penance
for all the ones we got wrong.
Agreed.
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
- Hmm?
- What's wrong with him?
Nothing.
Charlie, I do think
you should tell them.
That I'd love to do.
Can everybody quiet down?
Everybody quiet down.
Charlie would like to
tell you something.
Um...
I need to tell you
that you're going
to remember this night
for the rest of your lives.
It's going to be a long night
and we need you to work fast
and we need you to work well.
But once in a while,
take three seconds--
You can't spare more than that--
Take three seconds to notice
where you are
and what you're doing.
Will's gonna go on
the air in a few minutes
so that we can report
that at the order
of the President
of the United States,
US Special Forces
have shot and killed
Osama bin Laden.
Get to work.
You're out here.
Neal's looking for you.
I think word's starting
to get out we got Gaddafi.
Yeah.
Neal, she's out here.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Hey.
You should be working.
I told you when we knew
for sure you'd know it.
Yeah.
I just didn't want to be
the skunk at the garden party.
- Why would you--
- You're not.
I was an idiot.
I thought it would make me
feel better when it happened.
- Like an on-off switch.
- Of course it doesn't.
You knew someone
in one of the Towers.
Her father was a partner
at Cantor Fitzgerald.
We've been celebrating
around you all night.
You should.
Everybody should.
- You guys should get back to work.
- Nah, it's all right.
No, I want you to.
All right.
I'll be right inside.
- He wants us to wait?
- Until the White House says it's reportable.
- Aren't we the only ones with Harkin?
- As far as I know.
- So we are the only ones who have double confirmation?
- We're going.
- No.
The White House just pushed the speech
another 15 minutes. We're going.
If I have to bring Charlie
in here to tell you himself,
he's gonna do it
in a different voice.
Washington's keeping
the audience warm for Will.
We're getting
our facts straight.
We got bin Laden,
what do you want?
For one thing, I don't want it reported
like the Redskins won the Super Bowl.
I don't believe you people.
We're waiting for the White House
to tell us it's reportable.
- We're not.
- Jane. Jane!
- Okay, I've just received...
- Cut the fiber from Washington.
- It'll go black.
- Yeah.
- Cut the fiber.
- Copy.
You think she got
the message yet?
- Couple of more seconds.
- Okay.
Bring 'em back.
- Hi.
- Damn it, Mac.
Move one inch
in that direction again
and you're blacked out
for the night.
The decision to go will be made
by the president of the news division
Charlie Skinner.
And the announcement will be
made by the face and voice
of Atlantis Cable News
Will McAvoy.
Keep an eye on her.
What are you working on?
Will asked me to look over
his intro copy.
Wow, that's a compliment.
I know Charlie's right,
but I wish we'd get on there.
This is just counterintuitive.
So's Lisa being
attracted to you,
but you still have
to deal with that.
Are you kidding?
I'm not doing it tonight.
- You have to.
- Tonight?
You can't sleep with her again.
Why are you sure I would?
"She is very sexy because
of her sexy sexiness
- and the very sexual sexiocity of the--"
- Fine.
Tell me what you're gonna say.
- I'm not gonna tell you what I'm gonna say.
- You need to rehearse.
- I don't need to rehearse.
- You're gonna be like Spiderman?
- What?
- The musical.
They didn't have enough rehearsal
and actors died, Jim.
They lost their lives.
I don't think anybody died.
Well, they got bruised pretty bad.
So tell me what you're gonna say.
Lisa, you kind of took me by surprise
last night when you told--
Shh, shh, she's coming over.
Dummy up.
Okay. Thank God we're not
in the middle of breaking news.
Hey.
You mind if I talk
to Jim a second?
No.
I'll be right there at my desk.
- It's right there.
- Where?
Right there.
- I'm sorry, where?
- Okay.
It's too bad the SEALs
are in Pakistan tonight
because they'd be getting some mad ass
if they were in New York City.
- Lisa, I--
- This is the worst possible time,
but I feel ridiculous because you guys
are talking about me and I'm standing there.
No, we weren't.
- We weren't talking--
Shh.
Last night I said something.
I forced you to say it, too,
and that's not fair.
- I didn't feel forced.
- This was a fix-up that you never wanted,
and it went too far, and now I have to
let you off the hook because you're so nice
that we'd be searching for preschools
before I realized that you were just being polite.
I'm breaking up with you.
Just say okay.
I really did like you.
- Okay.
Um, I'm gonna
go talk to spy girl.
Get to work.
That's an order.
And thanks for
bringing me here for this.
- Look, I--
- Work.
What happened?
- I broke up with him.
- He did?
I mean, you did?
What?
I saw your face when
I was talking on the phone
and he said, "I love you."
He said, "I do, too."
And what are you talking about?
I'm not doing this
to you anymore.
You're not doing anything to me.
I've got Don.
- I shouldn't even be standing here.
- I'm with Don.
- I saw your face.
- Come with me.
- James Tiberius Harper.
- Not my middle name.
Lisa is-- No--
Is under the impression
that you broke up with her
because you have feelings for me.
I didn't break up
with her at all.
- But you were about to.
- Any reason she needed to know that?
- She already knew.
- This isn't at all embarrassing.
And she is under the impression that
I also have feelings for you.
- Did you hear what killed bin Laden?
- We're in a holding pattern.
Now, can we please state clearly,
unambiguously, and for the record
that neither of us likes the other
in any romantic context?
- I so state.
- As do I!
You guys can't begin to imagine
how unconvincing that was.
Is it all right if I stay
for the president's address?
Yes.
But we're not nearly done
talking about this yet.
- Maggie, I need you.
- Not nearly done.
I'll be over there
out of the way.
- Wait, I--
- Just say okay.
Okay.
I'm the guy who wins the lottery
and loses the ticket.
Biggest story in a generation
and I'm a spectator.
You are not a spectator.
We are locked on a plane
and we still helped put it together.
That's pretty good.
What is this compulsion you have
to look on the bright side?
I can never count
on you to be Jewish.
If it helps, we should probably
be concerned about violent retaliation.
That does help, man.
Thanks.
My regret is that I'd like to have
been with my wife for this.
Tell her to wake up the kids,
bring them down to the studio.
We'd all watch together.
Yes, I'd like to be
with your wife, too.
I'd like to be in
the newsroom with Will
and Charlie and her and you.
- And Maggie.
- I said Maggie.
- No, you didn't.
- You didn't.
So you have to ask yourself
what happens
when you and Maggie break up,
which you know is going to happen,
- and Jim's with someone else.
- We were talking that loud?
Over Delaware
after the second scotch.
There's passengers in row 22
who know about you, Maggie, and Jim.
- True story.
- Shut up.
Excuse me,
I've got a text message saying
the president is speaking
tonight in a few minutes.
Do you know
anything about this?
The Internet says he's speaking
on a matter of grave
national security.
Yeah, I've got the same thing.
I've got a flight
that's been canceled.
Does that have anything
to do with what--
- Has there been a terrorist attack?
- No.
- Wait, there's been a terrorist attack?
- No, there hasn't.
- I've got an email saying we're at war with Libya.
- Nope.
You guys know what's going on,
don't you?
Folks, there hasn't been
a terrorist attack.
None of your friends
and family are in danger.
The president will be speaking
in just a few minutes.
- No.
- Listen, they're just nervous.
I don't care.
You do not take over control of the cabin.
They're getting emails
and going online.
You do not take over
control of the cabin ever.
- Now sit down. I'm getting the captain.
- Ma'am, no, you know--
Yeah, get the captain,
'cause I'd like to have a word with him.
The seat belt while we're standing still
is one thing, but how paranoid
do you have to be to think that
I'm declaring myself in charge of the--
- Is there a problem, sir?
- Yeah, I was asking how paranoid you have to--
- You have to be--
- Sir?
Sir?
Captain, my name is Don Keefer.
That's Elliot Hirsch
and that's Sloan Sabbith.
We work for Atlantis Cable News.
And we wanted you
and your first officer
and Flight Attendant Crazy Lady
to be the first ones
on this plane to know
that our armed forces
killed Osama bin Laden for you tonight.
You're serious?
Yes, sir.
We reported the news.
Sorry, I thought it was a spider.
Tapping you on the shoulder?
- Not everything makes sense.
- Most things do.
Look, can I say something?
You have to get
the last word, too?
- This never would have worked.
- I want to find out.
Yes, this was a fix-up
that I didn't want.
And Maggie forced
Valentine's Day on me.
And there was a certain
amount of...
cowardly behavior
disguised as politeness.
But now I'd like to
ask you out on a first date.
A complete do-over.
I like you and
I'm asking you out on a date.
Took your breath away,
didn't I?
Now I get to make a cool exit.
Less cool because you said so.
- McAvoy!
- You don't have to shout.
You haven't heard me shout.
Where is he?!
Lonny.
Good evening, officers.
Uh-oh. There's no way
they can know, right?
- No.
- Can we help you?
Mr. McAvoy,
you know this man?
Of course,
he's a very famous jockey.
- You know what--
- Sir, we'd appreciate your cooperation.
He's my bodyguard
and I ran out of the car because
we were stuck in traffic,
and chances are he abandoned the car
to try to protect me
'cause he's good at his job.
He's also a former MP
in the US Army,
so I want to tell him something.
Lonny, come here.
- You should tell them.
Officers,
I have some news for you.
This is Charlie Skinner.
So, we've established trust?
Is this Late For Dinner?
Yeah.
You work for
the White House or DOD?
Neither.
You've been calling me
on a cell phone.
- There are about 19 different ways--
- The calls are encrypted.
I know how to find out who I am,
but you don't.
- So you're with the NSA?
- I am.
I'm with a unit that's
been monitoring
illegal electronic surveillance.
- By whom?
- By AWM.
News of the World
isn't the only tabloid
that figured out
how to hack a phone.
If you're fucking
around with me--
I think by now
you know I'm not.
You've got a big night
ahead of you.
- We'll talk again.
- When?
When I want to.
AWM owns a tabloid magazine, TMI.
Are you saying
you have evidence
that they've been engaging
in the same kind of--
You're not there, are you?
Charlie.
Charlie?
What if I told you that bin Laden
wasn't the only story we got tonight?
What are you talking about?
Don't worry about it.
I think we should go.
Jay Carney or someone's office
would have sent us an email
saying reportable.
They also would have called us
begging us not to report it.
I'm unwilling
to take that chance.
When was the last time
you checked your emails?
- 15 seconds ago.
- When was the last time you did?
Hmm?
Look at your BlackBerry.
- Press the buttons!
- Sure.
Okay, not tonight,
but in days to come,
you'll look back and think
that this moment was funny.
- It's from 20 minutes ago.
- Yeah.
- What's it say?
- "OBL reportable.
Knock 'em dead
just like we did."
Who's it from?
- Joe Biden.
- Are you kidding me?!
We used to play softball together
when he was in the Senate.
He knows something
about the landing leg.
Get on the air!
We're going!
When did you turn
into Ted Baxter?
Oh, come on.
Enjoy the moment.
Herb, have Washington
throw it to us in 30 seconds.
Copy that. DC control,
you're gonna throw it here in 30.
Good thinking.
- Let's see the banner.
- Right here.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
In five.
Do it for me, Will.
Good evening.
From New York City,
I'm Will McAvoy.
ACN is now able
to report and confirm
that for the first time
in almost three decades,
the world has no reason
to fear Osama bin Laden.
In just a moment,
in a live address to the nation,
the president will announce
that in a coordinated operation
under the cover of darkness,
US Special Forces tonight
killed the leader of al-Qaeda
and the mastermind
behind the deadly attack
of September 11th, 2001.
It's been nine years,
seven months, and 20 days
since America's most wanted criminal
took from us
2,977 American sons and daughters,
fathers and mothers,
friends and colleagues.
We were transformed that morning
into a different nation,
more fearful and so,
of course, more hostile.
And while nothing,
not even this victory
our country has waited for
for such a long time,
can bring back the souls
lost on that terrible morning
in New York City, in Virginia,
in a field in Pennsylvania,
and all across America
and the world,
let tonight serve
as a welcome reminder
that throughout our history,
America's darkest days
have always been followed
by its finest hours.
Here now, from the East Room
of the White House,
the President of the United States.
Good evening.
Tonight I can report
to the American people
and to the world
that the United States
has conducted an operation
that killed Osama bin Laden,
the leader of al-Qaeda
and a terrorist who's
responsible for the murder
of thousands of innocent men,
women, and children.
It was nearly 10 years ago
that a bright September day
was darkened
by the worst attack on
the American people in our history.
The images of 9/11 are seared
into our national memory.
Hijacked planes cutting through
a cloudless September sky.
The Twin Towers
collapsing to the ground.
Black smoke billowing up
from the Pentagon.
The wreckage of Flight 93
in Shanksville, Pennsylvania,
where the actions
of heroic citizens
saved even more heartbreak
and destruction.
And yet we know
that the worst images
are those that were
unseen to the world.
The empty seat
at the dinner table.
Children were forced to
grow up without their mother
or their father...
www.tvsubtitles.net