It's another TMI story.
You've had Wade on the show
five times in six weeks.
- What's the story gonna be?
- It's gonna be
that you're trying to get
your boyfriend elected to Congress.
You can't think
I used you to raise his profile.
I know for sure
you didn't use me.
Plus, nobody in his right mind
would risk losing you.
- You look really nice tonight.
- Yeah?
Definite yes, yeah.
I didn't know that I was in love with you,
too, until--
- You cheated on me with your ex-boyfriend.
- That's what happened!
- It's been three years. Time hasn't helped?
- No.
I want to give you
five minutes every night
to talk about where we are
and how we got here.
There are people more
qualified than I am.
Yeah, the thing is,
they're not going to have your legs.
I would not ask you if I didn't think
you were qualified.
Come after me all you want, Nina,
but you touch my staff
and I will rededicate my life
to ruining yours.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
...$223 billion,
putting an edge on the current fight
on Capitol Hill about how deeply
to cut this year's spending,
along with projections
that it would bring the debt ceiling--
excuse me--
the deficit to 1.6 trillion,
ensuring that the debt ceiling
will be hit during this fiscal year.
That's News Night.
Thanks for washing us--
Watching us.
Let me get out of here.
Will McAvoy is coming up with
the Capitol Report from Washington.
- I'm Terry-- no.
- Wow.
- That's not true.
- End the broadcast.
- I'm Will McAvoy.
- Attaboy.
Terry Smith is coming up, mercifully,
with the Capitol Report from Washington.
Good night.
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm fine.
- "Thank you for washing us"?
- Think people noticed?
I do.
Stand here on this spot.
- What are you doing?
- Administering an eye exam.
- Excellent.
- Read the top line.
- E.
- Next line.
I don't know why people think there's
a problem with health care in this country.
- Our current system is fine.
- Next line.
L-G.
The next line, R-T-Z.
The Greek letter for pi,
the geometric symbol
for congruent,
and something off the table
of natural elements.
Great, put your tie back on
and get in the studio
so we can retape that
for the West Coast.
What's the problem?
I didn't get
much sleep last night.
- How much is not much?
- None.
- Seriously?
- I went to bed at midnight, didn't fall asleep.
Is this the first time
that's happened?
- No.
- Is it the second time?
I'm having a little bout
with insomnia.
Have you tried Ambien?
I don't want to wake up
in the middle of the Triborough Bridge
eating scrambled eggs
in my pajamas.
How those eggs got into my pajamas I'll never know.
You shouldn't do Groucho.
Seriously, you need to sleep
or you're gonna forget to
thank people for washing us.
I'm seeing my guy
tomorrow at 10:00.
- Who's your guy?
- Abe.
- Who's Abe?
- Dr. Habib.
You're still seeing Abe?
That's wonderful, Will.
Everyone could use
a little therapy.
And you a lot more than most.
I'm glad you're doing that.
- Well...
- You've been skipping appointments?
Sometimes.
When was the last
time you saw him?
- What's today, the 12th?
- Yeah.
- About four years ago.
- Why did you stop seeing him?
- I've kept the appointments.
- What does that mean?
I've had an appointment every
Wednesday at 10:00. I just don't go.
You've been paying him
for four years?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Thank God.
I have a business manager
who does that.
Why don't you read a magazine?
No, I've already read that
issue of Cat Fancy cover to cover
and I'm saving American Stamp Collector
for a long plane ride.
All right.
Why not just go
to your regular doctor?
When I go to my internist,
he asks me questions.
It's a half-hour interview
before he puts on a stethoscope.
- What kinds of questions?
- I don't know.
- How you feeling?
- Asshole.
Here, read Vegan Health.
- Will?
- Yeah.
I'm Jack Habib.
Come on in.
Are you Abe's son?
- I am.
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too. Come on in.
- Is your dad inside?
No.
I can wait out here.
My father died two years ago
and I took his practice.
Come on in.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Wait, what?
Will, I'm Dr. Jacob Habib,
son of Dr. Abraham Habib.
My father passed away
and his patients now see me.
You've been paying me
for two years.
Come on in.
How old are you?
I'm 29.
Shut up.
- Can you write prescriptions?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- I'll be two minutes.
- All right.
So if you're 29--
Don't try to count backwards.
I did everything early.
So unless you're certain
you've got a Doogie Howser joke
I haven't heard,
why don't we just assume
it was hilarious and move on?
- Okay.
- So what's going on?
I need something
to help me sleep.
- Why?
- I can't sleep.
- I don't know.
Any recent change in diet?
I haven't changed my diet
since college.
- You should.
- I invented a new sandwich.
Scrambled eggs, bacon,
and melted cheese on toast.
I make two of them every night
before I get into bed.
You invented an Egg McMuffin.
- Getting enough exercise?
- I have to scramble the eggs.
- And other than that?
- No.
Look, any kind of
sleeping pill will do.
Sure.
Just talk a little bit?
Oh, God, please, let's not.
- You're still taking Effexor?
- No.
- Clonazepam?
- Ativan?
- No.
Four years ago,
you were on 135mg of Effexor
- plus Clonazepam and Ativan at bedtime.
- I'm not anymore.
- Why is that?
- I was cured.
These are all
antianxiety medications.
And I have no more anxiety.
Except for not
being able to sleep.
Right, so if you'll just
give me a prescription for--
Yeah, I'm going to.
- Just a few more questions.
- Okay.
Any extra stress at work?
Extra stress?
- Yeah.
- No.
- No extra stress?
- One more question.
- Sure.
What are you
fucking around with me for?
I'm sorry?
What are you fucking
around with me for?
- I just asked if there's any extra stress at work--
- There isn't.
There isn't.
What about the death threat?
You know about that?
Anyone who reads a newspaper
knows about that.
- It's truly not a big deal.
- No?
Jack, can I get the prescription?
Just tell me how a death threat
isn't a big deal.
I used to be
a criminal prosecutor.
And I'm telling you nobody
who's serious about killing you
sends you a note
beforehand to warn you.
The gentleman who is with you
in the waiting room, he's a bodyguard, right?
Yeah, but you shouldn't--
That's the--
Our insurance company
makes that decision.
Based on what?
They have experts who determine
whether a cret is threadible--
Threat is credible.
And why do they think
the threat is credible?
Nine questions ago,
you said one more question.
Why do they think
the threat is credible?
Because I changed the rules
of the comment section of our website.
That's all. I changed the rules
of the comment section.
As always,
or at least since Monday,
we end our show with your own
viewer comments on our website.
So let's see
what we have tonight.
LollypopLollypop says,
"30 more seconds
and you would have had
that self-loathing hypocrite in tears."
That-- That was absolutely
not my intention.
SurrendrDorothee said,
"Your Log Cabin closet case
hit the Uncle Tom
Daily Double--
a traitor to his race and a traitor
to his sexual orientation."
Don't blow a gasket.
He's plainly not a closet case.
He's openly gay.
I also think he showed a lot of courage
coming on the show.
Certainly more courage than it takes
to post an anonymous comment on a website.
Terry Smith's coming up from Washington
with the Capitol Report.
I'm Will McAvoy.
Good night.
We're out.
- Neal!
- Believe me, those were the best two we had.
Why didn't we just
hit him in the head with a shovel?
- We've got to talk about what just happened.
- I'm trying to.
Not the website. We've got to talk about
what happened on the air.
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Were you outside your body?
I don't want to talk about it.
I want to talk about the website.
The website's not
the problem right now.
It's my problem right now.
We're putting up these comments--
- We've heard this before.
- But we're still doing it.
It's a trade with Reese.
The page views offset the ratings drop.
Is there any way of knowing
if LollypopLollypop
is 10 years old?
Or a basset hound?
The reason basset hounds
have such long ears
is so they can waft up the scent
when they're hunting.
- Is there any way of knowing?
- No.
Is there any way of
knowing if LollypopLollypop
- and SurrendrDorothee are the same person?
- No.
Who posts comments
on the Internet more,
- people who are content or people who are incontent?
- Discontent.
- What?
- It's discontent, not incontent.
- It's about 30-1 incontent.
- Discontent.
Final question:
In your wildest dreams,
can you imagine Walter Cronkite
saying LollypopLollypop
as many times as I have
in the last 10 minutes?
Not unless he was in an
a cappella doo-wop group, no.
He wasn't.
Here's what I'd love.
You want to join
the discussion, fine.
I want to know your name,
age, occupation,
- and level of education.
- Oh, God.
The thing about the Internet is
it's a populist tool.
Populists have names, too.
William Jennings Bryan, Will Rogers, me.
- Will.
- Unless you're Deep Throat
or in the Witness Protection Program,
anonymity is cowardice.
You're in a mob.
You're lobbing smack from the cheap seats.
Don't we have bigger fish
to fry than the--
Yes, but we can fry
more than one fish at a time.
And how could we possibly
verify someone's name,
- age, occupation, and level of education?
- Neal?
We implement a third-party
verification service.
All you had to say was,
"We can't"
- and the conversation would have been over.
- So it is possible?
It's what the IRS uses
when you're filing online.
Talk to me, Tonto.
- We can do it if you want.
- Oh, I want.
Won't the result be that nobody
posts comments on our website anymore?
First of all, oh, no. What will we do without
feedback from SurrendrDorothee?
And second, the result will be our website
will ghettoize every other website.
The result will be civility
in the public square
and a triumph of populism.
I'm going to single-handedly
fix the Internet.
- What could possibly go wrong?
- Will!
- What?
- We have to talk about what just happened.
No, we don't.
We're just gonna move on.
And when did you get
the death threat?
I don't know.
A day after the mosque interview.
We know that an Islamic trend
is to build large mosques
on the cherished sites
of conquered lands.
- You're talking about Cordoba.
- That's exactly right.
When Muslims conquered Cordoba,
Spain, they tore down churches
and synagogues and put
mosques in their place.
Ms. Greer, Muslims conquered
Cordoba in the year 712.
Do you think we can call something that
last happened in the 8th century a trend?
She'll say, "Why does it have
to be at Ground Zero?"
Anyone being honest about
the prospect of a mosque
being built so close
to Ground Zero
would say it
instinctually feels wrong.
Is it legal?
Of course it is.
Is it wrong?
It should be built somewhere
where the 9/11 families
don't have to feel the agony of having
a shrine to their loved ones stomped upon.
All over America we're seeing
the influence of creeping Islam.
We are?
What about those who would
impose Sharia law?
Women can be stoned to death
for committing adultery.
No, they can't. Actual laws are
the only laws that are enforceable,
including the one that says
you can't create religious laws.
And the US is in no more danger
of coming under Sharia law
than it is the rules
of Fight Club.
Let me ask you something.
Muslims the world over
are fighting a civil war
over the direction
Islam is taking.
Are you going to be stationed
at the door of that mosque
to turn radicals away?
Can you guarantee
that the current imam
is going to be the same imam
10 years from now?
It's worth pointing out that it's not a mosque.
It's a community center.
I'm not sure why you think
that makes it better.
What business does a community center
have in the religion business?
And then pivot
to the larger point.
I want the art and graphics
reviewed three times before air.
Ms. Greer,
you mentioned creeping Islam.
Are you concerned about
creeping Christianity?
Only that it's not creeping fast enough.
Okay, here are some things
done on American soil
in the name of Christianity.
The Ku Klux Klan burned down
black churches,
raped women,
murdered civil rights workers,
murdered children,
and terrorized communities for over a century.
The neo-Nazis all acted
and continue to act
in the name of white
Christian supremacy.
The Army of God fatally attacks
abortion clinics and doctors
across the country.
The Covenant, The Sword,
and The Arm of the Lord
targets local police
and federal agents.
The federal building
in Oklahoma City,
the attempted assassination
of Ronald Reagan,
and the successful assassinations
of Martin Luther King,
John F. Kennedy,
John Lennon,
and Abraham Lincoln,
all perpetrated by Christians.
Ms. Greer,
we weren't attacked by Muslims.
We were attacked by sociopaths.
And I, for one,
would join you in protesting
a community center
for the criminally insane.
But no one is suggesting
building one.
Here's the thing
about the Japanese.
Where we tend to hype things up,
they go the other direction.
You think they're
lowballing Fukushima?
I don't know anything
about nuclear reactors,
and I'm not at all
involved in this story.
I'm just saying I wouldn't
take their word for it it's a level five.
Excuse me, Will. There's a comment
on your website you need to see.
Ah, now I get to say who is it from?
What do they do?
It's serious.
From about 25 minutes ago.
"Fucking sand niggers should
get herded and slaughtered.
I've got a bullet for you, too.
You think I'm fucking around?
2 Hudson Street, 27."
- Is 2 Hudson 27--
- It's my address and apartment number.
Alice Cynkar,
an English professor at OSU.
It wasn't written
by an English professor
and it wasn't written
by Alice Cynkar.
How much effort does it take
to scam the new system?
You've got to want it pretty bad.
Millie, it's Mackenzie.
Would you tell him we're
coming right up, please?
They could have
stolen our password.
- How hard is that?
- Hard.
We implemented complex
password requirements
on the site because we knew
it was catnip for some sophomore at MIT.
It would take an average
computer 57 days to get in.
And that's with someone
who knows what they're doing.
How many days has
the new system been up?
- Three.
- Jesus.
- Will.
- Everybody relax.
Neal just said it.
It's a college kid pledging a frat.
With a death threat? No.
Charlie, I want a body on him
until this guy's in handcuffs.
- No way.
- You're not gonna have a choice.
- The insurance company makes that call.
- Come on.
Listen to me.
This goes to AWM security right now.
Security's got to show it
to the insurance company.
And that's going to trigger
some kind of protection.
Wouldn't it make more sense for me
just to wear a different disguise every day?
One more thing.
There's gonna be a tabloid story.
- Good. Yeah.
- What did I do?
Is it possible Maggie
filed a complaint with HR
saying that you created
a hostile work environment?
No, it's not possible.
Maggie wouldn't complain if her hair was on fire.
Someone else did on her behalf.
And it was a while ago
before you got here.
Thanks.
Would you excuse us for a second?
Sure.
Why don't we try to fully investigate
the anatomy of these stories?
- No, we're gonna fully investigate Will.
- Of course.
I want you to assign a team
to do opposition research on Will.
Let's call it
Operation Involuntary Colonoscopy.
I just want to know what the next
tabloid story is before it happens.
You won't be able to pin
nothing on me, Mugsy.
'Cause I've lived my life
straight as the Kingston Trio.
I'm not fucking around!
You know, when you're grumpier than I am,
we've switched roles.
Ask him what's the current
state of the reactors.
What did he say?
- What did he say?
- His daughter's on the diving team.
They came in second
at regionals.
- Did he understand the question?
- Did you?
I haven't spoken to him in two years.
We're catching up.
How does a company like TEPCO
not have a spokesperson who speaks English?
I don't know.
What is the current state
of the reactors?
Tanaka-san...
Units one and three have had explosions
due to hydrogen buildup.
They're currently stable,
but they're not safe to enter.
What are they doing
to contain the situation?
What's going on with Will?
Internal security is handling it.
But I have to give you
a rotten assignment.
- You got gum in your hair again?
- No.
Yes, but I got it out.
I need you to do
opposition research on Will.
Seriously?
About a year ago, somebody filed
a complaint with HR on your behalf.
I know what that was. Will didn't
do anything wrong. This is ridiculous.
I know, but Charlie wants to know
what else is out there so he can--
- Will knows we're doing this?
- Of course.
- And he's okay with it?
- No, he hates it.
- Fantastic.
- Go to work.
- Have you done this before?
- Yeah.
- Where do we start?
- Tell me about the complaint.
There was a desk producer who saw
Will yell at me about something.
- What?
- Doesn't matter.
What?
Doesn't matter.
- I mixed up Georgia the state with--
- No.
- Yes, Georgia the country.
- And this was...
- Yup. This isn't about me.
- ...during the invasion?
You thought the Russians
invaded Atlanta?
In retrospect,
it seems farfetched.
But that wasn't what
he was actually mad about.
The wife of a board member died
and Will asked me to send flowers.
I wrote on the card,
"I'm so sorry about your loss. LOL."
- LOL?
- I thought it meant "lots of love."
How are you still working here?
I dodge bullets.
Here comes a bullet.
Boom! I'm over here.
Ping! Here comes another bullet.
Ask him if TEPCO's gonna try
to keep the reactors going.
Tanaka-san...
They're classified at level five
and they think they'll be able
to get the reactor going.
Guys, do me a favor
and let us have a minute?
Anybody know where
Sloan Sabbith is?
- Sloan!
- Shh!
She's on the phone.
All right, she's off the phone.
Here are the notes.
It's gonna go to level seven.
- Holy shit.
- You got a minute?
Fukushima's a lot worse
than they're telling you.
- I need you to fill in for Elliot tonight.
- This is what the Japanese do.
- They-- Wait, what?
- I need you to fill in for Elliot at 10:00.
- Why?
- His five-year-old's having a tonsillectomy today.
Elliot's gonna spend the night
in the hospital with her.
- Was it an emergency?
- No, it was scheduled a week ago.
And you're just getting
around to this now?
- I...
- Forgot?
- Yes.
- You have a staff. They can write these things down.
They can, but I have to
remember to tell them to.
So what do you say?
You're my first and only choice.
- What about Jerome?
- He's in Bermuda.
- Kathy?
- It's her parents' 50th anniversary.
- Taylor?
- Bronchitis.
- So...
- Yes, you were my fourth and only choice.
I can't host Elliot's show.
Don't be ridiculous.
You host your own
show at 4:00.
- About financial news.
- You're expanding.
Oh, come on.
I gained four freaking pounds.
No, professor.
- Right, expanding.
- Yeah.
- No, I'm not doing it.
- Your copy will be written for you to approve.
You've got Marco Rubio,
Sandra Bernhard--
Sandra Bernhard's been
dead for 100 years.
- That's Sarah Bernhardt.
- She'd be a good guest.
- I hate my life.
- Hmm?
Nothing.
And the spokesperson for TEPCO.
- I just got off the phone with him.
- See? You're perfect.
I was just doing a favor for these guys.
I don't know anything about--
Thank God my first five choices
weren't available.
I thought
there were only three.
Let's not get
caught up in the math.
If you want a wardrobe change
after the 4:00,
we have Gucci ready to
send over some choices.
- Gucci?
- A whole rack of choices.
Your copy will be ready for your approval after 9:00
along with your questions,
and I will be in your ear the whole time.
Except for Fukushima,
you're mostly throwing to packages.
- They've been lowballing the radiation levels.
- I'd take their word for it.
- The Japanese have some experience with radiation.
- You think that's something--
That is not something
you should mention on the air.
- Oh, God.
- Mr. Will McAvoy.
You're not here to do my taxes,
right?
My name's Lonny Church.
Mr. Horn at AWM Security
told you I'd be here at this time.
I'll tell you right now
I'm gonna hate this.
I'll tell you now
I'm not gonna care.
- Let's go in my office for a minute.
- Sure.
It's not a real threat.
I don't make that decision.
Lonny Church?
Did you play college football?
Yes, I did.
Defensive tackle.
Started three years
for Clemson.
- And then?
- Got drafted in the eighth round by the Bengals.
- Got cut five weeks into training camp.
Excellent.
Joined the Army, became an MP.
- Where were you deployed?
- New Jersey.
You see a lot of action
in New Jersey?
See a lot of action
in your studio?
I'll be doing the jokes, okay?
- After you were discharged?
- Honorably.
I joined Blue North Security.
Who else's body
have you guarded?
- We don't talk about that.
- Okay.
Kanye.
It was awesome.
Are you armed?
I secure my weapon in a gun safe
when I come in the building.
Keep it there.
I really don't want an armed guard.
Maybe if you were drafted in
the first four rounds, I'd feel safer.
- Mr. McAvoy.
- You can call me Will.
Yeah, I was gonna
do that anyway.
I know you're used
to being the boss.
But you're not anymore.
At least for a little while.
How long?
Until my colleagues chase down
the source of the threat
or, of course, if you've been
successfully assassinated.
- A joke?
- What'd you think?
It was all right.
How does this work?
I pick you up at your home in the morning
and escort you to your office.
Then I pick you up at your office at night
and escort you to your home.
I'm with you any place
that's an unsecured area.
What's an unsecured area?
Anyplace that isn't
your home or your office.
I'm single.
What about a date?
I don't think we should
get romantically involved.
You get one joke a day.
- Come on in.
- I say that.
- I'm sorry. You got a second?
- Yeah.
I'll leave you.
Sloan, this is Lonny.
You'll see him around.
- Good to meet you.
- Wow.
- Can I tap your chest?
- Sure.
Holy cow.
- Have you felt his pecs?
- No, I haven't yet.
I'll be downstairs.
So I'm hosting
Elliot's show tonight.
I know. I'm the one
who suggested you.
You really think I can do it?
No, I have no idea.
So we're gonna find out.
All right. Well, your exuberant
confidence notwithstanding,
- I have the spokesperson--
- From TEPCO, I know.
He just told me, off the record,
that reactor three
is causing what is a level seven,
not a level five radiation leak.
What's the trick to getting him
to say it on the record?
There is no trick.
You just don't stop until he tells the truth.
What do you mean
you don't stop?
I mean you don't stop.
Sloan, I watch your show at 4:00
and you're brilliant.
But you let guests say things
that I know you know aren't true.
And then you just move on.
Ask the damn follow-up
and then demonstrate with facts
how the guest is lying.
You can't just sit there
and be a facilitator
for whatever bullshit the guest
wants to feed your viewers.
They're not coming on to plug a movie.
It's not Jimmy Kimmel.
You knowingly, passively,
allow someone to lie on your air,
and maybe you're not a drug dealer,
but you're sure as hell
the guy who drives the dealer
around in your car.
So maybe you'll get it, maybe you won't.
Show me something.
- Got it.
- Do you?
Yeah.
I just-- I don't know.
I was in a bad mood.
Honestly, I was just
trying to motivate her.
She's the last person
who needs motivation,
- so it just ended up...
- Scaring her.
I hate that
people are scared of me.
- I absolutely hate it.
- Why?
Why do I hate when
people are scared of me?
For the same reason
everybody does.
Everybody doesn't.
Some people like it.
Most people don't care.
I don't know what to tell you.
I don't like it.
And I'm pretty sure
I scared Sloan
because she's a veteran reporter
who's never done anything like what she did.
What's the condition
of each reactor?
- All six reactors are in stable condition.
- Great, let's wrap up.
What about the partial
meltdown at reactor three?
Wrap up for me.
Excuse me,
that's not what I asked.
I'm asking him specifically
about the core damage
at reactor three.
What's happening?
We know of no core damage
at any of the reactors.
That's not what
Mr. Tanaka just said.
He said our engineers can't
get close enough to confirm that.
Please translate
exactly what I'm asking
and exactly what
Mr. Tanaka is answering,
including what I'm saying now,
because I want him to be aware
that he's being misrepresented.
Miss Sabbith, I am translating.
He is not being mis--
Ask him if he believed the radiation levels
are going to a seven.
Please, please, don't go rogue.
The radiation
was categorized at level four
and then recategorized
at level five.
And that's where
it should remain.
Ma'am, he didn't say that's
where it should remain. You did.
Furthermore, he told me--
You know what? I'm just gonna--
Tanaka-san...
And now we're doing
the broadcast in Japanese.
We'll be right back after this.
Just say that.
Say it in English.
She just--
Put me back!
Mr. Tanaka, your company had
this incident rated at level four,
then adjusted to level five.
How confident are you that
that'll be the highest level we see?
At least we're back to English.
At this point, we see no reason
that level will need
future escalation.
Well, that's simply not what Mr. Tanaka
told me on the phone earlier today.
- No, no.
- When I spoke with him earlier,
he said there's enough evidence
to raise the level to seven.
- Go back to Japanese.
- And now he's not saying it, so I am.
- Oh, my God!
- So there it is.
The Fukushima nuclear
power plant is saying
that the level four radiation leak
that was raised to level five
has a chance at being
raised to level seven,
which is the difference
between life and gruesome death.
We'll be back after this
with Sarah Bernhardt.
Sandra Bernhard, you idiot!
Oh, what the hell
does it matter?
- Okay...
- 'Sup?
Okay, I know we were on
sketchy ground ethically
and linguistically, but--
Whatever you're gonna say,
save it for another 10 seconds.
What happens in 10 seconds?
Just hang on for another
five seconds and know
that we've all been there
at one point or another.
What happens in five seconds?
What in the name of holy fuck
were you thinking about?!
First, let me say that Don
was not responsible for that.
Yeah, when you severed
communication with the EP,
you pretty much absolved him
of responsibility.
But that doesn't make the cut
of the top three calamities
- that just occurred.
- Charlie--
I, along with most people
who don't live in Japan,
am not fluent in Japanese,
so I have to ask:
Did you just make up statements
for somebody
we had live on our air?
- I didn't make them up.
- About a deadly radiation leak?
I didn't make them up.
He told me the reactor
was going to a seven.
When? Tonight?
I'm asking honestly
because there was a portion
of the broadcast that turned
into a Kurosawa movie.
These things are measured
on a scale of zero to seven.
Five is Three Mile Island,
a seven is Chernobyl.
On air, did he say the reactors
were going to seven?
He said it to me
in the preinterview.
And then the company stuck
an interpreter next to him,
and I think her job
was more than interpreting
because she wasn't
accurately translating--
We don't report
what you think, Sloan.
The guy said
all six reactors are stable.
The Japanese are
a deferential people.
It's very hard for them to explain
when they've done something wrong.
I don't give a shit,
Madame Butterfly!
And right now the Japanese,
who are reading an online report
of your report,
are fleeing from
their fucking homes.
Now tell me what he said
tonight on air.
He said the reactors
were at five.
But you said he said
they would move to seven.
I made it clear he said that
during the preinterview.
First of all,
let's not kid ourselves.
There was nothing that was clear
about that interview.
He said it to me, and he said it
to a conference room full of staffers.
- The staffers weren't there.
- The staffers were not there.
I sent them out so we could
speak privately and off--
No, finish that sentence.
Off the record.
Good luck trying to get a source
to talk to you off the record again.
You have no value to me
as a reporter now.
- Charlie!
- And I have to suspend you.
- Come on.
- What?
I have to suspend you while
we bring in outside investigators
to comb through every report
you've filed in the last two years
to find out what other shit
you made up.
I didn't make anything up.
I would never make anything up.
I know that and you know that
and he knows that,
but why the hell should
anyone else know that?
You're suspended with pay
until I figure out--
- They were lying about a public safety issue.
- You're suspended with pay--
I don't want the goddamn pay!
Don't front off with me, girl!
- Don't call me girl, sir.
- Hey!
Everybody calm the fuck down.
Sarah Bernhardt
was a turn-of-the-century
stage and film actress
from France.
Sandra Bernhard is a...
I don't know what the hell.
There's no way she does that if
I hadn't given her my awesome pep talk.
Are you close with Sloan?
- Are we close?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Just asking.
- You seem very protective.
- We didn't used to be.
But she's become, I don't know.
I don't know,
like a little sister to me or something.
Your father was
an abusive alcoholic?
What?
Your father,
he was an abusive alcoholic?
I didn't say that.
But he was, right?
You got that in the 40 minutes
that I've been sitting here that
seem like a week and a half?
It's in the notes my dad left.
Can I have a prescription now?
- He hit you?
- Come on.
He hit you, right?
How many times did you
see Good Will Hunting?
- He hit you?
- Yes.
- He hit your mother?
You have a brother and two sisters.
He hit them, right?
Look, he didn't hit anybody once
I was old enough to hit him back.
And when was that?
Will, how old were you
when you had to protect
your mother, your brother,
and your two little sisters
from a grown man
who was drunk and violent?
Fifth grade.
I cracked a bottle of Dewar's
across his face.
It's in your notes.
Why are you pursuing this line of--
I'm not trying
to be an asshole.
I just want a sleeping pill.
I'm gonna give you one,
but I doubt it's gonna work.
Let's give it a try.
You've got another 15 minutes
on your session.
I didn't come here
for a session.
You could have gotten sleeping pills
from your internist.
Shit, you could have
got them online.
I didn't go to my internist
because he asks too many questions.
You didn't go to your internist because
he doesn't ask you the right questions.
I didn't come here
for a session.
I think you did.
I'm checking on
the opposition research.
Maggie was detained by the police
for attempting to blow up
her parents' house.
He's overstating it.
My cousins and I wanted
to shoot guns at soda cans.
Where did you place
the soda cans?
- On top of the propane tanks.
- Which were in front of?
The diesel fuel combine.
But I'm an excellent shot.
The Deep South could have used you
when the Russians invaded.
Will. How's the opposition
research on Will?
He once needed lenses for driving,
then didn't.
So he probably had Lasik surgery.
He did.
He registered for the New York Marathon,
but didn't finish.
My fault.
I twisted my ankle at the starting line.
He carried me to the first aid tent.
What else?
- He was hospitalized with tuberculosis.
- Already knew that.
He was credited
on a country album as a guitarist.
He's an accomplished guitarist who
occasionally jams with Leonard Cohen.
He got a C-minus
in Sociology of Emotion.
It was a clerical mistake.
He never registered for the class.
- Then a C-minus is pretty good.
- I need something I can use.
Wait, are we trying to protect Will
or give you ammunition?
Thought we could do both.
He contributed $250 to
the failed primary campaign
of a congressional candidate
in Nebraska.
- While he was a journalist?
- No.
Nothing I can do with that.
I mean, they--
Nothing they can do with that.
Oh, the candidate
was a Republican.
- So's Will.
- What?
He's a registered Republican.
The four of you weren't
able to uncover that?
We weren't looking.
He was a speechwriter for Bush 41.
What did you think he was?
I just thought he did that
as a public service.
Or to mess with him
like in The Sting.
That's nothing like what
happened in The Sting.
Jim got kicked out of
his a study abroad semester.
- He went to the Arctic Circle.
- I wanted to see the penguins.
- Those are in the Antarctic.
- Lesson learned.
Why'd you get kicked out?
You're not allowed to
fraternize with the Inuit.
He tried to score
with an Eskimo.
I was just trying--
I was just trying to get past
the disappointment with the penguins.
All right, so there's nothing so far.
Fox offered him
a ton of money in 2006
to come to LA
and get into late-night.
- A talk show?
- Yeah.
He'd have been good at that.
All right,
get back to the news.
- Did you say 2006?
- Yeah.
- How far did it get?
- A deal memo.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
All right.
You know that this is stupid.
Just go do your jobs.
I've just heard
something I can't believe.
Why don't you
attack this woman?
She doesn't seem
that threatening to me.
She's incredibly threatening.
My life is in constant danger when she's around.
- I'm Lonny Church.
- Mackenzie McHale.
- Attack!
- Nah.
Look, I'll be here at 9:00
unless you're leaving the building.
In which case, press pound five
on your phone and I'll be here.
- Nice meeting you.
Fox offered you
a late-night talk show.
- Great, when do I start?
- Five years ago.
They offered you the show
when we were together.
It was gonna take you to LA
and it got as far as the deal memo.
What is it you think
you've uncovered?
This whole time you've enjoyed
making me feel guilty
for ruining the life
we would have had together
when, in fact, you never had
any intention of marrying me.
No intention of marrying me.
I mean, you never
even mentioned it.
You were just gonna go to LA
and leave a note?
Let me tell you something,
the days of you being able
to lord my mistake over me
are behind us.
I've lived a life
that is good and pure.
You were deceiving me
while I was deceiving you.
You never had any intention of--
What's this?
I didn't tell you
about the Fox offer
because it was never real.
I knew I was being used as leverage,
and I didn't want
to be embarrassed
in front of you
when it went away.
I was still trying
to impress you.
The ring was meant for me?
But I've lived a life
that's good and pure.
Except for...
Cheating on you.
- Could you speak up?
- Cheating on you.
- Except for cheating on you!
- There it is.
Okay. Well, then...
back to work.
Yeah.
Listen, when you do
propose to someone,
that's the ring that'll do it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So as soon as you heard
they were doing opposition research,
you ran over to Tiffany
and bought the ring?
That's insane.
I had to send my agent or
it would have shown up in the papers.
- Will.
- I'm gonna return it.
Does that seem normal to you?
The world is made up
of two kinds of people.
The ones who think they're normal
and the ones who know there's no such thing.
Great, you took one semester
of Intro to Adult Psych.
But the world is made up of
a lot more than two kinds of people.
And I was speaking in the
psychiatric sense of the word.
- Does going out and buying a ring...
- Which I'm going to return.
As a bizarre--
I don't know what to call it--
seem normal to you?
You weren't around
for the exposition.
She had an affair
with her ex-boyfriend.
For four months
while she was with me.
- It's four years later.
- And you know why I don't talk about it?
Because I'm tired of people telling me
it's a "just get over it" situation.
Fuck you.
You don't know what it's like in my head.
Sloan Sabbith.
It's a Japanese news report
from a few hours ago.
We know they're talking about you,
but we don't know what they're saying.
"After releasing incorrect information
to the American journalist Sloan Sabbith"--
That's a picture of Elliot and he didn't
release incorrect information. I did.
And it wasn't incorrect.
"After releasing incorrect information
to the American journalist Sloan Sabbith...
TEPCO spokesman Daisuke Tanaka
has offered to resign today.
He said, 'I apologize
to my company,
my government,
and my country.'"
Please, I have to fix this now.
Help me.
I need wisdom.
- I have wisdom.
- Kenzie, I love you,
but a Japanese man's honor
is at stake,
and sometimes your wisdom
leads to...
like...
- No, I get it.
- Yeah.
Will?
She'd just been suspended and
she's thinking about the other guy's job.
Honor, actually,
is what she said.
Meanwhile,
she's a punch line on the Internet.
- And he's got students, too.
- Who?
Sloan. She teaches
at Columbia twice a week.
You said he.
He's got students.
And you feel that's
a breakthrough moment?
That my subconscious
revealed something?
'Cause I'll be honest. I'm pretty sure
the reason I said he instead of she
is that I've been awake
for a really long time now.
But those comments
weren't on your site, right?
No, because nobody's gonna say that
unless they're anonymous.
And if you don't count the death threat,
it worked.
It was bully kryptonite.
No more LollypopLollypop.
- What did SurrendrDorothee mean when--
- Huh?
The screen name
of the person--
- It's what the--
- Yeah, the screen name of the person--
- Yeah.
- On the last night you showed anonymous posts.
It's what the witch
wrote in the sky--
I'm not asking what
the screen name means.
I'm asking what the person
that when he or she said
that your guest that night had
hit the Uncle Tom Daily Double.
The guest he or she
was talking about
was a man named Sutton Wall,
who was the deputy chief of staff
to Rick Santorum,
former senator for Pennsylvania
who just announced
his intention to run
for President
of the United States.
The list of
prospective candidates
for the Republican
nomination for president
may yet include another name.
Earlier this week,
former Pennsylvania senator
Rick Santorum convened
an exploratory committee...
And Sutton Wall
is both black and gay.
The senator is perhaps best known
for his full-throated
advocacy of social issues.
Here to discuss how
those positions and others
may shape Mr. Santorum's
bid for the White House
is his former deputy chief of staff
Sutton Wall,
an adjunct professor of American Studies
at Temple University,
who will be serving as an advisor
to the campaign throughout this process.
He teaches at Temple?
Yeah.
So he has students?
Yes, he has students.
And LollypopLollypop
said you almost made him cry.
That-- That was absolutely
not my intention.
Well, you're hardwired
to hate bullies.
Like the way comic book heroes
are born out of
a childhood trauma.
Santorum was the bully
in that situation.
Speaking to the
New York Times in May 2005,
Senator Santorum said,
"Gay marriage threatens my marriage.
It threatens all marriages.
It threatens the traditional
values of this country."
Mr. Wall, how does gay marriage
threaten Mr. Santorum's marriage?
The senator believes
that marriage is defined
as the union of one man
and one woman.
I understand that's what
the former senator believes,
but what he said was that gay marriage
threatens his marriage and all marriages.
And I'm asking you exactly
how it's a threat.
Sanctity of life
is the number one issue
with Rick Santorum,
and he believes--
Mr. Wall, we'll get to purposely vague words
like sanctity in a moment.
But I'd like you to try
to answer the question.
How is Mr. Santorum's marriage
threatened
by the gay couple two houses down
also being married?
Will, I was proud to serve
on the senator's staff,
and I'll be proud to serve and support him
should he choose to run for president.
But that doesn't mean
I necessarily agree with him
on every single issue.
Gay marriage is now legal
in five states
as well as
the District of Columbia.
Has Mr. Santorum's marriage
been suffering as a result?
Has he complained to you
that he and Mrs. Santorum
seem to be fighting more
or talking less?
- Of course not.
- Has there been any infidelity
in the last seven years or
an inability to relate to their children
as a result of five states
legalizing same-sex marriage?
This is a preposterous
line of questioning, sir.
I'm afraid it has to be, sir,
because it's a preposterous assertion.
Now, are you able
to name one way
in which Mr. Santorum's marriage
to Mrs. Santorum
is threatened by gay couples
also having the right to marry?
I--
- I am not able to name a way.
- Thank you.
I could have just
stopped it there.
Does it bother you that
Mr. Santorum thinks
there's something wrong with you
that should be fixed?
Hang on, because I am sick
and tired of these attacks,
these wrongheaded attacks against a great man
and a great public servant.
Reasonable people can disagree
about how great a man
or how great a public
servant Rick Santorum is,
but they can't disagree about
the fact that he thinks
you're a sick deviant who's threatening
the fabric of society.
I have known this man
for almost a decade,
and I can tell you that he has treated me
with nothing but respect.
This is Senator Santorum
speaking to Fox News.
- Easy does it, Will.
- No, we're gonna do this thing.
That this is the equivalent,
that being black and being gay
is the same is simply not true.
There are all sorts
of studies out there
that suggest just the contrary,
and there are people who were gay
and lived a gay lifestyle
and aren't anymore.
I don't know if that's the similar situation.
I don't think that's the case
with anybody that's black.
Mr. Santorum is forgiving you
for being black
because there's nothing
you can do about that.
But you don't have to be gay.
I will say it again.
Mr. Santorum is a great man
who would make
a great president.
He has never treated me
with anything but the utmost respect.
Except for finding
you disgusting.
- That is a lie.
- Will, don't--
Has Rick Santorum on
the floor of the US Senate
compared homosexuality
to incest and bestiality?
Those remarks have been taken
out of context over the years--
Feel free to put the remarks
in the proper context.
He makes a clear distinction between
homosexuality and homosexual acts.
So he only finds you disgusting
when you act like a homosexual?
- He doesn't find me disgusting.
- Yes, he does.
And he also thinks
you're less than a man.
- No, he certainly does not.
- Come on.
Our Declaration
contains the words
"We hold these truths
to be self-evident
that all men are created equal."
In order to arrive at the conclusion
that homosexual love
is something less than
heterosexual love,
you have to begin
with the premise
that a homosexual is something
less than a man. That's inescapable.
And so I'm asking you
to explain to me
why you would work for a man
who believes that you're inferior?
- That you're damaged. That you're ill.
- Stop hitting him.
Unnatural.
A threat to children.
Unfit to serve in the military.
Unfit to be a parent.
And unloved by God.
- I'm asking you, sir--
- Stop! Just stop!
I believe in the sanctity of life.
And if that word is too vague for you,
then look it up.
I support the senator because
of all the candidates in the field,
I believe he is
the only one whose passion
on the issue of abortion
equals my own.
And I believe he has the skills
to make a fantastic president.
I am not talking--
That's not--
You will not interrupt
me again, sir!
I am more than one thing.
How dare you reduce me
to the color of my skin
or my sexual orientation?
There are people
who look just like me,
thousands and thousands
who died for the freedom
to define their own lives
for themselves.
How dare you presume to decide
what I should think is important?
Yes, when it comes to equality
for the gay community,
Senator Santorum is wrong.
But I am far more insulted
by your high-handed implication
- that I need your protection.
- Sir, I--
Shut up!
I'll let you know when I'm finished.
I came on this program
because Rick Santorum
believes that the right
to kill an unborn child
is not inalienable.
And I stand with Rick Santorum.
And I stand with
the Catholic Church.
I am not defined by
my blackness.
I am not defined by my gayness.
And if that doesn't fit
your narrow-minded expectation
of who I'm supposed to be,
I don't give a damn
because I'm not defined
by you either.
So get this through your head.
I don't need your help.
Mr. Wall?
Does Mr. Santorum
think you're fit to be a teacher?
No.
We'll be back after this.
He has students.
And parents.
And friends.
And colleagues.
And strangers.
I was the bully.
Mm-hmm.
You've got to give me credit for uniting
the far right, the gay community,
and blacks
in their dislike of me.
The Internet exploded.
Everybody thought
I'd become unhinged.
It sort of brought
back this thing
that happened about
a year ago at Northwestern.
When you yelled at a student.
I scared her.
All right.
That's News Night.
Thanks for washing us-- Watching us.
- Let me get out of here.
- End the broadcast.
- I'm Will McAvoy.
- Attaboy.
Terry Smith is coming up, mercifully,
with the Capitol Report from Washington.
Good night.
If you're here to make me feel better,
it's not necessary.
You think I'm here
to make you feel better?
The story is right.
In this one case,
I don't give a damn about on the record,
off the record.
- And no one in Fukushima does either.
- I do.
The story is right.
- His spokesman denied it on the air.
- He said it to me.
And you got proof of that
I can bounce off our satellite?
- No.
- Is Maggie into Jim?
For Christ's sake,
we're talking about radia-- What?
Am I losing Maggie?
No.
Are you good
at knowing these things?
No.
Make sure he's at Dr. Habib's office
at 10:00 tomorrow.
When are you and me
gonna get busy, huh?
I'm flattered,
but you'd crush me.
That's true.
That's happened before.
Dress up like a tailback and he
won't be able to lay a hand on you.
Shrimp boat, if I wasn't
being paid to keep you alive...
- Let's go.
- Hey, girl!
Do you really have
to call her that?
She's packing up her office.
She's gonna unpack her office
'cause I figured a way out.
What?
The Japanese words
for four and seven sound alike.
- Hey, girl!
- Yes?
Come on down.
I am here.
What's the Japanese
word for four?
Shi.
What's the Japanese
word for seven?
- Shichi.
- Those words are easy to mix up.
- No, they're not.
- Yes, they are.
Not for someone
who's fluent in Japanese.
- You're not fluent in Japanese.
- Yes, I am.
No, you're not.
That's how you mixed up the numbers
when you were talking to
Tanaka in the preinterview.
No, it's for exactly
that reason
that there are two words for four
and two words for seven.
Yon and nana.
And it went from a four to a five to a seven.
That sounds very complicated.
Not if you're fluent
in Japanese.
You're not anymore.
You're gonna go on TV tonight
during Elliot's show,
which I pray to God
Elliot is hosting.
- He is.
- And you're going to apologize and explain your error.
In exchange,
Daisuke Tanaka is going to say
that you made it clear
that you were on the record
and he doesn't have to resign
and you don't have to be suspended.
We're all just going to lie
and I'm going to look stupid.
- You bet. One more thing.
- What?
Fukushima's announcing
the radiation levels are a seven.
Thank you.
I don't know what the hell
you're thanking me for.
Well, it takes a big man
to admit he was wrong.
That isn't even remotely
what I am doing.
Hang on, she's got to go on the air
and say she made a mistake,
that her Japanese is poor--
- Which it certainly is not.
- Just-- God.
She's gonna go on the air
and say she thought it was a seven
when it's really a four
that then moved up to a five
and she's really sorry,
but also now it's really a seven?
It won't be our proudest moment,
but it'll save the guy's job.
Save his honor.
Help very slightly with our increasingly
dinged-up reputation,
and it'll help the girl
who we will now go back
to addressing as Sloan
or Miss Sabbith.
Will.
You want me to lie?
On television?
From a news desk
with the ACN bug in the corner?
I do.
And if there's any fallout,
I'll be standing
right next to you and in front.
I'll always be standing
We fucked up.
Let's just live with that now.
We lied on television
from the news desk.
It was a pretty harmless lie,
wasn't it?
You know how many air hours
I've spent railing against lying?
Calling people out on it?
We're the news and we're all gonna know
we lied for the rest of our lives.
All right, so it turns out
you know what you're doing.
So I'm sorry I've been a jerk.
Obviously the reason I can't sleep
is the Santorum aide.
And I haven't talked to anyone about it,
so I was trying--
- Bacon.
- What?
The bacon, egg,
and cheese sandwiches.
Bacon has tyramine, which increases
the release of norepinephrine,
- which is a neurostimulant.
- When did you figure that out?
When you said you made bacon,
egg, and cheese sandwiches.
- That was like an hour ago!
- Yeah.
Will, listen, and I'm going to write
you a mild prescription,
but you should come back.
If you don't like me,
see someone else.
But see someone.
You've had a lot going on for a long time.
Very serious stuff.
And, by the way,
you should be at an Al-Anon meeting
at least once a week.
You have a lot going on now.
You're being hunted.
In the press,
on the Internet,
very possibly literally.
This whole file here
from four years ago,
every page is about Mackenzie.
In these notes
are a lot of evidence
that you're experiencing
acute depression
and doing a masterful job
covering it.
That's done.
Buying the ring
was not normal.
I don't know what else to call it.
It wasn't normal.
It really doesn't take a team
of Viennese specialists
to see that you have unresolved issues
with Mackenzie.
No, my feelings
are completely resolved.
She's a good friend
and my most trusted partner.
The ring was just a prank.
I know what you think
of all this.
But I would really urge you
to spend an hour a week
faking it.
That's it.
Our time's up.
Sync, corrected by icephoenix
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net