There's a beautiful tone of...
...regret an longing
in that first episode.
That's what it feels
like for this characters.
They all need to hold
on to one another.
If one brakes, if the chain
brakes then there are all at risk.
We're getting this slice
of his life of normality.
And then...
Rick!
When he wakes up
he is tying to work out...
...whether or not
he is still in a coma.
If it's some horrendous dream.
We're able to see the
zombie apocalypse...
...through Rick Grimes eyes.
Through someone who wakes up...
...to find the world has
completely changed.
I don't think he's able to comprehend
the enormous in the scale,
the vision that he's confronted with.
He's trying to keep it together,
trying to keep his grace...
...and his good intentions
intact in the zombie apocalypse.
Lori.
Lori!
When he gets home
there's an unrevealing.
He comes apart.
It's just this horrendous epiphany.
It's actually Morgan that saves him.
What's your wound?
You tell me...
...or I will kill you.
Morgan is wandering
this new nightmare world...
...with his ten years old son.
and still trying to raise his
son into being a good man.
Sit down, before you fall down.
It's the first human contact Rick has.
He gets fed by these
people an it's that kernel...
...of humanity and hope...
...that starts to bring him
back to the man he is.
It took my breathe away...
...because it was all about
what have been lost...
...to what they were
trying to hold on to.
From that point there is a
choice that he mades, he says "no".
As soon as the sheriff badge
comes back on and the hat...
...then there is this semblance
of structure and order.
Then you see that is a
man that does all he can.
From then on.
You're a good man Rick.
I hope you found your wife and son.
Rick's journey is a man's
search for his family.
At the beginning of the story...
...he meets the worse
side of that search...
...which is what he
meets in Morgan really.
This scope is accurate.
The reality of Morgan world
is that he is left having to do...
...what in the surface seems like
a bad thing for a good reason.
It's a horrible situation
for him to be in.
He is a man who has gone through
the same things that Rick gone through.
But he is a month further
on. He is a month wiser.
He is a month more prepared.
The way that I see killing the zombies
justified is about erradicating that.
And reclaiming what his lost.
For the middle of this madness,
the two man try to do the right thing.
- Come on. - I'm sorry
this happened to you.
Two men yearning for family.
You always express your thoughts?
Do you share you feeling,
that kind of stuff?
Shane has extreme loyalty to Rick.
To a large extent, I think that
Rick's family is Shane's family.
When to him Rick was
not gonna make it...
...It was Shane absoluteley top
priority to save Lori and Carl.
Nobody goes anywhere
alone, you know that.
Filling into Rick shoes
was something that...
..naturally he was doing
for his friend.
Yes, sir.
What's really
complicated for lori is that...
Rick and Lori marriage
was under a lot of stress...
...right before this happened.
Shane has only ever try
to protect Lori an Carl.
That boy has been through too much.
He's not losing his mother too, OK?
You get the sense that...
...he is willing to let the rest
of the world burn to the ground...
...as long as the two of them are safe.
This is a need to physically affirm life...
...when everything surrounding
us is death and destruction.
We turn this 21st century guy into
basically a western icon almost...
Is iconic, you know. Man on
horseback riding into town.
He's going into Atlanta
with good intentions.
He doesn't know the
true scale of the epidemic.
It's only when he arrives
that he realizes...
...the enormity of the problem.
Then it's absolutely about survival.
In the middle of a sea of inhumanity...
The spark of the story...
...are the moments of humanity.
Hey, you in the tank...
Cosy in there?
www.tvsubtitles.net