Little girl?
I'm a policeman.
Little girl.
Don't be afraid.
Sync & transcript by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
What's the difference
between men and women?
- Is this a joke?
- No, serious.
I never met a woman
who knew how to turn off a light.
They're born thinking in a switch,
it only goes one way.
On.
*** blond *** lit room.
I mean every woman, every lady has a ***,
I swear to God.
Come home,
house all lit up,
and my job, apparently because...
because my chromosomes happen
to be different
cause I then gotta walk through that house,
turn off every single
light this chick left on.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, baby.
Alright, Reverend Shane's preaching
to you now, boy.
The same chick, mind ya.
She'll bitch about global warming.
That's when Reverend Shane wants to
quote from the Guy Gospel and
say "Um, darling?"
"maybe you, and every other
pair of boobs on this planet
just figured out that the light switch
see, goes both ways,
"maybe we wouldn't have
so much global warming."
- You say that?
- Yeah.
Anyway, uh...
Polite version...
Still man, that... that earns me this.
This look and loathing
you would not believe.
And that's when
the exorcist voice pops out.
"You sound just like my damn father.
"Always, always yelling about the power bill,
"telling me to turn off the damn lights."
- What do you say to that?
- You know what I wanna say.
I wanna say, "Bitch, you mean to tell me
you've been hearing this your entire life
"and you are still too damn stupid
to learn how to turn off a switch?
You know...
I don't actually say that, tho.
- That would be bad.
- Yeah, go with the uh...
the polite version there...
- Very wise.
- Yes, sir.
So how's it with Lori, man?
She's good.
She's good at turning off lights.
Really good. I don't know
why sometimes ***
Not what I meant.
- We didn't have a great night.
- Look, man, I may have a...
fail to amuse with my sermon,
but I did try.
The least you could do is speak.
That's what she always says:
"Speak". "Speak".
You think I was the most closed mouth
son of a bitch you'd ever hear to hear her tell it.
Do you express your thoughts?
You share your feelings and that kind of stuff?
The thing is...
lately whenever I try...
everything I say makes her impatient,
like she didn't want to hear it after all.
It's like she's...
pissed at me all the time,
and I don't know why.
Look, man, that's just shit
couples go through.
Nah, it's... It's a phase.
- Last thing she said this morning?
- Mm?
Sometimes I wonder if you
even care about us at all.
She said that in front of our kid.
Imagine going to school
with that in your head.
Difference between men and women?
I would never say something
that cruel to her.
Certainly not in front of Carl.
All available units, high speed
pursuit in progress
Lincoln county units
request local assistance.
Highway 18 south GTAAD W217 243.
Proceed with extreme caution.
Suspects are two male Caucasians.
Be advised, they have fired
on police officers.
One Lindon county officer is wounded.
Unit 1, Unit 3, please ***.
18, 2 miles west of lnterstate 85
and we'll patch in Lindon County Sheriff radio.
Roger that. We're 5 minutes out
on the route 18 intersection.
Dispatch, Unit 1, Unit 3, we are 10-97
in code 100.
Highway 18, *** Interstate, please advise.
***
Sounds like they're chasing those idiots
up and down every back road we got.
Hey, we'll get them on one of
those video shows, you know,
like World's craziest police chases,
what do you think?
What I think, Leon, is that
you need to stay focused.
Make sure you got a round
in the chamber and your safety off.
Would be kind of cool to get on
one of them shows.
Holy shit.
- Gun, gun, gun.
- Put it down!
Put the gun down!
- Rick!
- I'm alright!
I saw you get tagged, man,
it scared the hell out of me.
Me too.
Son of a bitch shot me.
You believe that?
We'll get you a new vest.
Yeah.
Shane, you do not tell Lori
that happened. Ever.
You understand... Aah!
Rick! Rick!
No, no, no!
Shh, shh, shh.
No, no, no, no...
He's hurt!
***
You get that ambulance down here, you tell
them there's an officer down, you do it now!
Shh, shh, shh, hey, you look at me,
stay with me, you hear me? Shh, shh. okay.
Shh, shh, stay with me, you hear me?
Shh, shh, ok?
You stay with me, ok?
Hey, bud...
We're still here.
We're still hanging in.
Look, I'm sorry, man.
I'm mean watching the same crap
every time I come in here.
Everybody pitched in on these. They uh...
They wanted me to bring them down,
they send their love and they just...
They hope you come back real soon.
Linda and Diane from dispatch,
they picked these out.
You probably could tell, hmm?
I'll just set this on your side table, ok?
That vase has something special.
Fess up. Did you steal it from
your Grandma Gene's house.
I hope you left her that spoon collection.
Shane?
Shane, you in the john?
Nurse, help.
Nurse.
Help!
Lori!
Carl!
Lori! Carl!
Is this real?
Am I here?
Wake, wake up!
- Daddy, daddy!
- Carl...
Carl?
I found you...
Daddy, I got this sumbitch.
I'm gonna smack him dead.
He say something?
I thought I heard him say something.
- He called me Carl.
- Son, you know they don't talk.
Hey, mister!
What's that bandage for?
- What?
- What kind of wound?
You answer me, damn you!
What's your wound?
You tell me!
Or I will kill you.
Got that bandage changed out.
It was pretty rank.
What was? The wound?
- Gun shot.
- Gun shot?
What else? Anything?
Gun shot ain't enough?
Look, I ask and you answer,
It's common courtesy, right?
Did you get bit?
- Bit?
- Bit. Chewed.
Maybe scratch? Anything like that.
No, I got shot.
- Just shot?
- As far as I know.
Hey...
Just let me...
Feels cooler now.
Fever would have killed you by now.
- I don't think I have one.
- Be hard to miss.
Take a moment, eh?
Look how sharp it is.
You try anything...
I will kill you with it,
and don't you think I won't.
Come on up when you're able.
Come on.
This place...
It's Fred and Cindy Drake's.
Never met them.
I've been here. This is their place
It was empty when we got here.
Don't do that.
They'll see the light.
There's more of them out there than usual.
I never should have fired that gun today.
The sound draws them,
now they're all over the street.
Stupid... using a gun...
It all happened so fast...
- I didn't think.
- You shot that man today.
Man?
- No man... - What the hell was that
out of your mouth just now?
- It wasn't a man.
- You shot him.
In this street, out front, a man.
For him, you need glasses,
that was a walker.
Come on.
Sit down, before you fall down.
Here. Eat.
Daddy...
Blessing...
Yeah.
Father, we thank thee for this food...
Thy blessings...
We ask you to watch over us in these crazy days.
- Amen.
Hey, mister, do you even know
what is going on?
I woke up today.
In a hospital.
Came home, that's all I know.
- But you know about the dead people, right?
- Yeah, I saw a lot of that.
Out on the loading dock, hauling trucks.
No...
Not the one's they put down...
The one's they didn't. The walkers.
Like the one I shot today.
Cause he would have ripped into you.
Try to eat you, take him
some flesh at least.
But I guess if this is the first
you're hearing,
I know how it must sound...
- They're out there now, in the street?
- Yeah.
They're even more active
after dark sometimes.
Maybe it's the cool air or...
Hell, maybe it's just me
firing up that gun today.
But we'll be fine long as we stay quiet.
Probably wander off by morning.
Well, listen...
One thing I do know...
Don't you get bit!
We saw your bandage
and that's why we were afraid of.
Bites kill you.
The fever... burns you out.
But then after a while...
You come back.
Seen it happen...
Come on...
Carl...
He your son?
William..
He said his name today...
He's a little younger...
than your boy.
And he's with his mother?
I hope so.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
Did you ask him?
Your gun shot...
We got a little bet going.
My boy say you're a...
bank robber...
Yeah...
That's me. Deadly as Dillinger.
Kapow.
Sheriff's deputy.
Aha.
Hey, it's ok, daddy's here.
It's nothing.
One of them must've bumped a car...
- You sure?
- Happened once before.
Went off a few minutes.
Get the light, Dwayne.
It's the blue one, down the street.
Same one as last time.
I think we're ok.
That noise...
Will it bring more of them?
Nothing to do about it now.
Just have to wait 'em out till morning.
She's here.
Don't look.
Get away from the windows.
I said go! Come on!
Come on, quiet.
Shh, shh...
It's ok, here. Cry into the pillow.
Can you remember?
Shh...
She, uh...
She died in the other room, on that bed...
Nothin' I can do about it here...
That fever, man...
Her skin gave off heat like a furnace...
Should have put her down, I should
have put her down, I know that, but...
You know what...
I just didn't have it in me...
She's the mother of my child.
- You sure?
- They're dead.
They have to ask, at least one more time.
They're dead.
Except for something in the brain.
That's why it's gotta be the head.
You alright?
Need a moment?
They're alive.
My wife and son.
At least they were when they left.
How can you know?
- By the look of this place...
- I found empty drawers in the bedroom.
They packed some clothes. Not a lot.
But enough to travel.
You know anybody could've broken in here
and stolen clothes, right?
You see the framed photos on the walls?
Neither do I. Some random thief
took those too, you think?
My photo albums, family pictures, all gone.
Photo albums...
My wife...
Same thing...
Here I am, packing survival gear,
she's grabbing photo albums....
They're in Atlanta, I'll bet.
That's right.
- Why there?
- Refugee settle.
Huge, when they said it,
before the broadcast stopped.
Military protection, food, shelter...
They told people to go there.
Said to be safest.
Plus they got that disease place.
Center for Disease Control.
Said they were working on
how to solve this thing.
Gas and light have been down
for maybe a month.
Station got its own propane system.
Pilot's still on.
Oh, my Lord.
Hot water!
- Whoo!
- That feels good, right?
Dwayne...
Dress in room back there.
What you say, Dwayne?
Thank you.
Mhm.
Atlanta sounds like a good deal.
Safer anyway. People...
That's where we were heading.
Things got crazy. Man, you won't believe.
The panic...
Streets won't fit to be on,
and then we'll...
My wife...
couldn't travel. no, not with our herd,
so we had to find a place to lay low.
And then, after she died...
We just stayed hunkered down.
I guess we just froze in place.
Plan to move on?
Haven't worked up to it yet. (*)
A lot of it's gone missing.
Dad, can I learn to shoot?
I'm old enough.
Hell yes you're going to learn.
We gotta do it carefully, teach you
to respect the weapon.
That's right. It's not a toy.
You pull the trigger, you have to mean it.
Always remember that, Dwayne.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Go on.
Take that one.
Nothing fancy.
Scope's accurate.
Conserve your ammo. Goes faster than
you think. Especially at target practice.
Dwayne.
- Yeah?
- Take this to the car.
You sure you won't come along?
A few more days...
By the end, Dwayne will know how
to shoot and I won't be so rusty.
You got one better.
I'll turn mine on, a few minutes
every day at dawn.
You get up there, that's how you find me.
- You think they're here?
- Can't afford not to.
- Not anymore.
- Look, just one thing.
They may not seem
like much one at a time...
but in a group all round up and hungry...
- They you watch your ass.
- You too.
You a good man, Rick.
I hope you find your wife and son.
Be seeing you, Dwayne.
- Take care of your old man.
- Yes, sir.
Leon Bessi?
Didn't think much of him.
Careless and dumb, but...
can't leave him like this.
You know, if they hear the shot..?
- Let's not be here when they show up.
- Let's go, son.
Come on.
Read your comic books a while.
Daddy'll be upstairs.
- Daddy?
- It's alright, Dwayne.
You stay there, son.
Don't come up here.
Come on, baby.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
Come on, come on.
Broadcasting on emergency channel.
We'll be approaching Atlanta on Highway 85.
Anybody reads, please respond.
Hello. Hello.
Can anybody hear my voice?
Anybody out there?
Anybody hears me, please respond.
Hello, can you hear my voice?
Hello? Hello? Can anybody hear my voice?
Hey? Hello?
- Can you hear my voice?
- Yes, I can hear you.
You're coming through. Over.
Anybody who reads, please respond.
Broadcasting on emergency channel.
We'll be approaching Atlanta
on Highway 85.
Anybody reads, please respond.
We're just outside the city.
Damnit.
Hello?
He couldn't hear me. I couldn't warn him.
Try to raise him again.
Come on, son. You know best
how to work this thing,
Hello, hello, is the person
who calls still on the air?
This is officer Shane Walsh, broadcasting
a person unknown, please respond.
He's gone.
There are others. It's not just us.
Yeah, We knew there would be, right,
that's why we let the CB on.
Lot of good it's been doing.
And I've been saying for a week,
we ought to put signs up on 85
to warn people away from the city.
Folks got no idea
what they're getting into.
We don't have enough time.
I think we need to make time.
Yeah, that, uh...
That's a luxury we can't afford.
We are surviving here.
We are day to day.
And who the hell would you propose to send?
I'll go. Give me a vehicle.
Nobody goes anywhere alone, you know that.
Yes, sir.
Hey, hey, hey, come on, take a sit, buddy.
You're alright, go on, you're alright.
What, you're pissed at me?
Well pissing me all you want
won't gonna change anything.
I'm not putting you in danger, okay?
I'm not doing it for anything.
I make you feel like sometimes you wanna
slap me outside the head...
I'll tell you what, girl. You feel that need,
you go right ahead. I'm right here.
You cannot walk off like that,
all half-cocked.
Look, if you don't wanna do it for
my sake or for your sake, that's fine.
But just...
You do it for him.
That boy has been through too much.
And he's not losing his mother too, ok?
Okay.
Ok, fine.
You tell me okay.
It's not hard.
Hey...
Mom?
What's up, buddy? She's in there, go on.
Hey.
I don't want you to worry.
Your mom is not going anywhere.
Okay?
- Yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Go finish your chores.
- Okay.
Hello?
Police officer out here.
Can I borrow some gas?
Hello?
Anybody home?
Easy now, easy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Nothing like that.
More like a proposal.
Atlanta's just down the road ways.
It's safe there.
Food, shelter, people,
other horses too, I bet.
How's that sound?
There we go. Good boy.
Good boy. Now come with me.
Come with me.
Let's go easy, ok?
I haven't done this for years.
Easy. Easy, boy. Easy, easy, easy.
Let's go.
Steady. It's just a few.
Nothing we can't outrun.
Okay, whoa whoa whoa.
Lori, Carl, I'm sorry.
Hey, you.
Dumb ass.
Hey, you in the tank.
Cozy in there?
ADDIC7ED FTW!
Sync & transcript by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net