Vice President Matthews.
Mr. Vice President.
Frank.
Sir, I'm gonna need you
to stand on your mark.
I'm fine right here.
Two minutes, people.
So they pull me from the car, both
legs broken, fractured skull,
punctured lung.
My heart stops.
Two full minutes.
They're pumping my chest.
Nothing.
They grab the defibrillators.
Third time,
the pistons start firin'.
Doctors tell me
it's a miracle I'm alive.
But seriously, you talk about
a wake-up call from God.
You don't get to come
back from the dead twice.
The President of
the United States.
Good morning.
The Education Reform and Achievement
Act that I sign into law today
will affect every child and
parent in the United States,
will ensure a better educated
workforce for decades to come,
and will reinforce America's pre-eminence
as an intellectual superpower.
And I'd like to thank
one man in particular,
who never lost sight
of the larger mission,
who spearheaded this
bill from the beginning.
And that's
Congressman Frank Underwood.
Invited guests, please join us in
the East Room for refreshments.
Media,
we will convene immediately
in the Briefing Room
for our conference.
Linda, thank you so
much for all the help
you gave us in
getting this bill passed.
No, thank you, Frank. This was
your baby from the beginning.
I appreciate you standing your
ground on this one, Frank.
I'm smart enough to
admit when I was wrong.
I was just telling Frank
we should set up a weekly,
so he can keep us up-to-date on
what's going on in the House.
That sounds like a great idea.
Congratulations, sir.
Garrett...
I was wondering if we could
talk for a few minutes.
That thing I mentioned
a couple of weeks ago,
about the jobs tax credit...
I've been giving it a lot of thought,
Jim, and I think it's a good idea,
but I'd like to look over my
notes first, if you don't mind,
so I can talk about it
intelligently with you.
Sir, you have your call
with the Prime Minister.
Busy man.
Yes, he is.
Frank, I hear that
you are heading up
the special election
in my home state.
Peter Russo.
We're trying to keep that under the
radar until he officially announces.
In fact, we're not even working
out of my office
until that happens.
Where are you working from?
The basement of my house.
Any reason why the DNC didn't
ask my advice on the candidate?
Well, I thought they passed
it by you, or that Linda did.
Nobody did.
Well, that is unacceptable.
And I have major doubts
about Russo.
His inexperience?
Yes. And he's urban-based. I don't know
if he'll connect with rural voters.
Look, frankly that's one
of my concerns as well.
We're working on that.
But if you were to come
out and stump with him,
that would go
a long way to convince...
Frank, I can't stump for
somebody I don't believe in.
It's early days yet. I'd ask
you to keep an open mind.
And let me know if you want me to set
up a meeting between the two of you.
Because, sir, an endorsement from
you would be a big coup for him.
It's good to see you,
Mr. Vice President.
Frank.
Congressman Underwood.
Ms. Barnes.
I was under the impression
you didn't want to
cover the White House.
Slugline just got
access yesterday.
I know.
I left The Herald because I didn't
want to cover the White House,
and now here I am.
Access isn't the same
as a ball and chain.
Am I only gonna see you
at bill signings now?
I haven't heard from you
in three weeks.
Insecurity bores me.
I feel the same way
about condescension.
Your place. This evening. And I'll
text when I'm about to arrive.
What if I'm busy?
You're just afraid I'm
gonna stand you up again.
I just want to make sure
it's worth my while.
It'll be worth your while.
This'll make up for last time.
It's a piece of history. From
the President's hand to yours.
You believe in all that higher power
stuff they talk about in the room?
I believe there are things
beyond our control.
Who or what's controlling
them, that I don't know.
I don't believe in God. Heaven.
Hell. None of it.
Too much Catholic school?
Maybe.
I'm not saying you have
to believe in God, Peter,
or anything for that matter.
But you shouldn't
rule anything out.
I should go.
It's on the campaign.
Our cross tabs show
81% of likely voters
are willing to consider
a recovering alcoholic.
Now, those numbers dip a little
when you introduce
cocaine, but not by much.
Randy?
It's a risk,
but it'll make waves.
Free coverage across the board.
The narrative has
to be redemption,
a phoenix from the ashes.
Well, let's not
focus on the ashes.
We don't want people to
think Peter was a disaster.
No, no.
We focus on the positive.
A "fresh start" and a "clean start"
both did well in focus groups.
"Clean start" sounds too
much like "clean slate."
I like "fresh start."
Yeah, I do too.
How we doing on
the fundraising?
The alcoholic thing will turn off
some of the in-state donors,
but it's an off-year election.
We can hit up the usual suspects
in New York and California.
Walter, how vulnerable are we?
I'm not prepared to
answer that question.
Peter and I have yet to perform
the holy sacrament
of confession.
We still need to address
the shipyard closing, too.
Claire's helping us with that.
We are pushing a bill called the
Delaware River Watershed Act
and I think it's going to bring
about 5,000 jobs
into Peter's districts
over the next three years.
We have a draft
of the bill completed.
Peter's in the process
of securing co-sponsors.
And who have you called,
by the way?
I have some emails out, but most
of them wanna see a bill first.
Have you set up a meeting
with the shipbuilders yet?
I don't think
they're gonna back me.
That's the entire point
of the bill, Peter.
Well,
if I go to them and I say,
"Hey, some of you maybe
will get your jobs back,
"not tomorrow,
but three years from now,
"and most of you won't be getting
your jobs back anyway..."
All right, let's put a pin in
this until we get more sponsors.
I have to go to the office.
I'll catch you all later.
Okay, let's move on
to our field plan.
I want to go through the
regions one by one...
Francis.
We spent six weeks
on that bill.
It'll be fine.
He'll come around.
I'll see you later tonight?
I have an appointment.
So I won't see you
until morning.
I'll be back before you get up.
I appreciate your taking
the time today, sir.
Did you get that
tax credit memo
the economic
research team
put together?
You didn't ask me here
to talk about memos.
I know small talk
when I hear it, Linda.
The President has asked that you
take a step back from Pennsylvania.
You've been taking a lot of trips
there, meeting with legislators...
It's my home state.
There's a jobs crisis.
We can't afford
to play favorites.
The message is 50 states,
one solution.
Not one state, 50 solutions.
I never expected to be involved
in every policy or decision,
but I have been completely
cut out of everything.
We value your input, Mr. Vice
President, but right now, we can't...
Don't condescend, Linda.
No one even asked me who I
thought should fill my seat.
Why is Frank Underwood leading
the charge on that, not me?
That is a DNC issue.
We are staying out of
it and so should you.
And so I'm supposed to just cut
ribbons and go to funerals?
You know
what you signed up for.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
I didn't get my pen.
Your pen?
From the bill signing.
We'll see what we
can do about that.
I can see your security guy.
Meechum?
He's cute.
He'd never go for you.
Why not?
You're too intimidating.
He's the one with the gun.
But you're the one
with the Congressman.
Uh-uh.
We'll talk after.
We'll talk before.
Peter Russo.
Pennsylvania's first district.
He's gonna run for Governor,
fill Matthews' seat. It's
an exclusive profile.
With someone
no one's ever heard of.
What's the angle?
Alcohol, drugs.
He's a kid from the streets.
I want the profile to come
out as soon as he announces,
and I'd like it to be kind.
I don't write puff pieces.
Then get someone
else to write it.
I thought you had
something for me.
It's too easy for people
to link me as your source.
It's dangerous.
I don't benefit from handing
out headlines to other people.
Generosity is its
own form of power, Zoe.
Step six.
Take the opposite edge
and fold it into a...
Step seven.
Turn the model over
and fold both edges
to the center of the model.
You always wear
sunglasses at night?
How did you find me?
I figured you had
to be in government.
I kept googling till
I found your picture.
This won't work,
what you're doing.
That was a one-time deal. You don't
get to keep coming back for more.
I'll go to the police.
They'll laugh in your face.
Look at you.
If the police won't listen to
me, I'll call TV stations.
I know the names...
Douglas Stamper, Peter
Russo, Frank Underwood.
You are walking down a road
you do not want to walk down.
Please, I won't call anyone.
But I need your help.
I don't have anywhere to go. I
don't have anyone I can call.
I've had to do things. And I
don't want to do it anymore.
That's all I've got right now.
Find a place to stay and
let me know where you are.
I'll figure something out.
You hungry?
What's your name?
Sapphire.
No. What's your name?
Rachel.
Your ex-wife. Anything uncouth?
How do you mean?
Bondage, orgies, water sports?
No. Definitely not.
Narcotics?
She wasn't into that.
Not even a little ganga?
Okay, once in a blue moon.
Ever with your children?
God, no!
Ever in front of them?
Look, I'm not the world's best
dad, but I would never do that.
Fine. Let's move
on to prostitution.
How long is this gonna take?
Until there's nothing I
don't know about you.
I wrote all this down.
I've been doing this a
long time, Congressman.
I know when I've scraped
all the shit off the shoe.
Prostitution.
After my divorce, I took a trip to Thailand.
It was about two weeks.
How many women?
Ten. Fifteen.
I... I don't know.
It was a bit of a blur.
There were drugs?
Yes.
Opium, speed, some smack.
Powder or needles? Both.
Would any of these women
know who you are?
No. None of them spoke English.
And I never mentioned
I was a congressman.
Have you mainlined heroin
back here in the States?
Just once.
Any scars on your arm?
No. I was mainly into cocaine.
What about prostitutes here in D.C.?
How often?
I fucked around a bit, okay?
Details, please.
Do you get off on this
or something?
Does a doctor enjoy it
when he cups your balls
and asks you to cough?
You wanna know how
many times I came?
I honestly don't care
whether you win.
But if you do, work with me.
How often did you solicit
prostitutes in D.C.?
Once every two or three months.
Sometimes more frequently,
sometimes less.
Do you have reason to believe
any of them were underage?
Jesus! No. Look, they
were mostly high-end.
That doesn't mean they were 18.
I need a fucking break!
What's going on?
He's an amateur, Frank.
If I can get under his
skin in less than an hour,
how do you think he'll
hold up under the press?
It'll be a turkey shoot.
All right. I'll speak to him.
Frank, it's just, it's not gonna work.
I'm gonna get crucified.
You'll be fine. We've got
a crack team behind you.
It doesn't matter how good the team is.
With my past? Come on.
From the very beginning, I
said this was the plan.
You agreed to it. I
didn't think it through.
We have to tackle this head-on,
or the GOP will crucify you.
We have to steal their
ammunition from them.
Honesty is your best
defense and offense.
I'm the one that
has to get in front of
these cameras
and say this shit.
They don't have to say it.
I do.
Peter...
I wanna be governor. I do.
But not this way.
I just can't do it.
If you weren't unsure now, there'd
be something wrong with you.
I expected this.
Not easy,
what we're asking you to do.
It's okay to
vacillate a little.
I'm not trying to throw
a wrench in the works.
I know you're not.
I'll tell you what.
You take the rest of the day off.
You go back to your office,
you catch up with whatever
you have to catch up on,
you get a good night's sleep,
you go to a meeting tomorrow,
and then you come here and we'll
talk the whole thing through.
Can you give me at least that?
Yeah. Okay, Frank.
Good.
What's going on with all
the little sculptures?
I found a flower on
the dining room table
and a bird on the
nightstand a few days ago.
It's a swan.
You made them? Yes.
A new hobby?
No.
It's an interest.
May I bring up something
else I've noticed?
What's that?
You...
Standing in front
of the refrigerator.
Is there a reason you haven't
talked to me about it?
I haven't felt the need to.
Is it bad?
It's not pleasant.
But, no, it's not bad.
What can I do?
Nothing.
If there were something,
I'd ask.
Did you think it was
weird that I called you?
Totally weird.
Except for the fact that I
was planning on calling you.
Really? Why?
I was a real grade-A bitch
to you at The Herald,
and I almost apologized when I
saw you at the White House,
but I chickened out.
So, anyway, I am drunk
enough, and I am sorry.
Why did you call me?
I was just wondering how things were
going at the old stomping ground.
Here you go. Thank you.
It's just not
the same since Tom left.
And I don't blame you
for doing what you did.
But this new guy?
Six years running EW Online does
not a managing editor make.
Would you ever want
to come work with us?
I mean,
it'd be a huge fucking deal.
Chief Political Correspondent of
The Herald moves to Slugline?
Did Carly Heath
put you up to this?
No. Not at all. But if you
want, I could talk to her.
You think she would go for it?
Honestly, I don't know.
She's got this sort of
anti-establishment "fuck you" attitude.
Conventional news bores her.
But if you had
something gritty to show...
I've got a story
if you want it.
It's pretty fucking great.
You would give away a story?
If you're not interested...
No, I'm interested.
If I seem a little hung-over,
it is because I am.
A lot hung-over, actually.
God, I almost had
a couple of months,
and then last night, I...
Well,
I don't remember much,
so...
But anyway, here I am.
Keep coming back.
It works if you work it.
Thank you for sharing, Diane.
I'm Doug, and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Doug.
One of the things I do
for a living is count.
I count votes.
Yeas, nays,
neutrals, abstaining.
And I'm good at it.
But the most important count I
do has nothing to do with work.
It's the number of days
since April 4, 1999.
As of this morning,
that's 5,185.
The bigger that number gets,
the more it frightens me,
because I know all it takes is
one drink to go back to zero.
Most people see
fear as a weakness.
It can be.
Sometimes for my job, I have
to put fear in other people.
I know that's not right.
But if I'm honest, like the
fourth step asks us to be,
I have to be ruthless,
because failure
is not an option.
The same goes for my sobriety.
I have to be
ruthless with myself.
I have to use my fear.
It makes me stronger.
Like everyone in this room,
I can't control who I am.
But I can control the zero.
Fuck the zero.
Thanks for sharing. It
works if you work it.
Who would like to share next?
Was he at the meeting? He was.
I tried to find him afterwards,
but he was gone before I
could catch up with him.
Did he say anything? No.
He never shares.
He looked preoccupied.
You think he'll show
up at the house today?
I have no idea.
He's not answering my calls.
Mine neither. Anything
else I need to know?
I hear silence.
I don't like that sound.
Something came up.
I'm handling it.
Something serious?
Serious but solvable.
Do I wanna know more?
I don't think you do.
We'll be okay.
I might have to involve Nancy.
I'm hoping I won't have to.
But if I do, she'll have no
knowledge of anything damaging.
All right.
Use your best judgment.
Of course, sir.
I've gotta go.
Miss Gallagher?
Can the Congressman
have a moment?
Things are...
They're complicated.
I realize that,
but he truly needs you.
I don't know what
I could say to him.
I think just showing up would
do him a world of good.
Today is tough. The Speaker
has a full schedule...
Look, I already spoke to Bob,
and he said he'd be fine
if you took
the rest of the day off.
In fact, he said it'd be
fine if you wanted to take
the next six months off. What?
I want you to be
deputy campaign manager.
You work under Nash Aarons.
No. I spent years being Peter's crutch.
If you just want me there...
Well, of course we want you there
to help, but not as a crutch.
Peter is a talented young man
with a lot of potential.
He knows this,
but he needs to hear it
from someone other than me.
Someone he truly cares about.
I'm sorry.
This is just a lot right now.
Well, you don't have to
make a decision now,
but at least talk to Peter.
I mean, there's no harm
in that, now, is there?
10 grand.
We divert it from
your campaign accounts.
We itemize it
so it looks like...
Wait.
You want me to pay for this?
Use Frank's re-election fund.
Commissioner, the majority of
the money that you've raised
has come from people
we've sent your way.
And you sent them because I sprung
your boy, Russo, in the first place.
We're even.
I don't owe you shit.
There's a girl in trouble.
Let's help her out.
Not my problem.
It could be.
We put her back on the streets,
there's no telling
what she could do.
I'm a hell of a lot more
afraid of the U.S. Attorney
than I am of some hooker.
This is a very inexpensive
insurance policy.
I already broke
the law once, Doug.
There's no fucking way
I'm gonna mess
with campaign
finance regulations.
I don't even wanna
be hearing this shit.
Funeral for the former ambassador
of Japan tomorrow at 9:30,
followed by a luncheon with the
National Board of Directors
for the Girl Scouts of America.
Mr. President. Jim.
After that, you've got a meet
and greet with the finalist...
I'll catch up with you
in a minute.
This way, sir.
Hi.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
The Congressman
wanted me to come over.
Why?
He wants me to work
for your campaign.
Deputy manager. Frank!
He said you're
having some doubts.
I was just about to tell him
that I decided not to run.
Okay.
If you've made up your mind,
then I should
probably get going.
Did he tell you about the whole plan?
About coming clean?
Yeah, he did.
I have Kevin and Sarah
to think about.
Everyone has a past.
Not like mine.
You don't know half the
things I've done, Christina.
My kids read. Their friends read.
I can't take that chance.
Look, if you don't want to
run, then you shouldn't.
I do wanna run. I wouldn't have
let it go this far
if I didn't want it.
Then maybe it's a good thing,
confronting your past,
even for your kids.
They're a lot stronger than
you give them credit for.
Look, if Underwood, if the DNC,
if they all think
you can do it, then...
I don't care what they think.
I care what you think.
I think you'd be great.
So, she really wants this?
That's the impression I got.
What about ego? I don't need
to be dealing with a diva.
She's not a diva,
she's an award-winning journalist
with 15 years experience.
You told me
she treated you like shit.
There was some friction.
So why are you
going to bat for her?
Don't we want to work
with the best people?
Plus, it'd be big for the site.
The Herald's senior
political writer?
Sure, but she's so old guard.
Everything's by the book.
There's no bite to it.
She told me about a
profile she's working on.
It's got serious bite.
What is it?
She can tell you herself.
You should talk to her.
Here's the deal.
My children stay
out of the limelight.
No photo ops, no press.
We wouldn't dream of it.
Okay.
Let's do this.
No.
Where you from?
Outside of Lynchburg.
Virginia?
Yeah.
Are your parents still living there?
No. I can't.
If I find a place for you
to stay for a while,
can I count on you to be smart?
What kind of place?
A nice place.
A safe place until we can
figure out something permanent.
But I need to know that you won't
pull anything like this again.
Promise me.
I promise.
Look at me when you say it.
I promise you.
How you doing on money?
I don't have
enough for tomorrow.
What are you doing?
I thought you wanted me to...
You said you were
done with that.
I'll be in touch.
If you own up to
some of the shenanigans,
sweep the rest under the
rug, you might have a shot.
How much do we
have to sweep under?
Well, that kid had a talent
for covering his tracks.
I've highlighted all the items
I think you should admit to.
The rest I wouldn't mention.
It's a lot not to talk about.
I need your help with something.
Right now?
Yes. Is it important?
Because you told me I could
leave early this weekend
to go visit my daughter
down in Virginia.
You have a guest room
in your house, right?
Well, it's Mary's
old room, but, yes.
I need you to put someone up for a while.
A young woman.
What? Who?
Her name is Rachel.
I can't tell you
anymore than that.
I don't understand.
Why do you need...
No questions, Nancy. I just
need you to do this for me.
I wouldn't be asking
if it weren't serious.
Put up for how long?
I don't know.
It could be a while.
I'm supposed to put up a complete
stranger and not ask any questions?
Nancy, please. You're the
only person I can trust.
Is something illegal going on?
No. She's just a girl in trouble
who needs a place to stay.
We have to be discreet.
Can I at least meet her first?
I need to know now.
Okay, I guess.
Thank you.
There's no catch, Larry.
Your district gets over $20
million if the numbers hold.
And most of
the money is earmarked
for economic development,
not research.
That's great, but I need
more than your support.
I need you to be a sponsor.
Fantastic, Larry.
Great. I'll put you down.
You too. Bye.
So that just leaves
Clayburn and Price?
With Jennings on the fence.
And I know Roger.
I'll call him.
And I'll track down these
other two over the weekend.
Really good work today, Peter.
Do you know
where I put my purse?
It's right here.
Did you make those? I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
This? I've been fooling
around with it a little bit.
Can I see?
Sarah learned how to make
these birds in her art class.
Then she taught it to Kevin,
and they got obsessed,
and there were little pieces of
paper all over the apartment.
Do you wanna take
them for the kids?
No. I can't.
Please. I'll just throw
them out eventually.
Thank you. They'll love them.
So you should bring the kids by the
house sometime so I can meet them.
Kevin and Frank can
play the video games.
He told you that?
I was a little surprised,
I have to admit.
If anybody knew he came
home every day to...
It's embarrassing.
There's worse secrets to have.
Yeah, there are, I suppose.
I'll call you Monday after I
talk to Clayburn and Price.
Okay, great.
Have a good weekend, Peter.
You too.
I had Linda talk to
the Vice President.
He'll keep his nose out of it.
I appreciate that.
He's a good man, but this is a very
delicate moment in the campaign.
He starts
spreading doubts, and...
He's a pain in the ass.
We all know it. You don't
have to mince words, Frank.
I have to say, sir, the
Vice President has a point.
I'm not 100% sold on Russo.
Do we really wanna go with
someone this untested?
Frank?
We're grooming him, sir.
When do you announce?
Next month.
That's not enough time.
What do you see in him?
I was wondering the same thing.
There's not that much to see.
What I see is a recovering alcoholic
with a history of drug abuse.
What? Excuse me, Frank?
But he's clean now.
Has been for a year.
This is a redemption story,
Mr. President.
This is a bright young man who's
put his life back on track.
Now he wants to help put
Pennsylvania back on track.
Drugs, Frank?
People love an underdog, Linda,
and people love someone who
stands up after they've fallen.
Combine those two, it's a
very powerful narrative.
All of our polling indicates
this is gonna work.
You want us to endorse someone
with a history of substance abuse?
Let us get his story out there and
watch it connect with the voters.
All I care about
is a win, Frank.
And I believe Russo
is our best chance.
This is not a Hail Mary,
Mr. President,
this is
a well-thought-out game plan.
Mr. President...
I realize that I sometimes
think out of the box,
but the last time I did, we
signed an education bill.
All right.
We won't stand in your way.
But if it backfires, Frank...
I'll guide Peter
every step along the way.
We will not
disappoint you, Mr. President.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Linda.
I didn't plan on telling
them so much so soon,
but if I didn't, Linda
would've swayed him.
There's no better way to
overpower a trickle of doubt
than with a flood
of naked truth.
This is why the Education
Bill was so important.
It bought me influence precisely
when I needed it most.
How long have you
been drinking?
A long time. Since I was a kid.
How old were you when you
had your first drink?
Nine.
Nine years old? Yeah.
My dad gave me a beer
for my ninth birthday.
When did you first
start using drugs?
I won't go into
too many specifics
other than to say I had
a few minor brushes
with marijuana and cocaine in
the past but not recently,
and only a handful of times.
No other drugs besides
marijuana and cocaine?
No.
Under what circumstances?
Occasional social gatherings.
That's the most I'll say.
Ever while you were
in public office?
No. Never.
My chief problem
was alcohol.
And you've been
sober how long now?
A little over a year.
And what made you
want to get sober?
Two things.
My children, whom I love more
than anything else in the world,
and my renewed faith in God.
Zoe.
Lucas.
I was just in the neighborhood,
and I thought...
No. That's a lie. I was at
the bar around the corner.
The one with the...
And I remembered that time that
I dropped you off after work.
I knew it was...
This block.
And I buzzed,
and then I waited...
You're wasted.
I'm pretty wasted.
Do you wanna know a deep,
dark secret?
Now we don't work together...
Anymore.
Lucas...
I'm really flattered.
But I'm just not in a place
where I'm even thinking
romantically right now.
I'm sorry.
I...
Yeah.
Hey, hey!
You want me to
pull up now, sir?
I still have my key.
I'll be in the kitchen
if you need anything.
Thank you.
Hey, I got us wine, but I can't
find a corkscrew anywhere.
Give it to me.
I need a pen.
The pen the President gave you?
That'll work.
Did you talk to Ms. Skorsky?
I did. She said it was intense.
I think Carly's gonna offer
her a job at Slugline.
Was that your doing?
Janine expressed interest.
I took the next step.
Well done. Always
good to be owed favors.
I was wondering. Do you
ever think about my age?
No. Does my age bother you?
You must have other lovers,
men that are younger than me.
No. Not that I would mind.
I am married, after all.
I don't have time
for other lovers.
Hmm.
Shit.
It's turned. Give me that.
You could've
just stepped on it.
I have asked the super to get
an exterminator in here,
and he won't do it.
So any time I see a cockroach,
or a spider, or whatever,
I try and trap it, and then
I leave it by his door.
You really ought to get your parents
to let you borrow some money.
Then you wouldn't have to
live in the third world.
I would never
take money from them.
Because they don't have it,
or because you don't want it?
Because I don't want it.
It's Father's Day, you know.
It is?
You should call your father.
I'll call him tomorrow.
Tomorrow you'll be the daughter
that forgot Father's Day
instead of
the one who remembered.
Go ahead. Call him.
Hey, Dad. Sorry it's so late.
'Cause you weren't home the
last time I called her.
There's so little she'll ever
reveal to me or I to her.
I bet her father
knows even less.
I'm sure she's speaking
half an octave higher.
Same voice she had
when she was 16.
Telling him all about her new
job, how much she misses him,
and sorry she didn't
send a card.
Telling him everything
but the truth.
Just like she wouldn't tell me
about that young man downstairs.
I'm calling now, all right?
You're gonna make
me feel bad about it.
It was the best thing
that could've happened.
I didn't fit in there.
I've been called worse, Dad.
There's a value
in having secrets.
Creatures like myself,
like Claire, like Zoe,
we wouldn't be
ourselves without them.
But Peter Russo, on the other hand,
he's trapped by his secrets.
What I'm trying to do is
give him the opportunity
to set himself free.
I don't know.
I don't know yet.
After all, we are nothing more or
less than what we choose to reveal.
What I am to Claire is
not what I am to Zoe,
just as Zoe is not to me
what she is to her father.
Probably Thanksgiving.
'Cause I don't think I can
make it back before then.
Okay. I'll try.
I said I'll try.
For Christmas?
No.
Uh-uh.
No. I'm not seeing
anyone right now.
I don't feel like it.
Because I'm not
interested in that.
I would tell you, Dad.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't be worried about me.
I'm fine.
Yeah.
Dad, I'm in...
I'm in a really
great place right now.
I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try to come, okay?
Happy Father's Day.
Aren't you gonna wish me
a happy Father's Day?
You don't have any children.
Don't I?
www.tvsubtitles.net