We're almost a month
into the strike,
and we've got millions of
kids stuck home from school.
Do you blame the White
House or Congress?
I personally have very little
sympathy for the teachers.
We're over three weeks
into this strike.
It's costing the country
billions of dollars,
and instead of
offering solutions...
There's a big
difference between
taking a stand and
sitting on your hands.
I don't know whether to
call it cowardice...
It's his agenda.
And the problem is that he stole
sound, conservative ideas.
The only smart thing
he's done is lift
his platform from the
Republican platform.
I admit it, Linda.
This got away from me.
But we can't turn back time.
We have to hold our ground.
While our approval ratings
continue to nosedive?
Spinella and I
worked together for years
on dozens of
labor-related bills.
I thought he'd be reasonable.
Well, you were
wrong about that.
Well, I didn't think he'd be
insane enough to go on strike,
and I didn't think the
strike would last this long.
So you've been
wrong twice about this.
Why should I believe you're
right about holding out?
We threatened collective
bargaining in order to get
performance standards
and charter funding.
That's the deal that we made.
We took that stand.
We lay down now,
we lose it all.
There'll be no reform,
just an empty bill.
I understand the logic, Frank,
but we're in damage control now.
But we can't close one
wound by opening another.
But we're the Democrats.
We're the ones who are supposed
to be defending the teachers.
But you can't have
it both ways, Linda.
You can't have
the reform you want
and keep the teachers
happy at the same time.
You knew that when we started.
Okay, then if we
have to choose,
we choose to keep
the teachers happy.
That is a mistake, Linda. We've
already crossed the Rubicon.
I'm telling you this. The President
wants to change the bill.
We should've done
it three weeks ago.
We didn't.
So you have to do it now.
Give me more time,
Linda, please.
If I can break
this strike and get
everything we
want in this bill,
can we agree that's
preferable to folding?
Of course.
If we can count on that...
Then count on me for
just one more week.
If the strike isn't over by
then, I'll change the bill.
Frank...
No. One more week. That's all.
This is the worst possible
position to be in.
If I water down the bill, the President
will still see me as a failure.
If the strike
doesn't end in a week,
I've forced
myself into a corner.
Only total victory will put
me back in his good graces.
The alternative is exile,
which would mean the last
five months were for nothing.
I cannot abide
falling back to square one.
Does the Congressman
need me, ma'am?
No. I just was wondering if
you wanted a cup of coffee.
I just brewed a fresh pot.
I'm good, ma'am. But thanks.
Are you sure?
My shift's done in a couple hours.
I'll be fine.
You know, come on.
Stretch your legs.
I won't take no for an answer.
What did you do before you
joined the leadership detail?
I was a cop here in D.C.
Before that,
I was in the
Marines, ma'am.
Thank you.
Did you serve overseas?
I did, ma'am.
Bahrain, then Afghanistan.
Served most of my second
tour in the Korengal Valley.
You wanna know if
I killed anyone?
I think I know the answer.
I got a dinner meeting with Birch.
I'll be...
I invited him in for coffee.
Well, drink it fast.
We leave in five...
Get down!
Stay away
from the windows!
Stop!
You'll have six of my best men
covering you around the clock.
I guess I'm wondering why
we didn't at least have
one of your best
men covering us now.
He'll be disciplined, sir.
He shot a gun in a
residential neighborhood.
I want him fired.
There will be
a full investigation,
and we'll take
the necessary action.
Steve never
would've let
this happen.
Is he better yet?
Because I would
feel a lot safer
if he was with us.
Unfortunately, he won't
be coming back, sir.
I thought he just had a
gallbladder infection.
He did, they found more.
His pancreas, stage four.
Jesus.
Oh, my God.
That's awful.
How much longer does he have?
Not long. A few weeks.
At least that's
what his wife told me.
We have to go see him. Can you
get the information where he is?
Of course. I'll make sure
you get it right away.
Thank you, Captain. Thank you.
You're welcome. Good night.
Front door. Yes, sir.
Your weapon.
Your badge, too.
Am I suspended, sir?
You had a suspect on foot,
and you fire your gun?
Sir, I realize that...
Do you know how
this reflects on me?
That one of our men
could be so careless?
Not only do you abandon
your post for coffee.
You could've
killed a bystander.
That slug was found on
somebody's front stoop.
What if it went in their house?
Your badge, Meechum.
Two reasons, which are
really the same reason.
I was sick of
working for
other people,
and I knew I could do a
better job than my bosses.
They kept trying to suppress
me, shutting me out.
So I said, "Fuck it.
I'll do it my way."
And then you just quit?
Not like you did.
I slaved away until I lined up
the money to start Slugline.
Once Slugline gets big
enough, what's the plan?
Are you gonna
sell it like Arianna?
Probably. And then who knows?
Whatever the next adventure is.
Maybe Shanghai.
So I shouldn't expect to
have a job in two years?
Do you ever wanna have any
job for more than two years?
What about you?
What's your big plan?
Uh, I don't know yet.
Come on. Slugline is just
a stepping stone for you.
You know what?
I should take this.
Go. Do your thing.
Hey. Do you have proof
Spinella was behind it?
Put it in context. Three weeks into
a national teachers' strike...
At the home of Francis Underwood,
who has led the charge on...
There you go.
Now post that
before one of
my neighbors calls
a local 11:00 hack.
When do I see you next?
I'm background on this.
I'm not your source.
You can't talk now?
No. When?
Soon, with bells on.
What about "more school
books, less bricks"?
No, it's too broad. We
need a better sound bite.
Something specific,
something that
points the finger
directly at Spinella.
He'll deny any involvement.
Well, of course he will.
So how do we get around that?
We say he can't
control his troops.
There's no evidence
it was a teacher.
Who else could it be?
Look, he's gonna shift blame for
the strike back on Congress.
No. We need something
clear, something clean,
something that
sticks in your head.
"Teachers need a lesson
in self-restraint."
No. You're not hearing me.
People like teachers.
No. We need something that
makes Spinella the villain.
His lack of control,
his inability...
Disorganized labor.
It's disorganized labor,
plain and simple.
When you've got angry
teachers throwing
bricks through
congressmen's windows,
you've gotta blame the
union leadership.
We'll be beefing up the security
for the entire leadership.
And I strongly encourage Marty
Spinella to keep his people in line.
This is starting to look
like disorganized labor.
Do you really think Marty
Spinella is to blame?
Whether Mr. Spinella
is behind this or not,
he might wanna tone
down the rhetoric,
before disorganized labor
turns into organized crime.
No one can prove anything. So
that's the most cogent response.
Well, go on TV and say that. You
deplore violence in any form.
It's Congress that should
take responsibility.
I don't want to degenerate
to Frank's level.
We need to kill
this brick thing.
It's distracting
people from the issues.
She's right.
It'll eat up one cycle,
and it'll disappear.
No. This story is
getting traction.
Support for
the strike is dipping.
So is the President's
approval ratings.
But he gets to stay
in the Oval Office
another three years,
no matter what.
We can't afford
another three weeks.
When I told
the unions to strike,
I told them to
prepare for the long haul.
All right? Their accounts
dry up, we keep going.
We figure it out.
I am not going
to blink over
something like this.
Fine. But if we lose the
public relations battle,
none of that does us any good.
Frank wants us
on the defensive.
I think this story
is going to blow over.
If I'm wrong, we'll reevaluate.
But I wanna give it another
day or two first. Okay?
Hi, Adam.
You all right? I saw the news.
Yes, I'm fine.
That's gotta rattle the nerves.
Brick coming
through the window.
It did, some.
So are you
staying in the house?
We've got extra
security now, so...
Well, it made me think of you,
so I figured I'd just check in.
I appreciate that.
We still haven't
talked, have we?
There's no need to.
I think we should.
Here's how I see it.
You asked me to
come down. I did.
We both had ideas about
what that could mean.
Probably very similar ideas.
But then you changed your mind.
So be it.
There's no reason we can't be
in touch or remain friends.
Let's not fool ourselves, Adam.
So I won't call again.
Done. I'm not saying that.
What are you saying?
I just called because
I care about you.
No agenda.
If you wanna
talk again, call me.
If not, I understand.
It's up to you.
You think I'm
being unreasonable?
I think you're doing whatever
it is you need to do,
and I'm not gonna question it.
It was sweet of you to call.
Listen, you probably need
to get back to work.
I know I do. I should go.
Yeah. Okay.
Take care. Okay.
Frank, you got a minute?
I'll see you inside.
I wanna be governor,
and I want your help.
Am I still on the short list?
You are.
I haven't had a drink in over a month.
I'm clean.
Is that because I asked, or
because it's what you want?
It was about time I took
responsibility for myself.
Taking responsibility is one
thing, and it's admirable.
But running for
governor of a major
state is a whole
nother ball game.
Let me tell you something, Frank.
I got elected to Congress
'cause I seized the moment
that opportunity struck.
You kept me on that list. I
wanna seize that opportunity.
If you help me out, I'll
give you everything I got.
Well, that's all I've
been waiting to hear.
All right. I'll tell you what.
I need to make some calls,
check in with some people.
Give me a few days.
I'll get back to you.
Of course. And, Peter...
I feel like I've met the real you
for the first time just now.
Janet.
Is this a bad time? No.
No, not at all.
I'm sorry. I didn't
know you were coming.
Here. Take my chair.
Oh, no. I'm fine.
I'll take these.
Thank you.
Hello, Steve. Hey.
These could use some water.
I'll be right back.
Francis and I were so
upset when we heard.
I'm sorry I
haven't come sooner.
I didn't want too
many people knowing.
Yes.
Francis wishes
he could be here.
He wants you to know
he's praying for you.
Couldn't make it, huh?
No, there's a big teachers'
strike going on right now,
and he's been stuck in
his office for weeks.
I get it. I saw the news.
The brick.
Right.
I told Francis
that probably wouldn't
have happened if
you were there.
No. Probably not.
I never seen him pray.
Not in eight years.
You said he was praying for me.
You've seen us in church.
Yeah, but I never went inside.
They're just gorgeous.
Mrs. Underwood,
thank you so much.
Please, call me Claire.
I know you got things to do.
Of course.
If you need anything at all, call me.
You have my cell.
Anything at all. And I'm
sorry to have surprised you.
No. It was so
nice of you to come.
Thank you. I know
Steve appreciated it.
Check this out.
It's foam.
How many of these we have?
200. But I can get more.
Get more.
Bring it on!
You need to give the teachers
the respect they deserve.
We can't back
away from this, Marty.
We've gotta face it head-on.
They provoked us.
They were throwing foam. Our
guys were throwing punches.
We're gonna come
off the bad guys here.
Okay. Okay. I get it. I get it.
But I wanna be
smart about this.
I wanna do something definitive
that'll put this to bed
and get us back on message.
CNN.
One-on-one, you and Underwood.
8:00 tonight.
Frank is excellent in debates.
Go strong against him. Address
the brick right to his face.
End of story.
Underwood says
he's in if you are.
Okay. But I want as much
prep as possible, okay?
I want to run questions.
You moderate,
you play Underwood.
Wear this one.
Then come in here. I
wanna put powder on you.
Well, there's somebody at
the studio can do that.
Yes, and they always cake on too much.
I'm doing it.
War paint.
How bloody do
you think it'll be?
I think I oughta be able to
dispatch with him easily enough.
You remember Peter Russo?
He's doing well. He hasn't
had a drink in a month.
Good for him. I like him.
Good, because he
could use your help.
How?
We're running him for governor.
Ambitious.
Mm. We wanna create
jobs in his district.
It's on the Delaware River.
I thought we might be able
to put a bill together.
Something with
an economic upside.
This has to do with
the shipyard closing?
We need the shipbuilders'
support for his campaign.
You think you might be able to
draft a bill that he can sponsor?
I'm really trying to focus on
international projects, Francis.
Not domestic legislation.
I understand, but I could
really use your help, Claire.
Does Catherine
Durant still owe us?
When you make someone Secretary
of State, they owe you for life.
We're having trouble getting our water
filters through Sudanese customs.
I'll call from the car.
Tomorrow's fine.
I would have done that anyway.
I know.
I'm ready for battle.
You wanna come watch?
No. You go on ahead.
Come on.
Watch me put the final
nail in Spinella's coffin.
It'll be fun.
Marty.
Frank.
Come on, people.
Take your marks.
Congressman, would you
like to respond to that?
Yes, I would.
$2 billion of taxpayers'
money being wasted.
And Congress should be ashamed
of itself for that, Frank.
What? Did Congress force the
teachers to go on strike, Marty?
No, we didn't. Really, Frank?
When you threaten teachers'
ability to negotiate as a union,
when you threaten
their job security,
you threaten their livelihood,
of course you
force them to strike.
And did we also
force them to start
throwing bricks
at people's houses?
You know what, I'm really
glad you brought that up,
because you know there's
absolutely no proof that
that incident had anything
to do with this strike.
And I wanna take the
opportunity to say publicly
that we categorically condemn
any use of violence
whatsoever, or intimidation.
What you're saying,
essentially,
is that you can't control
your own people.
That's not what I'm saying.
That is what you're saying.
You're disorganized.
Disorganized labor.
You know what, you could keep trotting
out that phrase all you like,
but you know what I'd like to do, Frank?
I would like to get back
to the issue here of
educating our children
and the fact that Congress is not
living up to their commitment.
Well, you know what
I would like?
What?
An apology.
If not to me, then to my wife.
When that brick came through
our window, it was terrifying.
She's standing
right over there.
Claire? We need camera
two on the wife.
Now, why don't you
look her in the eye
and tell her that your people had
nothing to do with that brick.
Are you serious? Yes.
Okay.
Mrs. Underwood, Claire,
I am sincerely sorry
that you had to go through
that ordeal, truly.
And it actually sickens me
that someone made you feel
unsafe in your own home.
And I give you my word that
to the best of my knowledge,
none of our people had
anything to do with it.
But you know what
sickens me more?
That right now, your
husband is using you
as a prop on national television
to try and win a debate.
So I think you're the one that
owes your wife an apology, Frank.
And when you're
done apologizing,
can we please get
back to the issue here
of educating our children?
No. You've got
this wrong, Marty.
There is no "you"
and "I" in education.
Well, I mean,
yes, there's the letters,
"U" and "I" are in
the word education.
But education
with a capital "E"...
You know what
I'm talking about.
I don't think I do.
Yes, you do, Marty.
"U" and "I", education.
So, we're gonna
waste the rest of
this debate naming
all the vowels in...
I'm happy to
play the vowel game.
You wanna play the
vowel game with me?
All right."U" think "I"
"O" "U"
"A" apology?
But no, no, no.
"U" "O" "I."
Interesting. You left out
"E" for "Education."
So let... Defecation.
Edification. I'm sorry.
LOL. Uh...
You like Sesame Street so much?
Why don't you give the kids
the money they deserve?
What I'm trying to say
about education...
Well, I guess school's
still in session.
I guess you schooled
me there, Marty.
Let's move on. Please.
Humor aside, there are more
important issues out there.
I had no intention of
bringing you into this.
It wasn't part of a plan. I
would've told you if it was.
I know.
The idea just struck me,
and I went with it.
I don't mind
that you improvised.
I just wish
you'd done it better.
Congressman Frank Underwood
says he got, quote, schooled
by AFT spokesman and chief
strategist, Martin Spinella,
during a debate last
night on this network.
In the past 24 hours,
reruns of the gaffe
have played nonstop on TV news
programs and the Internet.
A YouTube clip
set to techno music
has logged more
than 300,000 hits
and spawned
dozens of other spoofs.
♪ No, no, no
♪ "E" "O" "I"
♪ With a capital "E"
♪ Education LOL ♪
That was as clumsy as the Lee
Harvey Oswald prison transfer.
What was he thinking?
Just give me one second.
There's a deli down the street.
Patti, thanks for coming.
Sit down. You want some coffee?
No, thanks. I'm good.
Hey, did you see Bill
Maher last night?
No, I didn't.
It was about the CNN thing.
I have to admit, Frank,
it was kind of funny.
Well, I'll have to
catch a rerun.
How you doing? You holding up
all right with the strike?
Let's talk about Pennsylvania.
I have your candidate.
Peter Russo.
1st Congressional District.
We crossed him off.
I know. It's a mistake.
He's young, he's
handsome. He's bright.
Nobody knows who he is
outside of Philadelphia.
There's no donor base,
no infrastructure.
You start me off with
funding from the DNC
and I'll raise
an army around this guy.
I will personally
oversee his campaign.
Is that the best we can do?
What's better than a blank
slate in the right hands?
Ed, you need to go.
Congressman,
do you have a moment?
Thank you, Patti.
Have him call me.
I will.
Ed? Please.
What is going on?
I'm taking care of it.
One second, sir. Please.
All right.
Make it fast, Meechum.
It's not easy
for me to ask this,
but I was
wondering if you could
put in a good
word with my boss.
A good word?
They're going to
discharge me, sir.
I messed up. I'm fully aware.
But my job,
it means
everything to me,
and I know a good
word from you would...
Look, I have nothing against
you personally, Meechum,
but I can't get involved
in these sort of affairs.
There's protocols and rules.
Sir, please,
if you spoke to Cardiff...
There is nothing that I can do.
If anyone could convince the Captain,
it would be you, Congressman.
I'm sorry. I wish you
all the best, Meechum.
Doug.
What did Barney Hull say?
That we'd be the first to know.
I can't believe there hasn't
been a single 911 call.
There's been plenty. It's just
not the sort we're after.
We got that kid in Atlanta.
No, it's got to be here. I
can't be getting on a plane.
It looks too opportunistic.
Maybe if we open
it up a little bit?
No, we cannot
lower our standards.
We just have to be patient.
New rule. Now that
the debate's over,
Frank Underwood has to tell
us what the hell that was.
Seriously, Congressman,
was that a joke?
I haven't seen something just
lay there like that since...
I gotta go all the way
back to my prom night.
Can we just settle
this strike please?
Teachers have been out of
the classroom for so long,
middle-schoolers are starting
to have sex with each other.
Enough.
I don't know why you had
it on in the first place.
I love you, Francis.
I know.
We should say that more
often to each other.
I need to clear my head.
North and east of the airport.
I'm gonna need that in
time for that meeting.
Peter, let's talk.
So. I've spoken to Patricia Whittaker.
She's on board.
You'll be getting $4 million in
start-up funding from the DNC.
I'll pick the team. You
announce in August.
But the campaign starts today.
Are you ready?
I've already put
together a platform.
It's mostly broad strokes,
but we can hone it.
Good. The first thing we need
to address is your sobriety.
You don't need to
worry about that.
Have you been
going to meetings?
You mean AA?
Yes.
That's not really my thing.
If you want my help,
then going to meetings
is my one requirement.
I know I had a problem, Frank.
I accept that.
And I've taken
responsibility for that,
but I don't think going
to meetings is necessary.
You cannot white-knuckle
your recovery, Peter.
This campaign will be the hardest
thing you've ever done in your life.
I realize that.
I'm prepared for that.
You think you are.
But we can't take any chances.
The party's investing in you.
I need to make sure you're
investing in yourself.
All right. I'll do
whatever I have to do.
Good. You'll start
tomorrow morning.
Doug will take you.
Stamper?
He's been sober 14 years.
Doug has a drinking problem?
Had. Not anymore.
He'll be your sponsor.
In the meantime, I want you
to meet with my wife, Claire.
She runs the Clean
Water Initiative.
She's expecting you,
so clear your schedule
and head over there now.
Frank.
Thank you.
For believing in me.
You're gonna make a
great candidate, Peter.
The shipyard closing frees up
1,100 acres of federal land.
Our goal is to pass a Watershed
Act for the Delaware River.
We develop the land in an
environmentally responsible way,
creating jobs in the process.
How many jobs? Thousands.
We're aiming for
the $200 million mark.
We got a lot of work to do.
We do, but you can start
with the congressmen
whose districts fall
within the watershed.
Do you have a draft of the
bill you can show me?
We haven't sponsored any
environmental legislation.
We'll draft it in
consultation with your staff.
Gillian will be the point
person on our end.
I don't have any
legislation experience.
I'll help you.
When do we start?
We just did.
Will you introduce him
to the research team?
I'll be there in one second.
Sure.
Mr. President?
I want it over.
As soon as possible.
Gut the bill, Frank.
Do whatever's
necessary to end this.
Mr. President,
if we give in now,
the public won't credit
you with a victory.
Not even a hollow one. They'll
chalk it up as a colossal defeat.
Well, that's on you, Frank.
You let this situation
devolve to where it is.
I've already been blamed for the largest
teachers' strike in U.S. history.
I won't be held accountable for
it dragging on months and months.
Mr. President, we have to end
this strike on your terms.
Not anyone else's. How?
By debating Marty
Spinella on CNN?
Sir, you have placed your
faith in me thus far.
I would ask that
you continue to do so.
Well, whatever you're
doing, Frank,
isn't working,
so I'm stepping in.
Gut the bill. Like Linda said.
No.
I'm sorry, Mr. President,
but I will not do that.
Are you letting pride cloud
your judgment, Frank?
Respectfully, sir, you're
allowing fear to cloud yours.
Not an easy thing, to say no
to the most powerful
man in the free world.
But sometimes the only way to
gain your superior's respect
is to defy him.
What do we have on
the schedule, Linda?
Your meeting with the Fed
Oversight Committee.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Do you have my briefing?
Right here.
Good. Let's look it over.
Hi. How'd it go with Peter?
It went well.
Is he game? Completely.
Thank you.
That's a big weight
off my shoulders.
You sound tired.
Tired. Impatient.
What can I do?
Nothing. This one's up to fate.
I don't like when we
leave things to fate.
Neither do I.
Does that mean I'm gonna have
the bed to myself tonight?
Probably.
Can't Doug man the fort?
Well, he could, but I'd
just toss and turn.
If I'm not gonna sleep, I
might as well not sleep here.
Well, I'll leave the ringer on.
Call me if you want company.
I will. Good night.
Good night.
You should go home. I
could take it from here.
Vigilance.
It's good for the soul.
10-59.
Corner of 16th and Q. 10-59.
What's that?
Disorderly conduct.
Do you believe in karma?
Absolutely not.
Well, I do.
At least tonight.
Get Captain
Cardiff on the phone.
Let's do
something about Meechum.
What? Get him his job back.
He fired his weapon.
He overreacted.
Cardiff. On the phone. Now.
Nancy, give me
Captain Cardiff, please.
We might as well do one
productive thing while we wait.
It requires very little of me
and will mean the world to him.
It's a very
inexpensive investment.
Hello, sir.
This is Doug Stamper.
I have Francis
Underwood for you.
I got him on.
Captain, I know it's late,
but I'd like to talk to
you about Edward Meechum.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Are you hungry? Mm-hmm.
You have any
trouble getting in?
No, they made me put it through
the X-ray machine twice,
so I hope it
didn't overcook it.
Frank, you always pay too much.
This is way too much.
It's for the inconvenience.
You know, 20 years you
been coming to my joint.
This is the first
time I've been to yours.
What do you think?
I could get used to it.
Well, you're welcome any time.
Thank you, Freddy.
Always, Frank.
We got a 27 Delta two.
446 3rd Street...
That's a drive-by shooting.
Get details.
Sir, I want to thank you for
talking to the Captain.
He told me you called, and I can't
tell you how grateful I am.
I want you to
listen very closely
to what I'm about to say.
From this moment on,
you are a rock.
You absorb nothing,
you say nothing,
and nothing breaks you.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Welcome back.
Steve?
I'll leave you be.
Where... Where's Janet?
She's been here every day
for the last few weeks.
I told her,
go home, get some rest.
Well, is everything okay?
Your text said
it was important.
I don't know how to put this.
The thing is, I...
I've been thinking.
A lot.
About my life.
About the things
I haven't done.
Things I haven't said.
I hate your husband.
A lot of people do.
The past eight years,
I watched over him.
But it wasn't
him I was watching.
And every time I saw you,
every time I heard your voice,
all I could
think to myself was,
"Jesus, what I wouldn't give."
I can't tell you how many
times I thought about that.
You know what Francis said
to me when he proposed?
I remember his exact words.
He said, "Claire, if all
you want is happiness,
"say no.
"I'm not gonna give
you a couple of kids
"and count the days
until retirement.
"I promise you
freedom from that.
"I promise you'll
never be bored."
You know, he was the only man,
and there were a lot of
others who proposed.
But he was the only
one who understood me.
He didn't put me
on some pedestal.
He knew that I didn't want
to be adored or coddled.
So he took my hand and
he put a ring on it.
Because he knew I'd say yes.
He's a man who knows how
to take what he wants.
Is this what you wanted?
Is that the way you wanted it?
Stop. Stop.
Please. Please. Stop.
Don't.
You told me your truth.
Now you know mine.
Hey, it's Peter.
I don't expect
you to call me back,
but I wanted to let you know I
stopped drinking last night,
and I went to my first
AA meeting this morning.
I'm supposed to reach out and
make amends to those I've hurt.
But I guess the real
reason I called you
is just to say I love
you and I miss you.
I hope you're well.
This is work, not play.
Then why'd you
bother coming over?
I was hoping you'd
answer the door naked.
That would be play.
That would be work with a view.
Sorry to disappoint.
How many characters in a tweet?
140.
Type this, let me know
where you land.
Eight-year-old
Washington D.C. boy
killed by a stray bullet
in gangland shoot-out.
61 characters left.
He should have been in school?
30 left.
Spinella to blame.
Question mark.
128. Press send.
Now give me a name, details.
Tyler Davis. Third-grader
at Vernon Baker Elementary.
Shot outside his home in Southeast
just before noon today.
Sent. Where are you going?
To see the mother.
You don't wanna...
There's work to do. I'll
see you later tonight.
Tyler never did anything wrong.
He was a good boy.
Everybody loved him.
It's okay.
If Tyler's school had
been in session,
this senseless killing would
have never taken place.
We need to end this strike now
and get all our children back
in school where they belong,
before we risk another
death like this.
So, Mr. Spinella, I am headed
to the Capitol right now,
and I will remain there until
you are ready to meet and talk
so that we can end
this pointless strike.
Thank you all for coming.
Let's go back inside.
Mr. Spinella, one question.
Mr. Spinella is not gonna
make comments at this time.
No comment. No comment.
Thank you.
Frank.
So?
You said you wanted to talk.
You said you wanted to
work out a compromise.
I lied.
Excuse me?
I have no intention of
working out a compromise.
So then why the fuck
are we here, Frank?
What the hell's
the matter with you?
You think this is
some kind of a game?
No.
These are real people
with families to feed.
Would you please stop that?
Stop what?
In five seconds,
I'm out of here.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four. Goodbye, Frank.
You know the difference
between you and me, Marty?
What?
I'm a white-trash cracker
from a white-trash town
that no one would
even bother to piss on.
But here's the difference.
I've made something of myself.
I have the keys to the Capitol.
People respect me.
But you, you're still nothing.
You're just an uppity
dago in an expensive suit
turning tricks for the unions.
Nobody respects
the unions anymore, Marty.
They're dying.
And no one respects you.
The most you'll
ever make of yourself
is blowing men like me.
Men with real power.
Yes. I can smell the cock
on your breath from here.
You think you can
get under my skin?
I know I can. Yeah.
Kiss my ass, Frank.
You can't afford
to walk out.
Watch me.
I've got a dead, underprivileged
kid in my pocket.
What do you have?
I have two million
honorable teachers.
Fair enough. But I got
something even better.
Go ahead. Open it.
Okay.
I'll play your game.
You're an idiot.
Stamper threw it.
You're full of shit.
Oh no, Stamper threw the brick.
And I made sure Claire
distracted my security.
Are you kidding me?
And to think you wanted me
to apologize to my wife.
You would do
something that low, Frank?
I arranged the brick, Marty,
just like I arranged this
meeting this afternoon.
Back off, Frank.
Why don't you just
get down on your knees
where you really belong?
Back off, Frank.
Because the only thing
you're gonna get from me
is cum on your... Fuck you!
Everything okay in there, sir?
Look, I'll tell
them you provoked me.
I'll tell them that you
threw the brick yourself.
And who's going to believe you?
You just assaulted a
United States Congressman,
which is a felony.
But I'm not gonna
press charges, Marty.
Because the strike ends now.
You think it'll leave a scar?
I have a thick skin.
The next time you ask me to
invite someone in for coffee,
will you please make
sure no guns go off?
I'll do my best.
I saw Steve again today.
How is he?
In a lot of pain.
Should I go see him?
I don't think you need to.
Zoe Barnes.
When he dies,
we'll pay for his funeral.
You don't need to take it?
No.
I'm done with work today.
www.tvsubtitles.net