Climate controlled stacks,
energy efficient,
now mind you
the whole collection
could probably fit on a Kindle,
but at least
the cadets will have
another place to
get out of the rain.
Did you have much
input on the design?
I approved the blue prints.
If something's gonna
have my name on it,
I want to make damn sure
they build it right.
I think my husband fancies
himself a bit of an architect.
Well, Jefferson
designed Monticello...
He also fucked his slaves.
Luckily I don't have any,
so that particular temptation
hasn't presented itself.
The Sentinel, South Carolina's
premiere military college.
They taught me the values
of honor, duty and respect.
They also hazed me,
tried to break me,
and senior year,
nearly expelled me
when I volunteered for a Senate
race and my studies suffered.
But that didn't stop them
from soliciting a hefty sum
for their new library
30 years later.
How quickly poor grades
are forgotten
in the shadow of
power and wealth.
Your drink is only about half
as full as it should be, Frank.
Are you trying to get me drunk?
Drunk, passed out in the gutter
so I can steal your wife.
Did you get
the email about the Riflemen?
What email?
From my office.
About the invitations.
I was hoping
they would be here.
I'll check the list, but I
don't remember any email...
Oh, not a problem.
I was just wondering.
Shit, Frank, I'm sorry...
Don't you sweat
it for a second.
In fact, here's how you
can make it up to me,
freshen my drink.
That I can do.
Congratulations, Congressman.
Remy, nice to see you here.
Gerry and all the folks at
SanCorp give you their regards.
Well, I'm sorry
they couldn't make it.
Where's Claire?
She's here somewhere,
fending off admirers.
SanCorp was very disappointed
she turned down their donation.
I can imagine.
And they're also concerned about
Peter Russo running for governor.
Now, how do you
know about that?
Three-quarters of Pennsylvania sits
on top of the Marcellus Shale.
If I can't find out who's
running for governor,
I don't deserve a dime of
what they're paying me.
This Watershed Bill
Russo sponsors
places a lot of
restrictions on drilling...
Remy, Congress is in recess and
this weekend is not about work.
I apologize,
you are absolutely right.
Is SanCorp your only account?
I have plenty.
But my other clients didn't pay
for your library, or my
plane ticket down here.
Yes,
nice little junket for you.
I do hope you're
taking in the sights.
This isn't my first
trip to Charleston.
But I'll bet it's your first
time not as my Press Secretary.
It is.
Who else you have coming in?
I didn't want to
pack tonight too much.
You know,
these receptions are usually
just for the money people,
like yourself.
Normally, this is
where I would start
to drone on about the
Sentinel's history,
its philosophy, its
yadda, yadda, yadda...
But I'm gonna save that for
my big speech tomorrow,
and that way I'm not gonna
bore y'all to tears twice.
Tonight we're
gonna turn it over
to a man who
needs no introduction,
'cause we all know what
a son of a bitch he is.
Seriously, though,
Frank Underwood exemplifies
all the virtues
we try to instill
in our graduates.
We're so proud to call
you an alumnus, Frank,
and to have your name as a
permanent fixture on our campus.
Congressman Frank Underwood.
Thank you, President Higgins.
I first want to thank
SanCorp Industries
for providing the funds to
make the library possible.
When I matriculated
here as a young cadet,
Jimmy Carter had just
been elected President.
After I graduated,
I wished that I could have had
another four years, just like Jimmy.
Well,
neither of us got our wish,
but I left this campus
with fond memories.
The first time I ever...
♪ Old times
they are not forgotten
♪ Look away!
Look away! Look away!
I got your damn email.
♪ I wish I was in Dixie
♪ Hooray, hooray
♪ In Dixie Land
I'll take my stand
♪ To live and die in Dixie
♪ Away ♪ Away
♪ Away
♪ Away down South in Dixie
♪ Away, away Away
down South in Dixie ♪
♪ From the Halls of Montezuma
♪ To the shores of Tripoli
♪ We will fight our
country's battles... ♪
How long has that
light been like that?
I don't know. A month, maybe.
And nobody's come to fix it?
Nobody don't fix
nothing around here.
Well have you asked?
I'm watching.
Leave it alone.
I'm used to it now.
Oh...
Better, huh?
Now it's too dark.
What'd you do that for?
Listen, Ma.
I'm running for governor.
I'm gonna announce
in a few days.
That's why I came up to Philly.
There's a community
meeting tomorrow.
I'm gonna talk to
the shipbuilders
about a plan to
bring their jobs back,
so they support me
in the election.
I don't know nothing about that stuff.
It's over my head.
Okay, listen, there's
gonna be some stories
coming out about me,
in the news,
about my past.
I just wanted to
give you a heads up,
so it doesn't
catch you off guard.
I don't watch the news no more.
Bunch of garbage.
You want to see some
pictures of Kevin and Sarah?
Too dark to look at pictures.
No, no, it's on my phone,
you don't need any light.
Get it away from me.
I hate those things.
Brain cancer.
It wasn't just up the stairs, it
was up three flights of stairs,
in the science building.
And Gluckenheimer,
what he did...
"Well, you look lovely
today, Mrs. Governor."
And the thing took a dump.
Right. And they
couldn't get it back...
You can get a cow up three flights of
stairs, but you can't get it down!
And that's why in the end he said,
"Who wants steak for dinner?"
How are you boys doing?
We're good.
- You think I'm fat?
- Take the Fifth.
Seriously, Phil here thinks
I got fat with old age.
You're a big man with
an even bigger heart.
There you go!
She says you're chubby.
I think I'm going to go back to the hotel.
Okay? Have fun.
I love this woman.
Don't let him get
into too much trouble.
They'll have grounds for impeachment
when we're done with him.
We better get another drink
before they close up.
You're comin' with
me to help carry them.
You're gonna be
the waiter tonight.
Lazy-ass cadet. Lazy-ass cadet.
Hold on a second there,
partner.
You had no idea we were coming?
Complete surprise.
I thought Higgins might've...
No, he played it perfectly.
Made me think you
weren't coming at all.
Are you kidding?
We wouldn't have
missed it for the world.
On the library, are they
gonna put Frank or Francis?
Francis.
It's the same as the name above the
door in my office in the Capitol.
Francis is
better for libraries.
Frank is better
for bumper stickers.
I got a few of those.
Does anybody ever actually
call you Francis?
Claire does.
She's the only one.
She seems like a real prize.
She is.
Bar was already shut down,
but look what I scored.
Hey, Caroline.
What do you want?
Is Paul around?
Paul, did you invite him here?
Did you ask him here after
we said all those times
that we're not gonna
let him bother you?
He screwed you over
one too many times.
Who you talking about?
I'm talking about Peter
Russo at the front door.
Did you ask him here, or did
he just come on his own?
Does he know as soon as
we're finished with him...
Stop.
No, I'm not gonna
stop until you
actually deal with it
and get rid of him.
Paul, you got a minute to talk?
There's nothing to talk about.
I want to apologize for when I
saw you last time in Washington,
how I treated you.
Is that it?
And I want to talk
about the shipyard.
I got a plan to fix it.
You don't want everything
going into the Roth IRA.
Five, ten grand a year,
and I'll set you up with a
nice diversified package,
low risk, high yield.
I think Claire and I have things
pretty well under control.
If I brought a senior U.S.
Congressman into the fund,
that would really up my
stock in the company.
What're you all gabbing
about back there?
We were talkin'
about the old library.
Yeah, what's happening to it?
They gonna tear it down?
I don't know.
They could gut it, they could
turn it into a student center.
Hey, we should sneak in there.
Like we used to.
Do it. I'm game.
What the hell, why not?
There you go, that's it.
It's a library!
The Association
had about $3 million
saved up in reserve
for emergencies.
But you split that up between
12,000 members, it's nothing.
Couple weeks' groceries.
There's a bill I'm working on.
Major federal funds
going towards
public parks, green commercial
spaces, cleaning up waste sites.
That's construction jobs,
park management, retail...
How many?
Five thousand jobs.
That's not even half...
It's a start. How soon?
A year, maybe two...
Two fucking years?
What're we
supposed to do until then?
Listen, there's a community
meeting tomorrow...
I heard.
I'm gonna go over
everything in detail.
You gonna be there? I
wasn't planning on it.
I'd like you to be there.
Everybody respects you.
You want me to vouch for you?
Listen,
I'm gonna tell you something
that only a handful
of people know.
I'm running for governor.
I announce soon.
But I need the Association
behind me before I do that.
Now I know I let you
down with the shipyard,
but if I win
the governor's race
I can get
everything back on track.
You show up on my doorstep
asking for my forgiveness,
and now you want me
to be your lapdog?
After I lost my fucking job?
Okay, this Watershed Bill
is just the beginning.
If I'm governor,
there's so much I can do.
Yeah, it's bullshit. You
just want to use me.
It's not like that.
Yeah, it's exactly like that.
Jesus Christ.
You fucking politicians.
Paul...
Claire.
I didn't realize you and
Frank were staying here.
We always stay here when
we're in Charleston.
You know that, Remy.
The '08 campaign...
I promise it was a coincidence.
My assistant booked it.
Is Frank around?
He's not. He's off cavorting
with his old classmates.
Hmm.
You want to sit down
and have a drink?
They booked me the bridal suite.
There's champagne on ice...
My, my, you've grown very confident
since you worked for Francis.
I've always been confident,
Claire.
You never would've
invited me upstairs.
Never had the bridal suite.
The staff always stayed in the
Best Western four blocks away.
Enjoy your champagne.
I wasn't suggesting
anything more than a drink.
Weren't you?
Purely being polite.
Good night, Remy.
The bridal suite's on the top
floor, at the end of the hallway,
if you change your mind.
Good night, Claire.
♪ I know a girl All
dressed in pink ♪
Hey, Kenny, I think you got
a little too big for this.
I think the hole
got a lot smaller.
Don't let
a little girth stop you.
Look, look, look.
You found it.
Yeah, look, it's still there.
Wow, look at that.
♪ Oh, Shenandoah
I long to hear you
♪ Far away, you rolling river
♪ Oh, Shenandoah
Just to be near you
♪ Far away, far away
♪ 'Cross the wide Missouri ♪
Hey.
Good, and you?
I'm in Charleston, actually.
Mmm-hmm.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd surprise you.
Surprise.
Come on, let me show you where
I went through puberty.
I can totally
see you here at 16.
Ooh!
Got in some trouble
on this bed, huh?
Woke up the whole block.
Hey, how'd it go with Paul?
He told me to fuck off.
Which is what my mother told
me, in her own special way.
Am I gonna meet her?
You don't want to meet her.
I just want to stop by,
say hey, see her face.
Christina, it was really sweet
of you to come up here.
Seriously.
I'm officially
convinced that you're
the most amazing woman
I've ever been with.
But I meant it when I said I
wanted to take this trip alone.
This thing tomorrow isn't
gonna be pleasant.
Which is why I came. To be here for you.
Moral support.
I know these people, they're
going to lay into me big time.
Tomorrow's an important
day for the campaign.
Don't fight me on this.
Okay.
So do I get a hotel?
Do I stay here?
Come on, don't be like that.
A hotel would be
more comfortable.
But it would be a waste of
valuable campaign funds.
Oh, campaign funds.
You see that crack
up in the ceiling?
Mmm-hmm.
I used to fall asleep
staring at it every night.
I know every inch and curve.
It's dark in here.
I'm scared of the dark!
Get out of the way!
Hey, hey!
Big fucking gamble, my man.
Let there be light!
What are you thinking about?
How come you and Frank
have never had kids?
You've never had kids.
Yeah, but I'm not married.
Answer the question.
We just decided not to.
There wasn't some
big conversation.
I think you're lying.
Think whatever you want.
You honestly never
thought about it?
I mean, yeah,
maybe once or twice.
I mean, I don't feel
there's some void.
I'm perfectly happy without.
What about you?
Can you imagine me wiping a
baby's ass and changing nappies?
No, I can't.
Actually, yes, I just did, I'm going
to have to get off the phone.
You've ruined everything.
We really should get off. It's
been over an hour I think.
Okay.
Go on then.
I'm hanging up right now.
No, I am.
Yeah! Let's go, Ken, let's go.
Go, go, go.
Yeah, come on. Giddy up, come on.
Don't quit on me.
I lost count.
Come on,
don't quit on me.
Don't quit.
No. Oh, God.
You win.
But it's not a fair fight.
You run a rafting company. I
sit behind a desk all day.
I'd love to see
your ass with a paddle
bouncing through
a class-four rapid.
If I can whip
Congress into submission,
I'm not afraid of
a little white water.
You can't tame a rapid, Frank.
My heart is beating so fast. If I
have a heart attack it's your fault.
Mine too.
Here.
I need another drink.
I think I'll have another, too.
Don't bogart that.
Do you think
this place made us?
How do you mean?
When I walked on campus today I
wondered, did it mean anything?
If it's just a place
we spent four years
of our lives or was there more?
I don't know.
I do know you
were always the guy
who was going to get a
building named after him.
I knew that the moment I saw you
cuss out the drill sergeant
when we were knobs.
The library is a sham.
Higgins asked me a favor, I
asked someone else a favor,
they slapped my name on it.
Politics. Like everything else.
Not everybody gets
asked those favors.
Or knows how to
deliver on them.
In 50 years, they'll just
replace it with something else,
just like they're doing
with this for mine.
You still built something.
However long it lasts.
The library doesn't matter.
But I want to think
that this place did.
I think it meant
a lot to us, then.
And what about us?
Honestly, I haven't really
thought about it that much.
It's a long time ago.
We were so close.
Like brothers.
More than brothers.
We were kids, Frank.
We messed around
a couple of times.
I was so drawn to you...
I could always make you laugh.
How did we lose touch?
You went to law school.
I joined the army.
You ran for Congress.
I moved to Colorado.
Thirty years goes by.
I got children older
than we were back then.
Do you have anyone, Frank?
I have Claire.
Besides Claire.
I have, from time to time.
If I want someone, I want them.
It's attraction.
It made me happy to
make you happy, Frank.
Didn't see any harm in it.
You know why I love rafting?
When you're on the water,
all you're thinking about is
what's right in front of you.
Everything is in the moment.
I don't really have time
to think about the past.
You meant something to me.
I believe that.
All gone.
I don't feel so well...
You gonna be sick?
No. No, I just...
Take a break.
Can we just stay here for a little bit?
Until I feel better.
Take as long as you like.
I got nowhere to go.
A few more weeks
and we'll be through.
And I won't
have to look at you.
Ugly, ugly, ugly you.
It's almost 7:00.
I don't even remember
going to sleep...
Come on.
1,100 acres of development.
Yes.
30% public parks.
Yep.
45% shopping and office space.
Yes.
25% middle-income housing.
You going?
Is it required?
I don't think so.
Who is he that they're
naming the place after?
Some guy who went here.
I think he's dead.
We had to set up the chairs yesterday.
It was hot as shit.
That sucks.
I'm gonna try to get some
shut-eye before the ceremony.
I'll see you all later?
Later it is.
Hey, Frank,
before I forget,
here's my card, so your
money manager can call me.
Get some rest.
Claire.
You look like you're hurting.
It was an all-nighter.
Was it fun at least?
It was fun.
I need to get some shut-eye.
Remy's staying here.
He harassing you
about the donation?
Oh, nothing I can't handle.
Go get some rest.
Were you good?
Not bad.
I wasn't a starter, but I
got my time on the court.
I think you look sexier
now, all grown up.
Congressman?
We're ready for you.
You said two years.
Yeah, I think two years
is a realistic estimate.
If it passes at all.
Which I think it will.
You think or you know?
I can't predict 100%, but
I'm confident it will.
You think, you're confident,
you can't predict 100%,
how does any of that help us?
I'll tell you something,
I'm 100% unable to pay
my mortgage right now.
I'm 100% unable to buy
my kids school supplies.
We supposed to live off
my husband's disability?
There'll be paid training
programs available.
How much will they pay?
Granted, it's less than
you made at the shipyard.
So how much?
It's about $6 an hour.
That's not even minimum wage.
Horseshit, Russo!
You have to see it
as an investment.
The training programs are
a valuable resource...
You're not getting it.
I can't afford to
make investments.
$6 an hour puts my
family on the street.
What, do you want
me to work five jobs?
If you get a part-time job, that
and the training program...
You want to know what I think?
I think you sit
around in Washington
coming up with all
sorts of fancy numbers
and solutions that
look good on paper,
but that doesn't cut
it for the rest of us.
You said you had our backs,
you lying piece of shit!
We don't eat paper for dinner. You
can't put a paper roof over your head.
When we all voted for you,
I didn't think that every
one of those votes
was another nail in
our own coffins.
Please, everybody, just
sit down for 10 minutes,
we can go over this
proposal point-by-point.
And you can get the
information you need
to get the resources
that you want...
It's like they don't
want to find a solution.
They're scared.
I understand
that they're scared,
but that doesn't mean
they can't listen...
You don't know
these people, Christina.
I worked in your office
for three years.
I spoke to them, I took their
calls, I replied to their emails...
You didn't grow up with them.
I don't need to
grow up hand-to-mouth
to empathize with
the fact that...
They're not interested
in empathy.
The house keys
are in my jacket.
I'll call you.
Peter.
I said I'll call you.
Do your homework or
Sister Mary Joseph...
You didn't do it...
Don't lie to me.
I used to use the same
ploy with my parents.
Baloney.
We do the homework,
and then we eat.
Who's hungry?
- What do you guys want?
- Hamburger.
- Pizza.
- No.
No pizza, you guys
can eat that every...
Sweetheart,
take the kids upstairs.
How'd you get in here?
You still keep the spare key behind
the loose brick on the porch.
You break into my house? You
scare my kids like that?
We gotta talk, Paul.
We talked last night.
Now get out.
I can convince these people,
but I need your help.
Leave my house. Sit down.
I don't want to
have to hurt you
with my children upstairs,
Petey.
Then help me.
This is your last chance.
I'm not going anywhere.
Get back upstairs!
What are we doing?
I don't want to
fight you, Petey.
fight you either.
I will, but we don't have to.
What do you want me to do?
You elected me
to represent you.
But I couldn't forestall
the inevitable.
The shipyard was closing.
If not this year, then next, or the year after.
We all know that.
I could have lied to you. I could
have pretended to do more.
But I don't believe
in living in the past.
I only care about the future.
Here's another truth that's
gonna be hard to swallow...
I'm all you've got.
Nobody in Washington gives
a fuck about you. No one.
He's right.
Whatever you think of Petey, we
either go with him or we got nothing.
Now does what I'm
offering you come
anywhere near what
you want or deserve?
No.
But you gotta open your eyes and
take what's in front of you.
We can build on that.
5,000 jobs becomes 10, then 15.
Not in the snap of a finger, but
faster than doing nothing will.
Can I count on all of you?
All right,
I'll take that as a yes.
We'll need your
contact information,
so we can send you materials
to share with your friends.
Now, let's talk about the way the
money's gonna get phased in.
It's gonna happen in six stages.
Stage one...
♪ Oh, say,
does that star-spangled
♪ Banner yet wave
♪ O'er the land of the free
♪ And the home of the brave?
Left face, forward march.
Francis Underwood's career,
Harvard Law degree,
one of the youngest
state legislators
in the history
of South Carolina,
a 22-year veteran of the U.
S. Congress,
House Majority Whip,
speaks volumes about the values
young people learn
here at the Sentinel,
values like honor,
duty, discipline,
like sacrifice,
service and respect.
Ladies and Gentlemen, the Francis J.
Underwood library.
Congressman?
Thank you.
I wrote a speech.
But I'm not gonna read it.
Nothing is permanent.
Not even this building.
I don't mean to
sound ungrateful.
I am very grateful,
I'm deeply honored,
and I am very moved.
I had the good fortune
of spending most
of this weekend with
a group of friends.
Friends I haven't seen
in a very long time.
Friends I made here.
Most of you young cadets
probably don't know who I am.
Politician. A name. A
few accomplishments.
But I don't blame you.
When I was your age, why,
I didn't care much for
what men in gray hair did
or what they had to say.
I wish I could describe...
Harmony. That's the word
that's stuck in my mind.
Harmony.
It's not about what's
lasting or permanent.
It is about individual voices
coming together for a moment,
and that moment lasts
the length of a breath.
That's what I think
about my time here.
You'll have to forgive me. I had
more than a few whiskeys last night.
You know, when I was a cadet,
we could drink all night,
then get up in the morning
and march 20 miles,
but these days I'm lucky I
got up these three steps.
I want to thank you very much.
This is a great honor.
I want to thank
President Higgins,
and of course, the love
of my life, Claire.
Thank you all very much.
Are you okay? Yes.
Hey, Ma.
This is Christina. I told
you about her yesterday.
Hi, Mrs. Russo. Hey.
We just came by to say goodbye.
We have to catch
a train in about an hour.
Okay.
They still haven't fixed that light?
Uh-uh.
Things went well today.
I think the folks in the yard
are going to get behind me.
Peter did a great job.
Hand me that blanket.
AC in here is nuts.
What happened to your hand?
I got in a fight. Did you win?
Yeah. I guess I did.
That's my Peter.
So you're fucking my son?
Lighten up.
I'm just messing with ya.
Excuse me?
Hold on a second.
Yeah?
Yeah, my mother's in room 409.
She has a light out that
needs to be replaced.
All right. I'll take care of it.
Okay, thanks.
Look, baby, you put that pink thing
on, I'm telling you. It's just...
What you want me to wear? You
want me to wear that little...
Hold on. What is it?
The light in my mother's room.
Right. I told you I'll
take care of it later.
No. You'll take care of it now.
I gotta go.
And turn the AC down while
you're in there, too.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
You're very welcome, sir.
Take care of yourselves.
Real proud of you, Frank.
I hate to admit it,
but I feel the same.
Well, having all you here
is what made it special.
Now, you stay in touch.
Will do.
See you, buddy.
Beautiful ceremony, Frank.
Yeah, they did a good job.
Your speech.
I'm glad I was here for that.
Me too.
You should come out
to Salida sometime.
I'll take you out on
the Arkansas River.
I should do that.
Anytime you want.
Yep.
All right.
Francis...
Edward has the car ready.
I'll be right there.
Take your time.
You hear from Peter?
Looks like
the shipbuilders
are on board.
Tomorrow morning
we start working
on his draft for his
announcement speech.
Got it.
And I want the brief on the
mark-up for the Watershed Bill...
I got that with me.
Ride with me to the airport, we
can go through it in the car.
www.tvsubtitles.net