The whole reason we do
these meetings, Frank,
is so I can get accurate
information from you.
I always said it
was going to be close.
Then why did every
article I read yesterday
say the leadership was
confident the bill would pass?
Do you know Janine Skorsky?
She used to be The Herald's
White House correspondent.
I remember Janine.
She wrote
an article for Slugline
reporting
a verified vote count.
Once the media got ahold of
that, it went everywhere.
I don't know where she got that number.
Maybe she made it up.
It doesn't matter
if she made it up.
The Democrats seem divided. The
leadership looks incompetent.
But compared to the budget
and our Education Act,
why, this was
a minor bill, sir.
That happened to be in
the national spotlight,
which is what you wanted.
I got the count wrong.
It rarely happens,
but it happens.
See, what worries me is that
the White House's influence
isn't translating into
support on the Hill.
Linda's involvement
had no effect?
I wouldn't say that
that's the case, sir.
Did you sense any pushback, any
fallout from the education battle?
Sir, the truth is
I wasn't there.
I had to make a trip
to California to meet
the Provost of Stanford,
for my son.
I told you about it last week.
It was my decision, sir.
I made a judgment call
that we could pass the
bill without her help.
But, look,
tight votes like this,
you can analyze them to death,
but at the end of the
day, we came up short.
That's my fault, no one else's.
Certainly not Linda's.
I shouldn't have gone. The
meeting didn't even work.
I thought you said they
were reconsidering.
No. I got an email
this morning.
They decided not to overturn
the admissions decision.
Oh, Christ. I'm sorry, Linda.
Yeah. Not a great day so far.
But I appreciate your
covering for me in there.
There may be a way to turn Linda's
bad luck into my good fortune.
But first, I must deal with
treason within the ranks,
the two renegades who
voted against the bill.
I have zero
tolerance for betrayal,
which they will
soon indelibly learn.
I know why you lost the vote.
Somebody got to
Vanderburgh and Abrams.
Remy Danton.
Your wife.
I've got contacts
on both their staffs.
There was a meeting between
the three of them.
I know. I arranged it.
She told them to vote no.
No, not true.
Sources on two different staffs
saying the exact same thing?
That makes no sense.
I'm not telling you what makes
sense, I'm telling you facts.
This is a juicy story, Francis.
Carly will love it.
The Majority Whip's wife
stabs him in the back.
Be careful, Zoe.
I'm feeding you.
Now you have to feed me.
So give me something better.
Are you going to
answer my question?
Did she or didn't she?
Tell me now, or so help me God,
I will make it
my mission in life
to not only
destroy your careers,
but to obliterate all hope and
happiness that you manage to cling to.
She said it would be okay...
To backstab me?
To do what we
thought was right.
So she did tell you to vote no.
She said it wouldn't be the end
of the world if the bill failed.
Those were her exact words.
You discuss this with no one.
Is that understood?
Do you blame
yourself for not being
in Washington to
secure the votes?
A bill this size is a team effort.
There were a lot of sponsors.
But you were the chief sponsor
and the bill manager.
That's true.
So shouldn't you
have been in Washington?
I'm running for governor.
I have a commitment to
the people of my state.
Are you aware that
the Swofford campaign
is putting out a new
commercial today that says,
quote, if Peter Russo can't
follow through in Congress,
can he follow
through with sobriety?
That's all.
Thank you very much.
Do you want to comment?
Thanks, guys.
Congressman!
All I said was what you always
say, to vote their conscience.
You encouraged them to defy me.
I met with them. That's
what you asked me...
No, that is not what you did.
I specifically told you I needed
them to vote yes on this bill.
There was no room
for interpretation.
It's a deliberate lie, so don't
try to sugarcoat it, Claire.
I needed Remy's help.
You wouldn't offer any.
Oh, wait.
You did this for Remy?
No. For myself. To get my
shipment out of Sudan.
He provided assistance.
In exchange for
defeating the bill.
No. In exchange for not
helping it succeed.
Which is the same
goddamn thing.
Do you realize
you have endangered
everything that we have
been working toward?
There was
a timetable here, Claire.
We needed strong momentum right
up until the last minute.
I can't operate based on plans
you haven't shared with me.
Then you should've
asked me first.
No, I'm not going to
ask for your blessing
on every decision
I make, Francis.
We make decisions together.
Yeah, well, it hasn't felt like that.
Not for the past six months.
I don't feel as though
I'm standing beside you.
Other people know, Claire.
This could become
a story about us.
And that's something you
do not recover from.
Who? That's something that
follows you for life.
Who knows?
Zoe.
I thought you said
she could be trusted.
What about our trust?
You can't control her,
can you, Francis?
She wouldn't have been a
problem if you hadn't lied.
No, she wouldn't
have been a problem
if you hadn't
dropped your pants.
And you come in here, to
my office, and berate me
when you're the one
who's exposed us?
Don't you try to
turn this around on me.
I fired half of
my staff for us.
I have turned down
donations for us.
I drafted Peter's bill for us.
I diverted time and energy
away from my goals for us.
Okay, I don't wanna have to say this,
but maybe you need to hear it.
CWI is important, yes,
but it doesn't come close to what
we are trying to accomplish.
You must see that!
I'm just being honest.
Then be honest about how
you've been using me
just like you
use everybody else.
That was never
part of the bargain.
Is it the hot flashes?
Get out.
I'll see you back at the house.
I'm on my way to the office.
Let me call you
when I get there.
No, no. We need to talk now.
I know you're upset, Peter, but
that's not going to achieve anything.
I am more than upset, Frank.
Change your tone.
I'm in no mood.
I don't give a fuck!
Goodbye, Peter.
You hang up on me now, you're not
gonna appreciate who I call next.
Excuse me?
I promised my people jobs.
You promised me you could
get this bill passed.
You failed on your promise.
I'm not gonna fail on mine.
So however you need to fix
it, you figure it out.
Otherwise, I go public with
Kapeniak and the Kern editorial.
You need to cool down and think very
carefully about what you just said.
You don't understand. I'm not
afraid of you anymore, Frank.
Then you're misguided.
My past is out in the open.
You don't hold that
over my head anymore.
They don't know
everything, Peter.
You destroy me,
you destroy yourself.
Fix it.
What do you want me to do?
We have to accelerate things.
Isn't it too early? It's almost two
full months into the election.
That gives the White House too
much time to vet somebody.
Peter's crossed the line.
We built up his confidence, and
now we're losing control of him.
Maybe he was just
blowing off steam.
No. He's determined.
We have to act now.
You have everything
you need in your end?
Give me a when and a where.
Some sort of social
setting is preferable.
Anything else? I'll need cash.
About 3 grand.
It'll be in your top drawer
by tomorrow morning.
Sir.
Once we do this,
we're committed.
Understood.
I can't predict
how he's gonna react.
Well, I won't be blackmailed.
Hello?
Zoe Barnes?
Yeah. Who is it?
Claire Underwood.
Zoe?
I apologize for not buzzing.
Somebody was coming in the
building when I was downstairs,
so I just figured...
This is nice. Fire escape.
Hey, could you please not
go through my things?
Oh, I'm sorry. Am I intruding?
Yeah, actually. You are.
Well, that makes it a
two-way street, I suppose.
Okay, if you... If you
came here to punish me.
Fine. I get it.
Such a shame.
How naive you are.
I'm not naive.
No?
I've known everything
from the beginning, Zoe.
My husband and I tell
each other everything.
Don't you believe me?
Is there a spider I can trap?
I'm not here to punish you
or to tell you to stop.
I just thought I should
open those big bright eyes.
I think you should leave.
I think I should, too.
Maybe you're not that naive.
A lesser woman wouldn't
have opened the door.
Union Station, please.
This is Claire. I'm unavailable
to answer the phone,
but if you leave a
message, I'll be sure
and get back to you shortly.
Thank...
Hello? Zoe.
You don't have to tiptoe.
I thought you fell asleep.
No. Just thinking about work.
I don't have anything for you yet.
I will soon.
I know you will.
You can spend
the night if you want.
Early meetings.
Wouldn't have time to
get home and change.
You seem distracted.
I have a lot on my mind.
Like what?
Work, just like you.
No Claire?
Or maybe she qualifies as work.
She didn't mention anything?
About...
I thought you didn't keep
things from each other.
Look, just say
what you want to say.
She came by here
a few hours ago.
We had a nice little talk.
Don't let me keep you.
You should go home,
get some rest.
Tell Claire I said hi.
Claire!
This is Claire. I'm
unavailable to answer...
The lights in the Wartons' house
will go on in a few moments.
They always get up
precisely at 6:45,
which is just the time that Claire
would be going for her run,
if she were here.
Rebellion on all fronts.
Claire, Zoe, Russo.
I must not lose my resolve.
I will march forward,
even if I have to do so
alone.
See? Told ya.
Good morning.
Hi, Frank.
How are you?
I'm good.
Have you heard from Claire?
Yeah, I got her message.
How's she feeling?
A lot better.
Good. She said she'd be gone
for the rest of the week.
Is it the flu or something?
Something like that.
I just came over to pick up a
few things from her office.
Oh.
I could've sent somebody over.
No. It's no big deal.
In fact, I also came
here to ask you a favor.
You went to Stanford, correct?
Valedictorian? Yeah.
Do you know the Provost?
Warren Tynsdale.
He flies me out to
do fundraising events.
Supposedly I'm the
poster child for alumni.
Making the world
a better place.
Well, that is good, because
this is important.
Linda Vasquez, the
President's Chief of Staff,
her son, Ruben, applied.
I'd love for you to get on
the phone with Tynsdale
and tell him that
they should accept him.
I don't know. I... I've
never recommended anyone.
All the better.
It'll carry more weight.
Can I meet Ruben first?
I would really
prefer that Linda not know.
In fact, it would be better
if both she and Ruben
believed he got
in on merit alone.
Will you please do this
favor for Claire and me?
And for the President.
Thank you.
More contrast.
We need to catch
the edge of his face.
Let's re-crop it. Bring it in a
quarter of an inch on the left.
Would you?
Somebody named Claire?
Remy.
You hungry?
I don't eat pork.
When did that happen?
When we started lobbying for
the meatpacking industry.
Freddy, half a rack for me,
and some collard greens
for my friend here.
I'm good. I already ate lunch.
Half a rack coming up.
I don't usually do business here.
This is my little secret.
I'd love it if we
could keep it that way.
I don't think you have to worry
about me bringing clients by.
You seem tense, Remy.
I assume you're upset
about the Watershed Bill.
Not with you. You were
just doing your job.
But now I have to do mine.
I'd like to propose
a partnership.
I'm always open to
partnerships, Frank.
If Peter Russo were a
pro-natural gas candidate,
how valuable would
that be to SanCorp?
The Watershed Bill
is anti-drilling.
Peter's pro-employment,
not anti-drilling.
He just wants to bring
employment to his people,
and SanCorp is
building refineries.
Mostly on site.
Do you think they would be open
to considering Philadelphia?
I can talk with them, but I
can't make any promises.
I don't want any promises.
Just engage with Russo.
You know, give him a
glimmer of good fortune.
Ah, Frank, here you go.
Come on. Smell that.
You sure you don't want to
reconsider your stance on pork?
Brain food, brother.
I love it. $850.
You can afford that?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
First and last
month are taken care of.
So is the security deposit.
That's to buy some furniture.
I'll pay you back. I promise.
It's not necessary.
But I do need you to
do one thing for me.
I'd come across as a hypocrite.
You need jobs.
Do you really care
how you deliver them?
First, I advocate for more
regulation for the watershed,
then I cozy up to
the drilling interests?
Yeah, but natural gas
is the future, Peter.
This is an industry that
could bring 100,000 jobs
into your state
over the next decade.
I agree with Peter. It
seems like flip-flopping.
SanCorp's lobbying efforts is
why we lost the Watershed Bill.
But they can also be
a very powerful ally.
Our message is "A fresh start."
This makes you look like
"Business as usual."
This is politics.
There are seized opportunities
and missed opportunities.
Seize this one, Peter.
SanCorp can commit to building
new refineries in Philly?
SanCorp will commit to
discussing it with you.
I need more than that.
Look, you asked me
to fix a problem.
I've come to you in less than
24 hours with a solution.
Can you meet me halfway?
What would be the first step?
All right.
You remember
Remy Danton?
Oh, come on. He led the charge
against the Watershed Bill.
I know. That's not the point.
One of his other big clients is
the McNeally Cancer Institute.
They're having
a big gala tonight,
a cocktail party
for their donors.
Remy will be there.
We have events in
Haverford and Gladwyne.
Yeah, well,
this is more important.
You also have
a radio interview tomorrow
morning with a local
Pittsburgh station?
Yes. All right.
Meet with Remy tonight.
And if it goes well and
if you're comfortable,
tomorrow morning on the radio, you
support their drilling efforts.
And Remy has assured me
if you do that,
he can push SanCorp in
the right direction.
Cancel the events tomorrow.
Head back to Philly, do
some damage control.
I'll see you
tomorrow afternoon.
Peter...
Please.
Okay.
I'm gonna go make some calls.
Peter, have you mentioned anything
to her about Kapeniak or...
No. I haven't
mentioned it
to anybody.
All right. Stamper will
come by in the morning
and brief you on
the talking points.
When did you take this?
Oh, it was about
7:00 in the morning.
The sun had just come up.
You were asleep right here.
The light was perfect.
I had no choice.
I always slept so well
in this apartment.
How long are you in town for?
I don't know.
I haven't decided.
You have no luggage.
It smells the same.
Feels the same.
I think SanCorp is missing out,
not having a significant
presence in Philadelphia.
There are advantages to centralizing
in a major urban center.
But the disadvantages are
commercial real estate prices,
city taxes, political pipeline.
It's all very costly.
So they'd have to
reduce costs elsewhere.
Significantly.
How can I help with that?
Statewide permitted use zoning.
No more conditional zoning.
The municipalities are
slowing down development.
That's the state legislature.
You come out in support of permitted
use, and you get elected governor.
That'll put pressure
on the legislature.
SanCorp is very
interested in having
a powerful friend
in Harrisburg.
My opponent's pro-drilling.
Your opponent isn't asking for
refineries in Philadelphia.
We prefer friends
we can count on.
Have your clients listen
to WZPZ tomorrow at 7:45.
It's a Pittsburgh station.
It's been a pleasure,
Congressman.
I look forward to
talking again soon.
You got a light?
This is a cancer
research event.
I know. I helped organize it.
You work for the institute?
No. The hotel.
And they let you smoke here?
No. The manager would kill me.
Well, at least
it got you talking.
Are you having a good night?
You look happy.
Ah, I am. I am.
I'm having a great night.
Why?
I just got some very good news.
We should celebrate.
What are you drinking?
You know,
I was just leaving, actually.
You haven't even
asked my name yet.
I apologize, but I have to go.
It's Rachel.
I'm not trying to be rude, but
I got a big meeting tomorrow.
Then don't be rude. Just
stay a few more minutes
and keep me from
having to mingle.
My date ditched me.
So if you abandon me now,
that would be very rude.
These heels are killing me.
Feel that. Feel that blister.
Hey, I...
I have a girlfriend.
I'd be surprised if you didn't.
Why'd your date ditch you?
Mmm...
Very scandalous.
Mmm-hmm? What happened?
Clink glasses with me.
Wow.
Oh!
I'm petite,
but I can hold my liquor.
Obviously.
When I do get drunk, though...
What then?
I get undressed.
What about you?
What are you like
when you get drunk?
It's not pretty.
Pretty's overrated.
I like it when things
get a little bit ugly.
When I work late nights, they
let me stay at the hotel
so I don't have to drive home.
This one is yours.
Room 1121.
Sir? In here.
You wanted to see me?
I need you to locate somebody.
Who?
My wife.
Do you have
a way of doing that?
I do, sir.
I know a guy, Missing Persons.
She's not missing. I just
don't know where
she is at the moment.
I trust him.
We can do this off the books.
Good.
I'll get on it right away.
Come on. Give us another one.
No. I'll tell you why.
Because my mother always used
to tell me to smile more.
Always drove me crazy.
She'd say,
"Claire, why have you
that scowl all the time?
"You look so much more
beautiful when you smile."
It was never
a real conversation.
There was never, "Oh, what do you
feel?" Or "What are you thinking?"
Just so long as I looked
beautiful and happy.
That's all she cared about.
So you want me to ask you what
you're thinking and feeling?
All the time.
I actually do wanna know what
you're thinking and feeling.
How sad am I?
Okay, so tell me first.
What? Tell me first.
I think I'd better get dressed.
What? Why?
Ah, because...
I've got friends coming over,
and as a host, I should
probably wear clothes.
Really? Yeah.
Why do you do that?
Well, you know.
It's proper?
Kind of.
Oh, fuck.
Thought you might have bailed.
Sit down.
Vodka or whiskey?
Ah, you go ahead.
Come on. You can be a good
boy downstairs, not up here.
Seriously, I'm good.
Whiskey, I think.
So what's your good news?
I wanna know what
we're celebrating.
Why did your... Why did
your date ditch you?
I asked you first.
I did, downstairs.
He works on the Hill.
Some staffer or something.
I don't know. I think
he's a glorified gofer.
A friend set me up with him.
So I said he should come
tonight, keep me company.
But all he wanted
to do was schmooze.
So I brought him into
the women's bathroom,
told him he was
being an asshole.
He told me I was being childish.
So I slapped him.
You slapped him?
Yeah. Big red hand mark
right across his face.
I think he was embarrassed to
be seen by the schmoozerati.
So he left.
And that is the last
time I go on a date
with a guy who wears
a flag pin to work.
I'm one of those guys who
wears a flag pin to work.
This isn't
really a date, is it?
I really shouldn't be here.
That's what makes it fun.
Tell me your good news. I wanna
know what we're toasting to.
Let's toast to you.
I'm your good news? Okay,
I'll toast to that.
Hey.
What are you...
I didn't wanna
wait at The Herald.
I was gonna call you, but...
Can I stay at
your place tonight?
Uh, stay with me?
Well, just on your couch
for a night or two.
Uh...
Why?
I can't be in my apartment.
Did something happen? No. I...
I'm sorry.
Zoe.
Come on.
What time is the interview?
7:45. I'll be with him.
And where's Peter now?
Are you sure you
want the details?
Mmm.
Just tell me, is it going well?
Hasn't been any updates.
But if it does go well,
you'll be ready?
I'm ready.
I've been ready. I'm ready.
Anything else?
We never played
chess before, have we?
I don't know how.
You want me to teach you?
I should really get some rest.
Be fresh for the morning.
Yeah, another time.
1160, WZPZ, 7:45. Good night.
I hate being kept in the dark.
Waiting.
Speculating.
Useless.
Oh, come on! Let's dance.
This is really nice.
Do you want anything?
Water? Juice?
No, thanks. I'm good.
Uh, you can have the bed.
I'll sleep on the couch.
No. No.
It's fine.
Please, Lucas, let me sleep on the couch.
I'll feel bad.
All right.
Could I help? I got it.
So...
You know, we don't have to
talk if you don't want to.
But I haven't
seen you in, like,
six months.
Except for when I drunkenly
stalked you at your...
Right.
That was kind of adorable.
It was either psychotic or sad.
Not adorable.
Yes, it was.
Can you hand me that pillow?
So, why do you need to get
out of your apartment?
It just felt small.
Well, it can't be
smaller than my place.
No. I don't mean size.
I mean...
I felt trapped.
Like I was in a place that
I didn't actually live.
Does that make any sense?
I guess.
Okay.
There you go.
Um...
Any time you need
to get up? Or...
Um, I'll just set
an alarm on my phone.
All right.
Well, feel free
to watch TV.
I can sleep through anything.
Hey, thank you, Lucas.
Hey, that's the last of it.
Better make it count, then.
Drink up.
Do I look familiar to you?
Familiar? No.
My face? My body? No.
How about my voice?
Have we...
No.
No. I was just
wondering if you had
a thing for brunettes
with blue eyes.
Hey, where you going?
Come back here.
I wanna see you better.
Shit. The sun's up?
Has been for a while.
Oh, fuck. What time is it?
7:15.
Fuck. I have an interview
in half an hour.
Skip it.
I can't. I gotta do it.
You can keep
the room till noon.
Hello? I'm at your building.
The front desk keeps calling
up, but there's no answer.
I'm not there.
Then I'll come to you.
Where are you?
I'm at the Park Highmore Hotel.
Are you okay? You sound drunk.
It was...
Yeah, yeah.
I'm all right.
You have the interview.
I know!
Have you been drinking, Peter?
Uh, what? No. I just decided
to spend the night here.
What room are you in?
11... 1121.
Stay there.
I'm coming right now.
Jesus, Peter. What happened?
You're drunk.
I'm fine.
I can smell it on you.
Okay, I had a drink or two.
It was nothing crazy.
We can't do this interview.
I'm sober. I can handle it.
You're slurring your words.
I'm good.
I think we should cancel.
I'm gonna do the interview.
Just give me
the talking points.
Sorry.
Sorry. I...
It's all right.
The couch had a spring in it
or something, and my back...
Stop.
It's all right.
I don't mind.
Sir, I heard from my friend.
Missing Persons.
And?
She's in New York.
What hotel?
Not a hotel, sir.
So she's not alone?
No, sir.
Adam Galloway?
Yes, sir.
I have more information.
I don't need to know.
Turn on 1160 AM.
He's running to fill Jim Matthews' old
post as Governor of Pennsylvania.
Glad to have you with us, sir.
It's good to be here, Jim.
It's Mark.
Sorry. Right. Mark.
That's okay, Congressman.
It happens
all the time this
early in the morning.
So, Congressman,
the Watershed Act.
Yes. Uh, I'm ashamed of the...
Well, I'm not ashamed.
That's not the right...
I'm disappointed,
because, you know...
The water is...
It's... Actually, what I'd
like to discuss is...
We all know that natural gas...
That it's... It's a growing...
In our state...
It's a...
It's a big part of, um...
Economically,
the way things are going.
And I'd like to say...
To announce...
In terms of...
Are you familiar with
drilling regulations?
Permitted use
versus conditional use?
Are we still talking
about the Watershed?
No. Drilling. Natural gas.
Sir, you supported
increased regulation.
Well, no. I... I...
It may have
looked that way, but...
In fact, to be clear,
I'm for less...
Regulation.
Yes, sir. In the Watershed Bill,
the language clearly stated...
It didn't pass.
Well, right. That's
what I'm asking about.
What about it?
Why it didn't pass?
I just said.
No, sir. I don't think you did.
It just didn't.
Sir, three days ago,
you predicted...
I'm talking about
fucking natural gas.
I'm sorry.
Congressman, I have to
ask you a question,
and it may come
across as indelicate,
but are you drunk right now?
What? No. No.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm just... I'm really
tired, you know?
I've been on the campaign
trail for a few weeks now...
Congressman?
Congressman? Congressman?
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have let you.
I'm fucked.
Okay. Listen. We sober you up.
We'll make some kind of
announcement as soon as possible.
There's nothing I can say.
We'll figure this out.
Come on.
You're gonna take a shower.
There you go. Come on.
How bad is it?
It all depends
on whether it gets
picked up by
the mainstream press.
Well, shall I fill
in the President?
No. Hold off on that.
I need to speak to Peter,
coordinate with his campaign.
You'll be
the first call I make.
Uh, Frank, before you go, I
got an email this morning.
Stanford reversed
their decision.
That's wonderful.
The Provost said Gillian
Cole reached out to him.
I googled her.
She works for Claire.
Thank you.
No reason to thank me.
Ruben was just ecstatic. I don't
know how I'm gonna repay you.
The fact that your son is
happy is more than enough.
You'll keep me posted on Peter?
You bet.
Okay.
Hey, boss.
Are you still with him? Yeah.
He's taking a shower.
How're we looking?
Zoe Barnes
posted 10 minutes ago.
It's already on The New
York Times website.
The kid is done.
Have Nancy set up a meeting
with the Vice President.
Today if possible.
Will do.
And keep an eye on Peter.
He's done his duty.
Let's get him back on his feet.
You got it.
And now Jim Matthews comes to the
fore, though he doesn't know it yet.
He will find solace in his
beloved Pennsylvania,
though Peter Russo will
find solace nowhere.
It only takes 10 seconds to
crush a man's ambitions.
I need to take care
I protect mine.
Peter.
Peter!
Peter?
Hey!
www.tvsubtitles.net