Ok...
The X10's are online
Gentlemen, I am now about to send a
signal from this laptop through our
local ISP
racing down fibre optic cable at
the speed of light to San Fransisco,
bouncing off a satellite in
geosynchronous orbit to
Lisbon, Portugal,
where the data packets will be headed
off to submerge transatlantic cables,
terminating in Halifax,
Nova Scotia
and transfered across the continent
via microwave relays back to our ISP
And the extend receiver
attached to this...
Lamp.
Look at me, look at me.
I've got goosebumps.
- Are we ready for the stereo?
- Go for stereo.
- Hey guys.
- Hello.
It's a little loud.
No problem... Turning it down.
San Francisco, Lisbon, Halifax...
... et voil?
- OK, thanks.
- Hang on, hang on. Do you not
realise what we just did?
Yeah, you turned your stereo
down with your laptop.
No, we turned our stereo down, by
sending a signal around the world via
the Internet.
Oh. You know you can get one of those
universal remotes from Radioshack?
They're really cheap.
No, you don't get it. Howard,
- Enable public access.
- Public access enabled.
- Boy, that's terrific. I'll see ya.
- No hang on, hang on...
See?
No.
Someone in Sichuan province,
China, is using his computer
to turn our lights on and off.
Oh, that's handy.
Here's a question... Why?
Because we can.
They found our
remote control cars!
- Wait, what's on top of that?
- Wireless webcams, wave hello!
The monster truck is
out of Austin, Texas,
and the blue Viper is being
operated from suburban Tel Aviv.
- You may want to put on slacks.
- What?
Ew, stop it! No!
Leave me alone!
- Who's running the red Corvette?
- That would be me.
Season 1 Episode 9:
The Cooper-Hofstadter Polarization
You know in the future,
when we're disembodied brains in jars,
we're going to look at this
as eight hours well wasted.
I don't want to be in a jar.
I want my brain in an android body.
Eight feet tall and ribbed.
I'm with you.
I just have to make sure if I'm a
synthetic human I'd still be Jewish.
I promised my mother.
I suppose you could have your
android penis circumcised.
But that's something your rabbi would
have to discuss with the manufacturer.
Not to mention you'd have
to power down on saturdays.
Sheldon, why is this
letter in the trash?
Well, there's always
the possibility that
a trash can spontaneously
formed around the letter
but Occam's rasor would suggest
that someone threw it out.
It's from the Institute of
Experimental Physics, they want us to
present our paper on the
properties of supersolids
at the topical conference of
Bose-Einstein condensates.
I know.
I read it before I threw it out.
Ok, if I may drill down to
the bedrock of my question:
why did you throw it out?
Because I have no interest in standing
in the Rose room of the
Pasadena Marriot,
in front of a group of
judgmental strangers
who wouldn't recognise true genius if it
was standing in front of them giving
a speech.
Which if I were there,
would be.
I don't know Sheldon.
Those topical conferences on
Bose-Einstein condensates' parties
are legendary
- Forget the parties!
- Forget the parties? What a nerd.
Are there any other honours I've
got that I don't know about?
Did the UPS dropped off a
Nobel prize with my name on it?
Leonard, please don't take this the
wrong way, but the day you win a
Nobel prize,
is the day I begin my research on the
drag coefficient of tassles on
flying carpets.
The only thing missing from
that insult was: "your mama".
I got one... Hey Leonard,
- Your mama's research methodology is so flawed...
- Shut up, Howard.
- Sheldon, we have to do this.
- No, we don't.
We have to take a nourishment,
to expel waste,
and inhale enough oxygen to
keep our cells from dying.
Everything else is optional.
Ok, let me put it this way:
I'm doing it.
You can't. I'm the lead author.
Come on, the only reason you're the lead
author is because we
went alphabetically.
I let you think we went
alphabetically to spare you
the humiliation with dealing with
the fact that it was my idea.
Now to put too fine a point to it,
but I was throwing you a bone.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, I designed the experiment
that proved the hypothesis.
That doesn't mean proving.
So the entire scientific community
is just supposed to take your word?
They're not supposed to,
but they should.
Alright, I don't
care what you say.
I'm going to the conference
and I'm presenting our findings
And I forbid it.
You forbid it?
If I'm not taking credit
for our work then nobody is.
- So, you admit that it's our work.
- No.
Once again,
I'm throwing you a bone.
And once again,
you are welcome.
So, how's it going with Sheldon? Are you
guys still not talking to each other?
Not only is he still
not talking to me,
but there's this thing he does where he
stares at you and tries to get your
brain to explode.
You know, like in the classic
sci-fi movie "Scanners"?
Like... . Bzzz.
Nevermind.
How about this one?
It says, I know my physics,
but I'm still a fun guy.
Oh, I didn't know they
still made corduroy suits.
They don't,
that's why I saved this one.
Ok, well,
let's just see what else you have.
Ok, here. Take this.
And this, and this,
and this, and these...
Is this all stuff you
want me to try on?
No, this is stuff I
want you to throw out.
Seriously, don't even give it to
charity, you won't be helping anyone.
What's this?
That's the bottled
city of Kandor.
You see, Kandor was the capital
city of the planet Krypton.
It was miniaturised by Brainiac
before Krypton exploded
and then rescued by Superman.
Oh, nice.
It's a lot cooler when
girls aren't looking at it.
Here, why don't you put these while
I find a shirt and a sport cut match.
Right, be right back.
Where are you going?
Just put them on.
Here?
Oh, are you shy?
- No, I'm not shy.
- Don't worry I won't look.
I know you won't look.
Why would you look?
There's nothing to see...
Well, not 'nothing'...
Sweetie, put the pants on.
So, you know, isn't there maybe
some way you and Sheldon could
- compromise on this whole presentation thing?
- No, No.
Scientists do not compromise.
Our minds are trained
to synthetize facts
and come to
inarguable conclusions.
Not to mention,
Sheldon is back-crap crazy.
What is this?
Oh, careful.
That's my original series
Battlestar Galactica flight suit.
Oh, why didn't you
wear it on Halloween?
Because it's not a costume,
it's a flight suit.
Ok, alright, moving on.
Oh, wow. A paisley shirt.
It goes with my corduroy suit.
If you mean it should end up in
the same place, then I agree.
Is this your only tie?
Technically, yes.
But, if you'll notice...
It's reversible!
So it works as two.
Sweetie, I don't even
think it works as one.
- Is this all your clothes?
- Eh, yeah.
Everything since
the eighth grade.
- The eighth grade?
- My last growth sprout
Ok, well,
let's go back to the curdoroy suit.
- Great.
- Yeah.
I said no. Put it down.
Hey Sheldon.
Hello Penny.
Get anything good?
Just the latest copy of Applied
Particle Physics quarterly.
Oh, you know, that is so weird
that yours came and mine didn't.
It was a joke.
Yep.
Tip you waitresses.
I'm here all week.
Penny, just to save you
from further awkwardness,
know that I'm perfectly comfortable with
the two of us climbing the stairs
in silence.
Oh, yeah ok, me too.
Zip it, lock it.
Put it in your pocket.
- So, you and Leonard...
- Oh dear God...
Little misunderstanding, huh?
A little misunderstanding... ?
Galileo and the Pope had
a little misunderstanding.
Anyway, I was talking to Leonard this
morning and I think he feels really bad
about it.
How do you feel?
I don't understand
the question.
I'm just asking if it's difficult to
be fighting with your best friend.
I haven't thought
about it like that.
I wonder if I've been experiencing
physiological manifestations
of some sort of unconscious
emotional turmoil
Wait, what?
I couldn't poop this morning.
You should just talk to him,
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
- Certainly preferable to my plan.
- Which was?
A powerful laxative.
You absolutely
should talk to him.
Look, I know Leonard values you as
a friend and he told me himself
without your little idea there's no way
he could come up with this whole
experiment thing.
Excuse me. "Little idea"?
Yeah, I mean he tried
to explain it to me,
- I didn't really understand it but...
- Of course you didn't.
He said: "Little idea"?
Oh, well, no... Not...
- Not in those words.
- In what words then, exactly?
Oh, you know... Gee. The exact words
are... It's more the spirit in which
he said...
- What did he say?
- You had a lucky hunch
Hey, Sheldon, I've been thinking,
instead of arguing about this...
Don't you ever
speak to me again.
What... ?
Ok, I'm leaving
for the conference.
Have fun presenting
my "lucky hunch"
Shel, I didn't
mean it like that.
- Then why did you say it?
- I don't know, I wasn't...
- Were you trying to impress Penny?
- No, no, not at all. A little bit.
How did that work out for you?
- Leonard, ready to go?
- Libido: 1 Truth: 0.
Ok, I'm gonna ask
you one more time.
We did the work together,
let's present the paper together.
And I'm telling you
for the last time,
it's pandering,
it's undignifying, and bite me.
Let's go.
- Bye Sheldon.
- Goodbye Penny.
One of these days... bshh!
There you go.
You're right this side
does look better.
No, no, I didn't say better,
I said "less stained".
I just checked the house.
There's probably 20-25 people in there.
- You're kidding!
- Is that all?
"All? " In particle
physics 25 is Woodstock!
- Then good!
- I wasn't expecting such a crowd,
I'm all nervous.
It's ok, just open with a joke,
you'll be fine.
A joke... Ok.
How about this? Um, ok...
There's this farmer
and he has these chickens but
they won't lay any eggs, so...
He calls a physicist to help.
The physicist then does
some calculations,
and he says:
"I have a solution,
but it only works for spherical
chickens in a vacuum".
Right?
Oh, sorry,
I just had heard it before.
- Let's roll. Hey, nice suit.
- It's a classic, right?
I really should have
brought my own car.
So, in conclusion,
the data show that at temperatures
approaching absolute zero,
the moment of inertia changes,
and a solid becomes a supersolid,
which clearly appears to be a
previously unknown state of matter.
Thank you!
- Are there any questions?
- Yeah.
What the hell was that?
Any other questions?
Doctor Sheldon Cooper here, I am the
lead author of this particular paper.
Thank you.
And you sir, you have completely skipped
over the part where I was walking
through the park
and I saw these children on a
merry-go-round which started me thinking
about the moment of inertia
in gases like helium
at temperatures
approaching absolute zero.
I didn't skip it.
It's just an anecdote, it's not science.
Oh, I see. It was the apple
falling on Newton's head,
- was that just an anecdote?
- You are not Isaac Newton.
No, no, that's true. Gravity would have
been apparent to me without the apple.
You cannot possibly
be that arrogant.
You continue to underestimate me,
my good man.
Look, if you weren't happy with my
presentation then maybe you should have
given it with me!
As I have explained repeatedly,
unlike you,
I don't need validation
from lesser minds.
No offense.
Really, so why did you come?
Because I knew
you'd screw this up.
I didn't screw it up!
Oh, please.
I admit that spherical chicken joke,
- that was hilarious.
- Thank you.
But it was straight
downhill from there.
I've had enough of
your condescendship.
Maybe I didn't go to college
when I was 11 like you.
Maybe I got my doctorate
at 24 instead of 16
but you are not the only
person who is smarter than
everyone else in this room!
No offense.
And I am clearly
not the only person
who is tormented by insecurity
and has an ego in need
of constant validation!
So you admit you're an egotist?
Yes!
My name is doctor Leonard Hofstadter
and I can never please my parents so
I need all my self esteem
from strangers like you!
But he's worse!
Ok, that's it!
Stop it!
You cannot blow up my
head with your mind!
Then I'll settle
for your aneurism!
- Stop it!
- You hit me!
You saw that he hit me!
You tried to blow up my head!
So it was working!
It wa... It was not!
You're a nutcase!
We'll see about that!
Heads up,
you people in the front row!
This is a splash zone!
Stop it!
Just quit it!
Is this usually how
these physics things go?
More often than you think.
You could have offered
me a ride home.
You're lucky I
didn't run you over.
I really don't understand
what you're so unhappy about.
You begged me to come, I came.
There's just no pleasing you.
You're right, I'm the problem,
I'm the one that needs help.
Well, that's not much of an
apology but I'll take it.
Excuse me,
is there anything you
would apologise for?
Yes.
I'm sorry I tried to
blow up your head.
It was uncalled for.
You won't believe this.
Somebody got the whole thing with
their cell phone and put it on YouTube!
What?
- Who would do that?
- That would be me.
Hey, check it out,
it's a featured video!
He hit me!
You saw that he hit me!
- Then it was working!
- It was not working! You're a nutcase!
We will see about that!
You people in the
front row heads up!
This is splash zone
Stop it! Leave it, leave it!
You want a volcano nerve pinch!
You should clip your fingernails!
Those hurt!
Oh, Jeez.
does this suit really look that bad?
Forget your suit,
look at my arms waving.
I'm like a flamingo on Ritalin.
Howard,
would you like to explain to
me why your Facebook page
has a picture of me sleeping
on your shoulder captioned
"me and my girlfriend"?
Uh oh, here comes the talk.
www.tvsubtitles.net