this is very exciting.
We are at St. Joseph's medical center Because today,andy dwyer Is getting his cast off.
It is a great day for andy. And it's a wonderful day For my subcommittee.
oh,my god.
Your boobs are dead. stop it. No,they're not.
It like a sweaty pinata.
hey,my ipod. oh,yeah...my pirate.
doctor,if i may, Could i keep that cast,please?
it's a highly Disgusting request, But i don't see why not.
thank you. This is a symbol Of new beginnings.
A symbol of hope And of our project.
We will build this park.
it is gonna feel so good To walk again finally.
easy,take your tim-- oh!
Oh,my go-- oh,no!
yeah,they might be A little weak at first.
- =WWW.YDY.COM/BBS=- Ptoudly Presents
=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
翻译:irini alegrarse
校对/时间轴:猥琐叔叔
公园与游憩
第一季 第06集 本季终
thank you,guys. welcome back To t yes.
i just wanted To say that we're-- quiet,everyone. Ann wants to say something.
i wanted to thank you all For being so supportive.
When andy fell in the pit, I didn't expect anyone In the government To reach out to us.
So thanks. you're welcome.
hey,you're welcome,ann.
babe,when are you Gonna tell them about my show? oh,yeah. Sorry.
Andy's band is playing a show, And we want you all to come.
it's gonna be a party, So check the suits at the door. It's gonna be crazy.
andy's band is really good, And it's been driving him nuts That he can't play.
He's been writing all These songs About things That are physically near him.
Sandwich Are you turkey or ham?
ham.
lamp!
I wish you were a lamp That would light up When you got touched
what kind of music Does your band play?
you know,i don't really Like to define it,
But it's like-- I don't know,matchbox 20 Meets the fray.
so...rock.
well,again i don't really Like to define it. totally get what you mean.
so i would love to come To this thing; when is it? tonight at 8:00.
no,tonight? yeah.
i can't go. why not?
my mom set up this meeting.
It's like a political Tte-- tte With the local bigwig.
leslie,you're not gonna go? Come on.
oh,you guys. You know how i love mixing work Into my personal life.
This guy is important. And he has valuable information That could help us build a park.
Mm,but i wanna go To the concert. come on,play hooky. Blow off the meeting.
oh,but i wanna go To that concert so bad, But i have to go to That meeting,i have to go.
But i'll meet up with you guys After the tte-- tte. I promise.
mark,congratulations.
Nks,nate.
For what? you got that Speed bump thing taken care of.
Finally. Nice work. oh,yeah.
There used to be this huge speed Bump in the center of town.
It we. So i decided i wanted To do something about it.
And i got it lowered twonches.
Apparently what i can achieve In government Can literally be measured.
hey,dr. Harris.
Um,andy's Playing a show tonight.
And we'd love it If you came by.
I think there's gonna be A good turnout At andy's show tonight.
He wrote this new song About what happened to him Calledthe pit.
It's one of those rare songs That rocks really hard...
And also informs people about A small public works project.
guess andy's doing well.
yeah,he's A little shaky still, But that's to be expected.
well,not really.
If he had his cast Removed two weeks ago, The Have atrophied so much.
i'm sorry,two weeks ago?
it's when they Were scheduled to come off.
but he told me that You told him he should wait.
no,he rescheduled.
He said it was personal, That he would explain later, But then he never explained.
i have waited on him Hand and foot
For two months.
well,i guess That explains it.
hey,what's up,people Of pawnee? All right.
All right.
In just a minute, Scarecrow boat Is gonna rock it out.
Please be patient while we Rock out the equipment setup.
The band has had a few Different nameover the years.
When it started we were Teddy bear suicide,
But then we changed it To mouse rat.
Then we were god hates figs. The department of homeland Obscurity.
Flames for flames. Muscle confusion.
Nothing rhymes with orange.
Uh,then Everything rhymes with orange.
Punchface champions.Rad wagon.
Puppy pendulum. Possum pendulum. Penis pendulum.
Hand rail suicide. Angel snack. Just the tip. Three skin.
Uh,jet black pope.
We went back to mouse rat. And now we are Scarecrow boat.
God,when i hear myself Say scarecrow boat Out loud,i kind of hate it.
now,you know That we're gonna be building A park in a residential lot,
So of course we're gonna have To get the zoning codes approved And amended by our city council.
what kind of movies Do you like? huh?
Oh,well,you know...
Documentaries. Political thrillers. i like all kind of movies.
great.
So i brought Some pictures of the lot, And you can tell that The houses are very close to it.
How difficult is Rezoning in your town?
Could you go into detail A little bit about that? sure. great.
it's refreshing To be with someone Who likes talking about Government issues.
most of the women I go out with find it boring.
well,you know, You veo have zoning codes, Or else the whole thing Could be chaos.
your mother mentioned That you don't date much.
what?
are we...focusing On my career? Why do you ask?
i haven't Been dating much either.
Since my divorce. I uh-- well,it hasn't been easy.
I'm coping, But it was tough on the kids.
Not my kids, 'Cause they're grown up. But...
It was tough on their kids.
I shouldn't bring up my divorce On the first date.
But i feel I can tell you anything.
i think It's going quite well.
And she looks Ling san duncan.
hi,mom. He thinks we're on a date.
Did you tell him We were on a date? honey,if i told you It was a date, You never would've gone.
You're not getting any ynger. well,neither is he.
And he's 62 years old.
oh,just go back in there And finish the dinner.
You don't have to have sex With him if you don't want to.
what!? Are you crazy?
Hi,how are you?
hey,parks department. hey,mark.
This is beth, My ex-wife tammy's Better-looking sister.
nice to meet you. nice to meet you.
You guys are together? yup. My ex-wife tammy cheated on me,
Then we divorced. Then last week,i ran Into her sister beth,here.
Turns out she hates tammy too. So we started dating.
It's like a fairy tale. tammy stinks.
brendanawicz. hey,tom.
hey,i want you To meet my wife.
hi,i'm wendy haverford. hi,you're tom's wife.
uh,don't hold it against me.
look at how hot she is. Isn't that crazy?
And she's a surgeon, She makes a ton of money. Bam!
his is derek.
cool,how long have You guys been dating?
we're just friends.
He's like, The gayest person i've ever met.
But i make out with him When i'm drunk sometimes.
if you don't want to talk To me,you can just say so. i don't wanna talk to you.
apparently tonight, I'm the parks department's Seventh wheel.
this is my oldest son.
He's a very no-nonsense person, Like yourself.
And this is my youngest. He's about your age.
terrific.
So um,did you give Any more thought To those zoning code questions I asked you?
oh,come on.
Enough business, Let's have some fun.
Try some of my chicken. oh,no. That'okay.
just a taste.
Have a little taste of chicken. Just a bit.
Just a taste.
Chicken,chicken,chicken.
mm. delicious,right?
i really like This restaurant.
yup,it's a great place For a business meeting.
andy. Andy. We need to talk.
baby,hey,uh, We're just about to start. Could you grab me A triple whiskey water?
you would like that, Wouldn't you?
yep.
>>ou have two perfectly Good legs; get it yourself.
all right,hey guys, Thanks for coming out. We're scarecrow boat.
This first song Is calledmenace ball.
Two,three,four...
I knowean change it
I've been changing,too
You said we had a bad time
thank you.
Wh kd of movies do you like?
you already asked me that. oh,sorry.
Senior moment.
hey,am i keeping you From something? no,no.
Yes.
My friend andy is playing In a band tonight, And i kind of wanted to go.
well,if you wanna go To the rock show,i dot mind.
really? Are you sure? sure.
I haven't been to a rock show In a long time.
The last rock show i went to Was the everly brothers.
mm. you like the everly brothers?
they're My favorite rock group. they're so good.
I am getting Very positive signals.
you and me together
You and me together
You and me together forever
Together Forever whoa. Whoo! whoo-whoo!
All right,take five,guys. I'm gonna go acoustic.
This next song,uh...
Is dedicated to her...
My girlfriend,ann.
I call itann.
Ann
hey,the band's really good.
I like that song Grapple hound.
>>gossip town? right.
My only criticism... I hate the name the band.
yeah,they should change Their name to big lying baby,
Or where's my sandwich? Or don't forget to bring home Beers after work.
okay,since you brought It up,i'm just gonna say it.
I don't get you and...
i mean it doesn't make Any sense to me. I mean,i like andy a lot.
But there's tons of guys Out there who have jobs
And who respect you...
And think you're attractive.
really? right.
you mean guys like you-- no. for instance?
no,no,no,no,not me. okay,good.
'Cause for a second there, I thought you were hitting on me In front of my boyfriend.
well,not my style.
Even though you did just Call him a big,lying baby.
all for ann
i really find you attractive.
so you are hitting on me? no,i'm not I promise you.
she's mad in the shed
but if i were, Would you be interested? no.
okay. let me tell you why.
Because i'm in a crappy mood, And i don't really appreciate What's happening right here.
Number one-- you've Never been in a relationship That's lasted Longer than a week.
Number two-- the girls you Do choose-- that's fine.
to spend the week with-- that's enough,that's enough. Look,i was not trying To ask you out,i promise.
well,i'm glad We avoided that.
yeah I fellin' in the pit
You've fellin' in the pit
Well,you're fellin' In the pit
Pit
I've fellin' in the pit
You've fellin' in the pit
We all fell in the pit
thank you very much, Everybody. We are scarecrow boat.
Ah,no,screw it. We are mouse rat.
Thank you very much. Good night.
damn it. I missed it?
leslie, Who's your friend?
i'm george. I'm leslie's date.
yes.
He's my date. George gernway. He's a city manager in eagleton.
hi,george gernway. I'm tom haverford. This is my wife wendy.
She's my age.
hi. hello.
i have no idea Why ann is upset.
But i do know that She's too nice to yell at me In front of all these people, So i am not leaving this bar.
so i heard you Went to indiana state. yes.
my buddy todd went there, Maybe you know him. What year did u graduate?
1968.
oh,todd graduated in 2005. So you probably missed him.
How was your date with leslie?
we change the band name And then we send the demo out.
We're completely ready. andy...let's go.
honey,i'm just debriefing With the band. It's just gonna be Just one second.
hey,hi.
I'm so glad you made it. You have to meet my band.
okay,hi,band. hey,
oh,i'm so sorry That i missed your songs.
Is there any way that you guys Could do an encore or something?
encore,i like it.
Guys,let's get the stuff Out of the boxes,let's go. no,we're going home.
no,don't leave.I just got here. yeah. Shs here with her dad.
It'd be kind of rude to not Do at least one more song. andy.
okay,let's go. Let's go.
sorry,leslie. We're gonna go. I'll call you tomorrow. okay.
this weekend,guys.
ihe dead...or asleep?
Dead?
Or asleep?
george.
George.
Look at me,out like a light.
I think i should Head home now. okay.
It was nice to meet you. i had a nice time.
Don't think I'd go out with her again.
There was just no spark.
how did leslie Meet her boyfriend?
she used to read him books At the senior center.
wow. how old is he? hs six,but he Has benjamin button disease.
hey,who wants To see me climb a tree?
i do. i do!
deputy director knope...
Where do you think you're going?
Home. It's been A really crappy night.
have a beer with me?
i can't believe my mom Tried to set me up With an 80-year-old man.
i went to dinner tonight With somebody's grandpa.
you know what? That guy was too young for you.
You should be dating guys In their early 100s.
I'm telling you You should be dating men That al roker Announces their birthdays.
Hey,congratulations Are in order. I heard that you got That speed bump thing through.
don't make fun of me. i'm not!
oh,yeah. I've made a bump Into a smaller bump.
It's a great day for america. what are you talking about? That thing Was a pain in the butt.
You fixed a problem.
That's what We're supposed to do.
Mark and i are Really connecting tonight.
Like we connected that night When we made love Five years ago.
There's actually A lot of similarities Between those two nights.
That time, We were also at a bar.
And he was also pretty drunk.
if you
okay,um... don't overthink it.
keep it simple. Nice,shady tree Lots of grass. Benches.
picnic table? sure.
Water feature. mm.
Like those huge rocks To climb on.
A play area for the kids. god,that sounds wonderful. I would live in that park.
then you'd be homeless.
hey,we're closing up.
oh,what time is it? I should g no,no,no,no,no.
We're getting drinks to go.
Come on,beers to go. where are we going? All the bars are closed.
you think i can Get my beer bottle In that shopping cart Right there?
what? Mark,don't. This pit isn't a dump.
yes,it is. Look around,leslie. I mean,there's crap everywhere.
One beer bottle is Not gonna make any difference.
damn it!
That was so close,though. yes.
it was pretty so close. so-- so far to the left.
So far to the left. oh,you think you could Do any better?
no,please. I don't want anyone to see-- I'm the deputy director.
oh,you're the deputy Director of parks And blabety blahlah--
You know, Nobody's gonna see it.
Go-- go and chuck it.
oh,no.
unbelievable. That's unbelievable.
You missed the entire pit. Which is huge,by the way.
N't donything wrong. you didn't do anything wrong? mm-mm.
i waited on you hand And foot,and it was exhausting. I fed you meals.
And you could've had Your cast off two weeks ago. that is not true. It's just--
it's not true? So you're calling Dr. Harris a liar?
yes.
i'm gonna cl dr. Harris Right now; how about that? you call,and you get me On the phone with dr. Harris.
i will. don't call him right now. why? because it's late.
Listen,just put the phone down.
Fine.
You want the truth? yes.
could i have gotten My cast off two weeks ago? Technically... Yes,but...
I really,really like it When you serve me food.
get out. Get out of my house. Get out. wha-- what--
take a walk With your overly healed legs, And let me think About this relationship.
okay,this pit.
Give it to me straight.
Arr gonn Turn it into a park?
leslie, This is already a park.
Look,i mean,you got-- You got dirt slide over here,
You got Ring around the diaper.
the kids play there.
You got,uh...duck,duck glass. they play right there.
Mystery trash.
What's not to love about This park right here and now? I wish we could Turn it into a pit.
Frankly. don't you?
But seriously. I mean,really.
honestly,leslie,it's Gonna be a long uphill battle.
You are gonna be super annoyed With all the people That want you to fail.
There is a sea of red tape.
Endless roadblocks.
So i don't know. I don't know.
crew it. I'm gonna try To do it anyway.
i mean,kennedy Put a man on the moon. he did.
i can build one park.
i really admire Your tenacity.
i really admire your...
No,no. Wait,what am i doing?
This isn't the way i want This to happen again.
leslie,it's not That big a deal.
i think You should go home,mark.
all right. Okay.
I'm sorry. It's,uh... I'm gonna get out of here.
I'm sorry. it's okay.
no,no,no,no. no,it's--
Oh,my gosh! Oh,oh!
Oh,my god! Oh,my god!
Mark,are you all right?
wow. are you okay?
Oh,my god.
i'll get some help. help!
Help.
hey,babe!
Baby! Open up!
That guy mark Just felin the pit.
what? you know that guy mark?
yeah. he just fell in the pit.
You gotta go check it out. You're a nurse. I think he's probably hurt.
Seriously,it's pretty bad.
The pit I've fellin' in the pit
You've fellin' in the pit
Well,you've fellin' In the pit
I've fellin' in the pit
www.tvsubtitles.net