so we've been called
out To his hiking trail
Because there's some
reports That some teenagers
Are digging bags of dog
poop Out of the trash
And having dog poop fights.
i don't believe it.
Oh, my god, it's real.
uh, yeah, i'm not gonna- I'm
not gonna go deal with this.
I'm leaving.
hey.
Hey.
Hello? Boys. I am leslie knope. I work
for the department Of parks and recreation.
Okay. All right.
Cool it. Okay. No! Ahh!
That's disgusting. What are you doing?
No! Oh! Help! Help!
Tom! Tom! Ahh! No! Ahh!
Oh, it smells so bad. Oh! Oh!
What would you think This was fun? Ow!
Oh, really? Oh, really?
Oh, really? Oh, hey, hey.
Okay. Okay, here we go. Who wants it?
Ha, ha. Whoo, missed it.
Yeah, oh! Actually,
this is a little fun.
This is fun.
Oh, hey, tom, Check it out.
Norton construction Just sent this over.
whoa, mama.
i love great lakes wine.
you can have the wine. I wanna take
that cheese And do terrible things to it.
oh, dah, dah, dah. No, no, no, no, no.
You know as well as i do That we are not allowed
To accept gifts over $25 For corruptioneasons.
We live in a fish bowl, and
The public is always watching.
That's why i go Two towns over If i
want to rent a movie With nudity in it.
yeah, i probably
Shouldn't have said that.
But you cannot Enjoy
this basket. I'm so sorry.
So to avoid temptation
I'm gonna lock it up.
when you're In the government, There's
a million ways To exploit your power.
Have i ever given in To that temptation?
No, never. I'm not
that kind Of politician.
Official parks and rec Business. I
just need to grab A quick hot dog.
Sorry about that, Little girl.
You can have the next one.
I have a moral code,
And i never violate it.
People look at me And they say,
"wow, tom, You are so pure. "you're
like a brown superman With a beard
"that just stands For justice
and truth And the american way. "
so, ann, I asked april to create One of those social
network Internet profiles For the sullivan street pit.
So are you guys ready For the debut?
yes, can we cut That red ribbon Around your monitor
now? absolutely. I love a good ribbon cutting.
Oh, april, that's good. Kids. hey,
look, the pit Already has six friends.
oh, yeah, mark. Mark's a friend.
who Gotta see mark's profile.
Look at the photos Of these
ladies on his page. wow. sick.
maybe those Are his relatives. yeah,
maybe fake boobs Run in his family.
look at this lady. She's
got a thong on her face.
oh, my god, his favorite Movie
isdances with wolves. okay, we're good.
We'll keep Checking in on this.
where is mark anyway? attending Yet
another meeting Of the old boys' club.
Politics is full Of boys'
clubs, Formal and informal.
Behind me are all the members Of the
city council Over the past 30 years.
And every day, As a woman, I have
to walk past This wall of men.
It can be very upsetting,
Especially because Of that guy.
No matter What direction i move,
He's always staring At my chest.
See?
what are they doing Out
there? wheeling and dealing.
Divvying up the empire.
eh, my wife Got me this shirt. She
swears it makes me Look thinner.
it kinda does.
you know what we should do? Let's go out
there. Let's bust up That old boys' club.
We're doing great work In the
government. We deserve to be included.
sure, yeah, I could use a beer. yes,
ann, that's good. Think like a man.
April, we're leaving. You're in
charge, And it's because you're a woman.
what, do you really like
Red tape and uphill battles?
hey, leslie. hey.
what is up? i'll tell you what's up.
Couple of ladies are coming to Bust up your
little boys' club. awesome. Gl thave you.
Get you a beer. We're in.
hey, i'm brian. hi, brian.
Leslie knope, Deputy director of-
drink that. okay.
i'm ann, everyone. I don't work here.
ann. so what are you guys Talking
about? What's topic du jour?
Did you hear that?
That was the sound Of a
glass ceiling Being shattered.
The boys' club is more about Socializing than
work, you know? I mean, you gotta loosen up.
I kinda feel like I'm already in the boys' club.
I mean, look at those bitches Clean up after me.
so is this, like, your Regular tuesday night
scene? well, it's just A way to unwind, you know?
really different from Your
friday night crowd, right?
what crowd? you know, the girls with The tribal
back tattoos Who drink red bull For a living.
oh. that crowd. oh, i
like this. Is is banter.
Banter's fun. where'd that come from?
we were just on the computer
Looking at your profile.
You know, you have a friend Who has a tattoo That
says "daddy's girl" And both words are misspelled.
oh, mixing it up With the boys. What
are you gonna say? What's your comeback?
those aren't really My friends
anymore. I don't hang out with them.
oh, boo. Brendanawicz, That's some
weak sauce. You need to hit harder.
natalie, It's your sister. Pick me up
or i'm gonna draw All over your jeans.
well, it's official,
People. We're outta beer.
ahh, that's the cue.
See you later, leslie.
It was nice hanging out, You
know, after work hours. wait.
i think i'm gonna Take off
too. yeah, i should go, leslie.
wait, you guys, let's keep This good
feeling going. It's just getting started.
yeah, 'cause partie Usually get
started When you run out of booze.
okay, wait. Just hold on a second.
I got wine. all: hey!
and cheese. all: hey!
good morning. Last night in a foolish
attempt To infiltrate a boys' club
I violated the government Employee
ethics code Of the state of indiana.
I have always tried to live My life in
an ethical way, And last night i failed.
I realize i have let down Every
female Public official in america,
And i would like to
apologize To them right now,
Individually And in alphabetical order.
Michele bachmann, Republican,
minnesota, I am sorry.
Tammy baldwin, Democrat,
wisconsin, I'm so sorry, tammy.
Lissa bean.
Double shift, remember?
Are you gonna be okay? oh, yeah.
I got, uh... dinner. oh, god.
Honey, can you just
Clean up a little bit?
i'll try. Don't expect much.
okay, well, I'll do it when i get home.
you will? yes.
ann is amazing.
She takes care of me. She takes care of
sick people, Sick babies. She is an angel.
And i seriously love her. Hard.
She's going to be gone
For the next 24 hours.
So i made this list, And basically This place is
gonna be Like a sparkling palace When she returns.
I took a bunch Of pain killers. They're
about to kick in, So i'm ready to go.
here it is. Let's clear the air.
Last night i opened up This gift
basket For my own pleasure. really?
Leslie knope, usually such A
prudish stickler For the rules.
i'm not happy About it either, tom.
it's like i don't even Know you anymore.
last year you wrote me up For
making personal one calls To my mom.
yes, i did, And i would do it again.
Two wrongs Do not make a right.
yes, but she Was in the hospital.
i did not know that At the time.
so can i have the basket?
no, i'm sorry. It's evidence.
it's a nice basket. what
would you Put in there?
i d't know, Potpourri.
that's a lot of potpourri.
hey, i am not the one On trial here.
i appreciate And thank you in
advance For your unwavering support.
i think you should Go to jail,
Think about what you've done.
go to jail? What's going on?
ron, I have a very important
And very long story To tell yo
put it in an email? nope.
It happened right out there,
Right outside this window.
Why can't i look away? let's
not blow this Out of proportion.
i will blow this In proportion.
The minimum punishment for this Is an
official reprimand From the city manager.
it's not that big a deal. maybe
in your world It isn't a big deal.
You're a white protestant man
With a full, rich moustache.
But i am a woman, And i need to
hold myself up To a higher standard.
this is ridiculous. Yore punishing yourself
More than anybody else no Is gonna punish you.
What do you suggest we do? You
think we should Cover this up?
no, i'm not saying that.
No one said "cover-up".
good because the cover-up
Is worse than the crime.
When you spill something And you try to wipe it up
With something that's dirty, Then you get double dirty.
please don't Make
this worse. oh, my god.
Good afternoon.
Since we last spoke, I have taken extraordinary steps
To make further amends For the mistakes that i've made.
I have written A full confession,
Which i will be emailing To everyone
in the entire Pawnee government.
I've also attached a link To the pit's web page
Just to remind people Of all the good work that i do.
I asked ron to blow The
whistle on me, And he refused.
And that is why I had
to whistle-blow myself.
i wish i could say Some of this
mess was ann's, But it's all mine.
I'm kind of a nester.
Eh, not bad for a guy
With two broken legs.
Hey.
doing a little Experiment tonight
To see what will Get me drunker-
Drinkingine- leslie, come here. See
what april Put on the pit's web page.
right now drinking wine Is winning.
oh, my god, What am i looking at?
a video of me drinking
Some of that wine you stole.
what? Why did you do this?
because i was waiting For my sister and
i was bored, And my hair Looked rllgood.
and you put it In the
pit's web page? yeah.
okay, take this off. Okay, i just sent an email To
everyone in the government And i put a link To this page.
a young lawbreaker.
A future leslie knope.
Play it again for us, jerry. you got it.
leslie. She's 19 years old.
I thought i told you Not to make this
worse. and i heard you Loud and clear.
but then you made it worse.
The disciplinary committee's Having a hearing
tomorrow And you're gonna Have to testify. oh, no.
april might get dismissed. You could get
fired. oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, no. Oh, god.
Oh, this bench Is so uncomfortable.
Ow, help. Please, ron.
Ron, ron, Tell me it's gonna be
okay. Tell me it's gonna be okay.
it's gonna- ron,
where are you?
it'll-
hang in.
ron. okay, you're okay.
Good evening.
I've spoken to you A couple times
About something That happened,
But i don't wanna- I dot
wanna Talk about it anymore.
so the disciplinary Committee awaits.
Feeling good? Feeling
strong? not really, no.
do you want me to run Some test questions with you, Maybe give
you an idea Of what the disciplinary Committee will be like?
yeah, that'd be great.
Yeah, thanks, tom. okay.
So, ms. Knope, You're
accused Of stealing wine.
How many drinks do you have
Per week on average? zero.
Zero to six. i'm gonna write down "ten".
yeah.
do u ever cheat On your
taxes? no, no, no, never.
good. You're doing great. How many sexual
partners Have you had in the last year?
are they gonna ask that?
this is a deposition-style Hearing, ms. Knope. Nothing is off-limits. You
have to answer. Now how many sexual partners Have you had in the last year?
zero to six. zero.
Have you ever thought
About ron sexually?
what?! including dreams.
Have you ever had A sexual dream About our
boss, Ron swanson? no, absolutely not, no.
yes. no.
now in this recurring dream
That you have about ron,
Is he, like, a regular ron Or is he
half-ron, half-animal, Like a ctaur? what?
is he wearing A football uniform? Are you making
love to him On a couch Shaped like his moustache?
Is he covered in powerade?
no, okay, Time-out, time-out.
this committee doesn't Take time-outs,
ms. Knope. Now answer the question.
i need something to drink.
how 'bout some stolen wine?
no, i meant water.
thank you for your ti,
Ms. Knope. You're fired.
So that's kinda your Worst-case scenario, you know?
If you can handle that, I think you'll be fine.
great.
Ron, thank you for
being Here with me today.
i'm your department hea
I have to be. nonetheless.
ms. Knope. yes.
you're here Because you allegedly Accepted a gift Of
over $25 And contributed To the delinquency of a minor.
Can you tell us What happened?
i'm gonna take a glass Of
water first if i may. certainly.
Sorry.
"two days ago i attended An informal boys'
club meeting "for the very first time.
"after one and a half beers, "awash in the glow
Of acceptance Into this elite, Exclusive club- "
sorry, What club is this?
a couple city planners Like to drink
beer In the courtyard On tuesday nights.
no one is supposeto drink
Alcohol on government property.
it's not my department.
Go ahead, leslie.
"i made A very unwise decision, "a
decision that will live In infamy.
"i opened a gift basket
Of wine and cheese.
"our intern, april ludgate, "drank
some of that wine Without my knowledge.
"that was never part Of the plan.
"she had not been invited to The meeting of
the boys' club. "i repeat, Notbeen invited.
"though it is my hope That someday
"she lives in a world "where the very
idea Of boys' clubs Is ancient history. "
but you did Open the gift basket.
And the intern Did drink the wine.
Please don't blame her For my mistake.
The biggest crime We could commit here Would be to
destroy A teenage girl's passion For local government.
there's only one more
thing I need to clean- Me.
Um, i can't really Get into a shower,
So i got this idea From my parents.
This is how They clean their dog.
You like that?
I wrote that for ann.
It's gonna be playing when she
Walks through the door today.
And check this out.
Washed my shorts. How you like that?
hey, turn that down.
no. I wrote that song.
i don't care. Turn it down. what are you
doing In my yard, lawrence? Get outta here.
okay, you know what, I'm
taking it. put down my boom box.
it's my boom box now. I asked you
nicely. you did not ask me nicely.
Put that down!
I just put 12 new
batteries In that thing!
Lawrence, come on.
ugh, ugh. give it to me.
Go back inside, hank.
ms. Knope, what was The first thing you
did When you arrived at work The next day?
Can you go over the timeline
For us once more? yes, of course.
I awoke at 6:21 a. m. After a fitful
night of sleep. we've been over this.
What more could you guys
Possibly want her to do?
well, we don't know yet. Frankly,
we've got A lot more questions.
ron, it's okay. no, it's not.
This is not communist china.
You cannot Make her whip herself.
You cannot make her Wear a hair shirt.
we weren't planning On doing either
of those things. this is america.
You wanna live In north korea, You can
live in north korea. I don't want to.
I want to live in america.
Leslie has never broken A rule in her
life, To the point That it's annoying.
If you want to slap her
On the wrist, go ahead.
You wanna Do anything more serious,
You're gonnaave To go through me.
Let's go. are we done?
we're done. Let's go.
So after all that, It's really not that
bad. You're gonna get a letter In your file.
ron, i just wanted To say thank
you- don't worry about it.
No, i didn't do it For leslie. I
did it because I hate bureaucracy.
My idea Of a perfect government Is one
guy who sits In a small room at a desk,
And the only thing He's allowed
to decide Is who to nuke.
The man is chosen Based on some kind of iq test And
maybe also A physical tournament, Like a decathlon.
And women are Brought to him maybe
When he sires them.
oh, hey, ann, You're here.
yeah, i came From the hospital.
How'd it go? i don't
wanna Be overdramatic,
But today felt like 100 years in hell And
the absolute worst day Of my life. oh, god.
i never shoulda opened
That stupid basket.
yeah, why did you Open that basket?
It doesn't really Seem like you.
i think it's 'cause i wanted
To shatter the glass ceiling,
You know what i mean? And just
kind of infiltrate The boys' club.
i did it for a guy.
oh. yeah.
Mark.
oh.
well, i- We had a brief
affair In february Of 2004.
And, um, there's still Something
very complicated Between us, so.
yeah, sure. yh.
smart woman. Iffy choice in men.
But then again, I'm not one to talk.
what do you think?
andy, this is so sweet.
nothing. what happened to you?
oh, i was chasing Our neighbor
Who is a total jag-weed.
And i fell In some prickly bushes.
Doesn't matter. What do
you think of the house?
Hmm? Were you totally surprised?
yeah. do you love it? yeah.
Here, baby, sit down. I'm gonna
put something On those scratches.
somebody is getting Gently
laid tonight. andy, god.
you look like You need one of these.
come on. You're over 21.
not supposed to be drinking
On government property.
Loosen up. You're gonna Drive yourself crazy
Trying to follow every single Rule in government.
mark, i have a letter In my file.
i got seven letters In my file.
Pretty much every guy In city
planning Has a bunch of letters.
So welcome to the team.
look out, boys. I'm in your club now.
I'm in your club.
and I'm in your... creepy
www.tvsubtitles.net