One of the funner things
that we do here in Pawnee
is the annual easter egg hunt.
Tom hides the eggs,
and I have to say,
he did an exceptional job this year.
I've been searching for 25 min,
and I haven't found one.
And I'm an adult.
Yeah, I forgot to do that.
Maybe Tom's trying to make this year
a challenge. And if so, he's succeeding.
I don't think an egg
has been found yet.
Let's keep looking.
We're gonna find one.
- Feygnasse Team -
Synchro: mpm, So.
Épisode 101
Canvassing
I'm going to see my mom.
She's a big mucky-muck
in the county school system.
She's my hero.
How do I explain her?
She's...
as respected as mother Teresa,
she's as powerful as Stalin,
and she's as beautiful
as Margaret Thatcher.
- In or out, Leslie. Doorway is creepy.
- Right, sorry.
Choosing in.
So, what do you want, Leslie?
Just here to gossip, gab, chat.
Stuff we do.
But it looks like you're super-busy.
And I am super-busy,
so I shall bid you adieu.
That's weird.
I just remembered something.
I have my own subcommittee now.
I'm sure you've heard something.
People are talking.
We're having a town hall meeting
tomorrow at 7:00 p.m.
At the Smithfield community center.
Yeah, I'm leading it.
It's no biggy.
I mean, it is.
It's a big deal...
I don't know, I mean, you know...
Wanna come?
Honey, jeez, you know how busy am.
I know. I know.
That's why I fake-invited you.
I'll try to be there.
Okay, so everybody's here.
Let's get started.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
- Metal. Sorry.
- It was really loud.
Subcommittee members,
are we prepared for tomorrow night?
- Have you booked the hall yet?
- Yes, sir.
- Ann, did you clear your schedule?
- I did. I changed my shift.
Leslie, I just have to say
I think you might be taking this
to the public a little bit too soon.
It doesn't matter
what you propose to the public,
they might call for a vote.
If they vote you down, then you're done.
I don't care if there's gonna be a vote.
I have a secret weapon.
Canvassing.
Nothing better than good old-fashioned
door-to-door campaigning.
I'm not above using my expertise
to change hearts and minds
if the cause is just.
When I was in sixth grade,
I was voted best dressed by 87 votes.
And there were only 63 people
in my class.
Andy fell into that pit.
I fell into that pit.
How many more Pawnee citizens
have to fall into that pit
before we turn it to park?
Zero.
Say it.
- Zero.
- A hundred.
I've got some sunscreen
for your beaks.
Tom, you probably won't need any.
And this is our canvassing guide.
This is gonna be the script that we use
when we speak with people.
"If a person is a man,
turn to page two."
"If the person looks like a celebrity...
Example: Jack Nicholson...
"Use this to help your pitch.
"Example: You can't handle the pit.
"That's why we need
to turn it into a park."
This is really thorough.
Ann and I are a team. You too.
We have even sectors.
You have odd sectors.
And we're gonna win.
Win what?
Go!
Someone's in there.
- That's gonna be fun. Excited?
- Yeah.
- Ready? Are you pumped up?
- Yes.
Look humble.
But confident.
Good afternoon. We are representatives
from your local government.
May we speak with you
about the Sullivan street pit?
Sure.
Excellent.
Positive response.
How would you feel if we turned that pit
into a beautiful community park?
Yeah, that would be a great idea.
Good, I live in the neighborhood,
so I could probably tell you
a little bit about...
Section three.
We are having a public forum
tomorrow night.
And that would be great
if you could come
voice your strong support.
Tomorrow? I can't.
I'm busy. Sorry.
We understand that people are busy,
but we would love for you to come to...
Sorry. Good luck, though.
I'm all for a park.
- Would it change if we told you that...
- She's gone.
Yeah, a park.
That sounds like a really good idea.
Great. Would you be willing to come
to a town meeting and show your support?
Absolutely.
Now, is this park gonna have
a playground or a pool for the kids?
How old are your kids?
No kids.
- I'm gonna put him down as a yes.
- Don't.
Also is the park gonna be at least
a thousand feet from my house?
Because, yeah,
I really can't move again.
April, please stand behind me.
That's it.
That's all that we got.
- No flier?
- Nope.
Man, this is great.
This is so great. I love canvassing.
What a great way to spend my time.
All right, team Haverford,
you guys are awesome,
but I think I might work better
as a solo artist,
so I'm gonna head out, peace.
- He runs weird.
- He really does.
It's a good idea.
But I'm just not sure.
Okay, which part
are you not sure about?
Turning the pit into a park.
That's kind of the whole thing.
I think this is a great idea,
but I can't make any forum.
- I would have to get a babysitter.
- How old are your kids?
Four and two.
Could the four-year-old
watch the two-year-old?
Mickey!
What's up, buddy?
How's my number one sod man doing?
Here's the 1, 2, 3 of the situation.
One: we're building a new park.
Two: I'm on the committee.
Three: you're putting in the sod.
Maybe down the line, situation'll arise
where you could hook me up.
Are you gonna commit to coming
to this forum or are you  a bitch?
Yes, you do owe me.
Okay, keep going.
Keep moving.
Nose to the grindstone.
No means yes.
Can we stop, please?
Because it's really hot and I'm tired.
Yeah, I'm hot too.
Let's blow in each other's faces.
- Or we could drink some water.
- Let's do that.
My house is really close by.
Let's go take a break for an hour or so.
Look, I didn't want it to have
to come to this, but, Ann,
please open the sealed envelope
that's in your binder.
This is a little something
I learned from Karl Rove.
If you want to guarantee
the results of a survey,
you design the question to give you
the answer that you want.
"Wouldn't you rather have a park
"than a storage facility
for nuclear waste?"
That seems iffy.
- Don't worry. I made it all up.
- Yeah, that's what I mean.
Wouldn't you agree,
like most decent Americans,
that it would be a good idea to turn
the abandoned lot on Sullivan street
into a beautiful community park?
Actually, no.
I'm not really a fan of parks.
Very noisy.
Barbecue smell all the time.
Would you change your mind
if I told you
that nine out of ten meth users
said the same exact thing?
What?
How would you even know that?
Survey.
We surveyed crystal meth users.
We're actually having a little
town meeting tomorrow night
- if you wanted to...
- I know it sounds weird,
but I just don't like
living near parks.
So do you have a flier or something?
I'd be happy to take it.
You don't care about your kids
if you don't support it.
Excuse me?
It's... what I mean is,
kids love parks
- and you should too.
- If I don't support your project,
then I don't love my daughter?
- I didn't...
- What time is this thing anyway?
- It's next month. Forget it.
- It's tomorrow night. I'll be there.
Great.
Okay, come on.
We got one.
Am I talking to the two sexiest thighs
in landscaping?
Yes, I am, 'cause I'm talking to Marcy.
How's it going? Tom Haverford.
Kevin, your sandboxes are the best.
That's why I want you involved.
I want the best monkey bars in my park.
I don't mind hooking you up.
Maybe down the line, there will be
a situation where you can hook me up.
Thank you for your time, sir.
He said some upsetting things.
I can't believe you gave him
your home phone number.
Well, I'm a public servant.
I need to be accessible.
What the hell is wrong with people?
I should show them
Andy's medical bills.
- Maybe they'd have a little sympathy.
- Oh, my God.
Ann, game changer.
- You busted the game wide open.
- How?
We need Andy.
He's our symbol.
We'll wheel him around
the neighborhood to get sympathy.
He's a cute FDR.
- Ron, You got minute.
- Sure, Paul. What can I do for you?
Sullivan street park project,
you fast-tracked it, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
We have a public forum tomorrow.
Okay, great.
- I'll be there.
- Great.
"You fast-tracked that, right?"
I'm sorry.
Did you say something?
You didn't say anything to me?
There's a new wind blowing
in government, and I don't like it.
All of a sudden, there's all
this federal money coming in,
and Paul, the city manager,
is telling us to build parks,
start new community programs.
It's horrifying.
- Do you have like a nurse's costume?
- Costume? Like scrubs?
Yeah, put those on.
Bass, come on!
- It can be tricky...
- Don't.
Why do I want
to build this park so bad?
Maybe because
a pit filled with garbage
isn't the best we can do in America.
You know, in Russia...
they could pretend that pit was a park.
Bring their kids down there.
"Hey, Vlad!
"Look at these rocks.
Let's pretend they're potatoes.
"Nikolai,
"do you want to swim in the dirt?"
But not here.
'Cause we're a nation of dreamers.
And it is my dream
to build a park...
that I one day visit with
my White House staff on my birthday.
And they say, "President Knope...
"this park is awesome.
"Now we understand why you are the first
female president of the United States."
Builder of parks.
- How was canvassing?
- Canvassing was... okay.
But... I think we're going to have
to postpone the town meeting.
Postpone?
Only for 1 to 90 days.
No, you're doing this meeting.
You have my full support.
I was talking to the city manager,
exchanging ideas.
There's a mutual
respect there. And...
together, we have decided
to fast-track your project.
City manager?
Really?
I have to cancel this meeting.
Fast-track?
Did my nane come up at all?
- This meeting needs to be canceled.
- No, it's happening.
Look, just...
Just do a good job tomorrow.
We have to push this thing through.
Of course.
I'll push anything through anything.
You know me.
- Are you sweating through your suit?
- I doubt it.
It's a very breathable fabr...
Yeah, I am.
Jerry, what's up, man?
You're into pretzels, right?
Hit 'em up. Thanks for coming down.
I got a seat for you over there.
My top priority:
getting your fences in there.
I drove your fences the other day.
I was, "that fence looks awesome".
"Of course, Roy's."
If you're into chocolate muffins,
grab all you want.
Some people may say that bringing
in these contractors this early
is jumping the gun.
Well, guess what?
Here's the gun. Here's me.
Victor Miles,
Tom Haverford. How are you?
Thank you so much for coming down.
I want to introduce you to Leslie.
He's a gentleman I met canvassing.
He also happens to be the top sod guy
- in Indiana.
- That's terrific.
I really want you to nail this.
Don from Don's Cement,
Tom Haverford. Good to see you.
Thinking of a jingle
for your company. How's this?
Don's Cement,
is the best you can get
Don's.
- I'm so glad you're here.
- Andy came too to give support.
- I have a lot of stage experience...
- This will be fine, right?
It's a park, for God's sakes.
How much can they hate a park?
A lot of them seemed
to hate a park yesterday.
April, I need you in the audience.
Wait. And...
If the questions
start getting negative,
I need you to sell the crap out
of the park. Can you do that?
Please, this is serious.
Can you do that?
- Probably.
- Good girl.
Good probably. Good girl.
Here we go. Line up, everybody.
My mom's here.
I can't do that.
That's illegal.
Thank you so much for coming out
tonight. This is our first town meeting
about the proposal to turn
lot 48 on Sullivan Street
into a community park.
This is gonna be a train wreck.
I want my daughter to be successful.
Which is why I always tell her,
"there's nothing wrong
with being a wife and mother".
Now, there are many people
that I spoke to who are passionately
in support of this idea.
None of them were able
to make it tonight, unfortunately.
But...
they totally exist.
I did not make them up.
I see a question.
- No questions.
- My name is Kate Speevack.
- I remember you.
- And I live in the neighborhood.
And I am 100%
against this park.
I cannot believe the department
is moving forward with a project
without a single
environmental impact study.
And if you guys agree with me,
let's take a stand!
We are a little ahead of schedule
because we're holding
this town hall meeting so soon.
Which I was warned about
by Mark Brendanawicz, our city planner
assigned to this project.
So, what would he say?
Here we are.
Should I give them
some background info on the site?
Absolutely.
Mark Brendanawicz knows
the answer to every question.
He's amazing, and congratulations
for hearing him speak.
Hi, there. Leslie might have
oversold me a little bit.
Certainly did not. He's the man.
He's capable of anything.
Lot 48 is...
It's a rectangular lot.
It's got excellent drainage, and it's
on the corner of Sullivan and Collins.
Any questions?
I have more of a comment
than a question.
- Go for it.
- It's for the guy in the cast.
Here we go.
Lawrence.
That is Andy Dwyer.
He is a local resident,
and he tragicay fell in the pit.
Yeah, I don't care
about any of that.
He's the guy that plays music all night
in his garage. It's driving me nuts.
Lawrence lives with...
his grandma.
Which is pretty awesome.
He takes care of her, I guess.
But whatever. He's a douche bag.
It's loud. It's abusive.
And it's waking up my birds.
You have birds now?
Yeah, I have birds.
I have nice,
pretty, expensive birds. And you play
that music, and it wakes them up.
Look, I don't work
for the government.
I do play rock & roll.
Guilty as charged.
I'm in a band.
It's called Just The Tip.
And, actually, if anyone here
plays bass, we need a bassist.
Let's take a five-minute break,
shall we?
It is not...
going well at all.
It's going very poorly.
- Like you're crashing and burning.
- Democracy's happening.
People are talking. I mean,
at least they aren't apathetic, right?
You're right about that.
They're deeply negative.
You need to put a happy face on this,
give me a few positive talking points.
And whatever you do, avoid a vote.
I'm oddly attracted
to Kate Speevack.
Before we continue, I'd love
to just give you a little history
of Pawnee.
The city of Pawnee
was incorporated in 1817
when a young man by the name
of Reverend Luther Howell
came from Terre Haute on an ox.
He planted his flag in the ground
and was met soon after
by an angry tribe
of Wamapoke Indians,
who, when seeing
the whiteness of his skin,
twisted him to death.
Flash forward to 1969.
Man walks on the moon.
Pawnee is lousy with hippies...
My God, she's filibustering
her own meeting.
Filibuster.
They can't touch you
if you talk forever.
I can't speak of the future.
But I will.
The future of Pawnee will involve us
flying around in space taxis,
where we will communicate
on watches...
and blink our feelings to each other
rather than use words.
And now I'd like to take
a magical journey through...
a little something I like to call
The Phantom Tollbooth
- by Norton Juster.
- Excuse me, can't you read
- that children's book on your own time?
- I have the floor.
"There once was a boy named Milo
who didn't know what to do with himself.
"Not just sometimes, but always..."
- You know what? This is a public forum,
which means that we all get
to tell you what we think.
Well, you did already talk, ma'am.
And I would love to listen
to someone else, someone I don't know.
That girl , long brown hair
and yellow top.
Could you tell us
how you feel about this park?
Go ahead.
I'm a youth in the community,
and I think a new park
is a great idea.
And I fully support it,
as would the rest of the youth
in the community.
I recognize her.
- That kid came to my door yesterday.
- Oh, my God.
They have planted people
in this audience.
Unbelievable.
We all agree that this park is
a bad idea. We should just take a vote.
We will take a vote.
Before we do that,
I want everyone up,
lined up behind that microphone.
I want to hear from all of you,
one-by-one.
That was brutal.
A couple weeks ago, I was yelling
at Leslie at a public forum.
God, I hope I wasn't as obnoxious
as those people.
I wasn't, right?
At 5:00 in the morning, every morning:
Beep... I don't want to hear that.
How long is this project gonna take?
That's what I wanna know,
what's important to me.
- Because I need my sleep.
- Thank you, ma'am.
That concludes our meeting.
- What about the vote?
- We're out of time.
It's 9:00.
But we will have many public forums
in the future,
and we hope to see you all there.
Thank you so much for coming.
It was tough.
But, you know, that's Pawnee.
That's democracy.
A lot of people here want this park. You
just gotta get past the negative people.
But guess what?
My subcommittee held its first
town hall meeting tonight.
God, I loved it.
I loved every minute of it.
- Hey, park lady.
- Yeah?
You suck.
Hear that?
He called me "park lady".
Normally I don't agree with Leslie
about anything, but this book...
is awesome.
www.tvsubtitles.net