Previously on AMC's
The Walking Dead...
All I am anymore is a man
looking for his wife and son.
There's us and the dead.
We survive this by
pulling together, not apart.
Screw you, man.
See, if she's trapped, she's gone.
She's my sister!
You son of a bitch!
Don't leave me!
Where's Glenn?
( Thunder rumbling )
Merle: That's right.
You heard me, bitch.
You got a problem?
Bring it on
if you're man enough,
or take it up the chain
if you're a pussy.
You heard me,
you pussy-ass
noncom bitch.
You ain't deaf.
Take it up
the damn chain of command
or you can kiss
my lily-white ass.
( Laughs ) That's right.
That's what I said.
You heard me.
And then this idiot,
he takes a swing,
you know, and well...
( Laughing hysterically )
Oh, you should've seen
the look on his face
when I punched out
his front teeth.
Yeah, five of 'em.
Pow! Pow!
Just like that.
Huh.
Oh my God.
16 months in the stockade...
Oh, that's what
them teeth cost me.
That was...
That was hard time,
but by God, it was worth
every minute of it
just to see that prick
spit his teeth out
on the ground.
Yes sir,
worth every minute.
Mmm.
( Wind blowing )
Oh no.
No no!
No no! No no!
God! God!
No no!
( Grunts )
God! Jesus!
No no, merciful Christ!
No no. No no.
God, help me!
God! God!
Jesus, please!
Jesus, please.
Help me!
Come on now!
Help me.
( Zombies growling, banging )
( Softly )
No no. Oh, no no.
Oh my God.
Shh shh shh shh shh.
( Crying )
No, Jesus. Jesus.
No no no no no no.
Please.
I didn't behave, I know.
I know I'm being punished.
I know. I...
Oh, I deserve it.
I deserve it.
I've been bad.
Help me now.
Show me the way.
Go on, tell me what to do.
Tell me. Tell me.
God!
( Grunting )
That's okay.
Never you mind,
silly Christ boy.
I ain't begged you before.
I ain't gonna start
begging now.
I ain't gonna beg you now!
Don't you worry about me
begging you ever!
I'll never beg you!
I ain't gonna beg you!
I never begged you before.
( Grunting )
( Banging, growling continues )
Oh shit.
No!
( Theme music playing )
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Best not to dwell on it.
Merle got left behind.
Nobody's gonna be sad
he didn't come back...
Except maybe Daryl.
- Daryl?
- His brother.
( Car alarm approaching )
( Glenn whooping )
Whoo-hoo!
At least somebody's
having a good day.
- ( Rattling )
- ( Kids grunting )
- Girl: Give it back.
- Boy: Stop it.
- Girl: No!
- Boy: I found it.
- Boy: Give it.
Mijo, leave your sister alone.
- Why?
- Come on.
Baby, the more you fidget,
the longer it takes.
- So don't, okay?
- I'm trying.
Well, try harder.
Shane:
If you think this is bad,
wait till you start shaving.
That stings.
That day comes, you'll be
wishing for one
of your mama's haircuts.
- I'll believe that when I see it.
- ( Shane chuckles )
I'll tell you what...
You just get through this
with some manly dignity and tomorrow
I'll teach you something special.
I will teach you
to catch frogs.
- I've caught a frog before.
- I said frogs... plural.
And it is an art, my friend.
It is not to be taken lightly.
There are ways and means.
Few people know about it.
I'm willing
to share my secrets.
Oh, I'm a girl.
You talk to him.
( Chuckles ) It's a one-time
offer, bud... not to be repeated.
Why do we need frogs, plural?
- You ever eat frog legs?
- Eww!
- No, yum!
- No, he's right. Eww.
When you get down
to that last can of beans,
you're gonna be loving
those frog legs, lady.
I can see it now... "Shane, do you think
I could have a second helping, please?
- Please? Just one?"
- Yeah, I doubt that.
( Chuckles )
Don't listen to her, man.
You and me, we'll be heroes.
We'll feed these folks
cajun-style Kermit legs.
I would rather eat miss Piggy.
- Yes, that came out wrong.
- ( Shane laughs )
Heroes, son, spoken of
in song and legend.
You and me, Shane and Carl.
- ( Carl and Shane laugh )
- ( Car alarm approaching )
Man: Hey, Dale, can you
see what that is?
Talk to me, Dale!
- I can't tell yet.
- Man: Let him get a good look at it.
Is it them?
Are they back?
Dale:
I'll be damned.
- Amy: What is it?
- A stolen car is my guess.
- Holy crap. Turn that damn thing off!
- I don't know how!
- Pop the hood, please. Pop the damn hood,
please. - My sister Andrea...
- Pop the damn hood!
- What? Okay okay. Yeah yeah yeah.
- Yeah yeah!
- Is she okay? Is she all right?
- She's okay! She's okay!
- Is she coming back?
- Glenn: Yes!
- Amy: Why isn't she with you?
- Where is she? She's okay?
- Yes!
Yeah, fine.
Everybody is.
Well, Merle not so much.
Are you crazy, driving this
wailing bastard up here?
Are you trying to draw
every walker for miles?
- I think we're okay.
- You call being stupid okay?
Dale: Well, the alarm was
echoing all over these hills.
Hard to pinpoint the source.
I'm not arguing.
I'm just saying.
It wouldn't hurt you
to think things through
a little more carefully
next time, would it?
Sorry.
Got a cool car.
( Truck approaches )
Come meet everybody.
( Engine stops )
( Sliding door opens )
- Amy.
- ( Crying ) Andrea!
- Oh!
- Oh my God!
You scared the shit out of me.
- Boy: Papi! Daddy!
- Morales: Hey.
Come here, sweetie.
Morales: Hey.
I told you
I'd be back, didn't I?
( Silent )
( Whispers )
Dale:
You are a welcome sight.
- ( Both laugh )
- I thought we had lost you folks for sure.
How'd y'all get out
of there anyway?
- New guy... he got us out.
- Shane: New guy?
Morales: Yeah, crazy vato
just got into town.
- Hey, helicopter boy! Come say hello.
- ( Truck door shuts )
Morales:
The guy's a cop like you.
( Whispers ) Oh my God.
Dad! Dad!
( Crying )
Carl.
Oh!
- ( Crickets chirping )
- Rick: Disoriented.
I guess that comes closest.
Disoriented.
Fear, confusion...
All those things but...
( Thunder rumbling )
Disoriented comes closest.
Words can be meager things.
Sometimes they fall short.
Rick: I felt like I'd been
ripped out of my life
and put somewhere else.
For a while
I thought I was trapped
in some coma dream,
something I might not
wake up from ever.
Mom said you died.
She had every reason
to believe that.
Don't you ever doubt it.
Lori: When things started
to get really bad,
they told me
at the hospital that
they were gonna medevac you and
the other patients to Atlanta,
and it never happened.
Well, I'm not surprised
after Atlanta fell.
- Lori: Yeah. - And from the look
of that hospital, it got overrun.
Yeah, looks don't deceive.
I barely got them out,
you know?
I can't tell you how
grateful I am to you, Shane.
I can't begin to express it.
There go those words
falling short again.
Paltry things.
( Wood clatters )
Hey, Ed, you want
to rethink that log?
It's cold, man.
The cold don't change
the rules, does it?
Keep our fires low,
just embers
- so we can't be seen from a distance, right?
- I said it's cold.
You should mind your own
business for once.
Hey, Ed...
( Pats )
( Softly ) Are you sure you want
to have this conversation, man?
Go on.
Pull the damn thing out.
Go on!
( Mutters ) Christ.
( Wood thunks, sizzling )
Hey, Carol, Sophia,
how are y'all this evening?
- Fine. We're just fine.
- Shane: Okay.
- I'm sorry about the fire.
- Shane: No no no.
No apology needed.
Y'all have a good night, okay?
Thank you.
I appreciate the cooperation.
Dale: Have you given any
thought to Daryl Dixon?
He won't be happy to hear
his brother was left behind.
I'll tell him.
I dropped the key. It's on me.
I cuffed him.
That makes it mine.
Glenn: Guys, it's
not a competition.
I don't mean
to bring race into this,
but it might sound better
coming from a white guy.
I did what I did.
Hell if I'm gonna
hide from him.
- We could lie.
- Or tell the truth.
Merle was out of control.
Something had to be done or
he'd have gotten us killed.
Your husband did
what was necessary.
And if Merle got
left behind,
it is nobody's fault
but Merle's.
And that's what
we tell Daryl?
I don't see
a rational discussion
to be had from that, do you?
Word to the wise...
We're gonna have our hands full
when he gets back
from his hunt.
T-Dog:
I was scared and I ran.
- I'm not ashamed of it.
- Andrea: We were all scared.
We all ran.
What's your point?
I stopped long enough
to chain that door.
Staircase is narrow.
Maybe half a dozen geeks
can squeeze against it
at any one time.
It's not enough
to break through that...
Not that chain,
not that padlock.
My point...
Dixon's alive
and he's still up there,
handcuffed on that roof.
That's on us.
I found you, didn't I?
I love you, dad.
I love you, Carl.
I found you both.
Yeah.
I knew I would.
You're getting cocky now,
a little bit.
No. No, I knew.
Walking into our home,
finding an empty house,
- both of you gone.
- I'm so sorry.
I knew you were alive.
- How?
- ( Thunder rumbling )
The photos were gone,
all our family albums.
( Chuckles )
I told you so.
Now you're getting cocky, huh?
A lot.
It belongs in here.
Baby, I really thought
I would never see you again.
I'm so sorry...
For everything.
I feel like...
When you were in the
hospital, I just...
I wanted to take it all back...
The anger and the bad times.
But the mistakes...
Maybe we got a second chance.
Not many people get that.
I wondered where that went.
Do you want it back?
Of course.
( Rain pattering )
He won't wake up.
( Thunder rumbling )
( People chatting )
- Morning.
- Man: Morning.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Carol: Morning.
- Morning.
They're still a little damp.
The sun'll have 'em
dry in no time.
- You washed my clothes?
- Well, best we could.
Scrubbing on a washboard
ain't half as good
as my old maytag back home.
That's very kind.
Thank you.
- ( Tools clanging )
- Look at 'em.
Vultures.
Yeah, go on, strip it clean.
Generators need every drop
of fuel they can get.
Got no power without it.
Sorry, Glenn.
Thought I'd get to drive it
at least a few more days.
Maybe we'll get to steal
another one someday.
Morning, officer.
Hey.
You sleep okay?
Better than in a long time.
( Chuckles )
Well, I didn't want
to wake you.
I figured you could use it.
- God. What?
- I've been thinking
about the man we left behind.
You're not serious.
( Car approaches )
Water's here, y'all.
Just a reminder
to boil before use.
Are you asking me
or telling me?
- Asking.
- Well, I think it's crazy.
I think it is just
the stupidest way
- to break your...
- ( Woman screams )
- Carl: Mom!
- Carl?
Man:
It's over there!
- Carl: Dad!
- Lori: Baby!
- Girl: Mama! Mommy!
- Glenn: Rick!
- Carl!
- Over here, boy! Come on, come on!
Carl! Baby!
- Mom!
- You're okay! I've got him. I've got him.
- Nothing bit you? Nothing scratched you?
- No, I'm okay.
( Growling )
( Gasps )
( Men grunting )
It's the first one
we've had up here.
They never come this far
up the mountain.
Well, they're running out of
food in the city, that's what.
- ( Branch snaps )
- ( Footsteps )
- Oh, Jesus.
- Man: Son of a bitch.
That's my deer!
Look at it.
All gnawed on by this...
( Kicking )
Filthy, disease-bearing,
motherless poxy bastard!
Calm down, son.
That's not helping.
What do you know
about it, old man?
Why don't you take that stupid hat
and go back to "On Golden Pond"?
I've been tracking
this deer for miles.
Gonna drag it back to camp,
cook us up some venison.
What do you think?
Do you think we can cut around
this chewed up part right here?
I would not risk that.
( Sighs ) That's a damn shame.
I got some squirrel...
About a dozen or so.
That'll have to do.
Oh God.
Come on, people.
What the hell?
It's gotta be the brain.
Don't y'all know nothing?
Merle!
Merle! Get your
ugly ass out here!
I got us some squirrel!
Let's stew 'em up.
Shane: Daryl, just slow up a bit.
I need to talk to you.
About what?
About Merle.
There was a...
There was a problem in Atlanta.
He dead?
Shane:
We're not sure.
He either is or he ain't!
No easy way to say this,
so I'll just say it.
- Who are you?
- Rick Grimes.
Rick Grimes, you got something
you want to tell me?
Your brother was
a danger to us all,
so I handcuffed him on a roof,
hooked him to a piece of metal.
He's still there.
Hold on.
Let me process this.
You're saying you handcuffed
my brother to a roof
and you left him there?!
Yeah.
- ( Grunts )
- Hey.
T-Dog:
Watch the knife!
( Shouts, grunting )
Shane:
Okay. Okay.
- You'd best let me go!
- Nah, I think it's better if I don't.
( Grunting )
Choke hold's illegal.
Shane: You can
file a complaint.
Come on, man.
We'll keep this up all day.
I'd like to have a calm
discussion on this topic.
Do you think
we can manage that?
- Do you think we can manage that?
- Shane: Hmm?
Mmm. Yeah.
( Panting )
What I did was not on a whim.
Your brother does not work
and play well with others.
It's not Rick's fault.
I had the key.
- I dropped it.
- You couldn't pick it up?
Well, I dropped it in a drain.
If it's supposed to make me
feel better, it don't.
T-Dog:
Well, maybe this will.
Look, I chained
the door to the roof...
So the geeks couldn't
get at him...
- With a padlock.
- It's gotta count for something.
Hell with all y'all!
Just tell me where he is
so's I can go get him.
Lori:
He'll show you.
Isn't that right?
I'm going back.
( Sighs )
So that's it, huh?
You're just gonna walk off?
Just to hell
with everybody else?
I'm not saying
to hell with anybody...
Not you, Shane;
Lori least of all.
Tell her that.
She knows.
Well, look, I...
I don't, okay, Rick?
So could you just...
Could you throw me
a bone here, man?
Could you just
tell me why?
Why would you risk your life for
a douche bag like Merle Dixon?
- Hey, choose your words more carefully.
- No, I did.
Douche bag's what I meant.
Merle Dixon...
The guy wouldn't give you
a glass of water
- if you were dying of thirst. - What he
would or wouldn't do doesn't interest me.
I can't let a man
die of thirst... me.
Thirst and exposure.
We left him like
an animal caught in a trap.
That's no way for anything to
die, let alone a human being.
So you and Daryl,
that's your big plan?
Oh, come on.
You know the way.
You've been there before...
In and out, no problem.
You said so yourself.
It's not fair of me to ask...
I know that,
but I'd feel a lot better
with you along.
I know she would too.
That's just great.
Now you're gonna risk three men, huh?
- Four.
- ( Huffs )
My day just gets better
and better, don't it?
T-Dog: You see anybody
else here stepping up
to save your brother's
cracker ass?
- Why you?
- You wouldn't even begin to understand.
- You don't speak my language.
- That's four.
It's not just four. You're putting
every single one of us at risk.
Just know that, Rick.
Come on, you saw that walker.
It was here.
It was in camp.
They're moving out
of the cities.
They come back, we need
every able body we've got.
We need 'em here.
We need 'em to protect camp.
It seems to me what
you really need most here
- are more guns.
- Right, the guns.
- Wait. What guns?
- Six shotguns,
two high-powered rifles,
over a dozen handguns.
I cleaned out the cage back
at the station before I left.
I dropped the bag in Atlanta
when I got swarmed.
It's just sitting there on the
street, waiting to be picked up.
- Ammo?
- 700 rounds, assorted.
Lori: You went through
hell to find us.
You just got here and you're
gonna turn around and leave?
Dad, I don't want you to go.
To hell with the guns.
Shane is right.
Merle Dixon?
He's not worth one of your lives,
even with guns thrown in.
Tell me.
Make me understand.
I owe a debt to a man
I met and his little boy.
Lori, if they hadn't
taken me in,
I'd have died.
It's because of them that I
made it back to you at all.
They said they'd
follow me to Atlanta.
They'll walk into the same trap
I did if I don't warn him.
What's stopping you?
The walkie-talkie, the one
in the bag I dropped.
He's got the other one.
Our plan was to connect when they got closer.
- These are our walkies?
- Yeah.
So use the C.B.
What's wrong with that?
The C.B.'s fine.
It's the walkies
that suck to crap...
Date back to the '70s, don't
match any other bandwidth...
Not even the scanners in our cars.
I need that bag.
Okay?
All right.
Rumor is you have bolt cutters.
- Maybe.
- Yeah, we get to that roof, though,
we'll need to cut that
chain and the handcuffs.
I never like lending tools.
The last time I did...
And yes, I am talking
about you...
Let's just say
your bag of guns
wasn't the only bag
that was dropped.
My tools got
left behind with Merle.
Rick: We'll bring
your tools back too.
Think of the bolt cutters
as an investment.
Sounds like more of a gamble.
- What do I get in return?
- What do you want?
How about one of those
guns you bring back?
- My pick.
- Done.
( Man clears throat )
Dale, let's...
Sweeten the deal a bit.
Now that cube van of yours...
What about it?
The R.V.'s
radiator hose is shot.
That's a problem if we need to get
somewhere and wanna get very far.
And the hose on that van is
just about a perfect match...
Well, enough that
I can make it fit.
I'll tell you what...
We get back,
you can strip that van
down to the bare metal.
( Truck honks )
- Come on, let's go!
- Thank you.
Hey, Rick, got any
rounds in the python?
No.
Last time we were
on the gun range,
I'm sure I wound up with a
few loose rounds of yours.
You and that bag... like the
bottom of an old lady's purse.
I hate that you're
doing this, man.
I think that
it's foolish and reckless.
But if you're gonna go,
you're taking bullets.
I'm not sure I'd want to
fire a shot in the city,
- not after what happened last time.
- That's up to you.
Well...
Four men, four rounds.
What are the odds, huh?
Well, let's just hope that...
Let's just hope four is
your lucky number, okay?
- Thank you.
- All right.
( Truck starts, revving )
Hey.
( Sniffling )
You know, I bet
they'll be just fine.
I'm not worried.
Are you?
Yeah, a little.
Don't be.
- Why?
- Think about it, mom.
Everything that's
happened to him so far...
Nothing's killed him yet.
( Chuckles )
Better be ok.
It's my own ***
I told you.
The geeks can't get at him.
Only thing is gonna get
through that door... is us.
We'll walk from here.
Lori: Dale.
- Have you seen Carl?
- Shane took him down to the quarry.
There was some mighty bold
talk about catching frogs.
( Women chatting )
I'm not getting anything.
Yeah.
Being all wily,
staying submerged.
Little suckers,
they know something's up.
That's what's going on.
Just going to have to do
this the old-fashioned way.
All right, little man, look.
You are the... you are the
key in all this, okay?
All I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
go after one of them,
all right,
scare the rest of them off.
They're all gonna scatter.
I'm gonna drive 'em your way.
- All right. - What you need to do
is you need to round up
every bad boy you see,
all right? Are you with me?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Hells yeah. Give me your mean face.
- ( Both growl )
- Yes sir. Are you ready?
- Yeah!
- Are you ready? Here we go, boy.
Here we go.
All right, little
man, they're coming your way.
They're coming your way.
Go on, get 'em, get 'em.
They're coming
your way, come on.
Catch them frogs.
They're coming, little man! Get 'em!
Get that net in there and get 'em!
I'm beginning to question
the division of labor here.
They're coming, little man! Get 'em!
Get that net in there and get 'em!
What have you got, bad boy?
What do you got? What do you got?
- Dirt.
- Oh boy. All right, we've got to start over.
- Come on, let's find this bucket.
- ( Both laughing )
Can someone explain to me
how the women wound up doing
all the Hattie McDaniel work?
The world ended.
Didn't you get the memo?
It's just the way it is.
( Fence clatters )
- Merle first or guns?
- Merle!
- We ain't even having this conversation.
- ( Emphatically ) We are.
You know the geography.
It's your call.
Merle's closest.
The guns would mean doubling back.
Merle first.
( Scrubbing )
I do miss my maytag.
I miss my Benz, my sat nav.
I miss my coffeemaker
with that dual-drip filter
and built-in grinder, honey.
My computer...
And texting.
I miss my vibrator.
Oh!
- ( Women laugh )
- Amy: Oh my God!
- Me too.
- ( Women laughing louder )
What's so funny?
Just swapping war stories, Ed.
Yeah.
( Water dripping )
Problem, Ed?
Nothin' that concerns you.
And you ought to
focus on your work.
- This ain't no comedy club.
- ( Huffs )
Hey, Carl,
what did I tell you about
not leaving Dale's sight?
But Shane said we could
catch frogs, remember?
It doesn't matter what Shane says.
It matters what I say.
- Go on back to camp.
- ( Sighs )
I'll be right behind you.
I've got to tell you,
I do not think you should be
taking this out on him.
You don't tell me what to do.
You lost that privilege.
Lori, could you just
wait up a second?
- I think we should talk.
We haven't had a chance... - No. No no.
That's over too.
You can tell that to the frogs.
Damn it, Lori.
Look, I don't know how it appears to you
- or what you think...
- How it appears to me? I'm sorry.
Is there a gray area here?
Let me dispel it.
You stay away from me.
You stay away from my son.
You don't look at him.
You don't talk to him.
From now on, my family
is off-limits to you.
Lori, I don't think that's fair.
- Shane, shut up. Don't!
- I don't think that...
My husband is back.
He is alive.
He's my best friend.
Do you think I'm not
happy about that?
How dare you?
Why would you be?
You are the one that
told me that he died.
You son of a bitch.
( Shuffling footsteps )
( Growling )
Damn. You are
one ugly skank.
( Thuds )
Ed, tell you what...
You don't like how
your laundry is done,
you are welcome to pitch in
and do it yourself. Here.
- Oh!
- Ain't my job, missy.
- Andrea, don't.
- What is your job, Ed?
Sitting on your ass
smoking cigarettes?
Well, it sure as hell
ain't listening
to some uppity
smart-mouthed bitch.
Tell you what...
Come on. Let's go!
I don't think she needs
to go anywhere with you, Ed.
And I say it's none of your business.
Come on now.
- You heard me.
- Carol.
Andrea, please.
It doesn't matter.
Hey, don't think I won't
knock you on your ass
just 'cause you're some
college-educated cooze,
- all right?
- ( Gasps )
Now you come on now
or you gonna regret it later.
So she can show up
with fresh bruises later, Ed?
- Yeah, we've seen them.
- ( Laughs )
Stay out of this.
Now come on!
You know what?
This ain't none of y'all's business.
You don't want to keep
prodding the bull here, okay?
Now I am done
talking. Come on.
- No no. Carol, you don't have...
- ( Carol mutters )
You don't tell me what!
I tell you what!
( Clamoring )
- You think you can...
- Get off her!
- Come here! Come here!
- Get off her! Get off her!
- Get off me!
- ( Ed grunting )
- Carol: Ed?
- Amy: It's okay. It's okay.
- Carol: No!
- It's okay.
- No!
- ( Women yelling )
- Amy: Shane, stop!
Just stop!
Carol:
Stop it!
- Stop!
- You put your hands on your wife,
your little girl
or anybody else in this camp
one more time, I will not stop next time.
Do you hear me?
- Do you hear me?!
- ( Slurs ) Yes.
- I'll beat you to death, Ed.
- Carol: Ed!
Oh God!
( Crying )
No.
- God!
- ( Grunts )
( Crying ) Ed, I'm sorry.
Oh my God.
Ed, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Ed.
- I'm sorry, Ed.
- ( Coughing )
( Chain rattles )
Daryl:
Merle! Merle!
No! No!
No!
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net