Previously on AMC the Walking Dead.
You girls were the first people...
that I cared anything for.
Jenner here.
63 days since the disease abruptly went global.
My husband...He is alive.
He's my best friend.
Do you think I'm not happy about that?
We're heading to the C.D.C.
If there's anything left, it's got to be there, don't you think?
Walkers!
You're killing us!
Ma'am. Ma'am, please.
- Please, can you help me? - No no!
Check them all. Check them all.
Okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here, bud.
Okay. Okay.
What do I do?
Come on, corporal. Move out!
Listen to me. If you're gonna wake up, I need you to do it now.
Okay? Now.
Please, man, just show me a sign. Anything.
Please, Rick.
The place is coming down!
Fall back! All units fall back.
I'm...
I'm okay.
Daryl, you cover the back.
Hello?
- Hello? - Watch those doors.
Watch for walkers.
Hello?
Anybody infected?
One of our group was.
He didn't make it.
Why are you here? What do you want?
A chance.
That's asking an awful lot these days.
I know.
You all submit to a blood test.
That's the price of admission.
We can do that.
You got stuff to bring in, you do it now.
Once this door closes, it stays closed.
Vi, seal the main entrance.
Kill the power up here.
Rick Grimes.
Dr. Edwin Jenner.
Doctors always go around packing heat like that?
There were plenty left lying around. I familiarized myself.
But you look harmless enough.
Except you.
I'll have to keep my eye on you.
Are we underground?
Are you claustrophobic?
- A little. - Try not to think about it.
Vi, bring up the lights in the big room.
Welcome to zone 5.
Where is everybody?
The other doctors, the staff?
I'm it.
It's just me here.
What about the person you were speaking with?
Vi?
Vi, say hello to our guests.
Tell them... welcome.
Hello, guests. Welcome.
I'm all that's left.
I'm sorry.
What's the point? If we were infected,
we'd all be running a fever.
I've already broken every rule in the book letting you in here.
Let me just at least be thorough.
All done.
Are you okay?
She hasn't eaten in days.
None of us have.
Fine.
You know, in Italy,
children have a little bit of wine with dinner.
And in France.
Well, when Carl is in Italy or France,
- he can have some then. - What's it gonna hurt? Come on.
Come on.
What?
There you are, young lad.
That's my boy. That's my boy.
- Good boy. - Yuck.
That tastes nasty.
Well, just stick to sour pop there, bud.
- Not you, Glenn. - What?
Keep drinking, little man.
I want to see how red your face can get.
It seems to me we haven't thanked our host properly.
He is more than just our host.
- Hear hear! - Here's to you, doc. Booyah!
- Booyah! - Thank you!
Booyah!
So when are you gonna tell us what the hell happened here, doc?
All the-- the other doctors
that were supposed to be figuring out what happened.
- Where are they? - We're celebrating, Shane.
Don't need to do this now.
Whoa, wait a second. This is why we're here, right?
This was your move--
supposed to find all the answers.
Instead we--
we found him.
Found one man. Why?
Well, when things got bad,
a lot of people just left.
Went off to be with their families.
And when things got worse,
when the military cordon got overrun,
the rest bolted.
Every last one?
No, many couldn't face walking out the door.
They... opted out.
There was a rash of suicides.
That was a bad time.
You didn't leave.
Why?
I just kept working.
Hoping to do some good.
Dude, you are such a buzzkill, man.
Most of the facility is powered down
Including housing, so you'll have to make do here.
The couches are comfortable,
But there are cots in storage if you like.
There's a rec room down the hall that you kids might enjoy.
Just don't plug in the video games, okay?
or anything that draws power. The same applies--
If you shower, go easy on the hot water.
Hot water?
That's what the man said. -
Andrea?
That's it.
That's it. Get it out.
There you go.
Oh... god.
Everything's gone.
It's always better going down than coming up, huh?
I don't mean the wine, Dale.
You know, it's over. There's nothing left.
Don't you see that?
Oh, I-- I see a--
A chance to make a new start.
Oh my god, Dale.
Dale, didn't you see the look on Jenner's face?
Hear what I'm saying.
There's nothing left.
How's the blood?
No surprises.
I came to thank you.
You did.
You all-- you all right?
You don't know what it's like.
You don't know what it's like out there.
You may think you do, but you don't.
We'd have died out there.
It was only a matter of time.
There's too many of those things.
My-- my boy...
My-- my wife, I never--
I never told 'em what I really thought.
I never even hinted, just--
Just kept it in.
Kept it in and kept us moving, you know.
Just kept it in. Kept us...
It'll all be okay.
It'll be okay.
Any good books?
Enough to keep us busy for years.
All right. Come on, kids, it's bedtime.
Baby, go say your prayers. I'm gonna browse a bit.
Come on.
This is the first night we might actually get some real sleep.
It's a miracle, isn't it?
Jesus, you scared me.
I'm gonna tell you a few things
And you're gonna listen to me.
Now is not the time.
Come on. When is it ever the time?
How can you treat me like this?
- You're kidding, right? - No. Huh-uh.
Because you told me my husband was dead.
I didn't lie to you, all right? I didn't.
Do you know what it was like there?
Stop. Things were falling apart.
They were slaughtering people in the hallways.
It was a massacre. There were walkers everywhere.
- So you left him? - Everybody else ran.
There were no doctors there. It was just me.
He was hooked up to machines and I did not know what to do.
I even took my ear and I put it on his chest
And I listened for a heartbeat and I did not hear one.
And I-I-I-I-- I don't know why.
Maybe it was gunfire. I don't know what it was,
But there was no way he could've survived that. No way.
- He did. - Yeah, but then I had y'all to think about, didn't I?
I had you and Carl,
- and I needed to think about-- - okay. No no.
I had to get you guys safe to Atlanta.
That's what I had to do. Just stop.
If you thought for one second
that he was still alive, would you have come?
So I saved your life--
You and your little boy's. That's what I did.
Right?
Okay.
And if I could've traded places with him, I would have.
I would trade places with him right now because--
No no no, you--
- I love you. Shh shh. - No. No, you're drunk.
- I love you. - No, you're drunk.
And I know there were some things that say that you love me too.
Because there's no way that
you could've been with me the way that you were.
Shane. Shane. Shane!
Listen. You love me.
Get your hands off me. Get your hands off me.
- I love you. There's nobody here. - Please! No!
Stop, Lori. It's all right. Just--
We don't have to be afraid anymore.
We're safe here.
All right?
- Morning. - Are you hungover?
- Mom said you'd be. - Mom is right.
Mom has that annoying habit.
Eggs. Powdered, but-- but I do 'em good.
I bet you can't tell.
Protein helps the hangover. -
Where'd all this come from?
- Jenner. - could you help me, please?
He thought we could use it.
- Thank you. - Some of us, at least.
Don't ever ever ever let me drink again.
Feel as bad as I do?
Worse.
The hell happened to you?
Your neck?
I must have done it in my sleep.
Never seen you do that before.
Me neither.
Not like me at all.
- Morning.  - Hey, doc.
Doctor, I don't mean to slam you with questions first thing--
But you will anyway.
We didn't come here for the eggs.
Give me playback of TS-19.
Playback of TS-19.
Few people ever got a chance to see this.
Very few.
- Is that a brain?  - An extraordinary one.
Not that it matters in the end.
Take us in for E.I.V..
Enhanced internal view.
What are those lights?
It's a person's life--
experiences, memories.
It's everything.
Somewhere in all that organic wiring,
All those ripples of light,
is you--
The thing that makes you unique.
And human.
You don't make sense ever?
Those are synapses,
electric impulses in the brain
that carry all the messages.
They determine everything a person says
does or thinks from the moment of birth
to the moment of death.
Death? That's what this is, a vigil?
Yes.
Or rather the playback of the vigil.
This person died?
Who?
Test subject 19.
Someone who was bitten and infected...
and volunteered to have us record the process.
Vi, scan forward to the first event.
Scanning to first event. -
What is that?
It invades the brain like meningitis.
The adrenal glands hemorrhage,
the brian goes into shutdown,
then the major organs.
Then death.
Everything you ever were or ever will be...
Gone.
Is that what happened to Jim?
Yes.
She lost somebody two days ago.
Her sister.
I lost somebody too.
I know how devastating it is.
Scan to the second event.
Scanning to second event.
The resurrection times vary wildly.
We had reports of it happening in as little as three minutes.
The longest we heard of was eight hours.
In the case of this patient,
it was two hours, one minute...
Seven seconds.
- It restarts the brain?  - No, just the brain stem.
Basically, it gets them up and moving.
But they're not alive?
You tell me.
It's nothing like before.
Most of that brain is dark.
Dark, lifeless, dead.
The frontal lobe, the neocortex,
The human part-- that doesn't come back.
The you part.
Just a shell driven by mindless instinct.
God. What was that?
He shot his patient in the head.
Didn't you?
Vi, power down the main screen and the workstations.
Powering down main screen and workstations.
You have no idea what it is, do you?
It could be microbial, viral, parasitic, fungal.
Or the wrath of god?
There is that.
Somebody must know something.
Somebody somewhere.
There are others, right? Other facilities?
There may be some.
People like me.
But you don't know? How can you not know?
Everything went down.
Communications, directives-- all of it.
I've been in the dark for almost a month.
So it's not just here.
There's nothing left anywhere? Nothing?
That's what you're really saying, right?
Jesus.
Man, I'm gonna get soon faced drunk again.
Dr. Jenner, I know this has been taxing for you
And I hate to ask one more question, but...
That clock--
It's counting down.
What happens at zero?
The basement generators-- they run out of fuel.
And then?
Vi, what happens when the power runs out?
When the power runs out,
facility-wide decontamination will occur.
Decontamination-- what does that mean?
I don't like the way Jenner clammed up.
The way he just wandered off like that.
What's wrong with him? Seriously, man,
Is he nuts, medicated, what?
In there.
Check that way.
Shane.
It's empty.
- Emergency lighting on. - What the hell is this?
Hey, you guys kill the lights?
- Nah, it just went ou. - Anything?
Yeah, a lot of dead generators
and more empty fuel drums than I can count.
It can't be down to just that one.
Mom? Something wrong?
Nothing. It's just...
the air conditioning stopped.
I did the best I could in the time that I had.
I hope you'd be proud of that.
We always think there's gonna be more time...
...then it runs out.
Why is the air off?
- and the lights in our room? - What's going on?
Why is everything turned off?
Energy use is being prioritized.
Air isn't a priority? And lights?
It's not up to me. Zone 5 is shutting itself down.
Hey! Hey, what the hell does that mean?
Hey man, I'm talking to you.
What do you mean it's shutting itself down?
How can a building do anything?
- You'd be surprised. - Rick?
Jenner, what's happening?
The system is dropping all the nonessential uses of power.
It's designed to keep the
computers running to the last possible second.
That started as we approached the half-hour mark.
Right on schedule.
- It was the French. - what?
They were the last ones to hold out as far as I know.
While our people were bolting out the doors
and committing suicide in the hallways,
they stayed in the labs till the end.
They thought they were close to a solution.
What happened?
The same thing that's happening here.
No power grid.
Ran out of juice.
The world runs on fossil fuel.
I mean, how stupid is that?
- Let me tell you-- - To hell with it, Shane. I don't even care.
Lori, grab our things. Everybody, get your stuff.
We're getting out of here now!
Oh, okay.
What's that?
30 minutes to decontamination.
Doc, what's going on here?
Everybody, y'all heard Rick.
Get your stuff and let's go! Go now! Go!
- Let's go. - Come on!
No.
Did you just lock us in?
He just locked us in!
We've hit the 30-minute window. I am recording.
- Carl. - Mom!
- You son of a bitch. - Shane!
- You let us out of here! - No, stop. Don't!
- You lying-- - No no no no!
Wait, no! No, don't do it.
Hey, Jenner, open that door now.
There's no point. Everything topside is locked down.
The emergency exits are sealed.
Well, open the damn things.
That's not something I control. The computers do.
I told you once that front door closed,
it wouldn't open again. You heard me say that.
- It's better this way. - What is?
What happens in 28 minutes?
- What happens in 28 minutes??! - COME ON!
You know what this place is?!
We protected the public
from very nasty stuff!
Weaponized smallpox!
Ebola strains that could wipe out half the country!
Stuff you don't want getting out! Ever!
In the event of a catastrophic power failure--
in a terrorist attack, for example--
H.I.T.s are deployed to prevent any organisms from getting out.
HIT
H.I.T.s?
- Vi, define. - HITs--
high-impulse thermobaric fuel-air explosives
cocoists of a two-stage aerosol ignition
that produces a blast wave of significantly greater power
and duration than any other known explosive except nuclear.
The vacuum-pressure effect ignites the oxygen
between 5,000 and 6,000 degrees
and is used when the greatest loss of life
and damage to structures is desired.
It sets the air on fire.
No pain.
An end to sorrow, grief...
regret.
Everything.
Open the damn door!
Out of my way!
Daryl!
You should've left well enough alone.
- it would've been so much easier. - Easier for who?
All of you. You know what's out there--
A short, brutal life and an agonizing death.
Your-- your sister-- what was her name?
- Amy. - Amy.
You know what this does.
You've seen it.
Is that really what you want for your wife and son?
I don't want this.
Can't make a dent.
Those doors are designed to withstand a rocket launcher.
Well, your head ain't!
Daryl! Daryl!
Just back up! Back up!
You do want this.
Last night you said
you knew it was just a matter of time
before everybody you loved was dead.
What?
What? You really said that?
After all your big talk?
I had to keep hope alive, didn't I?
There is no hope.
- there never was. - There's always hope.
Maybe it won't be you, maybe not here,
But somebody somewhere--
What part of "Everything is gone" Do you not understand?
Listen to your friend. She gets it.
This is what takes us down.
This is our extinction event.
This isn't right.
You can't just keep us here.
One tiny moment--
A millisecond. No pain.
My daughter doesn't deserve to die like this.
Wouldn't it be kinder,
more compassionate to just hold your loved ones
and wait for the clock to run down?
- Shane, no! - out of the way, Rick!
Stay out of my way! Open that door
or I'm gonna blow your head off. Do you hear me?!
Brother, brother, this is not the way you do this.
- We will never get out of here. - Shane, you listen to him.
- It's too late. - He dies, we all--
we all die! Shane!
Shane!
Are you done now? Are you done?
Yeah, I guess we all are.
I think you're lying.
- What? - You're lying.
About no hope.
If that were true, you'd have bolted with the rest
or taken the easy way out. You didn't.
You chose the hard path.
- Why? - It doesn't matter.
It does matter. It always matters.
You stayed when others ran.
- Why? - Not because I wanted to.
I made a promise...
To her.
My wife.
Test subject 19 was your wife?
She begged me to keep going as long as I could.
How could I say no? -
She was dying.
It should've been me on that table.
I wouldn't have mattered to anybody.
She was a loss to the world.
Hell, she ran this place. I just worked here.
In our field, she was an Einstein.
Me? I'm just... Edwin Jenner.
She could've done something about this.
Not me.
Your wife didn't have a choice.
You do. That's-- that's all we want--
A choice, a chance.
Let us keep trying as long as we can.
I told you topside's locked down. I can't open those.
Come on!
- Let's go! - Come on, let's go!
- Come on! - Move it! Move it!
- Come on, let's go! - We're gonna get out of here, Sophia.
There's your chance. Take it.
I'm grateful.
- The day will come when you won't be. - Let's go!
Hey, we've got four minutes left! Come on!
- Let's go. Let's go. - No no, I'm staying.
I'm staying, sweetie.
- But that's insane! - no, it's completely sane.
For the first time in a long time.
I'm not ending up like Jim and Amy.
There's no time to argue
and no point, not if you want to get out.
Just get out. Get out.
Dog. Come on, man.
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
I'm staying too.
Andrea, no.
- Just go! Go! - Come on.
Andrea,
This isn't what Amy would want for you.
She's dead, and you need to leave.
- Get them doors open! - Come on!
- It doesn't work! - Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Try it! Try it! Try it now!
- Come on! Come on! - Stay close, sweetheart.
Time's almost up.
Daryl, look out!
Dog, get down! Get down!
- Jesus. - The glass won't break?
Rick, I have something that might help.
Carol, I don't think a nail file's gonna do it.
Your first morning at camp,
when I washed your uniform I found this in your pocket.
Come on.
Look out!
- Get down! Get down! - Shit?
Okay.
You win.
- What are you doing? - I said okay.
- Don't pull this, Dale. - I'm not pulling anything.
If you're staying, I stay too.
He's right. We know what's waiting for us out there.
I don't want to face it alone.
Dale, get the hell out.
I don't want you here.
Too bad. See, you don't get to do that,
to-- to come into somebody's life,
make them care and then just check out.
I'm staying.
The matter is settled.
Wait wait wait. Wait wait.
They're coming.
They got out.
Come on.
Dale, get down! Down!
Get back! Everybody down! Down!
Get down!
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Get in, get in, get in.
Get in!
www.tvsubtitles.net