Subs by Raceman and Traff
www.forom.com
I thought Tracy was
getting here at noon.
Movie stars move at
their own pace, Liz.
We have to
accommodate them.
Yeah, well, a lot of people
are still upset
about Tracy
joining the show.
That's not
my problem.
I have other things
on my plate.
You hear about that chemical
factory explosion
outside
of Colorado Springs?
No.
Good.
All right,
here he comes.
I just think when it comes
to this whole Tracy thing,
it's best to
trlightly.
No, no, no.
Stop, stop.
It's just us.
Lemon, to tread
lightly is your job.
My job is to keep
Tracy Jordan happy.
Girls, girls, girls.
Let's save it
for Mr. Jordan.
Studio 68 is where
we do The Girlie Show.
Did you all see
Tracy Jordan
make a special appearance
the other night?
Wasn't that exciting?
That is what we
in the show business
like to call a "cameo."
Hey, this is the star
of The Girlie Show, Jenna Maroney.
Hi.
Thank you.
How do you feel,
NBC tour?
'Cause you look good,
like a solid gold candy bar!
Where else do you have
those piercings on your body?
This is it,
everybody.
Here he comes.
Stop, stop, stop.
It's only Jenna.
All right, it's just Jenna.
How you doing, Jenna?
Okay,
I mean granted,
Tracy Jordan has some commercial appeal,
but within his remunenerative body of work
there's just
nothing of value.
What are you
talking about?
Did you ever see
his stand-up?
Give up the butt,
ladies.
Give up the butt.
This is it, I mean it.
Here he comes.
He's an imbecile.
Well, he's our imbecile now.
I'm just surprised he's
still got his shirt--
Oh, there it goes.
Jack!
Oh, my goodness!
It's good to see you
again, brother.
It's good to see
you again.
Oh, that is fantastic.
You have to teach me
that handshake one day.
Listen, Tracy,
if there's anything you need,
anything,
you come to me.
Come on, Jack,
you know I'm the kid.
I'm easy like
Sunday morning.
Don't look at me!
Do not look at me
in the eyes.
Do not look at
Mr. Jordan!
Do not look at him
in the eye.
Just look away.
Look away.
Tracy, this is our producer,
Pete.
Hey!
Hey, Pete.
You smoke weed,
right, Pete?
Uh...
No.
Yeah, me neither.
Me and you, Pete.
Me and you.
Pete.
Good to see you.
Is it?
Oh, good.
It's good
to see you too.
'Cause that means
I'm not fired anymore.
I wasn't gonna
mention that.
But I did.
And now
I'm talking about it.
Relax your balls,
Pete.
Hey, everybody.
Tracy Jordan's here.
Don't just sit there.
Come and give me some sugar.
No, thank you.
Well if you ever want to piss off
your parents, you come see me.
Right this way,
Tracy.
This is Tim Grandy.
He's from Bowie, Maryland.
Rachel Baze,
she just got engaged.
Josh Girard,
he got 760 on his SATs.
Graduated from
SUNY Courtland.
Frank Rossitano has every copy
of Black Tail magazine ever published.
J.D. Lutz,
thyroid problem.
James Spurlock,
but we call him Toofer,
because with him
you get a "Two for One,"
he's a black guy
and a Harvard guy.
And, of course,
you know Lemon.
How did you do that?
It's my job.
Jerry from set design.
Wally,
cue cards.
Rupert Murdoch.
Melinda Gates.
Ziggy  from
the cartoon Ziggy.
Anthony Pellano.
Heidi Klum.
The guy that sleeps
with Heidi Klum.
This man's a genius.
Let me just say,
I'm excited to be here.
It's an honor for you
to meet me.
I've got a lot of characters
I'm ready to bust out.
I got a character
named Biscuit.
Write that up.
Got a another character
named Raylondo,
who's a two-foot tall
Spanish hustler.
Glasses, I want you
to write that one.
Got another character
named Ching Chong,
who loves to play
Ping Pong.
I just made that up
right now.
'Cause that's
how I flow.
Now I'm up for anything.
I thought me and you could play
Seinfeld and Bill Cos--
No.
I don't like that.
How you doing?
There is no way I am
working with that guy!
Do you know that he once got arrested
for walking naked
through LaGuardia?
And that he once fell asleep
on Ted Danson's roof?
Yeah, Tracy has
mental health issues--
He bit Dakota Fanning
on the face!
When you hear his version,
she was kind of asking for it.
I can't even believe that
you are doing this to me.
Listen, I understand
that this is tough for you.
But what did I tell you?
Not to freak out?
Right.
And what else?
Stop falling in love
with gay guys?
About this.
That you're
looking out for me.
But  it doesn't seem--
Jenna, I'm your friend.
I'm not going to let
anything happen to you.
This show is called The Girlie Show,
and you are the girl.
Nothing is going
to change that.
Okay.
Glaub mir.
Diese "Advantium Microwaves"
sind die beste.
How could you change the name
of my show without telling me?
Detlev, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
Yeah, wunderbar.
Plowchops.
The Girlie Show is now
T.G.S. with Tracy Jordan?
It tested very well
with the focus groups.
If you say you like it,
you can have some pizza.
You people like pizza?
You need to tell Jenna that
this whole thing was your idea
and that I didn't know anything
about it,
and that she should
be mad at you, not me.
Oh, sure.
Then we could sit around
and braid each other's hair
until we get our periods
at the same time.
Look, Lemon,
you're a supervisor.
These people are
not your friends.
Yes, they are my friends.
No, they're your employees.
Well one of my employees
is extremely mad at me.
Will you talk to her?
No, because then you're
not gonna learn anything.
You have to manage
these people, Lemon.
It's your show.
You have the tools.
Now get out there
and build the house,
add on a pool, and throw
yourself into the deep end.
What if I can't swim?
Then I'll do what my father
did when I was two.
Lure you to the edge
of the pool with a puppy,
and push you in.
Yikes.
Fine, I'll figure it out.
We're gonna be shooting
some promos
in an hour underneath
the new sign.
So have your people...
write some stuff.
So I said, "Rick, this chick's
got an Adam's apple."
And Rick said to me,
I'll never forget this.
He said, "Freaky deakies
need love too.
Freaky deakies
need love too."
Charming.
So, how you doing over there,
Theo Huxtable?
I'm doing good.
Unh-unh.
Superman does good.
You're doing well.
You need to study
your grammar, son.
Wow. That was embarrassing
for you.
I don't even have lines
in these promos.
It's all Tracy
he doesn't even mention me.
I'll fix that.
Just stay calm.
Stay calm?
They changed the name
of the show.
You said that you were
looking out for me.
I am.
I will handle it.
Lemon, Lemon.
Can I be real with you?
Yeah.
I haven't had a real job
in like two years.
I'm not used to
all these--
These cue cards
and all of that.
Don't worry about
the cue cards.
Look, you have two lines.
Just say,
"Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan,
I'm bringing the black
back to NBC."
I'm proud as a peacock,
baby."
You  don't even
need these.
You're right.
I got this!
Thanks for looking out
for me, Lemon.
I'm gonna crush it.
Show these people
how a movie star does it.
A little to your right,
Tracy.
Okay, here we go.
In three, two--
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan and I'm
bringing the black back to NBC.
And I'm proud as a peacork,
baby.
That's great, Tracy,
but it's peacock.
What did I say?
Peacork.
Peacock.
Think peacock.
Right, Jenna?
In three,
two--
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan,
and I'm bringing the black back to NBC.
And I'm proud as
a pea cock, baby.
Okay.
That time I think you may have
hit it a little bit too hard.
Also, can you throw Jenna's
name in there for me?
In three, two--
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan, and I'm
bringing the black back to NBC.
Right, Jenna Mulvaney?
Maroney.
Rhymes with Baloney.
Here we go.
In three, two--
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan, and I'm
bringing the black back to NBC.
And I'm proud as a peacock.
Right, Mabaloney?
Nope.
In three, two--
Hi, I'm Tracy Jordan.
I'm black, NBC.
Very proud,
like peacocks.
Right, Janet?
I think we got it.
Yeah,
I think we did.
Okay, that was
beyond insulting.
The guy doesn't even
know my name.
Why do you
love him so much?
No, no, no, no!
I don't love him.
Donaghy loves him.
That's it.
Pete can't stand him,
Toofer thinks he's an idiot.
Even Cerie
says he's a pig.
Frank likes
his movies.
Frank also loves that video of the monkey
smelling his own butt.
Mmm.
Nobody wants Tracy Jordan here
except for certified
non-genius Jack Donaghy.
Sorry  to interrupt,
Ms. Maroney,
but the sound guys
want their microphone back.
So everyone can...?
Hear everything you are saying.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh my God. I didn't use
the N word, did I?
Oh, no, no, no,
Miss Maroney, you did not.
Oh, good.
I mean, I never would, but, you know--
Jenna,
take the mic off!
Sorry.
Oh, my God.
That was bad, right?
It wasn't great.
Jack Donaghy
wants to see you.
No, no, no.
Tell him I'm very busy.
Come in,
she's very busy.
Mr. Donaghy,
I sincerely apologize.
I'm so embarrassed.
I guess you must
be embarrassed
if you're hiding
in the storage closet.
This is my office.
Really?
I see you bring
a little feminine magic
to everything you touch.
How did it go with Tracy Jordan
when you apologized?
I didn't think I needed
to talk to him.
I mean, he's not my friend,
he's my employee.
No, he's not your employee,
he's your product.
Like it or not, you're in
the Tracy Jordan business now.
And when you screw the pooch
the way you did today,
it's your responsibility to get
in there and make things right.
How do I do that?
I don't know.
I'm a non-genius.
I'm really sorry!
Lunch break,
that's a lunch break.
Back in 30 minutes.
Tracy, I hope I didn't
hurt your feelings before.
Please.
You can't hurt me.
I did stand-up
on the road.
A crowd once threw
a motorcycle at me.
Good, 'cause, you know, I'm just
trying to calm Jenna down.
'Cause she's kinda
paranoid and neurotic,
and your being is just
bringing out all of her crazy.
Please don't think
that everyone hates you.
Pete thinks that
everybody's an idiot.
Especially Frank,
who is an idiot.
Josh is just jealous
'cause you're gonna get
more screen time
than him.
And Toofer's just afraid
of black people.
Which one is Toofer?
The black guy.
Oh.
My point is,
don't worry about them.
You are the only person
that the network cares about.
Ms. Lemon?
I just wanted to let you know
y'all are on the monitors right now.
Everyone can--
Hear you and see you.
Yes, ma'am.
Son of a mother!
Paranoid?
Well, that just confirms
all my suspicions.
Sorry, everybody.
Hey, buddies.
All right,
I deserve that.
But I didn't say anything
about you guys
that I wouldn't have said
to your faces.
Fine. The important thing is
don't take this out on Tracy--
That dude sucks!
Okay, are we going to talk
about this like adults,
or are you just gonna
throw things at me?
All right.
Okay, fine.
Get it out of your system.
Nothing that plugs in,
you guys!
Nothing that could
really hurt me!
Hello.
Lemon.
How are things
in the deep end?
Fine.
The staff is meshing
together well?
Oh, yes, yeah.
Good.
I'm counting on you.
We got to do something.
Let's crash my car
to see if the air-bags go off.
Let me explain what
I'm talking about first.
Everybody is mad.
At us.
Mostly mad at you.
Yeah, well, that's
because Donaghy threw me
into the deep end of a pool
that I didn't even want
to build in the first place!
Look, I'm just saying,
we both screwed up today.
I think we should make nice
and buy everybody some pizza
and some soft drinks--
Nah, nah, nah.
This is what we're
gonna do, Lemon.
You're going to get
everybody on my yacht.
Harbor cruise.
Drinks.
Togetherness.
That's great.
You have a yacht?
I got a yacht.
I got a solid gold jet-ski.
Two Batmobiles.
The AIDS monkey's bones...
Welcome!
Welcome to your fantasy!
We're both hosting.
The ice cream bar was my idea.
This is surprisingly
tasteful.
Oh, yeah.
I've taken this boat many places.
Miami, Tokyo, Denver.
What does that mean,
Avanti Domani?
What?
The name
of the boat.
Oh, that's Spanish for
"remember your mother."
No, I don't think it is.
Hello, boys.
I brought champagne.
I'm so glad you came.
Get away from me.
My Baloney!
Look at you. Wow.
Yeah, thanks.
Let me make you a drink.
You love apple martinis, right?
Yes, how did
you know that?
I read your interview
in Amtrak Magazine.
Really?
You saw that?
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
Did you know that all the writers
in that magazine are also conductors?
I didn't know that.
Hey, Toofer,
see if I got any schnapps.
Good gravy.
This is a Dunwoody '62.
It's for you.
Take it, my friend.
Thank you.
That is just wasteful.
I  hear you sing.
I didn't know that.
Why don't you sing
something for me?
Oh, no.
Nobody wants to hear that.
I do.
Some folks like to get away,
take a holiday from the neighborhood
Hop a flight to Miami Beach
or to Hollywood...
Let's get out of here.
Is that a real song?
It's going well, right?
It has to,
it has to go well.
Relax, everybody's
having a great time.
How's Jenna?
Furious and drunk.
But at least she's
getting along with Tracy.
Well, he does know
how to throw a party.
Think we're ever
gonna leave the dock?
I don't know.
The engines haveeen running
for like three hours.
Hey, hey! Grizz!
Grizz, don't wreck
this boat!
Grizz is driving
the boat?
Don't worry.
He was in the Navy.
I got one,
I got one.
Jerry Seinfeld
and Bill Cosby!
What's the deal
with pudding?
I'm Bill Cosby.
Jell-o! Sweaters!
Whoo! Yeah!
That doesn't even sound
like the Cos.
I'm gotta go lay down.
Got you on
that one, man.
He got you again, man.
Get better references.
Tracy, thank you so much
for doing this.
You totally saved me.
You don't have to
thank me, Lemon.
We're a team now.
Like Batman and Robin.
Like chicken and
a chicken container.
Hey, where's
your bathroom?
Second door
on the right.
All right,
let's do another one.
That's weird.
Por favor,
no me dueles.
Me llamo María.
What?
Please calling
Ted and Nancy Peabody.
You tell Who Dat Ninja
is on the boat.
What are you saying?
Tracy Jordan
is on the boat.
He no see me.
I hidden from him.
I hide from him.
Oh, my God.
It's Spanish for,
"Remember Your Mother."
I've taken this boat
to Denver.
You can have that scotch.
Grizz was in the Navy!
It's not his boat!
Sir, you need to
disembark immediately.
This is not his boat!
We gotta get off this thing!
Disembark immediately.
Is this your boat?
Run! Jump!
Get out of here!
Good morning.
Morning.
Okay,
you were right.
I'm sorry?
I can't do this.
I can't manage these people.
It was a disaster.
What are you talking about?
Everybody loved your little Lemon party.
I think it brings the team together
like a harrowing experience.
You pulled it off.
Really?
They bonded.
Good job.
Okay.
I guess now I just have to read about
how Tracy Jordan tried to steal a boat.
No, I took care
of that.
The Peabodys will be getting
some free rides on the NBC jet.
There won't be anything
in the papers at all.
Really?
What about this?
Well, I had to give them
something.
Ugh.
Don't worry.
She's gonna love it.
That's just insulting.
Liz, Liz, did you see me
in the Post?
Oh, my God,
it's so embarrassing.
Look how thin I look.
And look how many emails I've gotten.
It's not even
8:00 AM in L.A.
Should I call Stern?
You're welcome.
www.tvsubtitles.net