Fall from...
Oh. [ laughs ]
Because I'm an angel!
Why are you so sweet?
Maybe just 'cause
I'm so damn happy.
Today is Jay's birthday.
So I'm taking him to Hawaii
for a whole week.
Big suite in Maui,
just the two of us.
Got Manny tied up
in the backyard --
Big bowl of kibble.
I'm kidding.
He's staying
with Claire and Phil.
This whole thing
was a big surprise.
I did it all myself --
The flight, the hotels.
Cost me a fortune,
but it was worth it.
Cost me a fortune.
In case I forget to say it
a few hundred times this week,
Thank you.
Happy Birthday!
What the heck?!
Mwah!
Surprise, dad.
The whole family is coming with us!
Uh-huh.
They are?!
Yes, and Mitch and Cameron
and Lily, too.
Yeah, and Phil --
he's just checking the bags.
Wow. That's...
Wow!
Well, it was all Gloria's idea.
She bought all of our tickets
and everything.
Really? Yeah.
Everyone's?
It's your birthday.
I didn't spare any expense.
Oh, gee.
Thank you, honey.
Are they, uh, all gonna be
up with us in first class?
Ay, no, silly goat.
You think I'm made of money?
Hmm!
Of course not.
Sync by kuniva
www.Addic7ed.com
We're gonna go to a luau,
swim with the Miami dolphins,
Take a tour
in one of those --
The tkkita-tkkita-tkkita-
tkkita-tee-tee!
Helicopter.
Helicopter. Mm-hmm.
Yes!
I don't like activities.
I wanted to hang out with Gloria
And read
my Robert Ludlum novels.
I got eight of them loaded up
on my book-reader thing here.
I mean, I love my family.
I love 'em at dinners,
I love 'em at barbecues,
But do I have to love 'em
in Hawaii?
Thanks, Daryl.
I know I got a lot of baggage,
But don't worry,
I'm seeing a therapist.
Just kidding, I'm fine.
Hey!
Daryl, I know these guys.
Can I borrow your hat?
This will be hilarious.
No.
Okay.
Aloha, Uncle Phil!
Hey. Hey!
You guys excited about the trip?
Oh, we're so excited.
You know, this is my first time.
Really?
Yeah, I know, it's surprising.
People always say
I scream "Hawaii."
Who says that?
People.
What people?
You don't know them.
Hey, Lily. Hi!
Oh, no. Oh, n--
I forgot my wallet!
Oh, that's all right.
I have cas
No, no, I can't get
on the plane without my I.D.
Thanks a lot, Cam.
How is this my fault?
Because if you had done what
I asked you to do this morning,
Then I wouldn't
have been overwhelmed
And I would have
remembered my wallet!
All right, we still need
to pack Lily's toys,
Print the boarding passes --
oh [snaps fingers]
Stop the newspaper.
Hey, no, wait. What are you
doing? I just packed those.
Oh, she just looks so cute
in this outfit.
I want her looking her best
for Jasper.
Nothing you just said
made any sense to me.
Jasper and his mother
are coming over for a playdate.
We scheduled it weeks ago.
We're about to leave
for the airport!
Not for an hour,
And this is the only time
Jasper could do it.
Really?
How full is Jasper's calendar?
This is a coup.
When you get in with Jasper,
doors open.
He's a legacy
at happy time preschool.
We're kissing up
to a 10-month old?
I just want him to like us.
Okay, that's them.
All right, but just in and out.
You know, we still have
a million things to do.
Would you relax?
You always worry.
It always gets done.
Oh, and we're methodists.
So...
Ah. Who am I kidding?
I-I'm not making this flight.
Unh-unh. I can get you home and
back before the plane takes off.
Let's go!
See if you can stall the plane.
That's --
I will get you later.
I really -- I really don't think
there's enough time.
No, just -- I'll meet you
at the gate. Go!
Okay, but you won't get
on the plane without me, right?
Oh. Well...
Seriously? You were gonna
get on the plane?! Cam!
Just go!
Nope.
Gotta get that one.
Door.
okay.
I can't -- ohh.
All right.
That's as fast as she goes.
Just drive!
I'll get the luggage!
Hey, check out that cute guy.
[ scoffs ]
he's out of your league.
He's reading a book.
I know.
Here today, gone to Maui!
Hey.
Have you seen Phil?
Oh, he drove Mitchell back
to get his wallet.
What?
Yeah, he said he's gonna
make it back in time,
But I think
it's gonna be close.
So he left me here.
Haley is still asleep!
And I have no idea where Luke is.
And are you even ready?
My bag's in the living room.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Okay, fine. I'm sorry,
I'm a little tense.
Coffee'll help that.
You're right.
We've been over this.
Air travel is incredibly safe.
I know. I know,
but at the end of the day,
It is still a building
on its side
Being thrown
from one place to another.
With a movie.
Not helping.
Do you want to take something,
maybe calm your nerves?
No. No, I want to be alert
if the kids need me.
What a mom.
Sometimes I wish
you were my mom.
Oh, God, Phil.
I'm already feeling
a little queasy. [ sighs ]
I hate this feeling.
I hate it, and it's just
gonna get worse and worse
Until the flight.
Hey.
It's gonna be fine.
Uncle Phil's here.
Great job, buddy!
First one ready!
Haley and Alex, let's go!
Bless you.
Coming.
All right, come on, girls.
Okay.
Okay, this is why we practice.
Come on through.
Come through. 15 seconds.
Are we ready?
I think so.
Yeah.
It's go time!
Go.
All right.
Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast.
Straight to the car. Straight through.
Very nice!
All right, let's go, let's go.
Hey. I think we got
an extra couple of seconds.
No, we don't.
Dad, come on.
Row 30
may now board at gate one.
Mmm. [ smooches ]
I will never g tired of this.
Me neither.
You know what would be cool, mom?
What's that?
If the plane flew into a storm
And crash-landed onto an island
like in Lost"!
Ow. Ow.
Ow.
Something wrong there, Cam?
Oh, well, I'm just breaking in
a new pair of hiking shoes.
This always happens.
All the men in my family
have wide ankles.
I have an Uncle that
can only wear bell bottoms.
Hand to God.
I wasn't doubting you.
Just, why are you wearing
the hiking shoes?
Surprise!
What, again?
Every morning, thole family
is gonna go hiking.
And then,
at the end of the week,
We all gonna make it to the top
of the volcano!
Every morning, huh?
yes.
When Cam suggested it,
I knew you were
gonna love it, baby.
Oh, so this
was your idea?
Happy Birthday, Jay.
Aw, thanks, buddy.
Ow.
Hi, sweetheart.
She's smiling.
Yes, I'm going hiking!
Yeah.
Thank you.
Look, mom, I'm pregnant.
Yeah. You still got to take
your Dramamine.
Oh, does somebody get
a little motion sickness?
Yeah,
I throw up all the time.
Oh, well, then Dramamine's
the way to go.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, I'm just trying
to keep her awake
So she'll sleep on the plane.
Nobody likes a crying baby
on a flight.
It's -- it's very stressful.
Yeah, uh, last year,
I flew back from New York
Next to a baby who was
very upset the entire flight.
I was on that flight with you,
and I don't recall --
Oh, I get it.
You're talking about me.
That's very funny.
Yeah, we couldn't get tickets
to "billy Elliot."
all he wanted to do was dance.
And that's my story.
Yeah, five hours of this.
I just want
to dance at the ballet!
Dramamine --
oh, I wish I had that
The last time I flew.
I'll tell you, the plane
was rocking up and down,
Back and forth.
I thought the wings
were gonna snap off, honestly.
Okay, you do it yourself.
Use your teeth.
I-is this the best way to go?
What about the freeway?
Relax, Pumpkin, I got this.
It's all about
knowing the route.
You're talking to a guy
who made his way through college
By driving a pedicab.
You know what one of those is?
Yes, yes.
I just saw one pass us.
Quick, who sang "Evilan"?
What?
E.L.O.
Phil, where the hell are you?
Uh...Let's see.
Oh, shoot,
I just missed my turn.
You're supposed to be here
with me.
I told you,
I get more and more freaked out
As we get closer to the flight!
Well,
I know, but Mitch --
I was counting on you
To be here, so, thanks...
A lot.
She's pretty tightly wound.
Some people are just built
that way.
Honestly,
could you drive any slower?!
Guess where the world's largest
wind generator is.
Is it right behind me?
Nope.
It's on the island of Oahu.
I'm thinking about using it
in my song about Hawaii.
What song?
Didn't mom tell yo
Surprise!
The whole family's
putting on a show for you
For your birthday.
Everybody's performing!
Even Phil brought his dummy!
Isn't that great?
Jay?
Oh, I'm sorry,
I was just thinking
How tragic it would be
if I fell into that volcano.
Ay, papi, don't say that.
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Not yet, sweetie.
Not yet.
See, he's perfect.
Look at him getting coffee
And not putting chocolate
in it.
He's so mature.
What about Dylan?
Dylan's no that guy.
Haley! Come on!
We're leaving in two minutes!
Get up!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no.
Is it tomorrow?
Dylan,
what are you doing here?!
I was gonna go,
but then you fell asleep,
And since you're leaving
for a week,
I wanted to stare at you
as long as I could.
You have to go.
My parents are gonna think
we did it!
As if.
Okay, get out of the house,
And make sure
that nobody sees you!
I'll miss you.
When you're gone,
it's like I'm this prisoner
Trapped in a cell
of loneliness.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
That's beautiful,
but you have to go.
Okay, uh...
I hate this feeling.
I hate it, and it's just
gonna get worse and worse
Until the flight.
Hey.
It's gonna be fine.
Mm.
Uncle Phil's here.
Great job, buddy!
First one ready!
Thanks.
- Haley and Alex, let's go!
- Coming!
Bless you.
Coming.
All right, come on, girls.
Okay.
Okay, this is why we practice.
Come on through.
Come through. 15 seconds.
Are we ready?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
It's go time!
Go.
All right.
Slow is smooth, and smooth is fast.
Straight to the car. Straight through.
Very nice!
All right, let's go, let's go.
Hey. I think we got
an extra couple of seconds.
No, we don't.
Dad, come on.
Oh, no!
What?!
My keys!
Stay awake, sweetie.
stay awake.
Whee...
Oh, no.
This is where your Realtor
training comes in handy.
Looks like a standard
Porter & sons d-model top-lock.
One quick swipe
ought to pop it.
All aboard.
Okay.
There we go.
All right.
Nice and easy.
Oh, whoa. Okay.
Yeah.
You're pinching.
Oh, I'm sorry.
If you show enough houses,
you learn all the tricks.
Every Realtor is just a ninja
in a blazer.
The average burglar breaks in
and leaves clues everywhere,
But not me.
I'm completely clueless.
Sure I'm not too heavy?
Please, you weigh less
than my paintball gear.
Oh, okay.
There we go.
We are in.
Yep.
Off-load.
There we go.
Squeezing.
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry.
I'm going for a ride.
okay.
Ha ha.
You all right?
Yep.
I'm good. I'm good.
What are you doing?
Just making it a little tougher
on the next guy.
You got to get up
pretty early -- son of a --
Oh, God!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I am.
Oh, oh...
Just, uh, almost killed myself
on your fire truck.
That's not ours.
That's, uh, Jasper's.
You know Jasper?
yeah.
I sold a house to his parents.
How did you ever get
a playdate with him?
Let's go!
Okay.
Please-- Cam -- yeah.
Look at him.
He's sketching!
He's like Leonardo DiCaprio
in "titanic."
I bet he goes to art school.
Do you think
he's sketching us?
Yeah.
"us."
...5:35 to Boston
may board at this time.
And contact.
Ugh.
It's Dylan.
"I'm trapped."
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What a drama queen.
We will go whale "washing,"
Explore the tropical forest,
get back into the nature.
That sounds fun.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Your attention, please.
Would Manny Delgado
please report to gate 22a?
Manny Delgado to gate 22a.
Check it out, grandpa.
The Dramamine's working.
I'm not dizzy!
Yeah.
Oh, watch the drink, kid.
Ooh!
Ooh, my Ludlums!
I-I'm sorry, grandpa.
All right, relax, relax.
We might be okay here.
It's not fair.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Is this Manny Delgado?
Yes.
Your son's name
is on a no-fly list.
Ay, please, we've been
through this at the check-in.
He's not the same
Manny Delgado.
I'm just a boy trying to bring
style back to travel.
We just have a few questions
to ask.
No, this is a mistake.
Where is my husband? Wait.
Step this way, ma'am.
Jay! Ma'am.
Ma'am, step this way, please?
Jay!
Son? No pushing!
Step this way.
Jay!!
Could you make it a double? I'.
No problem.
Yeah, life would be simpler
if I was gay.
Do you think you could get
in the fast lane?
Oh, I could totally
get in the fast lane.
I mean the road.
Ooh, I'm getting a text.
What does it say?
Um [sighs]
Oh, g--
well, it's nothing.
It's the alarm company.
Its says your --
your house was broken into.
What?! It's nothing.
They'll take care of it. Just drive!!
What happened?!
Okay, fun airport game.
Mm-hmm.
All right, you pick out a traveler...
Mm.
...You come up
with their entire story.
Okay, this guy,
his name's Henry.
He's on his way to Phoenix
to visit his grandmother,
Whose name is, uh...
Unh! Pass. Too hard.
Your turn.
Okay, fine.
I see a woman,
uh, wracked with fear,
Whose husband
has abandoned her.
Where? Where?
Who is she?
Me.
I made it perfectly clear
to Phil
That I needed him here.
It's going around.
Mitchell's mad at me, too.
He thinks because I didn't
help him pack this morning,
He forgot his wallet.
I'm -- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to be snippy.
It's just [sighs]
I'm a little upset with Cam.
I needed his help this morning,
And, you know, he let me down.
That doesn't sound like him.
You asked him to do something
and he didn't do it?
But he never asked!
I mean, all he said was,
"Lily's bag needs to be packed,
And the newspaper
needs to be canceled."
That sounds to me
like he was asking for help.
Sounds to me like you expected
him to read your mind.
What am I, a psychic?
No, it's not about
reading minds.
It's about knowing
what your partner needs.
Here's an idea.
Just say, "help me."
You don't even have to say "me."
just "help."
Then he'll know
exactly what you want.
You won't have to get all mad.
I'm not mad.
It's just...
You know, you want to believe
That you're on the same
wavelength as someone,
And then it's just --
It's a little disheartening
when you find out you're not.
That's all.
What's frustrating is I would do
anything for Mitchell,
And -- and, frankly,
it's a little hurtful
That he doesn't know that.
So...Airports, huh?
Yeah.
Are you drawing
something there?
Eh, it's no good.
Tortured artist.
Classic.
Oh. Yeah.
It's a robot!
Oh, yeah, sure is.
What's behind him?
A dinosaur.
It's for school.
We're supposed to
make a comic strip.
We had to do that, too,
back in the eighth...
He was 14 years old!
Shut up.
"he's my soul mate."
I...
This is the final
boarding announcement for...
Whatcha drinking?
Dad.
Hey.
Mostly tonic, actually,
thanks to my new sponsor here.
I'm a little jittery
about flying.
What are you talking about?
You fly all the time.
Yeah. I know.
This started just
in the last couple years.
I think I'm just --
I'm nervous 'cause I've got
so much to lose now, you know?
What about you?
I'm taking a break
from my vacation.
We haven't even started yet.
Well, I t to figure
I might not have a lot
of time for myself,
You know, what with the luaus,
the hiking,
The talent shows.
Are you not happy
that we're coming with you?
It's just not what I expected.
But, dad...
Doesn't it feel good to know
That your whole family
is willing to drop everything
To be with you,
To fly across the ocean
in a steel coffin?
I'm gonna finish that.
It's not you guys.
I love the family.
Mm-hmm.
It just kinda feels like
glia's going out of her way
Not to spend time
with me.
You don't believe that, do you?
Oh, come on, dad.
That is so crazy
and so adorable.
That woman loves you.
Well, I didn't say
I wasn't lovable.
It's not every wife
that would spend the money
To fly a family to Hawaii.
Okay, where does everybody
think Gloria's money comes from?
So, what kind of business
did you have in Japan?
I've never been to Japan.
You didn't go to Osaka
in November 2003
I was 4.
Enough.
Why don't you question the
other people in the gate, huh?
Did you see the old lady
with the cane?
What if she has
a ceramic knife in there
That can go through
the metal detector?
And yet you waste your time
harassing a little kid!
Ma'am, you seem to know
an awful lot
About sneaking contraband
onto a plane.
Yeah, I'm Colombian.
Have you ever been to Japan?
I would like to make
a phone call.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Pre-boarding
for our flight to Maui
Will begin
in the next few minutes.
Luke, please stop spinning.
Sorry.
Now make the airport
stop spinning.
We made it!
Cameron, oh, boy.
Claire!
Oh, my God,
thank God you're here!
Hi!
Oh, honey.
Mwah!
I am so sorry.
It was my fault.
It wasn't your fault.
I should have known
what you wanted.
Are you drunk?
Kinda.
And once I spent a week
in Cancún,
Which, by the way,
did not live up to the hype.
[ door opens
Can somebody tell me
what the hell is going on?
We're almost done here, sir.
So you and your son are
traveling together. Yes.
Then why are you departing Maui
on different dates?
Well, because...
He's traveling back home
with his family.
What?
Surprise!
They're only staying
for six days.
The rest of the time,
it's only you and me.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
I wanted to spend some time
alone with my husband,
Drink cocktails by the pool,
Sleep in. Mm.
I could not love you any more
than I do right now.
I also found a topless beach.
I was wrong.
Sync by kuniva
www.Addic7ed.com
Mr. Jackson,
have a great flight.
It's to the left.
Oh, gorgeous.
Oh, thank you.
It's vintage.
I think he meant Lily.
You don't know that.
Yo, there's another
hottie for you at 5:00.
It's whale "watching."
Whale "washing."
"watching." "watching."
It's close enough.
Hi, sir.
Have a good flight, sir.
Quick,
do your zombie impression.
Oh, she hasn't been drinking,
has she?
Oh, no, no, no.
She's -- s's hario.
Okay, let's do
"bride of Frankenstein."
Oh!
That is so -- so good.
www.tvsubtitles.net