Gloria? He better cool it,
or I'm gonna introduce him
To the captain and tennille.
sorry we're late. I was at work.
Oh, he loves to say that.
Happy barbecue. Oh.
Since mitchell is
between jobs... Wow!
...I've taken a part-time job
at a greeting-card store,
Which I love.
Plus, with my discount,
we're saving a fortune.
How is spending a ton of
money on greeting cards
Saving us a fortune?
It's math.
It's really not.
Look it up.
$2.95, $2.95, $4.95...
40% off, 40% off,
40% off....$2.95, $3.95, $2.95.
Mitchell, I got this
golf buddy of mine.
Great guy. Super successful.
You two should talk.
It could mean a job for you.
Oh, thanks, dad, but I'm --
I'm not really looking for
anything right now, but...
Yeah, that's right.
With me bringing home the bacon,
Mitchell doesn't have
to rush into anything.
Yeah, I know you have
All that greeting-card
screw-you money,
But talk to the guy?
He's expecting your
call in the morning.
Dad, I appreciate it,
but in the future --
Oh, I can't stand this.
I am sorry, but --
No. Those steaks have been
done for five minutes.
I'm taking them off the grill.
I'm sorry.
I-I know how it feels
To have him stick his nose
where it doesn't belong.
No biggie. That's
just Jay being Jay.
But one day I'm gonna
be a grandfather,
And then everybody
better hide their meat.
Sync By n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Ooh, who's she?
I hate it when you do that.
Who's he? It's charlie bingham.
He's the guy that my
dad wanted me to call.
I googled him. Look.
Oh, he owns earthgear apparel?
I have their ski pants.
Really? You don't - you don't ski.
I have cargo pants,
and I don't work at the docks.
God, I feel like such a slacker.
I mean, he has done so
much for being so young.
Okay, look, he's opened up
A dozen environmental
foundations and conservancies.
Wow.
So, are you gonna - are
you gonna call him?
I don't know. I mean, you know,
I-I sort of promised myself
And you that I'd take a
little time off and --
And you are loving your time off.
Totally.
I am losing my mind.
As much as I love lily,
Which is, you know,
more than life itself,
I am -- whew! -- Not cut out
to be a stay-at-home dad. No.
But I-it's cameron's turn.
It's cameron's turn
to be out in the world
Interacting with other grown-ups
while I get to stay at home
And plot the death
of dora the explorer.
I'd like to fill her
backpack with bricks
And throw her into
candy-cane river.
So, I don't know.
Should I -- should I call him?
I don't know. Maybe just to
get your dad off your back.
Yeah. You know, I mean --
I mean, because the last thing I want
for you is to take a job right now.
I am loving our life.
I am in a really dark space.
Being away from my lily
is literally torture.
and I can't pressure mitchell,
But I really, really,
really just want him to get a job
So I can go back to being a
stay-at-home dad/trophy wife!
Come on, ladies, move it!
Goodness gracious!
Turtles run faster!
Come on!
Could you run any slower?
I dare you to run slower.
You see? He's just
trying to light a fire.
No, I light him on fire.
Why do I always have to
come to these things?
Because you love your brother.
Why don't you make him come to
my orchestra concerts?
Because we love your brother.
Good job, luke!
Shoot!
Delgado! You're killing me, man!
I love you, manny, no matter what!
Come on!
Okay.
That's great. Okay, well,
I'll let you know.
All right. All right, bye.
uh, so, charlie bingham
just invited us
Over to his beach house
for a little get-together.
Oh! Uh, well, what did you say?
I said I'd check with you.
I mean, what -- what do you think?
What do you think?
well, I think it would be
rude not to hear him out.
Yeah. I mean -- yeah,
you're probably right. Yeah.
Okay. Cool.
And don't worry. You know,
I'm not gonna take any job.
You better not.
I just miss - I just --
I just miss, you know...
I just -- make
grilled-cheese sandwiches.
You're doing great, luke,
if your goal is to suck.
Phil. I'm on it.
Wait for me.
Hey, coach? Yeah.
Look, we appreciate your passion,
But some of us are
worried that the yelling
Is getting counter-productive.
I got this. Come on, stupid!
No you don't "got this."
What you got is a bad attitude.
Who are you?
I happen to be the
stepfather of...
Doesn't matter who.
What you need to start doing
Is a little more coaching
and a little less yelling.
'cause if I hear you call one
of these kids stupid again,
I swear to god,
I'll throw a shoe at your head.
Screw it. I don't need this.
You think you can do a better job?
You coach.
Jay, you know,
I was handling this.
I saw how you broke
out peaches and herb.
It's the captain and --
Why? Is he sick?
Yes. He's very, very sick.
Is he going to die?
Everyone dies, boys,
let's focus on what's important.
Our next game is in one hour.
We are going to go
from being five fingers
To being a fist.
How does that sound?
Great. Great.
I can't hear you? Great!  Great!
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout.
All right, gentlemen,
I talked to the referee. I'm coaching.
Oh, really? 'cause I --
Phil, I coached football.
Jay, I actually
coached basketball.
I think I can get these guys --
Relax, you've already
got the assistant job.
Now, think you can round
us up some waters?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Gentlemen, this is what I need.
I want you to hit them,
and I want you to hit them hard.
Father-in-laws are tough,
Because you can't let
them push you around,
And you also have to
show them respect.
It's like walking a tightrope,
Which, by the way, I can do
Because I went to trapeze school.
Did Jay? I doubt it.
Don't let them run over you.
Honey, I'm gonna take off.
I'm gonna buy alex some clothes.
Okeydoke.
How come you're not coaching?
'cause your dad coached football.
I'm sorry.
And I am going to make
it up to you tonight.
And I'll be thinking of
your dad while you do.
Mm. Disturbing.
Hey, phil.
Hey. How's it going?
Great. Your dad coached football.
Ahh, a fellow victim.
Thank you again for
taking care of lily.
I know it's last-minute.
Ay, don't be silly.
We'll probably just stick
around for a few minutes.
You know how fussy she gets
when we pass her off, so --
No, she seems fine.
Yeah.
Ay, I think she's getting
used to being away from you
Now that you have the new job.
Mwah!
So proud of you!
We need to talk.
Okay. What happened?
Mom, I love you,
but your words of encouragement
Encourage the other
kids to make fun of me.
Okay, I won't say anything
else on the next game. Promise.
We both know that your latin
blood makes that impossible.
I think it would be better
If you didn't come
to the next game.
Ah! I know.
I hate our house. I know!
And what's -- what's this thing?
I don't know, but it's fancy.
Stop -- stop playing
with it. Come on.
Just...Don't break it.
hey, mitchell!
Charlie bingham.
Nice to meet you. Hi!
This is my partner,
cameron tucker.
Pleasure. Cameron.
So we just went ahead and parked
On that round thingy
in the driveway.
Is that -- that's fine, right?
No problem. It's a turntable
so you don't have to back out.
Oh.
You have a car turntable
and you're wearing rubber.
You're like batman.
I really am.
Come on in.
Turn the music down!
Wow.
Pardon the getup.
Killer waves today.
You guys surf?
Only for bargains on the web.
Everybody, say hi.
Hi. Hi. Hello!
That's jolie. She's head
of my europe division.
She cheats at poker. You do.
And that's my girlfriend, jenny.
She makes a hell of a
margarita. Want one?
Absolutely. Oh, no, not -- o-okay.
Everybody, mitchell pritchett
and his partner, cameron.
Business partners.
Mergers and acquisitions.
I'm kidding. We're gay.
Stop talking.
When things are relaxed,
I'm great in social situations.
I would have fit in at the
algonquin round table.
But when the stakes are high,
I get a little tense.
I'd be the guy that would
knock over the round table.
Then dorothy parker
would make a quip,
James thurber would laugh,
And then I would end
up leaving, crying.
How long you been
on the lam? What?
Honey, you are looking around
like the feds are after you.
No, I'm not. Let's just
get this over with.
Oh! Great.
Oh, no. It's them.
Oh! Oh, you know those
girls from school.
Hey!
Let's go. Over here.
What -- what is your problem?
nothing.
I'll meet you at
the car in an hour.
Please, mom. Please.
Hi, jenna.
And just like that,
my baby girl became a teenager.
She entered that dreaded phase
Where my very existence
embarrasses her.
I-I think I can help.
You're not your mom.
Wow, that's your mom.
Oh, I just got chills.
So, first off, I'm a fan.
I saw you in court once.
seriously? Yeah.
Mayhew vs. Propyltech.
You are a good lawyer.
If you'd have handled my divorce,
This house would be twice as big.
Oh, he's better than good.
Try winning an argument with him.
Last night, I wanted to
have indian for dinner --
And we're talking again.
Top of your class at
cornell and columbia law.
Had your pick of jobs
But instead chose to
work in environmental law
Until last month.
And he used to be a really
great figure skater.
Why'd you quit?
His sister lost interest,
and then there was --
He means my job.
You can tell me about
figure skating, too.
Um, well, it was - she
did lose interest.
That's enough. Okay.
Iqué linda! Iay, qué linda!
Oh, my gosh! I didn't know
you guys were gonna be here.
Hola, claire.
Mwah! Hi, lily. Mwah, mwah!
I had enough
basketball for one day.
Oh, I know. Come here, sweetie.
Oh, sweet thing, you love me,
And you want me to
buy you a dress.
Ay, but I'm gonna buy
her some shoes first.
What's that, lily?
Do you want me to buy you a dress?
She said, "yes."
What?
She did not say, "yes."
Okay, "win" on 3.
1, 2, 3... 1, 2, 3...
Win!    Win! Win! Win!
Don't forget the pick-and-roll.
These guys won't know
how to defend it.
Phil, try not to
confuse my boys, okay?
Okay. I sleep with your daughter.
What? Good luck.
All right, let's go, let's go,
come on, let's go!
Get out there.
Hustle up! Get the tip!
Get the tip!
Oh! All right. Keep the hustle,
keep the hustle.
Come on, boys. Don't let
them push you around.
Oh! All right, little defense.
Play defense.
I did a little scouting,
And the other team
only has two shooters.
If we isolate both of them --
Good, phil, good. Thank you. Good.
Manny, pay attention!
What are you looking at?
What?
Oh!
So, tell me this,
What are the regulatory
challenges of a solar farm?
well, you know,
it could be anything.
Agriculture, military,
protected species,
Ironically, even some
environmental groups.
I think you got all of it. Mm.
I think you got it.
Yeah, I'm just gonna
freshen this up.
Okay.
Let me ask you a question.
How do you like the beard?
I'm thinking of growing one.
Jenny's against it.
Oh, well, I've - I've
been very happy with mine.
That's it. I'm doing it.
Look, I've made a fortune.
I want to use it for some good.
I need a lawyer to
help me navigate.
I like you. You get me.
So, in or out?
I'm very sorry.
It's okay.
Um, that's a very big question.
You know, I'm obviously gonna
have to go talk to my, um...
... Bull in a china shop.
I'll be right back. Sure.
Talk it over.
It's a major life decision.
Hey, jenny! The beard is on!
Okay, lily, it's time to
buy you beautiful shoes.
Oh, no, no, no. I saw another
really cute dress for her.
Ay, she has already
six new dresses.
What she needs is
strappy shoes. Oh.
Oh, oh. There's alex.
I'll -- I'll see you later.
Alex, honey. Hi.
Mom, I said I'd
meet you at the car.
Ugh.
Here.
Thank you.
Still wish you had a daughter?
Manny didn't want me
at the game today.
oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay. It sucks.
I miss babies.
They never tell you to go away.
Yeah. Or wait in the car.
I don't know about you,
But I'm not gonna stand here
and feel sorry for myself.
You know what we should do?
Get pregnant.
I was gonna say go for ice cream.
Okay, we'll do yours first.
Luke! Luke!
It's hard to guard a player
if there's no player near you!
We good in the hood?
This is a uniquely frustrating
group of boys. I hear ya.
Um, one thing that might help,
Instead of a zone, if you
switch to a simple man-to-man.
I got this. Really?
'cause according
to the scoreboard,
The only thing you
got is 4 points.
Good luck.
I need to talk to you.
Nice top.
Come here. You -- you --
Cam. Cam, you have got to relax.
I told you I wouldn't
take a job --
Take the job. What?
I want you to take the job.
I thought you liked
having me home with lily.
I don't. I mean, I do.
I just -- I miss
my time with lily,
And I know it's selfish --
No, I want the job!
You do?
Oh, my god, yes!
I-I love lily,
but I hate baby talk.
I wuv baby talk!
Oh.
Let's go get this job.
Let's get this job.
okay.
Oh, no.
It's locked.
Guys? [ knocking on door ]
Oh, my gosh.
They not gonna hear us.
We're trapped out here.
That's -- stop being so dramatic.
We'll just go through the garage.
That's why he wants to hire you.
You're good in crisis.
What's that sound? I don't know.
It's not opening. Push it again.
I'm hearing things,
but it's not --
Push it harder.
That's not -- is it this one?
I hear something. What is that?
No. Stop touching. Stop --
This -- oh, that was it.
All right.
Mitchell! Oh, my god! No!
Oh, my god! No, cam!
Cam. Did we do that?
What are we gonna say?
Oh.
I will take the job.
I kind of think you have to now.
Guys, you're on the
same team! Time-out!
time-out.
Get over here.
Guys, earlier,
we practiced a few set plays.
Did any of them involve
wrestling the ball
From your own teammate?
But you said to be
aggressive. Yeah.
Not on your own team!
Wait here.
You got to coach. I can't take it.
You talkin' to me? Yeah,
I'm talkin' to you.
You got to take over.
I'm about to lose it out there.
That sounds tough, coach.
What's your problem?
Hey, coach. Tick tock.
I was dealing with the coach,
you pushed me aside.
I was dealing with the boys,
Believe it or not, Jay, there are some
things that I am better at than you are.
Bam! It's out there!
Oh, for god's sake.
Coach!
He's calling you.
Listen, I don't blame you
for being angry. All right?
I'm used to taking charge.
That's all.
I should have let you
coach from the get-go.
And?
I love you.
No, the barbecue.
Oh, for god's sake.
I'm sure your steaks would've
been delicious and not chewy.
Okay. I'll do it.
Thanks.
And so the student
becomes the master.
The once mighty - you
know what? Forget it.
No, no, no, no. I'm good.
I'm good. I'm good.
Hey, hey, guys. Who wants
to go out like a champ?
Yeah! Yeah!
I love it!
Okay, jordie, you inbound to luke.
Manny, set a pick on luke's
man and roll to the bucket.
Luke, you know what to do.
No, I don't.
Bounce pass to manny.
But dad -- coach --
Manny hasn't taken a
single shot all season.
Then chances are he'll be open.
okay, guys, let's bring it out.
Hey, hey. Bring it in.
Let's show these guys
What kind of team
they're about to beat.
Huh? "li'l dribblers" on 3.
1, 2, 3... 1, 2,
3...            1, 2, 3...
Li'l dribblers! Li'l dribblers!
Li'l dribblers!
Okay, red ball.
Side out. Here we go.
What's my coaching philosophy?
Give a kid a bird...
Yes.
...And he becomes one
of those weird dudes
Who walks around with a
bird on his shoulder.
But give him a pair of wings...
...And he can fly...
Ohh!
...Unless he has absolutely
no hand-eye coordination.
Okay.
I support you.
Hey, mom.
That was 20 minutes.
mom.
I am so, so sorry.
I know it's no excuse,
But I've been feeling a lot
of pressure at school --
You know, with friends.
And I love you so much,
And I appreciate
everything you do for me.
I'm still your little girl.
I know, honey.
That is so sweet.
Can I get $20?
A bunch of us are
going to a movie,
And we're gonna get
something to eat afterwards.
Jenna's brother's
gonna take us home.
Okay! Of course.
Sweetie, you know what?
Take $40.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah!
That's right. Thanks, mom.
Go on. Have a great time.
Oh, alex, honey.
When you're out shopping,
You might want to pick
yourself up a training bra.
I know you don't need one now,
But pretty your little boobies
are gonna come in soon.
Mommy loves you,
kitten! Mwah! Mwah!
Teach her to screw with me.
Luke passed to me, I shot the ball,
and I almost made it.
Ay, I bought lily the
cutest little dress today.
And then I stole the
ball from the other team,
Did a 360, and almost dunked it.
That's nice.
Ay, I just had the best
day today with lily.
That girl is so sweet.
I have a game next Saturday.
You could come.
No, it's okay.
I wouldn't want tembarrass you.
I'll probably take
lily out for cupcakes.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Any suggestions?
I usually go with earrings.
Sync By n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net